Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Here you go.
Thanks. Say,
aren't you Sam Malone?
Guilty as charged.
Small world.
Marge Thornhill here.
Don't you remember me?
Ah, boy, you know,
I can't quite place the face.
Where'd we meet?
Well, we didn't actually meet,
but I know you'll remember me.
I went to every home game
you ever played.
Uh... Marge,
there are a lot of people
up in the stands there.
Sure, but you got
to remember me.
I always sat
right behind first base,
five rows up, remember?
I used to get there,
early so I could watch you
warm up in the bullpen.
I'm sorry.
I know,
you couldn't forget this.
Hey, Malone!
You pitch like my sister!
Why don't you go home
and make a dress!
Was that you?
Yeah.
Well, how have you been?
Guys, I want you to...
Do the one where you say
I couldn't get the ball
across the plate
if I drove it there in my car.
No, no, that was then,
and this is now.
By the way, I'm really sorry
for all those shots
I gave you over the years.
No hard feelings?
No, of course not.
It's all part of the game.
You're a real sport, Malone.
( laughs )
You call this a martini?!
What'd you use for vermouth,
turpentine?!
The great ones never lose it.
( piano plays )
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody knows
your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ¶
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
All right, I got it,
I got it.
The worst possible
way to die?
Mm-hmm.
Being eaten alive
by rats.
No. I think I can do
better than that.
I'd say the worst way to die
is to be sliding down
a razor banister, okay?
A greased razor banister.
FRASIER:
Wait, I've got it.
To die alone,
knowing that you
have never been loved.
Come on, Frasier, if you're not
even gonna try... Come on.
Ooh, Carla, what are you
all decked out for?
It's my second
wedding anniversary.
Oh. Things are
going okay with
you and Eddie?
I mean,
just last week,
you were calling him
a "dent-nosed, toothless
little frog."
Pillow talk.
Ah.
Well, actually,
I was a little upset there
about the fact that he's been
on the road with the ice show
for a month now,
and I haven't gotten
so much as a phone call.
But this morning, I suddenly
realized what he was doing.
Treating you like crap?
No. No, that's what
he wants me to think.
It's way of setting up
a surprise.
So you figure he's
been neglecting you
just to set you up.
It's got to be that--
I know this man.
Woody, what time is it?
Oh, don't go by my watch--
I always set it
ten minutes ahead so I
won't be late for things.
You were late this morning.
Yeah, I know.
I couldn't find my watch.
It's, uh, 6:30, Carla.
Well, he's still got
five and a half more
hours till midnight.
Yeah, he's really
cutting it close.
But it'll make it
all the sweeter
when it happens.
Yeah, anniversaries
can be just great.
I'll never forget
my first anniversary with Vera.
Yeah, we, uh...
Oh, my God, I did forget it.
Anybody know where I can get
a 17-year-old box of candy?
Frasier, my fawn,
I deserve a treat.
Today my belly button turned
from an innie to an outie.
Well, this is news.
LILITH:
Uh, Norm? We have
a few things we'd like
to ask you about.
Oh, great. Must be
pretty important if you're
willing to buy me a free drink.
Oh, of course we will.
A drink for Norm?
What do you drink?
( laughter )
( chuckling )
What's so funny?
It's just that everyone knows
Norm always drinks beer,
dearest.
Ah. That is hysterical.
Anyway, Lilith and I
have been talking,
and we have decided that
we would like you to decorate
our unborn child's room.
All right!
Sure, I can do that.
I just did a nursery
for my sister-in-law.
I went with
Gummy Bears rampant
in a field of Smurfs.
Oh, no, no, no.
We'd like to stay away from that
cutesie-ootsie drivel that
retards the child's creative
and intellectual development.
All right, uh, do we know if
it's gonna be a boy or a girl?
We are not going to cram sexual
identity down our baby's throat.
So, naturally,
the room should be,
oh, sexually neutral.
Good. Fine, I can do that.
When I'm finished,
your kid won't have
a clue what sex it is.
Hey, everybody, listen up.
We only got a few minutes
to the game here.
Who wants in
on the basketball pool?
OTHERS:
I'm in! Put me down! Yeah!
There you go, gentlemen.
Woody, how about you?
Oh, I don't know, Sam, I don't
like playing games for money.
You end up either losing money
or taking it from your friends.
No, no, Woody,
this is just a game, man.
You know, five bucks a square.
You got four quarters,
four chances to win.
I don't know, I don't like
taking money from my friends.
Aw, go ahead, Woody--
nobody here gives a
hoot about you anyway.
Okay, great.
It's just money.
This isn't
gambling, is it?
Gambling?
Sam, we have had
this talk before.
I can get
closed down.
This? Oh, no, no.
Thanks.
This is not gambling,
this is, uh...
well, this is a game.
Uh, haven't you ever heard
of, uh,
Championship Tic-tac-toe?
It's a game.
Uh, who's next here?
Me. Me.
All righty.
It's my turn.
And I will take
this square here.
And, uh... Oh,
by the way, Sam,
here's that five
bucks I owe you.
Ah, well, Normie, you, uh,
you fell right into
my trap there, buddy.
CLIFF:
Here you go.
Oh, Sammy, by the way,
this, uh,
slipped out of your wallet
a couple of weeks ago.
Oh!
REBECCA:
How stupid do you think I am?
I know exactly
what's going on here.
Come on, what's
the big deal?
It's just a friendly
little game of wagering.
It's a simple $500 pot.
I can't believe
you people.
Do you really think
you're gonna get
something for nothing?
Do you know how long
it takes me to earn $500?
Give me three squares.
Hey, guys, get a load
of that guy over there
with the fake beard
and the dark glasses.
Does that look like
somebody I'm married to
in a special
anniversary disguise?
Well, two can play
at the surprise game.
Your beard might be phony,
but I know something
about you that's real.
Wait a minute.
You're not Eddie.
But you're not bad.
( sighs ):
Where is Eddie?
Why haven't I
heard from him?
It's dear to see Carla so
concerned about her mate.
Do you remember
when you gave that
lecture in New York,
and in a fit of whimsy, I
flew in to surprise you?
It was hardly a surprise;
we booked those reservations
three weeks in advance.
So you were in on
it-- still it was a
wacky thing to do.
( TV sports announcer talking )
Hey, Sam,
end of the first quarter.
SAM:
Oh! What's the score here?
26-25, Boston.
Let's see,
the winner is...
Uh-oh. Woody.
What a shame--
I know how he feels
about taking any
of his friends' money here.
You think
you can talk him into it?
( chuckles ):
Yeah, I'll give it a try here.
Hey, Woodrow,
you won the first pot.
How much did I win?
$125.
Yes! Come to Papa!
Suckers! Aah!
¶ I'm in the money,
I'm in the money! ¶
Maybe, uh, we could
force him to take it.
Here, Woody, listen
to me for a minute.
I don't want to, like,
you know, put down
your good time here.
Whoa, listen to me.
Listen to me.
It's kind of a tradition
amongst gamblers--
especially gamblers
who want to stay alive--
that you don't, you know,
dance and wave money around
in front of people
you just won it from.
Can I sing?
No, you can't sing.
Well, I guess it'd be
out of line to chant,
"In your face, in your face"?
Evening, everybody.
ALL:
Norm!
WOODY:
What's going on,
Mr. Peterson?
A flashing sign in my gut
that says
"Insert beer here."
Oh, Norm?
Ah. My clients.
Guys, I've, uh,
devised a color scheme
for the nursery, but
I have to warn you,
it's a bit drab.
Oh, good-- I will not have
our child emotionally attached
to cartoon mice
and teddy bears.
No. Our child
will receive affection
from parental embraces,
administered at generously
scheduled intervals.
And I'll be he comes back
one day to thank you for that.
Probably while you're sleeping--
you won't feel a thing.
( game playing on TV )
SAM:
Okay, 46 to 55.
That's the half.
Let's see.
Uh-oh. Clear the dance floor.
Woody won again.
Thanks.
NORM:
"Thanks"?
"Thanks"? That's
all you're gonna
say, "Thanks"?
Well, sure.
No, wait a minute,
wait a minute.
Listen, the only thing
that people hate worse
than a guy who gloats
is a guy who
stands there smug
when they know that
he's gloating on the inside.
If you're gonna dance,
for God's sake, dance.
I don't want to dance,
you guys.
I didn't mean to hurt anybody.
I just want to sit here quietly
and count my bucks.
Let's see,
that would be five...
ten...
fifteen...
Wait, there's something written
on this five.
Oh, that'd be mine.
Here, let me give
you a clean one.
I'll take that back...
I don't mind.
No, it's all right.
You'll get ink all over
your fingers, and...
Let's see what it says.
Uh, "Happy 30th birthday,
Cliffie-bits.
Sorry I didn't have time
to shop. Love, Ma."
You've been carrying around
a gift
from your mother for ten years?
No, no, Sammy--
the post office just
delivered it yesterday.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
very funny.
You're just jealous
'cause I got a ma
who sends me five bucks
on my birthday and you don't.
What are you
talking about?
Your ma sends me money
all the time, Cliff.
I got one right
here, actually.
"Dearest Norm,
thanks for hanging out
with my dorky son.
You're a saint.
Love Ma Clavin."
Oh. "P.S. I'm writing
this in the nude."
My ma didn't write that!
My ma's never been nude
in her life!
I got some flowers here
for, uh, Carla LeBec.
Oh, yes!
Let the present parade begin!
Ah...
I wonder what Eddie's plan is.
Flowers every hour,
or maybe the presents
are just gonna get bigger
and bigger as the night goes on.
I'll tell you,
I wouldn't be surprised
if I left here
tonight with an
electric fondue set.
Yes! "Happy
second anniversary,
your loving husband,
Edward LeBec."
Aw...
Aw, what a guy.
Yeah, boy,
that's really sweet, Carla.
NORM:
Yeah. Nice flowers, too.
( spits )
I hear that keeps
'em fresh longer.
Hey, whoa, where you going?
What is that about?
Those flowers
weren't from Eddie.
What are you talking about?
His real name isn't Edward,
it's Guy.
Hah?
What?
G-U-Y. Guy.
People just
call him Eddie
because it's too weenie
to say Guy.
All right,
which one of you dirt bags
sent those gorgeous flowers?
Come on, we didn't
send those.
You know... I'll betcha
Eddie spent about 50
bucks for those flowers.
$50? You told me
it was gonna be $35.
No! Oh!
God! I-I
don't believe
that you guys don't think
Eddie's gonna come through.
I mean... I'll tell you,
I got faith in Eddie.
He's the best husband
in the whole world,
and he is gonna come
through. You'll see.
( Sam whistles )
She's right, you know.
Yeah. You know, seeing
a wife stand up for
her husband like that
makes me realize
what I have at home.
I guess that's kind
of why I'm here.
Yeah. Two dozen,
long-stemmed.
And make the card out,
"To Carla,
with all my love, Guy."
Yeah, Guy. As in "geek."
Well, Carla, it's midnight.
Your anniversary is over.
No, Sam, it's over here.
Where Eddie is,
it's still going on.
He's got almost
three hours left.
Carla LeBec?
Ah, flowers.
Aren't you a little old
for a delivery boy?
It's my father's night off.
Hey...
Thank you.
Does anybody know who these are
from and who they're for?
Cliff's mom for me?
No, they're from Eddie LeBec
for me for our anniversary.
Now, are you guys satisfied
or would you like
to sit on these?
Boy, that's love for you,
isn't it?
Yeah, really.
I got a tear in my eye.
And you're going to have this
in your eye
if you don't lay off my mom.
Oh, Carla,
those are gorgeous.
Who sent them?
Who do you think?
Oh, isn't Eddie sweet?
Oh, why can't more men
send flowers?
I didn't know Mormons
couldn't send flowers.
I said more men,
not Mormons.
I know they can't dance.
No, Sammy, that's the,
that's the Amish.
W-Why can't Mormons
send flowers?
They can.
Then what
are you talking about?
I just wish someone
would send me some damn roses.
Why does it have
to be a Mormon?
Oh, come on!
( phone ringing )
WOODY:
Cheers.
With some people, you just can't
discuss religion.
Carla, that
was your florist.
They didn't accept
your credit card
for the flowers.
You got
to bring them cash.
Okay, Eddie
didn't send the flowers.
I sent them to myself.
I just figured that when he did
do his wonderful surprise,
it might be later,
and you guys might miss it.
So, just get off my case.
It's gonna
happen, okay?
There is one bright
side to all this.
Yeah, what's that?
You're gonna have the sweetest
smelling garbage on the block.
CLIFF:
Sammy, well, that's the end
of that game.
Who's the winner?
Oh, dear; guess who.
Yes, again! Ha!
A clean sweep for
the Boyd machine!
All four quarters
are mine!
Hey, here's three bucks;
go buy yourselves some luck.
( chortling )
I'm sorry, Woody,
but you're wrong.
Rebecca won.
What?
Well, I hope you learn
from my example.
I'm going to show you
how a really
gracious winner behaves.
Read 'em and weep,
farm boy! Whoo!
Excuse me, miss?
Yes, sir?
I'm Detective McGuiness,
Boston Police Department.
I'm off duty here,
but, uh, for your sake,
I really hope there isn't
any gambling going on here.
Gambling?
No, sir.
I earned this money.
I'm a prostitute.
That isn't better, is it?
Um, no, this
is just a little joke.
We play a little game here,
but we never play for keepsies.
See, I take
the money in,
and I give the money back
like this.
Give this back
to me later.
( phone ringing )
CARLA:
I'll get it.
Give me that back.
Cheers.
Yeah?
Great!
Ho-ho!
That was Sarafina.
Anthony is on his way over here
with a package for me
from Eddie right now.
Hey, good for you.
( horn honking )
That's him!
That's Anthony with my present.
Woody?
Why didn't he come in?
No brakes in the car.
How does he stop?
Well, he either swerves
into hedges
or he coasts
around the block
until he can stop the car
with his foot.
Oh, man,
this is gonna be good.
Laundry?
He sends you
his laundry?
Yeah, once a month, but...
this has got to be
some kind of joke.
I mean, he wouldn't send it
on our anniversary.
There's got to be a present
packed in here.
Right?
Oh, that Eddie...
what a guy.
Packing a present
in some laundry.
It's got to be in here
somewhere.
I guess I was wrong.
What are you all looking at?
( murmuring )
What are you avoiding
looking at?
I know what you guys think.
You think he forgot.
You think my marriage
is in big trouble
and Eddie's turning into
my typical creep husband.
Well, it's not true,
so just go back to
your stupid lives.
Norm, order a beer.
Clavin, bore us.
Oh, Woody, why don't you tell us
about how another one
of your relatives
lost a body part
in some farm equipment?
I ever tell you
about my Aunt Lefty?
Shut up.
Just go on back
to your sad, pathetic lives.
Me, I'm going home.
I'm going to go sit in
a dark room and have some fun.
( phone ringing )
Putting on
a Gene Pitney record...
WOODY:
Cheers.
and I'm gonna slice Eddie's face
out of every picture
in the house.
Oh, hey, how you doing?
No, I don't think she can come
to the phone, Eddie.
She has plans
for the evening.
Give me that phone!
Is this really Eddie?
Well, sure it's me, babe.
Listen, honey, I'm sorry
I couldn't come home.
I mean, I wanted to make last
year's celebration look sick.
I already got my plane ticket,
I'm at the airport,
and everything,
and they called me back
to rehearsal.
They changed the whole script
of the ice show.
They've taken all the humanity
out of the big bad wolf,
and the three little pigs think
they're God's gift to ice.
I really don't want
to talk about it.
Hey, Eddie,
when am I gonna see you again?
Gee, I guess
in a couple of months.
A couple of months?
Listen, honey, I got to go.
The bus is about to leave
from Yakima,
and if I don't make it quick,
the pigs will grab
all the good seats.
Hey, Eddie, I love you.
I love you too, sweetie. Bye.
( phone click and dial tone )
Hey, everybody,
listen up.
I want you all
to repeat after me.
I am a very stupid person.
ALL:
"I am a very stupid person."
And I will never doubt
the undying love
and total commitment that
exists, always has existed,
and always will exist
between Carla and Eddie LeBec.
ALL:
"I'm a very stupid person."
Close enough!
Well, turns out the only reason
he didn't surprise me
was he had to rehearse.
That ought to show you mo-mos
a lesson.
Well, that was Eddie
on the phone.
Hey.
Isn't that just the nicest,
sweetest thing
for Eddie to remember?
Yeah, Carla, sure was.
Yeah.
You called and reminded him,
didn't you, rat lips?
How could I?
I don't even know where he is.
Sammy, I'm going
to ask you again,
and I'm warning you.
Hey, don't back up.
I'm not going to hurt you,
you wimp.
All right.
The women in my family,
for generations,
have had absolutely no talents
or gifts but one.
We can make up any curse
and make it stick,
okay?
Now, tell me the truth,
or my curse on you
is gonna be...
Let me think of a good one here.
No, not the hair;
anything but the hair.
Okay, okay.
Your eyes...
Oh, no, wait a minute.
I got it.
Your tongue
is gonna swell up
so big,
you're going to have to buy
a seat on the plane for it.
Carla, this
is ridiculous.
Sammy, you know I can do it.
Now, look into my eyes
and tell me the truth.
Did you call Eddie and remind
him about our anniversary?
No, Carla, I didn't.
Okay.
But you and your tongue
better be telling the truth.
Family curse.
( slurring ):
How gullible
does thee think I am?
Oh, no.
No, oh... Carla! Carla!
CARLA:
What?
Nothing.
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org