Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Sorry, Dr. Crane,
I just don't understand
this word association stuff.
Right, allow me
to demonstrate.
Now, I'll say a word,
and then you say
the first word
that you think of.
Norm, we'll start with you.
Over.
Under.
Inside.
Outside.
Bottom.
Thermostat.
( Norm and Cliff chuckling )
If you could make any sense
out of that, uh,
I got a sawbuck here
with your name on it.
Okay, you're on.
It might not be
a total non sequitur.
Let me see, uh...
Perhaps in the house
Woody grew up in,
the thermostat was
at the bottom
of the stairs.
Actually, it was in the kitchen.
I'll, uh,
take cash or check.
No, no, or, uh, well,
the, uh, the heater may have
been in the, uh, cellar,
and so it was at the
bottom of the house.
Nope.
Thermostat is
difficult to spell.
Woody was at the
bottom of his class.
Woody,
did you turn up the heat again?
Yes, Miss Howe.
I told you,
it's too hot in here.
Now, if you keep turning it up,
I have to keep turning it down.
That wouldn't
be a problem
if they hadn't put
the damn thermostat
in such an awkward place.
I can barely reach it.
Sorry, Miss Howe.
( piano plays )
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You want to go where everybody
knows your name. ¶
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Frasier, where the hell
have you been?
You were supposed to pick me up
at the airport.
Well, um, gee, I didn't do
a very good job of it, did I?
Well, welcome home, dear.
Where have you been?
Paris.
Perhaps
you remember,
we liberated it during the war.
Yes, now that I recall,
you did say something about it.
Well,
I've just been so damn busy.
You do forgive me, don't you?
Oh, of course.
I could never stay mad
at you.
Well, how was Paris?
It was thrilling.
The City of Light.
Here.
Ooh, what's this?
A souvenir.
I'm tired
of your pinstripe boxers.
They're dull, unimaginative
and bourgeois.
Well, they always speak
very highly of you.
An eye patch.
No, you ninny,
it's French underwear.
( Cliff chortling )
It doesn't leave, uh, much
to the imagination, there,
( chuckling ):
does it, Fras?
Not that I
was imagining anything.
They're all the rage
in Paris.
They sell them
everywhere.
I bought these
at the Louvre.
Well, Lilith, dear...
I do appreciate
the gift, dearest,
but, uh, I, I
don't know if
they're really me.
Well, don't make up
your mind
before
you even try them on.
NORM:
Yeah, what do
you say, Fras?
Strap them on.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I suppose I could
slip into the
bathroom for a moment.
Oh, Frasier, do.
( phone rings )
Say, what am I going
to do with the old pair?
Save them;
I'm making a memory quilt.
Sam, phone for you.
It's Judy.
Judy--
( chuckling ):
Hi!
Well, of course
I remember you.
You're kidding me?
Well, that's just
around the corner.
Listen,
why don't you come on over?
We can replay
all the old memories.
( laughs )
All right.
Judy who?
She didn't say, Sam.
CARLA:
How many Judys
have you dated?
Well, let's see,
there was, uh, Judy
Johnson, right?
The, uh, tall
redhead, remember?
She had freckles,
great legs.
There's Judy Petinski.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, Judy Chang.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
How come you guys remember
my love life better than I do?
Well, I think it meant
more to us, Sammy.
Wasn't there, um,
a Judy Marlowe?
( chuckling ):
Oh, that's the one I remember.
Sammy, hot stuff.
Oh, you betcha.
God, did we have
great times.
I remember all
the playgrounds, the circuses,
the pony rides...
Uh, excuse me, Sam.
Exactly how old was this Judy?
No, no, she
was a divorcee.
She had this
little girl.
Must be about
what, 15 years
since I've seen
the two of them.
Just in case, you know,
if she comes in here
and she's not
very good-looking,
will you do me a favor--
pretend like you're my wife.
Okay.
All right.
Give me all the money
in your wallet.
Why? What are you doing?
I'm practicing.
Lilith, I have only one thing
to say to you.
Vive la difference.
Woody, I asked you to bring up
a case of scotch
15 minutes ago.
Now, will you just do it,
please?
Sorry, Miss Howe;
right away.
Whoa. Get up on
the wrong side
of the web?
No, I am just sick and tired
of the way I am treated
by this company.
They're trying
to break my spirit,
to bring me
to my knees.
They want to see how
long its going to take
before I say I quit.
Why, what
do they want you to do now?
Throw a party.
Oh, my God,
these people must be stopped.
I'm supposed to throw
a kiddie party
for the executives' brats;
well, I'll show them.
I am going to throw the best
damn party of the year.
I am going to have
the best food, the best games...
Does anybody know where I can
hire a professional clown?
Would you settle for a couple
of amateurs with red noses?
Say, you know who
you should hire?
Woody. He's an actor.
At least a
perennial understudy.
That's not a bad idea.
I wonder if Woody's interested.
Woody?
I have to hire a clown
for a children's party.
Do you think
you could handle the part?
"Handle the part"?
I've always wanted
to play a clown.
You hear that,
everybody?
I get to be a clown.
I'm a clown,
I'm a clown, I'm a clown!
Sam?
Judy?
( chuckling ):
Oh, wow!
God, what a relief!
What are you talking about?
Well, it's been 15 years since
we've seen each other,
and you look just
as good as I do.
Oh, hey, how you been?
Oh, I've been great,
I've been great.
Well, come over
here, sit down.
Carla, let's have
some, uh, white wine, please.
Guess what?
What?
My daughter Laurie
came along to say hi.
I'd love
to see her again.
Weren't the three of
us, didn't we have
fun together, huh?
You were always a
great uncle, Sammy.
A lot of men
get jealous.
They don't want
to share.
Hey, I hope I never get
so possessive that
I'm not willing...
Hi, Mom.
...to share.
Sam, you remember Laurie.
Hi.
( laughing ):
Wow.
You used to be so...
And now she's so...
So, uh... hey, how are you?
I'm fine, Mr. Malone.
"Mr. Malone"?
Hey, come on, I'm the same guy
that used to push you
in the swings
and give you
piggy-back rides
and play with you
in the bathtub.
No, that was me.
Oh, right, right, right.
Well, look at the two of you.
Look at the three of us.
Let's look at the two of you
again.
Look, I know you two
have a lot of catching up to do,
but it was really good
to see you
again, Sam.
Oh, wow, I just flashed
on the way
you used to make me hold
your hand crossing the street.
Anyway, I'll see you.
Wait, wait, where you going?
What's the rush?
Why is my voice so high?
I got an idea.
Uh, why don't, uh,
why don't the three of us
uh, do, uh,
one of those things we used
to do in the old days--
You know, get an
ice cream cone
together, or something.
I would love that.
Do you know
something, Sam?
What?
I am really glad
that I picked up the phone
and called you.
Oh, me, too.
Come on, Uncle Sammy.
There's a lot of traffic
out there.
( high-pitched laugh )
Looks like Sammy's
heading for trouble.
Yeah, looks like
kind of a fun trip,
though, doesn't it?
Carla, did you have
the soft drinks delivered
to Mrs. Ridgeway's house
for the party tomorrow?
Yeah, yeah-- four cases.
The kids will be burping
all through Woody's act.
Don't worry, with this outfit
and these props,
I'm going to have those kids
rolling on the floor.
Yeah, rolling around
and burping--
now there's an attractive image
for you.
You know, Woody, I envy you,
I really do.
Creating laughter
can be a healing art.
Sometimes a clown can do better
than a psychiatrist.
Yeah, and you can fit more
of them into a little car.
Got my funny horn,
my squirting flower,
my joke book--
can't miss.
CARLA:
Oh, yeah?
Let's see an example
of a joke that can't miss.
"Did you hear about
Yeah.
"the human cannonball?
It's hard to find a man
of his caliber."
I don't, uh, hear any hilarity
ensuing there, Wood-man.
Oh, you have to try them
both at the same time--
the props and the jokes.
Try it again.
Boy, this is going
to be flop city.
"Did you hear
about the human cannonball?
It's hard to find
a man of his caliber."
( horn honks )
( laughter )
See? Can't miss.
Let me try this.
This looks like fun.
Uh, all right. "You hear
about the sword swallower
who only eats penknives
'cause he's on a diet?"
( horn honks )
( laughter )
All right, all right,
you think that's funny?
Go ahead, Norm,
do another one.
All right.
Uh, "Did you hear about
the, uh, the tightrope
walker who went nuts?
They had to, uh,
throw a net under him."
( horn honks )
You know, you're right.
It is funnier when you do it.
Here we go.
Thanks, Uncle Sammy,
that was great,
but I've got to get
to aerobics class.
I'll call you tonight,
Mom.
Bye, honey.
God, kids are fun!
Mmm.
I especially loved taking her
to that department store
and watching her little face
light up.
Obviously.
Hey, come on,
what's the matter
with you?
I'm getting a little tired
of having you invite Laurie
along with us everywhere we go.
Oh, now, come on.
Mommy needs a little
quality time for herself.
Well, sweetheart, all
you had to do was ask.
Listen, what do you say
I pick you up around 8:00--
just the two of us,
all evening?
Adults only.
Mmm.
Caution, some scenes
may be unsuitable
for immature viewers.
I'll close my eyes.
SAM:
Oh, God!
Why? What?
What's the matter?
I guess I'm remembering
what happened
the last time you tried
to pitch both ends
of a double header.
Oh, boy.
Is it that obvious?
I think it was
the drooling that
gave you away.
Yeah, well, see, the thing is
that I'm really attracted
to Laurie,
and I want to ask her out,
but I don't want to stop dating
the mother at the same time.
I mean, it's like
a real problem, you know?
Gee,
must be a burden
being so sensitive.
Yeah.
Uh, Sammy,
door number two.
Hey, Laurie, what'd you
do, forget something?
Well, my class was canceled,
so I was gonna find Mom
and see if she wanted
to grab some lunch.
But I guess she
already left, huh?
Yeah, just a few minutes ago.
Oh, well, it's no biggie.
Well, wait a minute,
wait a minute.
Listen, uh, if you
have a couple minutes
on your hand here...
I'm about due for a break,
aren't I, Rebecca?
Hell yes, you've been
back at work
for almost five minutes.
Wouldn't it be a hoot
if your uncle took you
back to the same zoo,
but 15 years later?
How about it, guys?
Would that be a "hoot"
or what?
Uncle Sammy,
you're too much.
I'll go bring
the car around.
Great, I'll meet you
up there, okay?
Just a minute.
Zoos are kind of sad,
you know?
Huh?
I mean, all those
sedentary animals...
can't move,
can't run free,
they just sit there
and drink
and shovel food
in their faces.
Sorry, man, that
is no kind of life.
FRASIER:
Sam?
You're trying to date
your girlfriend's daughter.
Now, isn't there
a little voice
in the back
of your mind
trying to tell you
something?
Little voice?
Your conscience?
My conscience?
You mean like
Jiminy Cricket?
Well, okay.
Well, yeah,
as a matter of fact,
I do hear
this little voice.
But it's not coming from
the direction of my brain.
CARLA:
Sammy,
you better be careful.
See, even Carla agrees with me.
No, I'm just worried
that he's going to blow
it with both chicks.
Mothers and daughters
talk to each other.
Well, not in my family,
but usually.
Sweetheart, I've handled
trickier situations
than this before.
You remember
the time I dated
those lovely
Henshaw triplets
all at the same time?
Sammy, first of all,
that was back when
you were drinking like a fish.
And second of all,
that was one chick.
Frasier, you okay, bud?
I'm a little
concerned here, Norm.
My fingers are tingling.
My hand's numb,
my feet are cold.
Either I'm having
a heart attack
or this new
French underwear
Lilith gave me
is too tight.
Ah... cancel
the paramedics.
All right, all right.
All right!
I'm going on tonight!
I'm going on!
What do you mean,
in your theater group?
Yeah, yeah.
The lead has a fever of 106.
The rest of the cast
tried to drag him out of bed,
but he kept falling down.
I get to go on!
Woody, are you
ready to go?
We're going to be late
for the kiddie party.
Oh, Ms. Howe, I hate to let you
down, but I can't be your clown.
I'm playing Marc Antony.
"Friends, Romans, countrymen."
What are you
talking about?
Countrymen-- people who live
outside the city.
You know, shepherds,
farmers, ranchers.
Woody, you can't
desert me like this.
I don't have time
to get anyone else.
This is the chance
he's been waiting for.
Butt out!
You are the one
who insisted I hire him
in the first place.
Well, I was merely
suggesting...
Where am I going to get
another clown now?!
I am ruined
and it's your fault.
You're the one
who got me in this mess.
You owe me a clown.
Well, where do you think
I can find one now?
Gee, Frasier,
I mean, weren't you
the one who said
how much you
envied Woody?
Well, yes,
I did say that...
And that clowns
do more good than
psychiatrists?
Well, surely
you're not suggesting...
Yeah, you'll be great,
Dr. Crane.
Stuff's all right here
in this box.
You can't miss.
Me?
You want me to don
the jester's motley?
It's got to be you, Dr. Crane.
It takes a big man
to fill these shoes.
Well, why not?
I mean, they're just children
after all.
And I always have had
a special rapport
with the wee people.
Where's the harm?
All right,
let's go, Frasier.
We're late already.
Here's your outfit!
Oh, gee, Woody, you know,
I haven't had time
to rehearse.
I don't know anything
about being a clown.
You got any last minute advice
for me?
Just be yourself.
Ah, words of wisdom.
Well, I'm out
of here, okay?
You think Bozo the Shrink
can really cut it?
Are you kidding?
That stuff is foolproof.
The squirting flower, the horn,
the trick handkerchief...
What trick handkerchief?
You never showed us that.
That's the best one of all.
You pull the handkerchief
out of your pocket
and your pants fall down.
Underneath I'm wearing
these ridiculous
big red polka dot shorts.
It's a riot!
You mean Frasier's supposed
to be wearing those shorts?
Oh, no.
I forgot to give my underwear
to Dr. Crane.
I should call.
Well, no, no.
I've got to get to the theater.
Listen, Carla,
somebody should warn him.
Would you call him?
Of course.
( laughing )
Okay, kids,
you say hi to Binky!
KIDS:
Hi, Binky!
Binky, do your act.
I don't have an act,
I'm a psychiatrist.
Show them your funny feet.
I can't, I've got
these big shoes on.
Oh, I see
what you mean.
Say, kids, what do you
think of these feet, huh?
I got such big feet
because my mother was a goose.
Want to hear me honk?
( horn honks )
The real clown was killed.
Rebecca, what am I gonna do?
I don't know what
you're going to do,
but you better think
of something quick
because you're making...
Do the flower deal.
Oh, you mean this.
( laughing )
Hey, they like it!
You want to see
that again, kids?
Yeah!
Hey, I'm a clown,
I'm a clown!
Hey, guys...
Wait till you hear this.
I'm sitting at a table
in this restaurant
with Judy and Laurie.
The mother reaches over
and grabs my knee and says,
"Sam, I want you."
Get out.
Then I feel the daughter
reaching over
and grabbing my other knee.
She says, "I want you,
too, Sammy."
Well, yeah, yeah?
Then I woke up.
You know what this dream means,
don't you?
Mm-hmm, it means
you even dream
better than we do.
No, no, it means
that Frasier's right.
That my conscience
is getting to me.
You know,
I must feel bad
that I'm going out
with this woman
while I'm trying to score with
her daughter at the same time.
Sammy, you're scaring me.
How do you think I feel?
I mean, this hasn't
ever happened to me before.
I mean, you don't think that...
that I'm getting scruples?
Now you just stop it
right there, buddy boy.
You're talking crazy.
Damn it, I mean,
I really hate this.
I keep hearing this little voice
and this time
it's coming from my brain
and it just, it won't shut up.
And I got this feeling
that it's going
to keep nagging me
until I just
do the right thing
and break it off
with the daughter.
Whoa, wait, wait,
Sammy, Sammy, listen.
I could probably weather
this scruples stuff,
but the guys...
I mean, they look
up to you so much.
Sammy.
Sammy, please.
Reconsider, okay?
A mother and
her daughter.
This was going
to be something
I could tell
my grandchildren.
Oh, Sam, Sam.
Listen, guys.
I just have to do
the right thing here.
Hi.
What ya doing?
I want to talk to you.
I hope I'm doing the right
thing coming to you.
My mom doesn't know
I'm here.
I don't know how
to ask you this.
I've never
done it before.
Ooh...
Go on.
Sam, when I
was a little girl
I used to think you were
the most wonderful man
in the whole world.
I still do.
But I'm not a little
girl anymore.
ALL:
Ooh...!
Would you, uh,
wait a minute?
I'll be right back.
Remember those scruples?
Yeah?
To the showers.
Say, Laurie,
I want to tell you
how happy I am
that you feel you can
come and talk to me.
Because I feel that
you and I have this...
Oh, look at that.
A new ring?
That's what I came
to ask you.
What?
I'm getting married
and I want you
to give me away.
Why you little,
sl... sly one.
Who's the lucky guy?
Oh, it's a guy
I met at school.
We've been going together
a couple years.
You know,
he's a lot like
a young you, Sam.
Thank you.
I can't wait to give you away.
Thank you, Uncle Sammy.
I love you.
Yeah, whatever.
Run along.
I'm so sorry.
Don't feel bad, Sammy.
I let you guys down.
CARLA:
Listen, Sammy.
Sure, things didn't
go your way
and, sure, we're
a little disappointed,
but we'll get over it.
What's important here
is that you tried
to do the wrong thing.
Hey, that's right,
I did, didn't I?
Sammy,
( chanting ):
Sammy, Sammy!
( applause )
Thank you. Okay, now I think
there's some more
cake and ice cream in there
for you.
Yay!
Oh, Binky, you were wonderful.
I must admit I was
a bit worried at first,
it took us quite a while
to warm up to you.
Yes, well, thank you,
kind lady.
See, actually I have
a confession to make.
Ah?
I'm really Dr. Frasier Crane,
practicing psychiatrist.
Clowning is
my avocation.
And, Ms. Howe,
I will be sure to
mention to my husband
the splendid work
you did on this party.
Thank you, Mrs. Ridgeway.
Now, if you will
excuse me for a moment.
You have no idea
how lucky we are.
That was Woody
on the phone.
He called
to check up on us.
That handkerchief
is a trick handkerchief.
If you had pulled
that out of your pocket,
your pants would have fallen
down around your ankles
and then we would've seen
those skimpy underpants.
Oh, good Lord.
That's not the half of it.
You see, I took off that
little French torture device
that Lilith got me
earlier today.
I've been doing this
al fresco.
Dr. Crane,
would you come here
for a moment?
I'd like you to
meet my mother.
Why yes, I'd be delighted to.
I've heard such wonderful things
about her.
( sneezes )
Gesundheit, madam.
Here's my handkerchief.
REBECCA:
No!
( woman screams, loud thud )
MRS. RIDGEWAY:
Mother? Mother?
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org