Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Sounds great, Kelly.
I'll see you Saturday.
Yeah. Okay.
Guess what, guys?
What?
I'm going to my first
country club dance.
SAM:
Whoo-hoo!
All right.
Yeah, I gotta check
the bus schedule.
Wait, wait, Woody--
you're going out with
the boss's daughter and you're
riding around on a bus?
Yeah, it's getting to be
a real drag, too.
Especially when
you can't sit together.
Maybe I can borrow Sam's car.
CLIFF:
Whoa, whoa, hey.
Hold up there, Woodster.
Lest you forget the
Ten Commandments
of Sam Malone.
Hence, commandment
number three:
"Thou shall not
loan thy car."
I thought that was
commandment number four.
That's
"Honor thy hair."
I think Sam might make
an exception
in my case.
Hey, Sam?
Sam?
Can I borrow your car?
My car?
Yeah, I'll be real
careful with it.
( laughing )
No, I'll bring it home early
and I'll wash it
the next day.
( cackling )
Well, food for thought.
So, Wood, is he gonna
loan you the car?
He didn't come right out and
say it, but I like my chances.
He's in a great mood today.
( laughing hysterically )
( piano plays )
¶ Making your way
in the world today ¶
¶ Takes everything you've got
¶ Taking a break
from all your worries ¶
¶ Sure would help a lot
¶ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ¶
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You want to be where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ You want to go
where people know ¶
¶ People are all the same
¶ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ¶
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I wish you luck, Woody,
because if Sam does
lend you that car,
you're home free.
That thing is
a rolling aphrodisiac.
Absolutely.
You know, any female that rides
around with Sam in that car...
Yeah?
...ends up going straight
to bed with him.
I've ridden in that car.
Right.
Well, I didn't go
to bed with him.
Huh. Right, and they
always deny it
afterwards,
you know?
I hate you guys.
Yeah, then they always cop that
anti-male attitude, you know?
Oh, Sammy, mind if I cut out
for an hour?
I want to catch
the last couple of innings
of my kid Ludlow's
T-ball game.
Hey, I thought he was the
intellectual of the family.
He's into baseball, huh?
Well, he didn't go willingly.
I had to trick him.
I used the old
"going to the library
"but running out of gas
in front of the ballpark"
routine.
Seems kind of drastic,
doesn't it?
Come on, Sammy,
please.
I don't want
the kid growing up
to be a soft,
doughy wimp
wearing an argyle sweater
and smoking a pipe.
SAM:
Go ahead, take off.
And don't worry about Lud;
he'll be fine.
"Lud: you know,
that's Carla's son
by Bennett Ludlow.
He's a cute little tyke.
Carla bore a son
to Bennett Ludlow--
the eminent psychiatrist,
your mentor?
Oh, this is prime dish.
I can't wait
to tell the girls
in the sleep disorder lab.
So, Carla, tell, tell.
Have you bedded
any other Rhodes scholars?
Uh... no.
But one egghead, long-distance,
phone-in father
is enough for
this baby factory.
In spite of the fact
that Dr. Ludlow's work
takes him out
of the country,
I'm sure he's
a marvelous parent.
No, a good parent
is someone who's there.
Who's there to help them out
with their homework.
There when they wake up
in the middle of the night
crying their eyes out.
He's there with
the bottle of Bactine
when they give themselves
a bad tattoo.
Well, I've been there.
I raised eight kids
on a waitress's salary,
and I want you to know
they're all good kids,
and not one of them
has had a conviction
that stood up on appeal.
I stand corrected, Carla.
Mom, how could you
do that to me?
Luddy, how did you
get here?
Did the coach drop you off?
Yes.
Oh, then the game
ended early.
So how'd you do?
Coach me had on the bench
all afternoon.
Well, what do you mean?
You didn't play at all?
Well, they finally put me in
after the kid
with the cast on his leg
and the two fat girls left.
So what did you do?
I hit the ball,
but they still made fun of me.
Like everybody's just supposed
to know which way to run.
I'm going to go clean up
your specs.
Carla's got herself a real
Poindexter there, huh?
Yeah.
It's sad to say
that kids not accepted
by their peers
really never learn how
to get along with people
in the big grown-up world.
Why is that, Cliff?
'Cause they keep
boring everyone and
driving them crazy
with long speeches
filled with meaningless
statistics?
Yep, yeah.
63% of them live lives
of quiet desperation.
And how about those
who sit next to them?
I'm Dr. Frasier Crane,
a friend of your father's.
I understand
you had a rough
afternoon.
You must never let the bullies
of this world
diminish your inner spirit
nor put out the fire
of your competitive nature.
Sir?
Yes, son?
You're kneeling
on some gum.
Heavens,
my new gabardines!
You and gum.
He attracts it
like a magnet.
We'll swing by our place
and pick up another pair
on our way to the opera.
Which opera are you going to?
Die Meistersinger.
Oh, I know that one.
That's where all
the master singers
get together in Nuremberg
and have a big contest
to find out who's best.
Oh, yeah, kind of
like Star Search.
Basically.
Frasier...
Frasier, I just had
a delicious idea.
Why don't we buy
an extra ticket
and take young Lud
to the opera with us?
LUD:
Oh, wow, great!
But I have to ask my mom.
Mommy, Dr. Crane and his wife
invited me to go
to the opera with them.
Well, you don't
have to be polite.
Just tell them to bug off.
But, Mom, I want to go.
Please?
Carla, may I have a word
with you?
Yeah. Sammy,
entertain the kid.
Carla, you'd be doing
us all a favor.
Allowing Frasier and me
to spend some time
with your son might help us
to formulate a decision
that's been under much
discussion as of late.
You see, the two of us are
considering whether or not
we wish to reproduce.
You're thinking
of having a baby, huh?
So, tell me,
how long does it take
one of your pods
to hatch, anyway?
Listen, you want
to baby-sit Lud,
be my guest.
What's that
on your shirt?
Huh? Ooh!
You're good.
Okay, Luddy,
you're going to the opera.
Yay!
Yeah, you're going
to love it, kid, too.
You know that Wagner,
he wrote all those pieces
when he was stone deaf.
No, that was Beethoven.
I meant blind.
That was Milton.
He had warts.
That was you.
I told you
not to tell anybody.
Shouldn't they be back
by now?
How long can an opera last?
Well, the last one
I remember
lasted about eight months.
Yeah, I just hope
everything's all right.
Carla, look, I know
you love your kids
and everything...
I mean, like your kids.
I mean, I know
you have kids...
but I have never seen you
this concerned before.
Well, Lud's special.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I mean, whenever I come home
at night,
he always brings me a pan
of hot water for my feet.
He actually asks me
how my day went.
I don't know
if I ever told
anybody this before...
I love him.
You don't have to be
shy about saying
that you love
your kids.
Oh, why don't you just take out
an ad in the Yellow Pages?
( Rebecca whistling )
Hey, Normie, I almost forgot
how much Sam's Corvette girls
love to whistle.
( groans )
I wish I had a nickel
for every time
I heard that sound, huh?
Classic slamming of the door.
( laughing
hysterically )
So Sam still
won't loan you
his car, huh?
No, but I'm starting
to love that man's laugh.
Sammy, come on,
give the kid a
break, will ya?
Just let him
borrow your car.
Please, Sam?
Kelly's the best girl
I've ever dated,
and she loves Corvettes.
Well, I tell you what, Woody.
I'll give her a lift in my car.
No way, Sammy.
Every girl who goes
for a ride in your Corvette
winds up going
to bed with you.
Right, Miss Howe?
( shrieks )
Well, now she's
just being redundant.
It's okay, Sam, I understand
about the car thing.
Oh, good.
I didn't mean to put
you on the spot.
And, uh, I want you to know
that, even though you won't
let me borrow your car,
there's no hard feelings.
And if I ever have
a car of my own,
and you want
to borrow it,
it's yours.
Ah, I know what
you're trying to do.
You're trying to guilt me
into giving you my car.
No, I'm not.
I wouldn't do that.
You're my best friend.
Ah, man, you're scum!
I mean it, Sam,
I love you.
Hey, fine.
Here, take the damn car.
What just happened?
You outsmarted him.
So that's what it feels like.
Mom, Mom!
The opera was so great!
All the singing,
and costumes.
This was the best
day of my life!
That's
terrific, Lud.
I never seen him
so excited.
Thanks, guys.
Oh, Carla, it was our pleasure.
He's an extraordinary child.
Yes, we had
an extensive discussion
on the way back
about opera,
the arts, film...
Oh, Carla, may we take Lud
to the movies tonight?
There's a revival
of Koyaanisqatsi
we'd love him to see,
and then we were thinking
he could sleep over,
We could have brunch and a
matinee of Peter and the Wolf.
Gee, I don't know.
He's never stayed
away from home before.
He's only six.
Please, Mommy?
Please?
Oh, heck, you really want
to go that bad, huh?
Go, go, go ahead.
Have a good time.
Stay as long as you want.
I'll see you when you get back.
Thank you, Carla.
We'll take good care of him,
don't worry.
Well, that's that.
I lost my baby.
Listen, Sam,
I hope it's okay
that I keep
asking you this,
but I just want
to make sure
one last time
that you haven't
changed your mind
about me
using your car.
No, Woody.
No, you haven't
changed your mind
or no, I can't
use your car
or no, it's not
okay to ask?
No, get out of my face
before I hurt ya.
He's special.
Hey, Carla, still listening
to that opera stuff?
She can't
hear you, Cliff.
She's got the music
blasting in her ear.
You mean she
can't hear me
if I say
she reminds me of
one of those little
plastic troll dolls?
Hey, what's...
what's the big idea?
I thought
you couldn't hear me.
No, but I can see,
and you're ugly.
So, are you still cramming all
that high-Q stuff in your head?
You know, Sammy, I
don't have any choice.
I mean, ever since
Dr. Cyclops and Morticia
started introducing
Lud to all this
culture crap,
it's like I don't
have anything to
talk to him about.
So I'm listening
to all this music,
and I'm plowing through
all these books here.
Look at this.
Good heavens, man.
History of Modern Art.
Comprehensive Guide
to the World Of Opera.
Hollywood Wives.
Yeah, I'm getting
into literature, too.
I've read this.
Oh, man, who am
I trying to kid?
I'm just stupid.
Hey, you are not stupid.
Oh, how would you know?
You're stupid.
If you were really stupid,
you wouldn't know that about me.
Good point.
Greetings, Carla.
We just dropped
your son off at home
after a lovely sojourn
at the Museum
of Fine Art.
You know, that child
is such a love.
He's so bright,
inquisitive,
creative.
He reminds me of
myself as a child.
Of course,
he has more hair.
We were wondering
if we could
treat Lud to dinner
this evening.
Come on, guys.
You've had him out
every night this week.
Besides, I had a special
family evening planned.
I was gonna cook
a big bowl of pasta,
and we're all gonna
sit around and watch
America's Most Wanted,
and see if we could
rat on our neighbors.
Yes, but, you see, Carla,
this is special, too.
I mean, I've just managed
to finagle reservations
for Magritte's.
It's the most exclusive
restaurant in all of Boston.
I never heard of it.
Precisely.
Carla, please.
It would mean a lot
to the child,
and I think Lud
would enjoy it also.
Oh, all right.
Who cares?
More spaghetti for
the rest of us.
SAM:
Hey, Fras.
Listen, why don't you invite
Carla to dinner with you?
Well, now, Sam, uh...
Carla is a fine woman
and a good friend.
Actually,
she's neither.
And why would I want
to eat with her?
Frasier, dear, I think
we should invite Carla.
I think it would
be very, very nice.
Do you know what
would be very,
very nice, Lilith?
If you would stop
digging your nails
into my palm.
But I'm sure I'll choose
to see your point
before you draw blood.
Carla? Carla, what say
we make it four
at Magritte's
tonight, huh?
You buying?
I'm going.
Well, good.
We're on, then.
We'll call for you at 8:00.
By the way, Carla,
please bear in mind
that this is a very
posh establishment.
Need I say more?
Oh, no, no, no.
I get the picture
loud and clear.
I'll shave my legs.
I hope this table
is satisfactory.
Oh, this is wonderful.
You know, the place is just
as I had heard it was.
It's delightful.
Everything looks
absolutely exquisite.
The menu is
a delightful combination
of nouvelle and provincial
with a nod toward
domestic ingredients.
And get a load
of all this ambiance.
The artwork
is stunning.
Yes, well, there's
a delightful example
of modern art.
If I might venture a guess,
I would say it's a "Schnaybel."
It isn't.
But, even if it was, it would be
pronounced "Schnahbel."
Excuse me.
It's a little hard to tell
this far from our "tahbel."
That's funny, Mom.
Ludlow, please,
we're not here to have fun.
We're here
to enjoy ourselves.
Now...
would it
please everyone
if I ordered
for the whole table?
It would
be delightful.
Fine. Thank you.
Now, I know that
Lilith's delicate constitution
is not amenable to shallots.
Is there anything else
I should be mindful of?
How considerate of you
to ask, Frasier.
Actually, I have a delicate
constitution, as well.
No extra-heavy barbecue sauce.
I'll be repeating
like a Howitzer.
Delightful.
Boy, this sure
beats taking the
bus, doesn't it?
Just you and me,
the open road.
I'm getting kind
of tired of driving.
What do you say
we park somewhere
and look at the stars
for a while?
Oh, that sounds
nice, Woody.
Hey, Sam, where's
a good place
to go next?
SAM:
Make a right
at the light!
And not so
fast this time!
Thank you.
Oh, and please tell Paul
that the salad course
was an absolute treasure.
His subtle
yet assertive dressing
was the perfect balance
for the arugula.
I concur in spades.
He'll be pleased
to hear it.
Well, shall
we bouillabaisse?
Ah, now...
smell
the piquant bouquet.
Taste it with every
part of your tongue,
and then let it just
dance down your throat.
Frasier, as usual,
your anticipation
is interfering
with my enjoyment.
Yeah, Eddie has
that problem, too.
Ludlow, you're not eating.
None for me,
thanks, Dr. Crane.
He doesn't like fish.
Look, Carla,
this is not something
that comes out
of your cupboard
in a tin can
with a mermaid on it.
This is fruits de mer.
At $32 a pop, I think
the lad should give it a try.
Now, Ludlow, you've
been very open-minded
about everything else.
Make him happy. Take a bite.
If you don't like it,
you can spit it out
in your napkin. See?
Carla, we are not here
to make me happy.
We are here to enrich
the lad's experience,
which, if I must say so,
I do believe is my provenance.
Now, Lud, you know we all have
certain things we don't like.
I detested fish
when I was a child,
but I kept eating it and,
finally, I overcame my aversion.
LILITH:
Likewise.
When I first
met Frasier,
I detested him.
Yes, but the point
is you love me now.
And Lud will
love bouillabaisse.
Try it.
Okay.
Eww! Fish!
You barely
tasted the broth.
Give it a better
chance than that.
No! I want
a hamburger!
This restaurant does
not serve hamburgers.
Now, eat
your bouillabaisse.
No! This fishy soup stinks!
And I hate it!
What an imp!
Luddy?
What are you doing?
I'm going to try to get him
out from under there.
No, Carla. Carla,
that's exactly what
he wants you to do.
One must not play
the game by his rules.
Now, I've taught
a seminar or two
on developmental
behavior,
and the first rule in
these acting-out situations
is to simply ignore
the offending child.
Just pretend that
he doesn't exist.
Eventually, he'll
get bored and come out.
So... what a lovely meal.
Mmm! Do you know,
I heard
that the chef here
was a protégé of...
Do you smell
something burning?
Yes. That's my shoe.
I heard that
he was a protégé of...
Your shoe
is on fire?
Yes.
LILITH:
Isn't that painful?
Excruciating.
But I'm not going
to give the child
the pleasure
of hearing me cry out.
So, you see,
it seems
he was educated
in a small village
on the Rhine.
He...
Oh, Lud.
One hotfoot might
be considered
a puckish prank.
But, if you light
that other match,
it is the end
of our tutelage.
Is that
perfectly clear?
That's it!
That's it! I've had it!
That severs
the relationship!
Frasier,
everyone thinks
you're arguing
with your clams.
Is there
a problem here?
No, no. Of course not.
The boy just slipped
under the table,
and his mother was
about to get him out.
His mother.
Uh... yes, yes.
Carla, could you
take care of this?
Gee, I don't know if I could.
I... I've never taken
a psychology seminar.
Sir, we have a very
nice table in the kitchen.
Please, Carla.
Please, please.
Hey, Lud, burger time.
Yay!
Ha-ha!
Hotfoot, huh?
My genes must
be in there somewhere.
Let's go, Mommy.
First, apologize
to Dr. Crane.
I'm sorry, Dr. Crane.
I guess I shouldn't
have acted this way.
Well, no hard
feelings, son.
Let's have dinner
again sometime
when you're about,
oh, in your late 30s.
Bye.
Uh... I was wondering.
Do you have frog legs?
Why, yes.
They're
nice pants.
No one will
ever notice.
( laughing )
I always wanted
to do that.
You're the best mommy
in the world.
Yeah. Tell me
something
I don't know.
You know, Lilith,
I think we've all
learned something
here tonight.
I'm going to try
to tell you what it is
before you coat
my blistering feet with butter
and drop me off
at the emergency room.
You see...
this incident has made something
very clear to me.
I... I believe my initial
instincts were correct.
We shouldn't have children.
I don't think I'd
make a good father.
I don't want to be a father.
I'll never be a father.
End of discussion.
Frasier, I'm pregnant.
I'm gonna be a daddy?
I'm gonna be a daddy!
Oh, Lilith, we must
come here more often.
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4a5s
Help other users to choose the best subtitles