Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
I hate this uniform.
It is ugly.
It makes me look like
a beached whale.
And on top of everything
I can't find any earrings
to go with it.
Try some broccoli.
Ha-ha-ha!
I mean it, Sam.
I really hate it.
I used to like it,
but now I'm getting
kind of tired of it.
Feel like I'm wearing
the same thing every day.
Listen, I'm not a big fan
of them either
but let's just
give it our best here.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, Sam...
No, no, don't...
Can't you just talk
to the Iron Maiden?
Convince her
to get rid of them.
Come on.
Oh...
Miss Howe, uh...
about the uniforms.
Oh, I'm glad
you reminded me.
The dry cleaning plant
is on strike.
Now, we may not have
fresh uniforms
for at least a week,
so I want you to be
extra careful with those.
Oops.
Oh, no.
Um...
you guys are going
to get it.
Didn't you hear
what Miss Howe
just got through...
( laughing )
I get it.
SAM:
Yo...
( piano plays )
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always glad
you came ♪
♪ You want to be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ You want to go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same
♪ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Hi, everybody.
Hey, Dave.
All right.
How are you?
I know who you are.
I've seen you
on the news.
I can't believe it.
Hey, everybody.
It's Dave Richards,
Channel 10.
Channel 13.
Oh, sorry.
Never mind.
Sam, I got a proposition
for you.
No, no, no...
if she's not good
enough for you,
I sure don't want her.
No, no, it's nothing like that.
You see,
I have to give up
my TV spot, I on Sports.
They're looking
for a fill-in
for the week and I thought
you might be interested.
Boy, sports on TV...
I've never really considered
that.
( with deep voice ):
Think I'd be any good at it?
Who knows? It may turn out
to be a permanent gig for you.
That's how I got my start.
Whoo, boy, I don't know.
Oh, come on, Sam.
Come on.
Every time we watch Dave,
you say, "I can do better
than that stump."
Thank you, Carla.
You're too kind.
Come on, Sam.
You'd be great.
You talk good like me
and you're handsome.
NORM:
Of course, Sam.
What do you say?
Listen...
if I were you, okay--
and believe me,
not a day goes by
I don't wish I were--
I would take this job.
Sam, look...
It's a lot of fun.
You see, you get
to sit behind this desk.
You don't have
to wear pants.
It's my little joke
on the audience.
I do know sports,
and I'm articulate at that.
Hey, you know something?
I'm going to do it.
All right!
Congratulations.
Thanks, man.
You're on at 11:00.
Wait a minute. Tonight?
Without any preparation
or anything?
Sure, I do it all the time.
Look, I want you to get down
to Wardrobe ASAP, huh?
All right.
See ya.
Wait, wait, wait. Whoa, man.
Who do I talk to over there?
A very good friend of mine,
Phil somebody or another.
I forget. Anyway,
I got to get going,
meet my lady.
She's terrific.
Huh?
This time the Dave Machine
is finally settling down.
Well, hey,
congratulations, man.
Excuse me.
The alarm just went off.
I make an ungodly
amount of money
and I know exactly
how to use it.
You must be a friend
of Mr. Malone's.
Well, you know
what they say,
"The good-looking ones
travel in pairs."
And, uh,
that's certainly true
in your case.
Do you have the time?
4:30.
Good, 'cause
I just wanted
to remember
the exact moment
I met the biggest jerk
on Earth.
( Sam laughs )
Tough woman, tough woman.
You got that right.
I wear a cup to work.
Well, the pulsating
Dave Machine's history.
All right, man,
take care.
Excuse me, Dave.
Dr. Crane here.
If you're interested,
I happen to conduct
a little session
for narcissists
about once a month.
My policy: only show up
if I get an award.
This is the Big Dave Machine
saying good night
and may the sports be with you.
You know,
I bet if you held your ear
up to his,
you could hear the ocean.
I'll have to try it sometime.
It, uh, may not
work for you.
Hey, guys,
I'm off to the station.
Listen, do me a favor,
will ya?
Woody, Carla, close up for me.
You know...
Whoa, Sammy, you're forgetting
something
a little important here.
What?
You don't own this joint
anymore.
Oh, boy.
And even if you did,
Field Marshal Howe
wouldn't give you the night off.
Yeah, yeah.
Silly me.
What am I going
to do about this, huh?
Sam, may I suggest deception?
Well...
Hold on your horses
there, Frasier.
As a psychiatrist,
isn't it your job
to seek and uphold
the truth?
Oh, get real, Cliff.
You know, you got
a good idea there, Frasier.
Yeah. Lying.
I do lying.
Woody, come here. Do me a favor.
When Miss Howe comes out
of the office here,
go down the hall
and call the bar.
I'll answer.
What do I say?
Nothing.
Just stand there
and hold the phone.
Okay, I'll give it
a try.
Um, Miss Howe,
we're running low on napkins.
So order more.
I don't know how many more.
I don't run the bar anymore.
Thank you.
I appreciate this
very much.
( phone rings )
I'll get it.
Cheers.
Yeah, this is Sam Malone.
What? You say
my apartment's been robbed?
Oh, Sammy!
You say
I've been cleaned out?
Well, damn.
Yeah, I guess I could
get over there right away
and maybe expect not
to be back here
for a few hours, huh?
Well, thank you very much.
Thank you.
That was my landlord.
Do you believe this?
I've been robbed.
What's happening to this city?
Go on, Sammy.
ALL ( chanting ):
Go, Sammy! Go, Sammy!
Go, Sammy, go!
We're a, uh, victim
support group.
I see.
Well, I better hire
a relief bartender.
Hello?
Is there somebody on this phone?
Oh, uh, hi, Miss Howe.
It's-it's me, Woody.
Woody, are you using this phone?
No, no, not really.
What are you doing, Woody?
Oh, I'm just standing here
holding it.
Woody, hang up
the phone, please.
I have to hire
another bartender now.
Oh, no, Miss Howe,
I'm really sorry.
I swear I'll never do it again.
REPORTER:
And Keller is scheduled
to be executed on Friday.
I guess he won't be around then
for the Patriots-Buffalo game
this Sunday.
For that and all the sports,
a new member
to the Channel 13 team,
here's former Red Sox pitcher
Sam Malone.
( cheering )
Nice to have you
with us, Sam.
Thank you, Joanne.
I'd just like to say
that you look better live
than you do in person.
Thank you.
Oh, very slick.
Very slick indeed.
Yes. Five bucks says
Sammy has Joanne at 11:00.
Red Sox pitcher Paul Willis
went on the 15-day
disabled list today.
Willis has floating cartilage
in his knee
and tomorrow will undergo
arthroscopic surgery.
All right! I can't bel...
On his first night!
Club soda,
Woody, please.
Sure, Miss Howe.
MAN:
Today on This Old House,
we're going to be grouting
counter tile,
so I'm sure you'll want
to stick around for that.
But first, let's go
in the kitchen.
Don't you guys
usually watch sports?
Yeah, well, yeah,
usually, but, uh,
they're going to be putting up
drywall in a minute.
MAN:
The subflooring
is just being laid.
And now for the I on Sports
commentary.
You know, the world
is full of negative people.
Okay, so the Sox aren't having
such a great season,
but that's no reason to boo
and say bad things about them.
You know, I don't know
where I heard it,
but I thought you were supposed
to root, root, root
for the home team.
So the next time
you're in Fenway,
you can't yell something nice,
don't yell anything at all.
This has been
just one guy's opinion.
Joanne?
Thank you, Sam.
You've given us all
a lot to think about.
We'll be right back
with the weather
after this message.
And we're clear.
That was quite
a commentary, Sam.
Well, I hope I didn't
offend anyone, you know?
I just feel like
it had to be said.
Mm. Would you mind
a little friendly critique?
No, no. Go ahead.
I know this is the first time
you've done this,
but I think you might want
your commentaries
to be a little more...
Oh, what's the word
I'm searching for?
Interesting.
Interesting. Right.
You know, that gives me
something to shoot for there.
Say, uh, there's a
late-breaking story
over at my place
around 12:00-ish.
Care to cover it?
Sorry, I don't do
fluff pieces.
And in five, four,
three, two...
Well, it was a little chilly
coming into work today.
Dr. Buzz, what does
our weather look like?
MAN:
...Not to waste
any of the grout.
Remember, it's nine cents
a ton...
This looks really
fascinating.
Oh, I'll say.
Gee, you should've seen
this guy put the flasher
on the roof.
I'm so sorry
I missed that.
I was watching Sam do the sports
on Channel 13.
Sammy!
Our I on Sports!
( applause )
How was I?
You were great, Sam.
Hey, I never found the
scores so fascinating.
Yeah, it was pure
Musburger, Sammy.
Sammy, it was the
single greatest exhibition
of sportscasting
I've ever seen in my life.
And I am not just saying that
in order to get a free beer.
If the spirit
does move you,
Sammy, I take a size 12 sudsy.
Hey, thank you, guys.
You know, coming from you,
it means a lot.
So, Carla...
how was I really?
It was like watching
old people eat.
You delivered the sports fine,
but you got to jazz up
the commentary.
Yeah, yeah, boy, they
said that same thing
down at the station.
You know, you got
to talk about something
a little more
interesting than...
rooting for the home team.
That's like saying,
"let's all drive safely."
There goes tomorrow's
commentary.
You know, I want to do
so great at this job,
but it's kind of tough,
you know?
I got to come up with
five opinions a week.
Well, they couldn't
pay me enough.
You know, I'll worry
about this later.
Right now I got to get
Rebecca to give me
the rest of my nights off.
No problem there, Sammy.
I don't think
you work here anymore.
What are you talking about?
Vampira knows.
She was watching TV
in her office.
She has a TV in there?
Yeah, one of those little
tiny ones, like her heart.
Great.
Uh, Ms. Howe?
I have a confession to make.
You know that story about
my apartment being robbed?
I made that all up.
No!
Yeah, yeah.
Actually, I was down
at Channel 13
doing the sportscast.
Hope you're not mad.
Well, you used
to be the boss.
How did you feel when
people lied to you?
Ah, well, I had a rule.
When anyone ever lied to me,
they had to go to bed with me.
Well, that's one way to make
sure it won't happen again.
You know, Mr. Malone,
you haven't been
dealing fairly with me.
I know, I know.
I'm sorry.
It's just that this...
this means a lot to me.
And now I suppose
you're going to ask me
for the rest
of the week off.
Yeah, I know,
it's a lot to ask.
No, it isn't.
You're on.
Oh, great.
What, am I fired or something?
Not at all.
Look, I figure one of
two things will happen:
either you'll do well,
they'll offer you a job
and I'll never
see you again;
or you'll screw up,
humiliate yourself
and come back here
a crushed
and broken man.
Either way, I win.
Son of a gun,
you do have heart.
Of course I do.
Tell me though.
What'd you think?
How'd I look out there?
I've never seen you
look better.
Really?
You should always
be this size.
Let me give you
some advice here:
never do this to a guy.
Guys, guys, he's about
to do the commentary here.
Anybody know what
the topic's going to be?
Well, no, no, he said
he was going to crank it up
by taking a firm stand.
Hey, Woody, wasn't he
rehearsing with you?
Yeah, but he made me promise
not to tell you guys.
It's too exciting.
And I don't remember.
Tonight I'm going
to tackle the issue
that's tearing
professional sports apart--
natural grass
or artificial turf?
Now this reporter's
not afraid to say
that he's firmly in favor
of natural grass.
It's softer,
causes fewer injuries,
and let's face it, folks:
it looks prettier on TV.
That's just one guy's opinion.
Joanne?
Gee, Sam, I heard somewhere
that in an indoor stadium
it's impossible
to grow real grass.
Well, yes, yes, uh...
in indoor stadiums,
you have to use the fake stuff.
And I've heard that some of
the more recent synthetic blends
actually do help
reduce injuries.
Oh.
Well, I hadn't heard that, Doc.
That's pretty amazing.
So what are you saying
here, Sam?
Well, I guess I'm saying that
I could go either way on it.
So you have no opinion on this?
No, I have two opinions.
And that's one guy's opinions.
SAM ( on TV ):
The Graf-Everett final
may be a good match-up,
but if you ask
this I on Sports,
the fact that
Martina Navratilova decided
to sit this one out...
Ooh, to say "Martina Navra-
whoever" without even...
You know, I got a phone call
today from a teenager
saying I was taking advantage
of my status as an ex-ballplayer
and that old squares like me
shouldn't be doing the sports.
Well, Corky,
tonight's commentary
is directed right at you.
( hip-hop music plays )
♪ Time to rap
about a controversy ♪
♪ Gonna take a stand,
won't show no mercy ♪
♪ A lot of folks say jocks
shouldn't be ♪
♪ Doing the sports news on TV
♪ I don't want to hear
the latest scores ♪
♪ From a bunch of old
broadcasting school bores ♪
♪ So get your scores
from a guy like me ♪
♪ Who knows what it's like
to have a groin injury ♪
♪ G-G-Groin, g-g-groin
♪ G-G-Groin injury.
( music stops )
Joanne.
Dr. Buzz, there must be
some weather.
Ah, poor Sammy.
Bet you they fired him
after that display, huh?
Yeah, I guess he won't
be showing his face
around here tonight.
Would you come into a place
where everyone thought
you were a complete idiot?
Never mind.
Well, I suppose he's out
wandering the streets,
rapping incoherently.
Yeah, yeah, but
what if he comes in?
What are we going
to say to him?
Well, just tell him
he was brave.
Yeah, like a kamikaze pilot.
Wow, I always wanted
to meet one of those guys.
The stories they
must tell, huh?
Well, I guess as per usual,
it's up to me as his best friend
to tell him the truth.
You?
I'm sure he'll understand
if I tell him.
Hey, nobody is tighter
with Sammy than me.
I'm the one who should
tell him he stinks.
So...
what'd you think
of my commentary tonight?
I thought you were wonderful.
It just felt great up there.
I tell you, ever since I sold
the bar I've been floundering.
It's like I'm standing
in quicksand.
You know, I've been
trying to get my feet
planted on the ground
and all of a sudden,
it's all come together.
It's like everything
I've ever done in my life
has been leading up
to this moment.
My knowledge of sports, my good
looks, my ability to rhyme.
You know, I tell you, I think
I found my niche in life.
They liked you down
at the station?
Are you kidding, liked me?
Man, they were speechless.
Oh, hey, yeah, Rebecca.
Listen, uh, did you
catch my act tonight?
Yes, I did.
So what'd you think?
Now you can be honest with me.
Honest?
Mm-hmm.
Let's see...
as news rappers go,
I thought you were fine.
But maybe rapping has just
been kind of done to death.
Oh, no, you think so?
I mean, I'd hate to think
I looked stupid out there.
No, no, not at all.
No, no, no,
it's just that
it's not unique
anymore, Sam.
I mean, uh, you know,
it'd be one thing if you
were the first guy to rap,
but they're rapping on
stations all over town.
You don't want to be
the last on a long
train of rappers.
Yeah, Norm is right
there, Sammy.
I mean, you got to do
something different.
Do something revolutionary,
something that no sportscaster
does anymore.
You know, like, uh...
read the sports.
You know, I have been
working on something,
but I was afraid
it was too much.
But if you guys think
that rapping's old hat...
you know, I just may
give it a shot.
I'm going to work on it right
now, as a matter of fact.
Suppose we ought
to stop him?
Oh, no, wait a minute.
How do we know it's going
to be another bad idea?
I mean, it couldn't be as bad
as tonight, could it?
( high-pitched voice ):
Hi, everybody.
( normal voice ):
Hi, Little Sam.
Are you ready for tonight's...
Oh, my God.
LITTLE SAM:
I sure am.
I think the Red Sox
are making a big mistake
trading away young players
for veterans
who can only help them
for a season or two.
Don't you agree,
Little Sam?
No, I think
you're full of hooey.
If I paid five bucks
to get in the ballpark,
I want to see them win now.
What do you know?
Your head's wooden.
Well, your lips
are moving.
If either of them mentions
the bar, I'm suing.
Stop it.
Well, that's two guys' opinions.
Joanne?
Oh, boy.
It seemed like such
a good idea at the time.
Boy, I wanted that job so bad.
I wanted to make it work.
I guess I just went
over the edge, huh?
Hey, make him talk, Sam.
Make him say my name.
Maybe later, Woody.
My lips are kind of tired
right now.
I know things seem
a little bleak right now,
but, um, I think
there's two important things
to look at here.
One:
at least you took a chance.
And two--
and this is the important one--
you know when to quit.
Yeah, boy, that's true.
You know,
I came real close to losing
my dignity tonight.
I've been thinking about it,
you know, I'm going to hang up
the old Channel 13 blazer.
You know, if that phone
were to ring right now
and they were to beg me
to come back, I wouldn't do it.
I think it's just time
that I grew up
and accepted what I am:
a bartender.
And a damned good one
at that, too.
( phone rings )
Cheers.
It's the station.
Well, you're kidding me.
The switchboard's
lighting up?
Well, look, hey.
Listen, I'm sorry,
I don't care if they loved me.
I happen to have
a job already...
and I have friends...
and I have my dignity.
Yeah.
Well, thanks anyway.
Yeah, bye-bye.
Very admirable,
Mr. Malone.
Well, I still have
a little nobility left.
All right.
Okay, Sam.
Oh, I have to cancel
that relief bartender.
Oh, maybe
you ought to, uh...
Hello?