Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
(alarm chirps)
(alarm blaring)
This never gets old.
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Doctor Crane, can you help me
with somethin'?
Of course, Woody.
You know, uh,
yesterday was mine
and Kelly's third anniversary
of goin' steady.
And, uh,
I gave her
a dinky keychain,
so she goes and gives me
this $300 camera.
So, my problem is...
Say no more about
it, Woody.
If I were you, I wouldn't
let Kelly's fine present
cause you any guilt.
I mean, after
all, she comes
from a very
privileged background
while you're a, an
unsophisticated
working man
who has nary two dimes
to rub together.
You know, these kinds
of relationships
rarely make it through
a third year.
Actually, I just
wanted to know
how to work
the automatic flash.
But now I just want
to go someplace and cry.
Frasier,
I've got to run.
I'm having my photograph taken
for a new I.D. badge
at the lab.
Are you gonna get your
hair done for that?
Why on earth should I?
Well, at least get the tension
on that bun checked.
I mean, if that baby goes,
we're all dead.
That hardly seems just
coming from a woman
whose hair has never
seen a greasy pot
it couldn't
scrub clean.
Watch it, babe!
Ooh, I'm
outta here.
Now, now, girls, girls,
there's no reason
to insult each other.
No matter how on the nose
either of you might be.
Frasier,
do you think I should
change my hair?
You're asking me?
Just a second, dear.
Uh-oh, I'm in
big trouble.
If I tell her
to change,
she'll assume that
I'm disappointed
with the way she looks.
On the other hand,
if I say it's fine as it is,
she'll think I don't care.
You know, Lilith,
you should do with
those raven tresses
whatever pleases you.
Because, my angel,
if you're happy, I'm happy.
You're chicken.
But happy.
For heaven sake,
take a stand!
Just a second, dear.
She's goin' to the
mat on this one.
Why don't you just tell her
to get her hair changed?
Perhaps you're right.
You know, she
probably wants
to change herself in
some way, but, uh,
doesn't have the confidence
to just let go.
Lilith, I think you
should restyle.
You know, to tell the truth,
there is a,
a part of me that would,
would like to see a-a little
change in your appearance.
Why?
Because you've secretly hated
the way I've looked
all these years and haven't
had the guts to tell me?
Just a second, dear.
Taxi!
That's exactly why I
never got married.
Oh, is that why,
Cliff?
Yeah, that's why.
Mornin', everybody.
EVERYONE:
Norm!
Hey, what's goin' on,
Normie?
It's my birthday, Sammy.
Give me a beer, stick
a candle in it.
And I'll blow out
my liver.
Hey, it's his birthday.
Did ya hear that?
EVERYONE:
Happy birthday, Norm!
I just want the day
to come and go
just like any other day.
Uh-huh.
I think
you can pull that off.
Well, Norm, you know,
despite the fact
that you don't want to make
a big fuss out of it,
we all, uh, chipped in
and got ya somethin'.
Now what is it
that, uh,
you want more than anything else
in the world?
Another beer.
CLIFF:
Close your eyes there,
Mr. Peterson.
Yay!
Oh, guys!
What could it be?
Let me see.
(gasps)
It's a beer!
Thank you, guys.
Thank you.
Hey, I got you
a very,
very special gift,
my friend.
More special
than a free beer?
Yeah. Come here.
Is it a keg and a snorkel?
(laughs)
Come, stand right here.
Now I know what a big fan
of the Celtics you are, so...
(knocking on door)
here's your present.
(Sam chuckles)
Kevin McHale?
Sammy, I love the guy,
but, uh, I know where
to draw the line, you know?
No, no, no, no,
no, okay,
he's just deliverin' it.
Come on, Kevin.
Norm, Sammy tells me
what a big fan you
are of the team,
so on behalf of myself
and the Celtics,
I'd like you to have
this team jacket.
Oh,
all ri...
Thanks, man.
Happy birthday!
All right!
Have a happy...
Look at this.
Ah, hey.
Hey. Smile.
WOODY:
Hey, whoa, whoa,
smile.
(camera shutter clicks)
Sam, how do you work
the flash on this?
I got my hands full
here, Woody.
Oh!
(glass shattering)
All right!
What a birthday, huh?
A free beer,
a Celtics jacket from
Kevin McHale,
and Sammy wipi''
out my bar tab.
Hey,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
I didn't say anything
about wipin' out a bar tab.
Well, happy
birthday to me.
Hey, Sammy?
Yeah.
I came through with that jacket
for Norm.
Where's that autographed
Red Sox baseball you got for me?
Oh, right, right.
I'll be, I'll be right back.
All right.
Is it almost ready?
Yeah.
How many G's
in Boggs?
Two.
Is that all?
Doesn't look
right.
Shh.
Hey.
All right.
Thank you, Sam.
Let me use
the phone,
all right?
Yeah, anytime. Anytime.
Normie?
Yeah.
Even though I, uh, chipped in
for the beer with the guys,
Mm-hmm.
I also got you a little
special gift.
Yeah? What's that?
Well, uh, I did some
research on the, uh,
historical significance
of birthdays.
Uncovered a lot
of interesting facts
and, uh...
I'm not gonna share 'em
with ya.
Oh, Cliff, man.
Happy birthday,
big guy.
Say, Kevin,
you know, uh, my birthday's
comin' up pretty soon.
Maybe you could come back
and deliver somethin' for me.
Oh, would you like
a jacket, too?
Yeah, right.
A jacket!
Well, guys, I feel like I own
a little bit of Celtic history.
Some of my fondest
memories as a boy are going
down to the Garden.
Yeah.
Being in the same building
as all my heroes.
Sittin' there next to my dad
and as he ordered beer
after beer from the vendor,
sayin' to myself,
"Someday, someday."
That's great.
Ah, the Garden.
Yes, perhaps
the most famous
playing surface
in all of sports.
Yep.
Well, you know,
it's a little known
fact that that, uh,
parquet floor
is comprised
of 240 individual
squares held down
by 2,860 bolts.
Uh,
you're wrong there.
It's 2,880 bolts.
And I got that from a member
of the bull gang,
the crew that works
the floor.
Well, I'm very sorry,
Norm,
but my source is
unimpeachable.
Yeah? Who's that?
My ma.
Why don't we settle this
right now?
I'll call the Garden
and find out, huh?
Oh, yeah, yeah. Who're
we supposed to talk to,
the guy in charge
of bolts?
We've got McHale here.
Why don't we just ask him.
Kevin?
Yeah.
Uh, tell this guy
how many bolts there are
on the floor of the Garden,
please.
Well, I-I've
never noticed
any bolts
in that floor.
You know, come
to think of it,
Bird, Parish,
Auerbach,
nobody knows how many bolts
are in that floor, huh?
There's a game
for ya.
Yeah.
Trivia...
Hey, stop,
stop, stop!
Stop it! Just turn around
and run the other way!
What're you
talking about?
Look, Kevin,
I'm warning you
because I love you.
Don't get caught up
in one of those
conversations.
You'll end up
like those guys.
They never leave
those stools.
It's a disease, and they're
tryin' to hook you.
I knew this guy once
who was a respected
psychiatrist.
It's too late
for him,
but you can still
save yourself.
Go on.
Okay, yeah, yeah,
you're... I got a game
in an hour.
Like to talk about those bolts,
you guys, but I gotta run.
(overlapping chatter)
Thank God.
Hey, I'll tell you
what, though.
If you multiply
the number of bolts
by number of squares
in that thing,
you'd be able to find out
how many bolts there were.
Oh Lord, take him now.
ANNOUNCER (on TV):
One minute to go in the game.
Here we go!
The Celtics still have a chance
to tie it up.
Brings the ball up...
Come on, guys.
Frasier...
...I've just come
from the beauty salon.
I asked them
to do something
a little different
with my hair.
Then you actually went
through with it?
My darling, I'm, I'm
all anticipation.
I've never seen
you out,
but with your by-now
trademark chignon.
Thus the change.
What do you think,
Frasier?
It's hard to say.
(laughs)
You're laughing!
(laughing):
I'm sorry, dear.
You're taking it
all the wrong way.
You see, it was just
the initial reaction
of seeing you
different and...
you know, now that I look
at it again, it's...
(laughing)
Stop laughing.
You're hurting my feelings.
I'm sorry.
Your what?
No, no, darling,
please, please.
Look, give me
another chance.
Please.
Another chance.
Please!
(laughs)
Ten seconds to go, the Celtics
down by two on their home court.
McHale's got the ball.
He goes up.
Yeah!
He's in the clear.
Oh no! McHale blows the layup!
(game buzzer)
And that's the game.
The Celtics lose.
Cleveland 102, Boston 100.
I've never seen
Kevin play
that poorly before
in my life.
What was he doin''
out there?
I don't know. I mean,
he wasn't even looking'
at the other players.
He was just staring'
at the floor
and moving his lips.
I think he was countin''
the bolts on the floor.
No, come on.
He wouldn't do that
in the middle of a game.
Hey, look, they're gonna
interview Kevin.
Here's Glen.
This is Glen Ordway
on the floor of the Garden.
We're gonna see
if we can catch Kevin McHale,
ask him a couple of questions
and find out exactly
what went wrong
out on the floor here tonight.
Uh, here he comes right now.
Uh, Kevin, can I ask you
a couple of questions?
Hundred and nine,
hundred and ten,
hundred and eleven,
hundred and twelve...
Now look what you've done!
You have ruined him!
You've ruined Kevin McHale!
You took
the scoring
machine, one of Boston's
greatest living sports legends
and turned him
into...
one of you!
GUYS (chanting):
Kevin, Kevin, Kevin, Kevin...
(phone rings)
Cheers.
Yeah, Sammy, this is Kevin.
Hey, Kevin!
Hey, Kevin McHale.
OTHERS:
Hey, Kevin!
Hey, Sammy, boy,
I'm having a rough night.
Yeah, ooh, boy,
we caught the game.
Yeah, you really stunk it up
out there, huh?
Hey, I saw you pitch.
You're not entitled
to an opinion.
You know what it is,
though...
it's those bolts.
I tell you, I can't get them
out of my mind.
You know, I've called the people
all over town,
and no two people seem to have
the same answer.
Sammy, it's driving me crazy.
Kevin, you, you got to take it
easy with this.
I mean, bar trivia can
eat you up, pal.
Kevin, it's not too late!
Get help!
Don't...
Honey, who's that?
Just the guys
down at Cheers.
(sighs)
My motive, of course,
was to please Frasier.
But this evening, after dinner,
he laughed so hard,
cappuccino ran out of his nose.
Rebecca, you're a friend.
Does this permanent make my hair
look utterly ridiculous?
No, not at all.
I think it's
a delightful change.
So do I.
Damn that Frasier!
For a moment, he had me
believing I was a laughingstock.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
What're friends for?
How can you just
stand there,
staring at that hairdo
and not bust a gut laughing?
(voice straining):
No problem.
Hi, everybody!
Hey, Kevin!
FRASIER:
How come you're
not in bed, man?
Oh, I couldn't sleep.
You got a big game tomorrow.
I don't care.
All I care about are
those bolts.
So I ran out and got a set
of blueprints to the Garden.
Find out how many bolts there
are in that floor right now.
Wait a minute. Where'd you get
blueprints this time of night?
Ah, I know somebody
down at City Hall.
Kind of a sports legend
in this town, huh?
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, all right.
Oh, hey, gee, there,
I'm sorry, Kevin,
but these are
the blueprints
for the new Garden
that they're building.
No...
Yeah, yeah, you see,
there should be
a mailbox right there.
No, no.
Oh, give me that phone!
I hope the mayor's still up.
Give me that phone.
No, no, no.
I don't think you should do
that, man. Don't do that.
Sammy, I'm telling you
right now, I got to know.
I got to know.
I'm telling you, nothing,
I mean nothing's
going to stop me.
Kevin.
Good night, guys.
You guys should be
ashamed of yourselves.
You're like vampires.
Big-butted,
do-nothing vampires.
And, and now you're
trying to make Kevin
one of your recruits.
Well, I say
it's got to stop.
I'm not going to let you
screw up his career.
Oh, come on,
lighten up, will you?
It's just Kevin's getting
a little carried away
with bolts, that's all.
Yeah, sure, Sammy.
Today it's how many bolts
are in the floor.
Tomorrow they'll
have him onto
"If the Brady Bunch
crashes in the Andes,
who's going to eat
who first?"
Well, they'd probably eat
the maid 'cause she ain't kin.
Well, you know,
but if they're smart there,
they'll ask her first how
she should best prepare herself.
Stop it!
All right,
so what do we do?
Well, we'll go down
to the Garden
and just count the bolts
in the floor,
so we can settle this thing
and get Kevin back on his game.
All right?
Well, how are we going
to get in there, Sam?
Don't they lock
the Garden at night?
Oh, hey, Woody, don't
worry about those locks.
We can get past
any one of them,
with my trusty
Swiss Army Knife.
(chuckles):
Yeah, I got the big one
with the, uh,
tweezer-toothpick combo.
Yeah.
That's a beauty,
Mr. Clavin.
Yeah, thanks, Woody.
Yeah, every soldier in the Swiss
Army owns one of these.
That's why nobody messes
with Switzerland.
Yeah, I'd rather run buck naked
through the neighborhood
than be without this baby.
Why is that always
the other option?
(lights buzzing)
Whoa, ho-ho!
WOODY:
Are they on?
Uh, yeah!
Look at this, huh?
Boston Garden.
I wake up this morning,
thinking my life has no meaning,
and now I'm standing here.
Yeah, it really, really kind
of clears things up,
doesn't it, Norm?
No, I'm still pretty sure
my life has no meaning,
but I'm standing here.
(laughs)
Every part of this place
is special to me.
Yeah.
It's sacred.
It's holy,
you know, like a cathedral.
Think I'll rip a seat out
and throw it in the back
of my car, huh?
Hey, wait a minute...
What? What?
Forget that.
What?
Hey, Mr. Clavin,
I have a question.
Yeah, fire
away there.
Well, how can they play hockey
in here-- there's no ice?
Oh, the ice is, uh, right
under the floor there, Woody.
It's under the floor right now?
Absolutely!
Why don't you, uh, pick
one of these things
up, have a look-see?
Here, use my
Swiss Army Knife.
Suppose anyone would mind
if we shot a few hoops?
Hey, where'd you get that?
Out of the trunk of my car since
last time I was at the gym.
Let's run the floor.
All right!
Here we go! Here we go!
(chuckling):
When was the last time
you were at the gym?
I don't know.
I used to go to that
one next door to Cheers.
There's no gym
next door to Cheers.
Yeah, there was.
They tore it down.
They put up
that bookstore.
There's no bookstore
there either.
Oh, they tore that down
and they put the bank there.
The bank's been there
as long as I can remember.
Well, there you go.
WOODY:
Wow!
Well, what have
we here?
Looks like plywood.
Oh, great!
Hey, I can use the saw.
(thumping)
Oh, great,
somebody's coming.
Woody, put, put,
put the floor back.
Come on, let's go.
Woody, come on.
Hurry up.
What a day.
First Sammy gets me
Kevin McHale's jacket.
Then I get to sneak
around the Garden.
Even look at the plywood
under the floor.
Now we're getting chased off
by security guards.
(laughs)
I'm sorry, guys.
I never had a more beautiful day
in my life.
Drinking alone?
No. Frasier asked to meet
me to be here today.
He probably wants a few
more boorish laughs
at my hair's expense.
Well, if it's
any consolation to you,
I think that look does
something for you.
Thank you.
I didn't say what.
Lilith?
Uh, please, don't speak.
I've behaved abominably.
You had the courage to try
something different
in order to please me,
and I've repaid you
with mockery,
which is unforgivable.
But I, I hope you can
forgive me because I love you.
And I love your hair.
And no matter how you might
change your outer appearance,
you'll always be
the most beautiful woman
in the world to me.
Oh, Frasier!
Thanks, Rebecca.
Oh, I better keep one.
NORM:
There you go.
Yeah, McHale's playing
a little better tonight, huh?
Yeah, of course he is. As soon
as I told him how many bolts
were in the floor, he just
settled right into his game.
Wait a minute. How could
you tell him that?
We never had a chance
to count them.
Well, I just made up a number,
you know.
I figure he'll never know
the difference.
As long as it improves his game,
you know, what's the harm?
Right.
WOODY:
Sam, I have
a question.
Not now, Woody, I'm, uh,
watching the game here.
No, it's
really important.
What?
Well, say a guy removed
the bolts from a piece of floor
in a very
important building.
Uh-huh.
Like, uh, I don't know,
say, the Boston Garden.
And, and say a guard came,
and he didn't have time to put
the bolts back in the floor.
What would happen?
You didn't put the bolts
back in the floor, Woody?
Oh, I knew
you'd catch that.
I should of just been
honest with you, Sam.
What should I do?
Oh, relax, will you, Woody?
For crying out loud,
they got a crew there to check
on everything before the game.
Yeah, I'm sure they just
found the missing bolts
and replaced them.
I mean, even if they don't,
I mean, what are the odds
of somebody hitting that spot
exactly, huh?
TV ANNOUNCER:
Bird passes to McHale.
McHale is in for it,
stops short.
Oh, he's tripped on something!
He's down!
It looks like a piece
of the floor came up.
That hurt just looking at it!
Oh, no!
I really did it
this time.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't blame yourself, Woody.
It's my fault.
It was my birthday.
I'm the one who got him
all interested in the bolts.
No, no, it's me who dragged
us all out here
in the middle of the
night to go count bolts.
It was my fault.
Oh, never would've happened
if I didn't have
my Swiss Army Knife.
Guys, it was my fault.
I'm the one who took
the bolts out of the floor.
He's right, you know.
That's true. Why are
we being so hard
on ourselves?
Yeah, you heard him
admit that, didn't you?
You guys, you heard it?
Hey, Kevin, how are you feeling?
Not too good, Woody.
I don't know
what happened out there.
I must look like an idiot.
It was my fault.
How could it be your fault?
I'm the clown
that slipped and fell.
You're right.
You were.
You heard him, guys,
let's get out of here.
Listen, we have
a confession
to make, Kevin.
Uh, when we came
over here the other night
to count the bolts,
we kind of got
carried away
and kind of took some of
the bolts out and then...
kind of forgot to
put them back in.
You mean to tell me
this really is your fault?
I'm afraid so.
Boy, that figures.
With you guys,
that really figures.
You know, I'll tell you what,
though,
I guess I can't stay
too mad at you
'cause you finally solved
that bolt question, you know.
We got another
confession to make.
We kind of never got around
to counting the bolts.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
You trying to tell me,
we still don't know how many
bolts there are in that floor?
Yeah, but what is
the difference, man?
You played a great game.
Yeah, but what
about tomorrow's game?
NORM:
...1,216...
1,217...
McHALE:
No, no, hold on.
I already counted that one.
(sighs)
One...
two... three...