Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Oh! Oh!
( gasping )
Sam, I think Carla
has a drink order.
Sweetheart,
are you all right?
Sammy, I think this could be it.
I think the twins are coming.
Oh. Ooh, ooh!
( groans )
What do you know?
The Sixers are
in town tonight.
Isn't it amazing
how Carla's labor pains
always seem to coincide
with Celtic home games?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Wait a minute.
Now, you think
that I would exploit
this beautiful thing
called motherhood
just to go
to some stupid basketball game?
( groaning )
I'm insulted!
Carla, I'm not falling
for it this time.
You can scream till you shatter
every glass in this bar,
but you're not going anywhere.
( groans )
Sweetheart,
you're just going
to have to give birth
right here in the bar.
Come on.
It won't be that bad.
Remember, the last kid
you had here was no big deal.
All you had to do
was a little
snip-snip
and a quick mop-up
and you were right back
on your feet.
( groaning )
Let me call you
a cab, Carla.
It's all right.
I got one waiting.
Thank you.
Hey, uh, there
wouldn't happen
to be another seat
in the delivery room,
would there?
No, no.
There are only seats
for me and Eddie, Sam.
Oh, come on.
Maybe next... child.
( groans )
( piano plays )
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always glad
you came
You want to be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You want to be where everybody
knows your name
You want to go
where people know
People are all the same
You want to go where
everybody knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Announcement! Announcement!
I just got a phone call,
and if things work out,
it might be
my ticket out of here.
( all cheering )
Don't you even want
to know what it's about?
There's more?
Yes. I have been asked
to organize a cocktail party
for Mr. Daniel T. Collier.
Ooh, Daniel T. Collier,
the lemon wafer king?
No, no, that's Donald P. Cooper.
Hey, I love
those lemon wafers.
You ever dip them in cocoa
and try to get them out
without breaking them?
Yeah, yeah.
Do you know you can make
a mock apple pie with those?
Excuse me.
Those are Ritz Crackers.
Stop talking about wafers!
This is Daniel T. Collier,
the chairman of the board,
the chief executive officer
of Lillian.
ALL:
Oh...
Sammy, don't you have,
like, the slightest bit of guilt
selling this bar
to a corporation named Lillian?
Well, we used to be called
Drax Chemical,
Dye and Munitions,
but people had trouble
believing our motto:
"We care about people."
Okay, I'm going
to need the best
of everything:
the best food,
the best liquor.
The best bartenders.
You?
( laughs )
Good one, Sam.
Did I say something
funny here?
Well, actually,
I didn't get it either.
I was just laughing
to be polite.
But in my own defense,
I do get some things
that no one else does.
When there's a shine
on your shoes
There's a melody
in your heart
Shiny shoes, huh?
Shiny shoes, shiny shoes.
Ah, gents, notice anything
different about me today?
Okay, I'll go out on a limb.
New shoes?
( chuckles )
Yes, siree, Normie.
And for a limited time only,
thanks to the US
Postal Service,
you, too, can be saying
to your feet,
"Thanks for your support."
Are we to deduce
from this, Cliff,
that you are now selling
mail-order shoes?
I am not selling
shoes here, Doctor.
I'm selling dreams.
Dreams of a little cobbler
in Missouri who pours his heart
into every sole.
Actually, Cliff,
with a pair of
dark socks
those could look
halfway decent.
How much
are they, Cliff?
$19.99.
Well, what the heck?
For 20 bucks,
I'll give it a shot.
All right,
order me a size 11.
Normie, Normie, Normie,
these are not
your assembly line clodhoppers.
These are precisely
machine-measured.
How do I do it then?
Just trace your tootsies
on a cocktail napkin
over here, fellas, all right?
I'll tell you.
This brings back memories
of my dad when I was a kid.
Did you all always
used to order
your shoes
through the mail?
He was always getting taken
by some huckster.
Sam,
if you were throwing
a party,
would you order Dom Perignon
or Cristal?
Cristal.
Dom Perignon it is, then.
This is getting insulting.
You know, I don't think
that she respects us.
What do you mean "us," Sam?
You're the one who goofed
up that champagne thing.
Woody, come on, man.
We're a team.
Is that the insulting part?
This... the point is,
she doesn't think
that we're worthy
of hanging around
with her society friends.
She thinks
we're nincompoops.
Nincompoops?
Let's go, Sam.
We're going
to talk to her.
What?
Nobody calls Woody Boyd
a nincompoop.
Except my dad.
( knocking )
Miss Howe,
with all due respect,
that nincompoop crack
really hurt.
Woody, I didn't call you
a nincompoop.
All right, then why
you won't let us tend
bar at your party?
Is it because you think
we're incompetent?
You think we're
not smooth enough?
You think we're uncouth?
No, I need you here.
Oh, okay.
Let's go, Sam.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Sam, now, look.
Really, why do you care?
Why on Earth do you want
to work this party?
All right, you know,
by not hiring us,
what you're doing is
you're telling the rest
of the world
that Sam Malone is not fit
for the society of decent folks,
that he's incompetent,
that he's a clod.
What about me, Sam?
You, too, Woody.
I'm going to tell you
something, lady.
We may not have come
out of Harvard.
We may not belong
to a yacht club.
We may not have tended
bar at a polo tournament,
but we know how
to do our job
and we do it with
dignity and class.
You're right.
I'm sorry. The job is yours.
All right!
Whoa, baby!
Whoo!
Whoo! Whoo, baby!
Lovely party, Rebecca.
Why, thank you, Mr. Collier.
Isn't this place
something, Sam?
Ooh, yeah.
I think it's even nicer
than Wheeler's Funeral
Parlor in Hanover.
Of course, that's
not the most fun
place in town.
Well, I'll bet not.
That would be
Bob's Funeral Parlor.
Oh, my God.
Woody, is it me
or is that woman gorgeous?
You look nice, Sam,
but I'm going
to have to go
with the woman.
Do me a favor here,
will ya, buddy?
Hold down the fort here
while I pass that lady
a tray of smoked Sammy.
Great party, huh?
Yes.
I'll have
a Manhattan.
What?
Oh, this.
Well, you think
I'm a bartender, huh?
What do you think you are?
Well, to tell you
the truth,
I used to be a bartender,
but now I'm an
eccentric millionaire.
I just dress like this
to remind myself
of my modest beginnings.
Back behind the bar.
I pay her to say that.
It keeps me humble.
Malone, now!
Ooh, that was
a good one, huh?
I'm going to have
to give her a raise, huh?
Looking good.
Woody, what are you doing?!
That is not a trash can.
That is a work of art.
Oh, my God.
This is just what I need
is for Collier to see this.
He is a collector.
Oh, hey, let's
calm down now.
Nobody's seen anything yet.
Woody, take it in the kitchen
and clean it out.
Sure, Sam.
Sorry, Miss Howe.
Woody, go.
Just go.
I got you. I got you.
I tell you, Sam.
This is the last time
I'm going to throw
one of these fancy parties.
The next time one
of these hotshots wants...
( glass breaking )
Don't worry, Ms. Howe.
It was only a tray of glasses.
Thank God.
Let's not tempt fate, Woody.
I'll clean it myself.
They weren't great glasses,
Sam, and they were dirty.
( glass breaking )
Just a guess here:
uh, the vase?
It was there.
I was holding it.
It was right in my hands,
and now it's gone.
Maybe we can glue it
back together
and no one will ever know.
Forget that.
Oh!
Just calm down now.
Calm down.
It was an accident.
I'm sure Mr. Collier
will understand.
No, he won't.
This isn't the
first time
I've goofed up
at the company.
I started out
as a junior executive
and I'm diligently working
my way down to the mailroom
with a brief stopover
at that Siberia called Cheers.
Shh-shh. Stop it.
Just calm down here.
Calm down.
I know.
I'll just resign now,
move back to San Diego,
join the Navy,
grow old and die.
Oh...
Boy, Sam,
I really feel
sorry for her.
Never thought I'd say it,
but so do I.
Look at this party
she threw together here,
and then that happens.
Poor kid.
You think they'll
make me manager?
Hey, yo, over here.
You know, Woody,
I'm about to do
a decent thing here.
Get out.
Yeah.
I'm going to take
the fall for this.
What the hell?
I'm a great bartender.
I can get a job anywhere I want.
Sam, that's the
second nicest thing
you've ever done.
Well, thank you.
What's the nicest?
When you let me
drive your Corvette.
Right. Right, right.
That's good. That's good.
Excuse me, young man.
What happened to the vase
that was sitting there?
Somebody move it?
Sir, I have a confession.
My name is Woody Boyd,
and by accident,
I broke your vase.
You...
you broke it?!
Do you know how many years
I waited
to add that to my collection?
Do you realize
the significance of that piece?
No, sir.
And I also broke some glasses.
No, Sam,
I can't let you do it.
It wouldn't be right if you...
Uh, Mr. Collier, there's been
a terrible accident.
Yes. This person just told me
how he destroyed
my vase.
But Woody didn't do it.
What she means
is I didn't do it
on purpose.
Yes, I know.
The only thing that can match
my great disappointment
at losing the vase
is the admiration
that I feel for this boy.
Woody, you showed
great courage
and integrity
in stepping up
to face the music here.
Rebecca, would you mind
standing in for Woody
for a little while?
You wouldn't mind,
would you?
I'd like to get
to know him better.
You want a drink?
Well, sure.
Well, just tell
the girl.
Miss Howe, I'll have a...
gin and tonic.
Well, come on.
She'll bring 'em in.
WOODY:
Oh.
Another Manhattan.
Manhattan, huh?
I own a lot of that, you know?
Right, the eccentric millionaire
routine.
You know, I got
to tell you the truth here.
I'm getting kind of bored
serving all these stiffs drinks.
What do you say
you and I go out
and spend some
of my money?
What time does France
close anyway?
I think they're
remodeling.
Oh.
Have any other
suggestions?
Unfortunately, my mansion's
being painted
and my yacht's
in dry dock.
Well, let me see...
Oh, I know it.
I know it.
You know, my chauffeur's
got a little one-bedroom
apartment downtown.
What do you say you
and I go slumming?
Let me guess:
you're not really
rich at all, are you?
Well, now,
define "rich."
I have my health.
I... uh, think I'll just
stick with the drink.
Let me get this straight:
when you thought
that I was a millionaire,
you were ready to go out
with me,
but now that I'm just
a healthy bartender,
you don't want to have
anything to do with me.
I gotta tell you, lady,
that makes you
an incredibly shallow person.
Do you actually think
this sort of approach
is going to work?
Absolutely.
You see, I'm an incredibly
shallow person myself.
Between the two of us,
we couldn't make
a decent wading pool.
What do you say, huh?
Don't I know you from somewhere?
Yeah, well,
you probably
caught me out
at Fenway, huh?
Of course.
I bought a bag
of peanuts from you.
Another round of brandies
for Butch and Sundance.
They're really, uh,
hitting it off, huh?
I should say so.
They're in there
singing school songs.
If you hate Ivy
League fight songs,
wait till you hear one
from bartending school.
You're not taking this
very well, are you?
What, that little
backstabber?
Oh, now cut that out.
Woody took a big risk, you know.
You broke the vase and
he took the blame for it.
It didn't have
to turn out that way.
He just had your best
interest at heart.
I know.
I could just hug him till
his tongue turns black.
You know, I'm not convinced
you're a millionaire,
but I am sold
on the eccentric part.
Well, that's a start.
And since
I'm not getting
any interesting
nibbles tonight anyway,
I'm reconsidering
your offer.
Nibbles are my specialty.
Great.
Well, what time will
you be getting off?
( laughing )
Oh, listen, I've got
to show you a trick shot.
Now you watch this.
Got you again, Pinky!
( laughing )
You can't do that!
Oh, uh...
You seem to have something
in your eye, Woodhead.
I'll get it for you.
Oh, Pinky, stop!
It's noogie time!
Oh, no! No! No!
No, Woody!
No! No more!
( stifled chuckling )
I see our serving
wench is here.
I mean, hello,
Miss Howe.
( chuckling ):
Oh, Woody.
I tell you, you have
no idea how hard it is
to find young fellas
with your stuff
in this day and age.
You ought to see
the buttoned-down brats
my granddaughter
drags home from college.
She really
deserves someone
more solid, someone real.
Someone with
a strong back
and a thick neck,
you know?
Someone like you, Woody.
Thank you, sir. I couldn't.
Yeah, I could.
She's out in Vail right
now on a skiing holiday.
I'm going up
there tomorrow.
Woody, why don't
you join me?
You mean that, Pinky?
You bet I do.
Well, I don't know if Miss Howe
would be too happy...
Oh, she'll be thrilled.
To my toes.
See?
So, great, I'll
go tell Jamison
to arrange it
right now.
Ah!
Woody, where do you
get these things?!
Go figure, Miss Howe.
I mean, you break the vase,
and I end up being
the big boss' buddy.
Isn't life funny?
Do you mean funny "ha-ha"
or funny "a living nightmare"?
Is something wrong, Miss Howe?
Yes, something is wrong.
I am the one who should
be playing pool.
I'm the one who should
be smoking cigars
and drinking brandy.
I'm the one who should
be going out with
his granddaughter.
You know what I mean.
Well, I'm sorry, Miss Howe.
I was only trying to help.
Okay, Woody, we're all set.
I'll stop by the bar tomorrow
afternoon and pick you up.
Pinky, I have a confession.
I didn't break your vase.
Miss Howe did.
Whew, glad I got that
off my chest.
You broke my vase?
Well, actually, yes.
That's the most cowardly thing
I have ever heard.
You'd let this fine young man
take the blame
for your clumsiness?
I don't know,
Miss Howe.
I'm going to have
to seriously reconsider
your future with
our organization.
Uh, Pinky, wait a minute here.
Uh, Miss Howe
is a very nice lady.
Klutzy, sure, but...
she has a heart of gold.
Well... well, all right.
Woody, if you'll vouch
for her, I'll give her
another chance,
I guess.
Thanks, Pinky.
Hey, by the way,
your barn door's open.
( laughing )
Woody!
Hey, everybody.
Look what the shoe fairy
left under my pillow.
Okay, Fox and Hounds,
that's you, Pete.
Uh, Hugh,
you had the Executives.
Uh, Norm, you had
the Old Smoothies,
didn't you?
Uh, let's see--
Frasier.
Would you give
those to Frasier?
All right,
who had the, uh, Playboy?
Who else?
Hold it. Hold it.
Wait a minute.
You bought shoes from
Boston's fashion king,
Oh Leg the Weenie?
Yeah.
I can't leave you guys
alone for a minute.
Hey, Cliff,
I got to hand it to you.
These are really comfortable.
Eh, you bet ya.
What style are these?
The Star Fighter.
Oh.
Yes.
I was sorely tempted
to get the Coup de Villes,
but, uh, I do love
tassels, so...
( squeaking )
Cliffie, mine squeak.
Uh, after a few weeks
of constant wear,
it'll be all right.
( squeaking )
Make it stop.
Normie, what's the big deal?
I mean, squeaky shoes are only
a problem if you're a mugger.
( squeaking )
Cliff, mine are
a little squeaky, too.
( both squeaking )
Mine are squeaking,
too, Cliff.
In E Minor.
( all squeaking )
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, stop!
Freeze, everybody.
( squeaking stops )
Back on your barstools
right now. Go on.
( squeaking )
SAM:
Hurry up.
Thank you.
Miss Howe.
May I see you for a moment?
Yes, sir.
He's changed
his mind.
I'm doomed.
Next stop: hell.
Compliment his tie.
Last night at the party someone
broke an irreplaceable vase.
That's a very nice tie.
Are you listening to me?
We found the remains
in the trash.
Now, is it any
of your people?
You mean you don't
know who broke it?
Unfortunately, I had
a little too much to drink.
The whole evening's
rather foggy.
And you mean you don't
remember anything,
and you have no idea
who did it?
No, but when I find out,
they're going to wish
they never crossed my path.
'Cause I'll find
a way to make
their life
a living hell.
REBECCA:
I don't blame you.
And you know, when you
find out who did it,
give me a call, because
I'd like to give them
a piece of my mind.
Guess who, Pinky?!
SAM:
Woody! Woody!
What in God's name
do you think you're doing?
Oh, I'll show you
what I'm doing. Ah!
Noogie!
Who is this madman?
This is Woody Boyd.
Woody,
last night, a very
valuable vase
was broken
at Mr. Collier's.
But he doesn't remember
who did it.
Of course he knows
who did it. It was...
Fire! Fire!
( shoes squeaking )
What fire?
Now wait. Hold it!
Now hold it.
There is no fire.
She didn't say "fire."
Uh, she said "flyer."
Yes, yes, I thought I saw
Amelia Earhart up there.
NORM:
Great, uh,
nice save, Rebecca.
( shoes squeaking )
What in God's name
is going on here?
Well, it's the, uh...
Squeaky Shoe Club.
Look, I intend to get
to the bottom of this.
Now Miss Howe, you were in
charge of that party last night.
Do you or do you not know
who broke my vase?
Of course she does.
I certainly do.
It's time the truth
came out.
It was...
Me.
No, Sam.
Yes, Rebecca.
I want to do this.
You, huh?
Sir...
you have grit.
COLLIER:
You don't ski by any chance,
do you?
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3dfxa
Help other users to choose the best subtitles