Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
You missing something, Woody?
Yeah, well, I had a $20 bill
in my pocket and now it's gone.
Well, say good-bye
to that Andy Jackson.
Oh, see you later, Andy.
CLIFF: Boy, oh, boy.
Talk about your lucky days, huh?
Just found 20 smackers
back there in the pool room.
Yeah, and to celebrate my good fortune,
I'm gonna buy a round of
drinks for all my, uh, friends.
What are you gonna do
with the other 19 bucks?
Woody, that could be your $20 bill.
The one you lost.
Hey, yeah, you know, I was
in the pool room earlier.
Wait a second.
Now let's be fair about this.
Uh, give me the serial number.
Oh, come on, man.
Nobody knows serial numbers.
L-2-1-8-8-6-1-1-9-B
That's amazing.
How'd you do that?
Oh, I memorize the serial
numbers on all my currency.
Why?
For just such an occasion.
Tell you, though, I pray
everyday I don't get rich.
(piano plays)
♪ Making your way in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like to get away♪ ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always glad you came ♪
♪ You want to be where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You want to go where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Oh, groom.
Hmm?
Sweetheart, we're
going to have to decide
where we're going for our honeymoon.
Where do you want to go?
Boy, I don't know.
Where, where, where do you want to go?
I told you where I
want to go-- Tibet.
Well, it's our honeymoon.
Of course we're going to bed.
No, you whammo.
Tibet the country.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Sam, imagine getting up in the morning
and looking out on
the roof of the world.
Look where we'd stay. Isn't it quaint?
Looks like where the dogs sleep. It is.
The dogs sleep with us.
You wouldn't want to
freeze to death, would you?
Diane,
I didn't sleep with
dogs when I was single.
I'm not about to start now.
For goodness sake,
don't you want to taste
the exciting and fascinating
things that life has to offer?
No.
I'd rather marry you.
Afternoon, everybody.
ALL: Norm!
Hey, Mr. Peterson, what
do you say to a cold one?
"See ya later, Vera, I'll be at Cheers."
You're looking unusually chipper today.
Yeah, I'm feeling kind of chipper, Fras.
Is there any particular reason,
other than the fact that
we live in a democracy
and sushi bars appear
to be on the decline?
Well, I was gonna
tell Vera first, but
why break tradition?
I just landed a great new job
at Masters and Holly and Dixon.
Oh, wonderful!
It's one of the top
C.P.A. firms in Boston.
Yes, I hear that's
quite a successful firm.
You know, over half of their executives
require therapy on a regular basis.
So, uh, here's my card.
Oh, great. Just in case.
Thank you.
It's a very impressive place.
Uh, they occupy the entire 25th floor
of the Boston Towers.
And they hired you?
It must have been the altitude.
No, no, no, no,
seriously, Norm, I'm sorry.
You know, I hope this
works out to be, you know,
sort of a long-term
arrangement for you.
Long enough anyway for them to see you
wear your other suit.
NORM: Very funny. Very funny, you guys.
But I'll have you know they
gave me the key to the executive
washroom this morning.
Did it come with a bucket and mop?
Laugh all you want, okay,
but I think this is
finally the job for me.
I've got a secretary.
I have an expense account,
a very ritzy office
all to myself, so...
Good for you, Norman.
How about a round of applause
for our new executive?
(middling applause)
Well, I started late.
I didn't want to be impolite.
I'm really excited for
you, Norman. Thanks.
I can tell by the way you're talking
that this is the job that's
going to fire your enthusiasm.
When do you start?
About, uh, three hours ago.
What are you doing here?
I didn't want to appear
over-anxious, you know.
Yeah, no danger there, huh, Buddy?
No, no, I'm on my lunch hour.
DIANE: Oh.
But, you know, I could
be late if I wanted to.
I mean, I got free rein over there.
I happen to be my own boss.
So that's how you got the job.
Thanks for the send-off, guys.
Well, I hope you're
all proud of yourselves.
SAM: Why?
What'd we do?
Well, I think we could have been
a bit more thunderous in our applause.
(clears throat)
Uh, except for Woody.
Sam, didn't you see the
hurt in Norman's eyes?
He was seeking our support and approval.
It's his first day on the job
and all we did was give him jibes.
Don't worry about it, sweetheart.
He's had hundreds of
first days on the job.
You know, Diane's right.
It's obvious how much we mean to him.
I think we may have let him down.
Oh... Gee, I hope not.
Yeah, me, too.
Oh, too late to do
anything about that now.
Refill, huh, Sam?
Hey, it's not too late.
We could march en masse
down to Norman's office and show
him that we're in his corner.
Oh, sure.
Perhaps buy the new hotshot
a little office warming gift.
Maybe a potted plant.
Good!
Okay, hurry up.
Let's get going here.
Wonderful, Carla.
That's the kind of enthusiasm
that's going to make Norman feel better.
The hell with that yutz.
I wanna go downtown and see
some Yuppie buns in tight Italian suits.
Well, then it's settled.
We'll go.
Wish I could join you,
but I've got an appointment at 1:00.
Oh, what the hell?
Mrs. Segal's rather
a compulsive cleaner.
If I'm a little late, maybe
she'll tidy up the office.
Give my best to Norm.
Well, aren't you coming?
Oh, I gotta take care of the bar here.
Oh, Sam, we've got to show Norman
our impressive phalanx.
Oh, that's all right, honey.
He saw mine at the gym.
CLIFF: And then there
was this 1938 accident
where the elevator plunged 86 floors.
Get me out of this thing!
Oh, my.
What an exquisite place
to come to work everyday.
Have you ever seen such
sumptuous surroundings?
Well, you obviously
haven't been to the, uh,
new downtown postal annex, Diane.
So, uh, where's Woody?
I hope he's not lost.
Gee, what are the odds?
2511. Here we are.
(gasps)
Damn. Got another one
of those carpet shocks.
Well, Carla, if you'd walk like a lady,
that wouldn't happen.
If I walked like a lady,
nothing would happen.
Sorry I'm late.
Ah, Woody, uh,
couldn't you find a bigger one?
No.
You know,
at the risk of sounding
self-congratulatory,
I think we're fabulous.
Just think
how Norman will appreciate this.
You know, I remember the first day
I worked at The Third Eye Bookstore.
Ramu was explaining to me
the difference between...
I think it was between
psychic and occult.
Ouch!
Think we could get
this carpet for the bar?
All right. Everyone ready?
ALL: Surprise!
Don't you guys ever think
about maybe calling first?
Yeah, well, we couldn't
find a phone booth.
Until now.
Say, did anybody ever see Das Boot?
What're you guys doing here?
Well, we wanted to come down
and celebrate your
first day on the new job.
WOODY: Yeah, we brought you a gift.
Uh, let me find the
perfect spot for this.
There.
Don't forget to water it.
Thanks, I'll write myself a note, Woody.
So, guys, I, uh...
guess I probably exaggerated
a little bit about the office.
(chuckling )
But, uh, you know, it's just 'cause
you were razzing me so much,
and it's actually quite
a big step to have an office at all.
I mean, many people in this
firm have to share an office.
(knocking)
Oh, just a sec. Sorry.
Yeah?
Just, uh, set it right
here, that's fine.
Let me guess.
Peterson.
Right.
I'm Thompkins.
Looks like we're office partners.
So...
if you're lookin' for a
secretary, I'm available.
But I want you to know
I do not take shorthand,
I don't type and I don't make coffee.
Well, what do you do?
Hire me and find out.
Carla, I don't think he caught that.
Next time try to be more obvious.
Okay, let's let Norman get back to work.
Thanks.
Oh, Norman, keep up the spirits, huh?
Remember-- no small
offices, only small people.
That's right, right.
Okay... oh, my God, look at the time.
If I don't get back right now,
Mrs. Segal will be shampooing the rug.
Well, okay.
Thanks, thanks a lot for the plant.
Wait, wait, my supervisor.
Everybody hide.
Peterson.
Hi, sir.
What are all these people doing in here?
Well, they're new clients, sir, and, uh,
we were just holding a little impromptu
seminar on the tax laws, and, uh...
So in conclusion, folks,
I'd like you to, uh,
file early and, um... file out.
Right, fine.
Thank you, Mr. Peterson.
Thank you. New clients, sir, so...
You're, uh, you're
Thompkins, aren't you?
Yes, sir.
Yes, well, welcome aboard.
Pay attention.
You can learn a lot from this man.
Thank you, sir. That's
very kind of you to say.
No, I was talking to you.
By the way, sir, I understand
you're a big Red Sox fan.
Yeah.
You know, my father has season tickets,
uh, right behind the dugout. No kidding?
Yeah, you know, I'm, I'm usually so busy
with work here, I, I
rarely get to use them.
Thompkins, let's have lunch.
THOMPKINS: Thank you.
Oh, that's a, wait.
That's a, uh, lovely tie
you've got there, sir.
What, this ugly thing?
Yeah.
Oh, my wife bought it.
Yeah, how is the missus?
We're divorcing.
Well, I hope you stick it to her, sir.
I just wanted to make sure you're okay.
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm great.
Top of the world, ma!
Hey, the first day at a
new job is always traumatic.
Look at me.
I'm pushing 40, practically
starting over again.
Oh, Norman, that's not true.
Yes, it is.
Yeah?
Yeah, I'm delivering
supplies to the supply room.
This isn't the supply room. Sorry.
Well, it's 2511, right?
Right.
Then it's the supply room.
Well, it may have been
the supply room once, okay,
but now it's my office.
What does it say on this invoice?
2511.
Thank you.
See what I mean, Diane?
I just wasn't meant to be a success.
Norman, may I speak to you for a moment?
You make me sick.
You're a quitter, Norman.
No, you're worse than that.
You're a non-starter.
You don't even try.
You sit around the bar all day.
You sit around your house all day.
You sit around here all day.
You sit around life all day.
How are you gonna feel some day
at the end of your
life when you're lying,
no, make that sitting, on your deathbed
and you realize
that the only thing you've
done in your life is sit around
and watch people do things,
make things out of their lives.
Well, maybe you're right, Norman.
Maybe you're not meant for success.
Maybe you're meant for
exactly what you are.
Nothing.
Diane, you have no
right to say that to me.
Norman, I said those things
to you because I care.
You must care an awful lot about me.
Well, I do.
All of your friends care
about you an awful lot.
And we're tired of seeing
you give up so easily.
Maybe I won't give up
so easily this time.
Maybe those harsh, stinging,
offensive words of yours,
words that I'll take to
my grave, by the way...
maybe they finally struck
a cord with me, Diane.
Oh, Norman, do you mean it?
Oh, yes, I do, Diane.
You know, every place I've worked,
my name has been synonymous with patsy.
Well, I think it's high time
my name stood for ruthless.
Now people may not like the new me,
but they're gonna respect the new me.
Diane, I want you to mark
this date on your calendar,
for today is the day
the new me is born.
Happy birthday.
Sign here. Uh-uh.
I'm gonna tell the boss.
No, no, Norman, Norman, Norman...
Thank you, Mr. Springsteen.
Well, it's a start.
Yeah.
You know, I was thinking
while you were gone,
it's not really fair to have you
make all the honeymoon plans,
so I went ahead and I did them myself.
All you have to do
is pack your bags and
set your dial for fun.
Oh, God, it's Niagara Falls, isn't it?
No, it's not Niagara Falls.
That place is a tourist trap.
You ready for this?
Disneyworld.
You want to go to
Disneyworld for our honeymoon?
Oh, yeah.
But, Sam, I always thought
that would be someplace
we'd go when we have kids.
Well, hey, no,
this is not just for kids.
This, this is for
"children of all ages."
I mean, can you say the
same thing about Tibet?
Well, how can you compare
Disneyworld and Tibet...
where we might possibly
unravel the mysteries of life?
Well, there, there are lots of mysteries
you can unravel at Disneyworld.
For example?
Um, all right, all right,
uh, why is it that, uh, Donald Duck
wears a top and no
bottom, whereas Mickey
wears a bottom and no top?
Oh, Sammy, it-it's
because, you know, uh,
a duck's private's are
hidden by their feathers
and mouse's is, uh,
well, need I say more?
While you're at it, I mean, why is it
we've never seen Donald fly?
I mean, I've seen that
damn duck do The Carioca.
Yeah, and if Mickey's dating Minnie,
how come he has such a high voice?
Oh, now, whoa, wait, are you trying
to tell me that Mickey...
All right, all right, all
right, we'll go! We'll go!
Evening, everybody.
ALL: Norm!
DIANE: Norman.
SAM: Well, look at you.
You look like the cat
that swallowed the canary.
Give me a beer to wash him down.
Hey, you're, uh, you're in
kinda late there, me bucko.
So how was your first day?
Well, I tell you, I
feel a lot better now
than I did this morning.
Diane, I took your advice
and I spent the afternoon
jotting down some ideas
I think'll save the
company a lot of money.
Oh, Norman!
That's wonderful!
I'm gonna pitch it to
my supervisor tomorrow.
But, I tell you, I'm a little nervous
about putting my butt on the line.
How do you think the line feels?
Norman...
why waste time with the supervisor?
He'll only take credit
for the idea himself.
Why don't you go right to the top?
Present your idea to
the Board of Directors.
I don't know, the
thought of standing there
in a room full of bigwigs
just gives me the cold sweats.
Boy, yeah, I can sympathize
with you there, Normie.
Yeah?
Yeah, I'll never forget
my first oral report.
Sixth grade. Yeah?
Yeah, boy, was I nervous. I tell you.
I went to my father and
he said, "Hey, just relax.
"You'll be fine as long as you can
imagine the other kids
in their underwear."
Which was no big deal for me
because I'd gotten that far with
half the girls in class already.
Even then, huh?
Yeah, anyway, I was, uh, just describing
how they make maple syrup by
draining the sap from trees
when I happened to look
down and notice how nicely
Cindy Van Rippen had filled out.
Ooh. Oh, yes. Ha-ha.
Well, what happened next?
Oh, well, I, uh, I smiled
at her and she smiled at me
and then after my little speech
we stole a few moments in the cloakroom.
No, I mean after they drain
the sap from the trees.
I don't remember, Woody.
Oh, great, Sam.
Get us all revved up and
then leave out the best part.
Norman, nothing takes the
place of personal support.
Therefore, when you're
ready to make your proposal,
I will be at your side.
Tell them that you've hired a personal
secretary to assist
you, at your expense.
Diane, please, I mean,
you've been more than
helpful already, okay?
I don't need anyone to hold my hand.
I just need a little practice.
CLIFF: Well, uh, Normie,
well, why don't you, uh,
try it out on us, huh?
That's a good idea actually.
Oh, yes, it is good. Good, good.
Stand up here so we can all see you.
All right.
Uh, now remember, guys,
uh, this room'll be a pressure cooker,
so just, uh, you know,
stay on top of me, okay?
Really heckle me.
It'll help.
(clears throat)
Good morning, gentlemen.
Uh, what's good about it?
What time can you be there?
...enjoy a 58% growth.
Cash flow.
And we'll achieve it no later...
Thank God.
Thank God you're here.
Norman, don't worry, please.
Everything is going to be perfect.
I hope so.
I'm, uh, having a very tough time
picturing the chairman of
the board in his underpants.
Oh, no.
What? Now what? What?
Oh, Pierre forgot the
chocolate croissant I ordered.
Don't worry about it.
It wasn't that good.
That's a nice suit, Peterson.
They make it in your size?
Pay no attention to him.
Norman is making a proposal
today at the board meeting.
Well, he's wasting his time.
Those stuffed shirts don't
care about anybody's ideas.
Why don't you just have the
courage to wish him well?
Why don't you take a flying leap?
Touche.
Now listen, I don't
like to make predictions,
but you're going to be
in the top echelon of
this company someday.
Your idea is so good
they can't help but applaud it.
I hope you're right, Diane,
but, uh, we have a few minutes now
and I just, I wanna splash
some water on my face.
Fine, fine, I'll go prepare the coffee.
Okay.
It's a special Viennese blend.
They're bound to be impressed.
Oh, great, great.
For my part I think I'd like to get
a second opinion on this pastry,
you know what I mean?
(whistling)
Diane!
It's-It's gone!
What's gone?
Well, my proposal and my career.
The pastry!
Oh, no.
THOMPKINS: If my plan is
implemented immediately,
we'll enjoy a 58%
growth in cash flow.
And we'll achieve it no later than
the third quarter of
the next fiscal year.
Thompkins. The thief.
Get in there and defend yourself.
Damn right I will.
MAN: Thompkins, you idiot!
You've completely ignored the obvious.
Our resulting tax liability
would cost us a fortune.
THOMPKINS: Uh, actually,
sir, it's not my plan.
It's the new guy, Peterson's, you see...
MAN: Don't try blaming
another man for this garbage.
Now stop wasting our
time and get back to work.
Just my luck.
I had to share the office with a moron.
Hey, sorry.
MAN: I'll give him this, though.
The man knows his pastry.
Oh, geez.
Now, Norman. Please.
Now don't let this faze you.
You have to keep pushing.
I know that this idea didn't succeed,
but others will.
No, no, Diane.
A few moments ago I almost made
the biggest mistake of my
professional life, okay?
And it was because I was doing something
that just wasn't me.
I am not a go-getter.
I've never been a go-getter.
And what's more, I don't
even want to be a go-getter.
I'm very happy right where I am.
And I'm tired of all
these people saying,
"Peterson, you've gotta push.
"You gotta get ahead.
You gotta make that goal."
I don't even wanna make the goal, Diane.
I wanna be a bench warmer, okay?
The world needs bench warmers.
I mean, if there were no bench
warmers, what would we have?
We'd have cold benches.
A lot of cold benches.
And the world does not need that, Diane.
In this great pageantry of life,
Norm Peterson may be
a, a motionless lump,
but he's a very damn good one.
Norman, I've never
seen you so impassioned.
That's 'cause I believe in this, Diane.
Look, Norm Peterson
is totally happy being an anonymous cog
in the gigantic machinery of this firm.
Oh, I forgot.
Didn't you wanna say
something at the meeting?
Just how delighted I was
to be part of the firm, sir.
Well, we're glad to have
you aboard, Springsteen.
I'm home.