Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Carla, what
are you doing?
Uh, would you hand me that
bucket of ice water, please?
Sure.
When you tell me
what you're doing.
Well, Clavin's almost done
with his route, see?
So I'm gonna put this bucket up
here on the ledge...
Oh, and then the water
will fall on his head.
How mature.
You know,
that's your problem, Rebecca.
You don't know how
to have any fun.
Sure I do. It's just not
at the expense of other people.
I just go out with my friends
and have a good time.
Now, don't you ever get together
with your friends and-and just
have fun?
Well, I guess I would,
but nobody ever asks me
to do anything.
I'm sorry, Carla.
CARLA:
Yeah.
Sounds like fun.
I don't know.
Say, Carla,
do you want to...
Yeah?
I don't have anything
to do later.
I mean, want to go grab a pizza,
or see a movie or something?
You and me?
Well, if you want to.
Yeah. I think I'd
really like that.
Yeah? All right,
we'll do it.
I mean, who knows?
Maybe it'll be fun.
Let me just
grab my coat.
So, what time should I be there?
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
(zany music
and gunshots on TV)
Okay, at the beginning
of that cartoon,
Casper, the friendly ghost,
had no friends whatsoever.
By the end of the
cartoon, of course,
he's surrounded by friends.
Next cartoon will start,
Casper won't have
any friends again.
What is it we're not seeing
between cartoons?
Could be, uh,
Casper sating his
thirst for human blood.
Right.
Oh, think
about it, Norm.
We are talking
about a ghost here.
Yeah?
You see, very often,
the, uh, walking dead crave
the taste of human flesh.
And things aren't
that much different
in the cartoon
world, I'm sure.
Was it really hot
on your route today, Cliff?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, blacked out a
couple of times. Why?
That was Woody.
He's in a car on the way back
from the airport.
Isn't that something?
Two weeks free in London.
All expenses paid
on Kelly's family.
Boy, he really stepped
into something nice there.
I'll tell you what, though.
He's lucky
I didn't spot her first.
Yeah, he really dodged
a bullet there, Cliff.
Everyone, I have
an announcement to make.
You may not have noticed,
but over the last year,
I've allowed myself
to gradually fall out of shape.
I'm frequently
tired, and I find
I no longer have the energy
for some of my daily activities.
Or some of your
weekly ones.
Which is why Richard here
is going to put me
on a strict exercise
and diet regimen.
Now you may ask, "Why is Frasier
sharing this information
with the general public?"
Because you're the
loneliest man on earth?
He has another
reason.
FRASIER:
Yes.
I want you all
to hold me accountable,
to be my collective conscience,
if you will.
Don't let me give up.
You-You gonna let
that little, scrawny guy
be your personal trainer?
Oh. Get a load
of this, Sam.
Show 'em, Richard.
SAM:
Oh, man!
FRASIER:
Hey, that's...
I could probably do that,
but I'd have to do it in shifts.
I was a professional
athlete.
I can train you like he can,
and I'd do it for free.
Besides, I'll, uh,
keep my chest off
your wife's hand.
You're history, Bluto!
Hey, your loss.
We have an opening
for a lab assistant!
Well, it's grant money.
We have to spend it somehow.
Hi, gang!
Hi-ho, chaps.
Wood!
CARLA:
Whoa!
Well, look at you.
If it isn't Oliver Twit.
Boy, check out the threads
on that dude, huh?
Oh, just a little something
I picked up at Savile Row.
Oh! Savile Row!
(mumbles)
Well,
well, yes.
I guess the trip to England made
a big impression on you, huh?
Ah, it's a fabulous
place, Sam.
Very civilized.
You know, when you drive
on the left-hand side
of the road over there,
they don't scream and honk
at you like they do here.
Got anything in the, uh, bag?
Here we go.
Toilet water
for everyone.
Don't worry, it's
not what you think.
KELLY:
Woody,
we've got to be going.
Right. If James has
to circle the block
more than once,
he has a hissy fit.
Boy, chauffeurs,
huh, Miss Howe?
Oh, yeah. I have that trouble
with mine all the time.
Really? What do you do?
I wake up.
Hey, Woody, can't
you, uh, hang around
and tell us
about your trip?
Love to, can't.
Love to, can't?
WOODY:
Right.
Uh, coming over
on the Concorde,
we met this adorable couple,
David and Arlene,
and we promised to spend
the afternoon with them.
Oh, well, all right.
All right, well, you
can tell us all about it
when you come to work
tonight, all right?
Ooh, about that.
Don't tell me.
Love to, can't?
Bingo. Ta, guys.
What-What the hell's
wrong with him?
Well, it's a common
phenomenon, really.
A young, impressionable lad,
such as Woody,
gets his first taste
of a foreign country,
and he comes back
a little affected.
I mean, give him a few hours,
he'll be fine.
You know, I remember when I came
back from my first trip abroad.
Oh, God, I was pompous
and unbearable!
Condescending
to all my old friends.
Of course, I wouldn't expect
you fellows to understand.
It's a complicated matter.
Keep going, man.
You're doing great.
(panting)
What's the matter,
jump rope too much for you?
Forgive me...
but a jump rope is a delightful
children's toy
used to while away
delightful spring days.
I'm not a delightful child.
I am a miserable,
overweight wretch
who is praying for death.
Got a saying, Frasier--
no pain, no gain.
I also have a saying, Sam.
I can't feel my right arm!
That's all right.
That's natural.
Okay, tell you what.
Why don't you give me one more
abdominal crunch?
No, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
Come on, man,
give me one more,
unless you want
to give me five more.
Okay.
Come on,
you can do it.
Okay.
Come on.
There we go.
And up!
Come on.
(grunts)
Can you see the
baby's head yet?
I am proud of you, man.
A lot of people
would have quit
after that little bout
of vomiting.
Thank you, Sam.
I feel that from
this point on,
I can live a life
of healthful moderation
and physical fitness.
Okay, everybody, Lud is
trying to raise money
for his class trip to
Colonial Williamsburg.
Now who wants to help by
buying some chocolate bars?
I'll take 15 boxes!
Boy, that's great, Doc.
All you got to do is
fill out this order form,
you'll have your candy
in two weeks.
Two weeks?!
I want them now!
Listen, Lud.
Lud, here, go down
to the store for me,
get me a couple
of KitKats,
and I will
personally
drive you
to Colonial
Williamsburg.
Sorry, Dr. Crane.
Two weeks.
Oh, forget it, then,
you rotten kid. No sale.
You should have the
chocolate on you.
What do they teach you in
that school of yours anyway?
Come on, Fras.
Well, it's true.
What the hell am I paying
property taxes for?!
Oh!
Sam!
(voice breaking):
I hurt so much!
(gasping)
Hey, Rebecca,
Lud is trying to raise money
for his class trip.
Now, how many chocolate bars
do you want?
I think you're taking
advantage of us.
Oh, Lud, Miss Howe doesn't
want to buy any candy.
Why don't you go
into your sales pitch?
It's not gonna work, Lud.
You can breathe now.
Okay, fine. I am
just gonna go about
my work as usual.
(whistling)
All right, fine!
Five bars!
(splutters)
Isn't he great,
you know?
He helped knock 500 bucks off
the price of our last car.
Remember that, Lud?
Part of it.
Lud, come on.
Let's go home.
Evening, chums!
I thought you were having drinks
with David and Arlene.
Good people, Sam,
but colossal bores.
So it turns out
I can work.
Well, thanks for, uh,
keeping us in mind here, Woody.
Tell you what, why don't you,
uh, help out
by getting a couple of cases
of scotch from the back?
(chuckles)
Whoa!
Do I look like I'm
dressed to carry scotch?
Oh, well, what are
you dressed for?
Well, certainly not
whatever you're dressed for.
Mr. Peterson, more crisps?
What the hell
are crisps?
Well, they're what
you call potato chips.
Although what I call chips,
you would call French fries.
So, what are you saying,
we have French fries?
Oh, Mr. Peterson,
there's so much you don't see
from your little bar stool.
Stop teasing
me, Woody!
Do we have French
fries, or don't we?
Norm, you don't have
to get upset with Woody.
He's just been on the trip
of a lifetime,
and it rubbed off
a little bit.
That's not such a surprise.
Say it, don't spray it.
This is cashmere, Miss Howe.
You little snot!
I knew you back when
you were just an
ignorant farm boy.
That was about a
week and a half ago!
You're right. That was
about a fortnight, wasn't it?
Oh.
SAM:
Come here.
I want to talk
to you
for a second.
Yeah, what
is it, Sam?
I don't know
how to put this.
Ow!
What's the matter
with you, Sam?
I'll tell you
what's the matter.
You're acting
like a real ass.
I think you
mean "arse."
That's starting
to hurt!
You know, it doesn't
take a fool
to see what's going
on here, but I do.
You're all jealous.
This is a case of
"Poor little us.
"We don't have the money
to do the things
that Woody can do."
Well, as we say back
in merry old England...
tough!
Woody, Woody, Woody,
Woody, come here.
Look...
Yes, Mr. Peterson.
All Sam was
trying to s...
Ow!
That was for the
French fries, okay?
What's the matter
with you guys?
Why are you all
hitting me?
Well, 'cause your hanging
around with rich people
has turned you
into a little monster.
What are you
talking about?
I'm no monster.
I'm still the same
old Woody Gaines.
Wait a minute, I'm
Woody Boyd, right?
Oh, Sam, I have
changed, haven't I?
Yeah, I'm afraid
you have.
Ah, don't... don't hit
me again, all right?
You don't have to beat it
into me, all right?
I know I'm a jerk!
I'm the biggest jerk
that ever lived!
(crying)
Hey, uh, how come
I didn't
get a chance
to smack him?
Hi, Woody.
I just dropped David and Arlene
off at the hotel, and...
Uh-oh, something's wrong.
I can tell.
(crying): I'll tell you
what's wrong, Kelly.
All your money
has changed me.
I don't know who
I am anymore.
I'm pretending
to be English.
I'm pretending to be
something I'm not.
My life has gone
completely down the loo!
(knocking at door)
Woody!
Aren't you ever coming
out of there?
You're starting
to scare me.
Sorry, Kelly.
I'm not trying to scare
you, but it... it's just,
your money is turning
me into a monster.
All my old friends
hate me now.
But everything
was going so well.
What happened?
I just looked
into a mirror,
and I didn't
like what I saw.
Whatever's wrong,
we can work it out.
It's a little more
complicated than that, Kelly.
It's like she's having a fight
with Señor Wences.
(door opening)
Come on in,
Kelly.
Thank you.
You know, Sammy, you could nail
that door shut right now.
I didn't see a thing.
Wow.
What a big moose head.
Kelly, I don't think this
is the time for name-calling.
What's wrong, Woody?
Don't you see, I'm
trying so hard
to fit into
your world
that I'm starting
to lose mine.
Yeah... so?
The point is, I'm changing.
Suddenly, Mr. Peterson
and Mr. Clavin
aren't that interesting.
It can't be them,
so it must be me.
Woody, I know
what you're going through.
Oh, Kelly, you
don't understand.
You'll never
understand.
It's hopeless.
Good-bye, Kelly!
Woody!
Woody, don't go!
Sam, do something!
All right, all right,
I'll get him.
Hey, uh, Norm, watch the bar
for me, will you?
Oh, all right.
(crying)
(crying continues)
Kelly...
There, there.
Mr. Peterson, you're
so understanding.
Uh, well, uh,
yes...
Thanks for
reaching out.
Yeah, Kelly, uh...
(laughing):
Cheer up!
It's just that
I'm so alone.
I feel that
all the love
has gone out of my life.
Am I bothering you,
Mr. Peterson?
No, no, it's either, uh,
listen to it here
or listen to it at home.
(clears throat)
What am I gonna do?
He says that all my money
bothers him
and he can't live in my world.
Kelly, why don't you try living
in his world?
What are you saying, that...
that we can make it if I
can just learn to...
to live without all my money?
Yeah, I guess.
Well, I can do that.
It'll be easy.
I don't know, Kelly.
You're gonna have to give up
an awful lot of stuff.
For example,
no more limousines.
Oh, that's okay.
I can take taxis.
No, Kelly, I don't think Woody
can even afford taxis.
You'll have to take the subway.
The what?
The "T"--
you know, the subway.
Come again?
The subway, the...
the little trains
that run underground,
carry people back and forth.
Right, an underground train.
You're such a joker,
Mr. Peterson.
Kelly, they exist,
and, and...
most people take them
to work every day.
Sure they do,
Mr. Peterson.
All right, I'll take your
little underground train
tomorrow morning.
Underground trains!
Woo-woo!
Okay, finally.
Daddy's home.
Oh, I couldn't catch up
with Woody.
I saw...
saw Kelly going down the street.
Is she all right?
Oh, no, Sammy, she looked
real... really upset.
You better go after her.
All right, all right.
Sometimes I swear it'd be easier
to just buy these things.
Boy, oh, boy.
Woody and Kelly
split up, huh?
Yes, well, I guess having access
to all her money
made him feel a little
like a leech.
You, uh, seem to make the word
"leech" sound, uh,
pejorative, there, Fras.
An educated man
would be proud
to be called a leech.
Leeches are a boon
to mankind.
I take it you're referring
to the practice
of using leeches
as a medical cure-all,
a practice
which has been
discredited for centuries now.
Discredited...
or covered up?
Well, you've got me there.
Sure, your big drug companies
don't want you
to find out about leeches--
you know why?
Leeches are free.
Yes, sir.
I... I have great respect
for the leech.
I'm sure the feeling's mutual.
Hey, Fras?
I've got the tools
of a perfect workout right here.
Jump rope, bag of doughnuts.
Guess which one's yours.
Didn't I tell you? I... I don't
need to work out today.
I think I've reached
my peak form-- isn't that great?
Yeah. Okay, get
in the pool room.
We've got
work to do.
You weren't listening,
I don't need any...
I'm all better!
Come on--
pool room.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Wood!
Woody!
Ah, it's good to be back, guys.
Yeah, even though I had
to give up Kelly
and I'm heartbroken,
I'm pretty miserable,
at least I'm not rich.
Well, Wood, it may not be
as bad as you think.
Well, what do you mean,
Mr. Peterson?
Kelly and I had a little
heart-to-heart last night,
and, uh, it turns out she's
gonna give up her money
and try to live
the way you do.
Kelly wants
to do that for me?
Yep-- matter of fact,
she's taking
the subway
over here right now.
Kelly's taking the subway
by herself?
Yeah, she wanted to prove to you
she could do normal things.
Well, she can't
do normal things.
She's never learned how.
She's gonna be eaten alive
on that subway!
Go after her, Wood.
Good idea,
Mr. Peterson.
Can you watch the bar
for me?
Oh, all right!
Some days, Cliffie,
it's like shooting
fish in a barrel.
Well, guys, I guess you're all
gonna eat your words,
'cause guess what I brought.
I give up.
Leeches!
Yeah, look at these babies.
They can't keep
themselves off each other.
Where'd you get those?
I have my sources.
Why are they here?
Oh, it's like a living
first aid kit, Norm.
You know, a cure-all
for anything
from a minor scrape
to a sucking chest wound.
Ooh, look
at the disgusting leeches!
(chuckling)
Hey, what's in the jar?
Hi, everybody. Where's Woody?
Well, he's out looking for you.
What happened, Kelly?
Did you get lost?
No, I was having such a great
time I didn't want it to end.
I love the subway.
Wait a minute,
you liked the subway?
Not at first.
I got real angry
because a lot of other people
tried to get
on my subway car.
And then I met
some young people
who apparently work
for the city
because they
were spray-painting the walls,
and they let me write,
"Kelly loves Woody,"
in a big red heart.
And then the pigs came
and we ran.
Well, I'm out of here--
workout's over.
Good day, all.
That was quick, huh?
It only lasted a
couple of minutes.
Yes, well, you know,
when you're focused...
Where's Sammy?
Um, I don't know.
Bye-bye.
(muffled shouting)
Woody!
Oh, Kelly,
thank God you're okay.
Woody, what
happened to you?
Oh, I got mugged
on the subway.
Oh, my poor Woody.
Come and sit down.
Do you want me
to call the pigs?
No, no, I...
I'm okay now.
They didn't get much.
They just scared
me a little.
Kelly, I don't
ever want you
to ride that
subway again.
Oh, but Woody, I just
wanted to show you
that I can live
without all my money.
Well, I don't want you to
live without your money.
I... I think it's
wrong for someone
to have to give
up their money.
Kind of came to
me as I was...
handing over
my wallet.
But if you live
on my money,
aren't you afraid you'll
turn into a monster?
Oh, here's what
we're gonna do.
We're gonna be a
two-income family.
You live off of
your income,
and I'll live
off of mine.
Woody, you're so smart.
I love you.
I love you, Kelly.
Ow!
Oh!
Oh, Woody, your eye
is swelling shut.
What are we gonna do?
Come on, babies, time
to earn your bacon.