Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Hey, everybody.
So, what's the latest?
Frasier passed out about 3:00.
Aw! Poor guy.
Yeah. For someone whose
wife is leaving him,
he seems awfully upset.
Oh, God! My head! Sam,
uh... coffee, please.
Oh, Carla, uh...
about last night...
I was in pretty bad shape,
you know?
I was drunk, and I was
carrying on about Lilith.
And I have this
half-memory of you
dragging me
into the office and cleaning me up,
putting me on the couch,
laying a blanket
over me and-and...
and sitting with me
until I fell asleep.
And, well, even
in my drunken stupor,
I wanted to thank you for
your... your unexpected kindness. Thanks.
Glad to help.
Here's your coffee.
Thank you, Sam.
Geez!
What time is it?
You know,
I could have sworn
I had my Rolex on.
FRASIER:
Hey, where's my class ring?
(theme song begins)
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Boy, I've never felt
so low in my life.
Well, Doc, if it means anything
to ya, I'm here for ya.
It doesn't, Cliff, but thanks.
Boy, Dr. Sternin-Crane having
an affair with another guy.
Mm, this reminds me
of a terrible scandal
we had back in Hanover.
Rocked the whole
town to its core.
Mayor's wife ran off
with old Mr. Smithers.
Oh, that's not
so scandalous, Woody.
Well, Mr. Smithers was a goat.
W-Woody, why... why
don't you take a break?
Again?
Man, this day is flying!
You know what the most
painful thing about it is?
I... I didn't
see it coming.
Lilith had an affair.
I had no idea.
Now she's leaving me and...
There were no signs.
Do you know what I mean, Sam?
Sam?
I'm sorry.
I'm still back
on Mr. Smithers.
Now, Doc, maybe
there were signs,
you were just
too blind to see them.
Yeah, I mean, what
with Lilith, uh...
spending every night late at
work for the last six months.
You know, whenever the
two of you were together,
you were just
bickering all the time.
And, worst of all, you know,
you spend all
your waking hours sitting in this bar.
Cliffy, I don't think
he wants to...
No, Sam, you know,
I want to hear this.
Maybe it's time somebody
did splash the cold water
of reality in my face.
On the other hand, at least
I'm not a career-stagnant,
middle-aged mama's boy with
little or no sexual experience.
I know what you mean, Doc.
We have a few of those
at work- very sad.
I can't believe
she wants to leave me.
I really blew it.
Well, Fras, you know,
marriage is a very tricky thing.
It takes a lot of work
and sacrifice and compromise
from both parties
to keep it fresh and rewarding.
How can you say that?
You work less at your marriage
than anyone else in the world!
I was hoping
the irony would cheer you up.
Well, Doc, if you ask me,
you're wasting your time
sitting around here
feeling sorry for yourself,
when you should be out there
trying to get her back.
How do you suggest I do that?
Get off your butt
and take charge.
Be a caveman.
A woman likes that.
Caveman?
Trust me-
Nick Tortelli...
now there was a caveman.
In fact, the next time you see
one of those drawings of how
man evolved from the ape,
look real closely
at that second guy.
Thanks for the idea, Carla,
but I hardly think
the primitive approach
would work on a woman
as sophisticated as Lilith.
Well, then why don't you
try the romantic route?
You know, take her up to the
Cape for a romantic weekend
and treat her the
way you used to.
Oh, no, no, no-
Come on, Sam, with that bush-wa.
You know, if you want
to keep a woman in your life,
nothing beats the old-fashioned
fake heart attack.
I beg your pardon?
She goes for the door,
you go for your chest.
I mean, nobody can walk out
on somebody who's
having a coronary.
It's foolproof.
I learned it from Ma.
She uses that on you?
Or I use it on her.
It depends who's
trying to leave.
Frasier...
Well, look who's here.
I suppose this is the
part where we fight
over who gets to
keep our friends.
No...
Then why are you here?
To humiliate me
again in public?
Seems to be a theme you enjoy.
No, I was worried about you.
I brought you a shaving kit
and some clean clothes.
You were worried about me?
Then you're not leaving me?
Oh, I'm still leaving you.
Frasier, this is so...
I'm sorry.
I think we should have
this discussion in the office.
WOODY:
Oh, no chance of that, Dr. Sternin-Crane.
Sam's office
is his inner sanctum.
The only person who gets
to use Sam's office is Sam.
It's all right, Woody.
It's all right.
Oh, well, maybe if Kelly
ever has an affair,
I'll get to use
your precious office.
Poor Fras, huh?
What about Lilith?
Huh?
She's probably just
trying to find herself.
Oh, come off it, Becs.
Nobody tries to find
themselves anymore.
And, even when it was in style,
it was just an excuse
for middle-aged people to quit work,
ride around on Harleys,
and have sex with young people.
Oh, is that right,
Miss Know-It-All?
Well, it just so happens
that my father once
left for six months to find himself.
And when he came back,
he was at peace with the world.
You could see it in his eyes
the second he came
roaring up the driveway.
Well, here we are.
Is this it?
Should I, uh... call a lawyer,
initiate divorce proceedings?
It's up to you.
You're the one making all
the decisions, apparently.
Frasier,
I do not want a divorce.
I want a trial separation.
Furthermore,
I'm going to be gone
for a while, so I need to know
that Frederick
is being taken care of
in the best manner possible.
It would be irresponsible
for me to take him
from a comfortable
and familiar home
where he feels stable
and secure.
Therefore, I would like you
to have sole custody for the
period of time that I'm gone.
Just like that?
You're not only
walking out on me,
but on your own son as well.
Oh, Frasier, you think this
is easy for me? It's not!
Please just promise me
you'll take care of my son!
Wouldn't have it any other way.
Personally, I don't
want him growing up
in your swinging
bachelorette pad,
what with your
love beads, your hi-fi
and your Dave Brubeck albums!
Frasier, if you can't
get into the '90s,
at least move into the '60s.
Well, then where are
you going to live?
All right, let me guess.
Don't tell me!
You're going to move in with
your boyfriend, Dr. Pascal!
That's right, Frasier, I am.
What's so great about this
Pascal guy anyway, huh?
I mean, the man
is obviously a crackpot.
All he's noted for is inventing
this ridiculous bubble underground.
It's called
an Eco-pod, Frasier.
A self-contained
subterranean environment
which will serve
as a prototype
for an eventual space station.
Similar to the Biosphere, only
on a much more ambitious scale.
To be inhabited by moles
and gophers, no doubt.
Yes, it will house a variety
of animal species.
And, for the first year,
two human subjects as well.
Oh, really?
And where in the world
do you expect to find...
Oh, no!
Yes, Frasier, I'm off
to live in the Eco-pod.
Oh, no!
It's a noble experiment.
I'm a pioneer.
The research we are going to do
is going to aid all of humanity.
This is the stupidest day
I've ever had.
It's anything but
stupid, Frasier.
Dr. Pascal is a visionary.
I'm proud to be associated
with him as we chart the future.
Oh, this will be a big hit on
the cocktail party circuit.
"Say, Fras, where's your
lovely wife this evening?"
"Well, Bob,
she's underneath the Earth's
crust with her boyfriend."
"What's new with you?"
I refuse to discuss
this any further.
You're being irrational.
No, wait, Lilith, wait.
Don't go, please.
Look, I... I'm sorry.
Please help me to understand
why you're doing this.
Well, Frasier...
ever since I was a little girl,
I've led a very disciplined,
regimented life.
But in the
back of my mind, I always had this
nagging feeling
that something was missing.
I tried to fill the void
with achievements...
scientific awards,
marriage to a prominent man.
But deep down inside,
I still felt empty.
Then along came Googie.
Googie?
Dr. Pascal.
He's a free thinker.
A radical.
I never know
what he's going to do next.
And when I'm with him,
I don't know
what I'm going to do next.
That's new for me, Frasier.
I like it.
I hope you understand.
(sighing):
I suppose I do.
You know, maybe
I haven't always listened.
Maybe I haven't always known
the right thing to say or do.
Just one thing
I want you to know.
I wish you the very best.
I adore you, and I always will.
Thank you.
Take good care of Frederick.
And yourself.
Good-bye, Frasier.
Good-bye, my love.
(gasping)
Oh! Oh, my God!
I'm having a heart attack!
Well, maybe not.
I'm going now.
I'd like to leave
a parting word.
I want you to know that what
I'm doing is very difficult.
It is not to hurt Frasier.
It's to acknowledge the
fact that I'm changing.
No one can go living year in and
year out without ever changing.
It's impossible.
Or at least it's very rare.
Well, I'm off.
I don't know what
the future holds.
Whatever happens, I only hope
I can realize my
full potential.
To acquire things the
old Lilith never had.
Like a body temperature?
That's very good, Carla.
Incidentally,
I've taken your
little wisecracks
for a few years now,
you hideous gargoyle,
and if you ever open
that gateway to hell you call a mouth
in my direction again,
I'll snap off
your extremities like dead branches
and feed them
to you at gunpoint.
God! That felt good.
Well...
that was just plain rude.
Oh, hey, Fras.
How you doing, huh?
Come on, talk to us-
we're your friends.
Say something
to him, will ya? Like what?
I don't know,
somethin' positive.
Something to cheer him up.
Frasier, say, have
you lost weight?
What? That would
cheer me up.
I appreciate your concern,
everyone, and...
you can stop worrying.
You see, I know exactly
how this is gonna go.
After the shock wears off,
there will be some initial pain
followed by resentment
and depression,
and a lasting
sense of insecurity,
as I ping-pong blame
between Lilith and myself.
Throughout this process,
all I have to do is...
keep telling myself that
everything is going to be okay.
Well, the shock
seems to be wearing off.
Here comes the pain.
Oh, boy.
Oh, mama, that's a big one!
Frasier, can we
do anything for ya?
Oh, no, Sam, no.
If anyone
has the inner resources
to deal with this,
it's Dr. Frasier Crane.
Trust me.
I know exactly
how to handle this.
I'm gonna jump, Lilith!
OFFICER (over bullhorn):
Attention, this is the police.
Do not jump.
I repeat, do not jump.
Whatever your problem is,
we can solve it.
Just go back inside.
I swear to God I'm gonna jump!
Where's that shrink we use
in cases like this?
You mean Frasier Crane?
He's not answering his pager.
Yeah, remind me
to put this in my report.
That man'll never work
in this town again.
Hey, you have
your whole life ahead of ya.
Anything good on?
Yeah, we got, uh, Oprah,
we got, uh... Quincy...
Home Shopping Network...
we got a guy on a ledge...
we got Barnaby Jones...
Wait a minute!
Wait a minute! Normie!
Normie, go back, quick.
Go back, go back,
go back- yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God!
Hey, that's that Quincy where
they buried the wrong guy!
SAM: Hey, Normie, go back
to that guy-on-the-ledge stuff.
Hey, that's just right outside.
No wonder all these people
are in here.
I wonder who the poor sap is.
OFFICER:
Go back inside.
FRASIER:
I swear to God I'm gonna jump!
Oh, my God!
Wait, wait, wait.
Sam, uh, you find Lilith,
and Carla and I'll go
up and find Frasier.
Come on, come on, Norm,
I'm going up there, too.
Normie, come on, will ya?
A buddy of ours
is on the ledge.
He's about to jump
to his death- let's go!
Geez, you're right-
I better go move my car.
Aw...
Frasier?
Hey, uh, I'll take it.
I'm a friend of his-
I think I can help.
I've operated these before, sir.
It's all right.
Frasier, it's me-
your friend, Cliff Clavin.
Now pitching for Boston...
Hey, come on, would ya?
All right. Just kidding,
just kidding.
Uh, Fras...
look, buddy, uh, don't think
I don't know how you feel.
Uh, it's not like
I haven't been there myself,
you know, standing
high above the city
with the wind
blowing through your hair,
praying this time
you'll have the guts to do it.
Give me that!
Frasier, Frasier,
don't listen to him, man.
So it didn't work out
with Lilith.
You know? What's the big deal?
That's okay.
What about your friends?
What about me?
I care for ya.
Hell, I love ya, man!
CROWD:
Aw...
Yeah, I said it.
Look, a guy can love another guy
without being the kind of guy
who loves other guys.
You knew what I was saying,
didn't you, Fras?
You didn't think that I meant...
the other thing, did ya?
Hold on a second, Fras.
Take that. Talk to him.
No, it's all right.
I'm his wife.
Don't aggravate him.
I'm the reason he's up there.
He's very unstable.
Frasier, you're making
a big fool of yourself.
Don't leave me, Lilith!
It's too late, Frasier-
I've made up my mind.
I'm gonna jump!
Lie to him- tell him
you'll go back with him.
Tell him to go inside.
I can't lie to you, Frasier.
It's over.
(crowd murmurs) Come on, lady!
What were we supposed to do,
go on living the charade?
Sure, we had
an amazing sex life,
but a relationship
is more than that.
I felt the confines
of our marriage
were not allowing me to grow.
Surely some of you women
know what I'm talking about.
VARIOUS WOMEN:
Right on! Right on! Yay!
Why don't you tell them
about your affair?!
(crowd groans)
Well, I was in
a very vulnerable state, and...
Frasier, this is ridiculous.
I'm coming upstairs.
Fras, a-about
what I was saying earlier.
You know, there are all kinds
of different kinds of love.
(gasps):
Frasier!
You stay back!
Okay, okay.
Rebecca, I found him!
Frasier...
Don't come near me!
I-I won't come
near you, Frasier.
Please, please,
just step inside.
Oh, Rebecca, go back to Cheers
and leave me alone.
No, Frasier, we're
your friends.
Don't jump- you have lots of
friends who care about you.
NORM (over bullhorn): Frasier,
listen to me- this is Norm Peterson.
I want you to listen
very carefully.
You left about a half a mug
of beer on the bar.
You don't suppose
that I could, maybe...
Help yourself!
Thank you.
Frasier...
Lilith, don't come near me-
I swear I'll jump!
Would you excuse us, please?
I'd like to speak
with my husband.
Okay... But before I go,
I want to say one thing.
Go ahead and jump, you coward!
Take the easy way out!
Go ahead and end it all!
(whispers):
Wow, that was reverse psychology, right?
What's reverse psychology?
Frasier...
I refuse to indulge
in this little game
of emotional blackmail
any longer.
You and I both know you have
no intention of jumping.
I know you better than that.
No, you don't, Lilith.
I'm gonna jump,
because I can't go on living
knowing that
you love someone else.
Very well, Frasier.
You win.
I won't leave you.
Really?
Really.
Now, come inside.
You mean, you're not
just saying that?
No, I'm not just saying it.
I won't leave you.
I may be unhappy for
the rest of my days, but...
I will honour my obligations
as your wife.
Baby, you're the greatest!
(sighs)
Oh, go on, Lilith...
get out of here.
What do you mean?
I can't be happy
knowing that you're not.
(window sliding closed)
(sighs)
Thank you, Frasier.
Well, thank you for...
getting me off the ledge.
I was gonna pretend to faint
and fall back in,
but this worked a lot better.
How you doing?
Oh, I'll be
okay, Sam. Thanks.
You want anything,
you let me know.
Well, you know,
there is, uh, one thing.
Could you, uh, take the bullhorn
away from Cliff and Norm?
CLIFF (on bullhorn): All right, McGerk,
you'll never take me alive! Ha-ha!
Come on, come on,
it's my turn! Come on!
Attention, K-Mart shoppers!
Whoa, whoa! Guys, guys, whoa.
Hey, come on!
Frasier, I just wanted
to say good-bye.
Dr. Pascal and I
are leaving
for the desert tonight.
Are you all right?
No... but I will be.
I said good-bye to Frederick
this afternoon.
He loves the thought of Mommy
going off to live
in a big bubble.
I'm sure this will be
a special memory for him
that he will relive
over and over again
in the years
of his psychoanalysis.
(door opens)
Lilith, you ready?
Googie, I thought
you were going to wait outside.
Before we leave there's
something I have to say to your husband.
Uh...
I-I-I know this is
an awkward moment, Doctor,
but I have to tell you.
I was pulling up
in front of the bar just now,
and I seem to have
dinged your BMW.
Oh. Of course you did.
Well, we're off.
We've got to be going.
Good-bye, Frasier.
Good-bye, Lilith.
Oh, there's just...
there's something
I'd like to say.
I know you've got a
rough year ahead of you.
You're in for some rocky times.
I-I'm sure you'll experience
some very painful moments,
and when you do,
I'd like you to feel free
to call on me for...
sympathy and understanding.
Thank you, Frasier.
I was talking to Googie.