You know, Sam,
this is my favourite time of day.
What's that, Coach? Closing time?
No. 1:37. I don't know.
There's just something about it.
I know what you mean.
I suppose we've all got
our favourite 1:37 story.
What's your favourite time of day,
Sam?
Gee, I don't know. 8:15's nice.
Yeah. I used to like 8:5.
I think I kinda grew out of it.
Wait a minute. Coach, Sammy.
I don't want to be left alone
locked up in this bar all ni...
Quarter to three
No one in the place except you and me
Once in a while, a man
needs a little time to himself.
- Evening, everybody.
- Hi, Norman.
Beer?
Nah, I'd probably just drink it.
What's new, Norm?
I just came from a late lunch
at the Copley Plaza.
You had lunch at the Copley?
Yeah. I took a prospective employer
there. Courting the guy.
- What did you have?
- The rack of lamb for two.
Don't remember what he had.
I saw Teddy Kennedy over there.
Whoa. Norman, really?
I still say that Kennedy will be
president some day.
No, wait.
Maybe even next time.
You know how politicians are.
- Doesn't make sense.
- I really don't think so, Diane.
I've got a pet little theory
about that.
You see, if you go back in history
and take every president,
you'll find that the numerical value
of each letter in their last name
was equally divisible into the year
in which they were elected.
So who's gonna win, Cliff?
Reagan again?
Mondale?
No. Not a chance.
See, I figured it out.
By my calculations,
our next president has to be named
Yelnik Mcwawa.
That's the stupidest name
I ever heard.
Sam, please. You're talking
about our next president.
So, Norm. What was Kennedy
doing at the Copley?
Having lunch. I got his autograph.
You disturbed him during his lunch?
No. God!
I waited
till he went to the men's room.
Mart... Martie Broder?
I got the wrong stall. I dunno.
Ho, Cliff.
Isn't that Tibor Svetkovic?
- Svetkovic, where?
- That's Svetkovic all right.
Based on the fact that he has a long
name that you can all pronounce,
I guess that he's an athlete.
Or will he be president in 1990?
Diane, the man was Czechoslovakia's
greatest hockey player.
He defected to us
just to play in the NHL.
It's an incredible story actually.
He dressed up as a woman,
hid in a haystack,
crawled on his belly
under barbed wire,
swam a couple of rivers and stowed
away on a tramp steamer to get here.
Amazing.
The next week, the rest of his team
came over on the Concorde.
That's what he gets
for not reading his schedule.
Nobody said
he was a smart hockey player.
Is this my day, or what? First
Teddy Kennedy now Tibor Svetkovic.
You better memorise his shoes,
you might want his autograph later.
Tibor, I see you play all the time.
I'm Sam Malone.
Your problem may be
too much caffeine.
Sorry, what?
He's learning English
from TV commercials.
And who are you?
I'm Lana Marshall.
I'm Tibor's commercial agent.
Is that right?
I'm Sam Malone, the boss here.
You're the boss?
You're gonna tell me what to do?
Something tell me
you know what to do.
I know what I like to do.
That's nice.
I like the lady who knows what she
likes to do and does what she likes.
The mating ritual of
the horny-breasted lounge lizard.
Two beers.
Let me take care of you two here.
- Tibor. Miller Time?
- TV! Yes, sir.
- What can I do for you?
- What's your speciality?
I do everything the same round here.
- Great.
- Then why don't you surprise me?
- It would be my pleasure.
- Mine too, I hope.
- I'll be right back.
- I'll be right here.
She'll be here,
he'll be back and I'll be sick.
So, you get jobs for professional
athletes to be in commercials?
Yes. As a matter of fact,
I specialise in male athletes.
Don't you know who you were
just talking to? That's Sam Malone.
Cute guy. Too bad he has dandruff.
- He used to play with the Red Sox.
- Really?
Who does he play with now?
You know,
you give broads a good name.
Excuse me, could I ask you
a question about your boss?
The king of the single entendre?
Tell me, does he have a wife,
or worse, someone he cares about?
He's available and very desirable,
if lummox is your cup of tea.
And it appears to be.
Tibor, I think it's time
to get to the Garden.
I'm late.
After game, your room?
No, Tibor,
I think I'm going to be busy tonight.
OK, goodbye.
And this concludes
another day of programming.
Sooner or later,
you'll own General.
Poor guy should really think
about wearing a helmet.
I understand
that you were an athlete.
I'm sorry, I don't remember you.
That's all right. I was a relief
pitcher before they became famous.
- I missed it by a year.
- Have you done any acting?
Well, you know, yeah, I have.
I had the lead in a school play.
The one about the evil woman
who pushes her husband
into getting rid of people
for more and more power.
You mean Macbeth?
No. How Boots Fooled the King.
- Was that what Macbeth was about?
- Tibor's looking better, isn't he?
Excuse me. I'll be right back.
- Hey, Diane, we're talking here.
- She's talking.
You're killing time between thoughts.
You got a problem?
Look, Sam. Just watch it, OK?
She's not
one of your usual bimboettes.
That's what I like about her.
She's got a lot of class.
While I have never been
a big fan of the women you date,
I will say that at least
they were too stupid to be harmful.
I knew they'd grow on you.
Is there something between you two?
No. That's just business.
I never mix in her personal life
and she mixes in mine.
I've just been talking to my
secretary about the winter schedule.
I think there might be some
commercials you might do very well.
Me? You're kidding.
No.
You have a very sexy, playful quality
that would come across on camera.
Wait,
I haven't played baseball for years.
I'm not exactly a household name.
Non-star athletes are in vogue.
They come across as regular people.
What do you say, Sam?
- I gotta think about it a bit.
- Come on, do it. You're a natural.
Look at you. You're tall, handsome,
you got a great smile.
Show her your smile.
I'll be damned.
Who the hell was I thinking of?
You know, I have to admit, all these
years watching those commercials,
I always thought
I might be pretty good.
Let's do it.
Wonderful.
Look, I'm staying at the Ritz.
Why don't you come over later
and we'll work out the details?
I don't get off until two.
All the better.
All these people at the bar
and no one introduced us.
No, they didn't.
I'd like to thank
each and every one of them.
Me, too.
Now for Fields Light Beer,
former Red Sox pitcher, Luis Tiant.
After the game,
I like to sit back, light up a cigar
and enjoy a Fields Light Beer.
Hey, Luis.
Hey, Sam.
When you get to be my age,
30, you don't want to get filled up.
That's why I drink Field Beer.
It's refreshing, satisfying,
and you don't full feel with Field,
you just full fine.
Full feel with Field, you full fine.
Sorry, Luis, I don't think
you've got it. I'm pulling you out.
- Skipper, let me stay.
- Sorry, big guy.
Go get them, Mayday.
Now pitching, Sam Mayday Malone.
Fields,
it's refreshing, it's satisfying.
You don't feel full with Fields,
you just feel fine.
Alright!
Another save.
I still get the win, don't l?
You were great.
Coach,
two bottles of Fields right here.
Normally I wouldn't use that to
shampoo my dog but you sold me.
Sam, you could sell me
ice cubes in summer.
You're in showbiz now.
You're a star.
Sam, could you introduce me
to Gene Tierney?
- I don't know Gene Tierney, Coach.
- OK, be that way.
Come on. How about a speech
from the big actor?
Yeah, how did it feel
to see yourself up there, Sammy?
It was nice. It was very nice, OK?
I was afraid of this. We have
to sedate the man, he's hysterical.
Sam, if there's anything you wanna
talk about, get off your chest.
There's nothing I wanna talk about.
I'm as giddy as a schoolgirl.
Just wait on some tables.
Fine.
Sammy, that agent of yours
is hotter than a pistol.
She's really earning
her ten per cent.
Listen, will you just leave me alone?
Please, got that? Leave me alone.
- Sam, let's talk.
- There's nothing to talk about.
It's important.
Come back to the office now.
Sammy's in trouble
with Miss Chambers again.
Sammy's in trouble with Chambers.
What do you want?
Sam, you're obviously unhappy
and everybody just wants to know why.
I'm not unhappy.
- You're not?
- No.
- You're happy with the commercials?
- Yes.
- Think you were good?
- Really?
- Yes.
Well, what is it, then?
Are you happy with the money?
yes.
- Are you happy with the auditions?
- Yes.
- Are you happy with your agent?
- Oh, God!
The Dragon Lady.
Tell me about it.
Why? You wanna hear me
say you were right?
Of course not.
Knowing that and knowing
you know it and are tortured by it
is plenty for this country girl.
I'm sorry. I am sorry.
I do wanna help. Come on, let's talk.
You wanna hear about my relationship
with another woman?
Well,... Maybe...
Maybe I should find a man out there
who's intellectually capable
of helping you.
All right, everybody line up
for the ugliest tongue contest.
Alphabetically by height, over here.
It appears that
all the other intellectuals are busy.
You're sure you wanna hear this?
I'll stop you
before I get the vapours.
You see, my relationship...
Lana and I are a lot friendlier
than most agents and clients.
Friendlier?
You know me. I'm never against
a wild night of friend-making, but...
There's some... Now I feel that I'm
supposed to be friendly on demand.
And you're afraid
she'll stop getting you commercials
if you stop being friendly?
When you play in the bigs like I did,
you get used to attention.
When I stopped playing baseball,
I felt something missing in my life.
I was just hoping that these
commercials would get it back for me.
Sam, Lana gave me a message for you
but I can't remember it.
- Lana's here?
- That's it.
By the way, what are you two doing?
We got a lot of customers out there.
I got a problem.
Diane's helping me talk through it.
Look, Sam, let me tell you something.
You've faced a lot of tough problems.
You always found a solution but
since Sir Isaac Hayes came along...
No offence, Diane,
I love Sir Isaac Hayes,
but since then,
it's been talk, talk, talk.
This is a pretty complicated problem,
Coach.
You see, Sam wants to break up
with Lana, and he knows he should,
but he's afraid that he will
sacrifice his acting career.
- See?
- I don't understand what's going on.
Let me show you something.
Come right down here.
Just, please, come right down
here. Stand right here, Sam.
- Pick that up.
- What do you want me to do that for?
Just pick it up.
Now, get the hell out there and tell
her you're finished with her.
Please tell him
it's more complic...
Out. Hustle.
What do you want me to do?
Hustle. I mean it.
That was wonderful. Somehow,
your instincts just told you...
Button it up, Diane. We got
a lot of people out there. Move it.
Right.
Tell me something, Red.
Are professional athletes better
between the old wamsuttas
than ordinary men?
I've had no experience
with ordinary men.
Me neither, but I'm trying
to work my way up to one.
Believe me, athletes take their pants
off one leg at a time, like anybody.
They take off their pants?
I'm glad you're here. There's
something I want to talk about.
Sam,
what do you think of your commercial?
- It was fine but listen....
- I thought it was wonderful.
I've had lots of calls about you.
- Calls?
- A lot of people saw you.
And they liked what they saw.
One of those calls was an offer
for you, a national commercial.
It's big money,
and they want to fly you to Hawaii.
You're going to do the commercial
with the Osmonds.
The Osmonds.
- The whole family?
- That's right.
- Even little Jimmy?
- Well, we're hoping.
Now, come on.
Wasn't there something
I wanted to say?
Later. We've got
to get some pictures for you.
We should buy a new sports jacket.
Afterwards, we can stop off
at the hotel for a bite.
And a nibble.
And a scratch.
Coach.
Sam, I'm getting real mad now.
- Lana, we can't nibble any more.
- Why?
I just don't feel right about it.
I see.
Does this mean
that you're no longer my agent?
Sam, what kind of person
would I have to be
to drop you as a client
just because of this?
- A dragon lady.
- I'm no dragon lady.
- Good.
- But I am gonna drop you.
I've learned from past experience,
once you've had an intimate
relationship with a client,
you can't go back
to being just business associates.
Perhaps it's time
for me to find a new face.
My face is new.
Good,
you still have time to return it.
She's good, Sam.
- So, that's it?
- Yep.
Good luck in finding a replacement
for me in the Hawaii commercial.
If it takes me
longer than six minutes, I'll quit.
Boy, she is good.
May I ask you a question?
You want to know how he was?
What?
You think I'm gonna stand here
and listen to you tell me
how good Sam was?
Fair?
What do you wanna know?
I want to know
how you can live with yourself.
I can't. That's why I like
having young athletes around.
I've always been crazy about them.
Sometimes when I'm with one, I swear
I can hear the crowd cheering.
I could understand this behaviour
from an oversexed adolescent.
- But you're..
- An older woman? Middle-aged?
All the more reason
to grab some youth.
There was a time in my life when men
would invent tricks and schemes
to get my attention.
Well, now I'm the one
who schemes to get theirs.
That's not too unfair, is it?
But don't be too concerned.
Someday, even that won't work.
Don't judge me until the bloom
is off your rose, honey. Ta-ta.
She is good.
Fields,
it's refreshing, it's satisfying.
You don't feel full with Fields,
you just feel fine.
Alright!
Another save.
Come on, admit it. I was good.
Come on, say it. I was good.
- You were OK.
- I wasn't OK, I was good.
What's it gonna do,
kill you to admit it?
All right.
You were...
Good.
You were OK.
You were good.
And you did the right thing.
Thanks. Hey, listen.
Before you came to work at this bar,
I never thought that much
about morality and integrity.
You made me aware of all that stuff
for the first time.
Thank you, Sam.
That's why I'm firing you.
You can leave your apron right there.