Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Sorry, Sam.
I can't fix
the jukebox here.
Got to take it back to
the shop and open her up.
I'll go get the guys.
Take it back to the shop,
my foot.
That's the biggest ploy
in the fix-it racket, Sammy.
You know they tell you that
just so they can jack up
the price on you. Trust me.
All this baby needs
is one swift, good...
(thuds, rattles, clanks, clangs)
Shop time.
(theme song begins)
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always
glad you came
You wanna be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You wanna be where
everybody knows your name
You wanna go
where people know
People are all the same
You wanna go where
everybody knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Well, what are we gonna do
without our jukebox?
The place won't
be the same.
No jukebox?
I feel naked.
Excuse me.
Why are you all mourning the
temporary loss of this jukebox?
I mean, you never play it.
No, no, no, Fras, the point is,
it's the perfect height
to lean on.
Take a look at what it does
to the line of my body there.
Perfect pick-up pose, man.
Hi.
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
I'm just demonstrating.
I'll talk to you later.
All right, Sam.
But you never play it.
Frasier, I never
play Vera either,
but I'd miss her if a couple
guys wheeled her out of here
on a refrigerator dolly.
Sam, I should have her back
in a week, good as new.
A week?
How can we live without
our juke for a week?
Now, don't you have
a loaner or something?
I'm all out
of jukeboxes.
How about
a cigarette machine?
Naw, we'd never use that.
You never use the jukebox!
Hey, if you want, I could
loan you a karaoke machine.
What's a karaoke machine?
CLIFF:
Walter.
May I?
You see, a karaoke
machine is a self-contained,
uh, musical gizmo
of Oriental origin,
much like yourself.
You know, it plays the, uh,
well, the background
accompaniment to popular songs
so that shower crooners
like myself can sing along.
Oh, Clavin,
I didn't know you did that.
I'm amazed.
That I sing?
No, that you shower.
By the way,
your singing stinks, too.
REBECCA:
Hey, you guys.
Look what it says here
on my limerick-a-day calendar.
Ohh, let me
guess.
"There was an old maid
named Becks
who went a long time
without sex."
Carla, why does your humor
always have to be at
someone else's expense?
That's what makes me laugh.
Well, for those of you
who do care,
Robin gets out of
prison on Monday.
Oh...
well, that's great, great.
But aren't you kind of
forgetting something important?
No, no, no.
No, I remember,
I r... we won't
have any money.
We'll have to
start all over.
No, no, no, no,
the limerick, read the limerick.
I cannot believe you guys
are more interested
in some stupid rhyme
than in my happiness.
Well, it's certainly not true
in my case, Ms. Howe.
Well, thank you, Woody.
I'm interested
in both equally.
Boy, she saw
right through me.
I'm dying to hear
that limerick.
Here we go, Sam--
the karaoke machine
and some song
catalogs to go
along with it.
Oh, great.
Just what we need--
a loud, abrasive
noise-making machine.
Fras, come on,
don't pick on something
that can't defend itself.
Thank you, Norm.
Well, perhaps I passed judgment
too quickly here.
This may have some merit in it.
It's filled with old standards.
It's got, uh,
"Someone to Watch Over Me,"
"All of Me,"
"You Made Me Love You."
(music plays)
Lollipop, lollipop,
oh, lolli-lolli-lolli
Lollipop, lollipop, oh,
lolli-lolli-lolli, lollipop
(pops)
Bah-dum-dum-dum
Lollipop, lollipop
Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli,
lollipop
Normie, Normie, how does,
how does this song end?
I don't know.
I think it just kind of
keeps going till
one of us drops.
Bah-dum-dum-dum
Lollipop, lollipop, oh,
lolli-lolli-lolli, lollipop
Oh, please!
Lolli-lolli-lolli
This is the silliest,
dopiest display
we've ever witnessed.
And if you want to make a pop,
you do it like this.
(pops)
I've got a delivery
for a Ms. Rebecca Howe?
I'm Rebecca Howe.
Here you go.
And here you go.
Oh, a shiny quarter.
Jeepers, this'll pay
for my sister's operation.
Look at this.
A single white rose.
I wonder what this means.
Well, if it means the same
thing it does in my family,
you'd better have Clavin
start your car tonight.
It's from Robin.
"Dear Rebecca,
I'll be free on Monday.
"If you're free as well,
would you care to join me
in holy matrimony?"
Oh, my God.
This is a proposal!
In three days,
I'm gonna be Mrs. Robin Colcord.
Yeah, that is a cause
for a special celebration.
Woody, I think
I'll have a beer.
Well, congratulations,
Ms. Howe.
I mean, gosh, you know
I may not be
the most inarticulate guy
in the world, but...
Wait, wait,
wait,
don't you mean articulate?
Well, isn't it
the same thing
like flammable
and inflammable?
Boy, I learned that one
the hard way.
Honey, I think this is great.
There's something
you ought to know
before
you get married.
What is that?
I have this strict policy
about going to bed
with married women.
So this weekend is
your absolute last chance
to have me again.
I don't think so, Sam.
All right. All right.
Stupid policy.
Uh, how about the weekend
after that?
No.
Come on.
Lilith, I can't believe
you did this.
Nobody's ever thrown a party
like this for me before.
Turnabout is fair play.
You gave me my bridal shower
three years ago.
Oh, yeah, but Lilith,
I just threw that together.
I really didn't put any thought
into it at all.
That would explain
the napkins
that said, "Mazel tov,
Si and Effie Kupperman."
I got a break
on those
when Si Kupperman skipped town
with his secretary.
How lucky for me.
Boy, these Mylar balloons
are a public hazard.
What do you mean?
Well, Mylar is a form
of metal, Paul,
and if you release
these things
they get caught up
in the high-tension wires;
they cause an arc,
sending a shower of sparks
all over the place,
and it... hey, it could
put out the lights
of a whole city block.
All right.
FRASIER:
Gentlemen.
If I may, I would like
to propose a toast
to the woman of the hour,
the reason we're all gathered
here at this wonderful party.
To a very special lady,
who, I must say,
has a glow tonight
like I've never seen before.
Thank you, Frasier.
Oh, pipe down.
I've gotta finish this toast
to Lilith
or she'll kill me.
To Lilith.
I'd just like
to say, it's a
really beautiful day.
And this is a really
nice party and...
if I'm ever lucky
enough to be married,
I hope it's to someone
just like you.
To Lilith.
This is more attention
than I got
at my own shower.
Well I'd like to make a toast
to the bride-to-be.
Mmm?
Yep.
Uh...
I'd just like to say
that, uh, you know,
when, when you and Robin
first got together,
none of us thought
that a match
between a billionaire
tycoon and a, you...
...you know,
would work out.
But, uh, this is
just great, honey.
I, I wish the two
of you, uh,
happiness forever
and ever.
That's very
sweet, Sam.
Hey.
And I want to make
a toast, too.
To you, and
all you guys
in the bar,
you really stood by me,
and I love you all.
To us.
Oh, thank you.
She didn't mention
my name.
Wait a minute.
I'd like to make another toast.
She's going to bail
herself out.
To Robin.
Robin.
Strike two.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait. One more.
I feel like I'm leaving
somebody out.
Here we go.
To me, and to
my happiness.
Okay, Frasier.
That's it.
Get your coat.
And of course
to Lilith.
Oh, Rebecca,
you didn't have to.
Frasier, put your coat down.
We're not going anywhere.
Okay, everybody,
uh, give me your attention.
A couple of the guys
have put together
a song for the future
Mrs. Colcord.
Hit it.
(high-pitched singing):
Lollipop, lollipop
Oh, lolli-lolli-lolli
Lollipop, lollipop,
oh, lolli-lolli-lolli
Lollipop, lollipop
Oh, lolli-lolli...
Excuse me.
Paul, shut
that thing off.
My wife is throwing
a lovely shower here.
The least you can do is
show a little respect.
Aw, Fras, we're just giving
a gift of music here.
Some gift.
And singing with those stupid
voices an even stupider song.
What's, what is that song even
supposed to mean anyway?
Well, it's, uh,
it's about this girl
and, uh...
Lollipop.
All right, if you must sing,
why don't you sing
something a little more
appropriate to the occasion?
Now, look, here's...
here's a lovely song:
"Isn't It Romantic?"
Yeah, it's kind of slow,
isn't it?
Yeah, you don't get to make
any funny noises in it either.
Yeah, really.
He calls that
a classic.
Well, of course
it's a classic.
It has a, a rare beauty.
It's a...
Yeah.
a haunting imagery,
an enchanting
melody.
Oh, yeah.
Excuse me,
and it goes, Paul,
something like this.
Isn't it romantic?
Music in the night
A dream that can be heard
Isn't it romantic
Moving shadows paint
the oldest magic word
(Norm and Cliff
singing high-pitched):
I hear the breezes playing
In the trees above...
You're right, Fras.
It is a lovely song
when sung properly.
Killjoy.
Boy, that's lovely,
isn't it?
Yes.
This is great "champlagne."
Did you hear me?
I said "champlagne."
I meant
to say "champlagne."
(laughing)
I said it again!
(snickering)
I think maybe
you've had enough.
No, no, no, no,
I want to make a toast.
Please?
To "champlagne"!
(laughs)
No, no, no,
I'm kidding.
To my sweet baby, Robin.
We may not have much,
but we have each other.
Then you don't have much.
Hit me again, Sam.
Oh, no, I think you've
definitely had enough.
Sam, I'm toasting!
You... no, you're
toasted plenty.
Sam, I'm not
through toasting.
I want to toast love and...
I want to toast commitment!
And I want to make a
toast to my whole...
(sobbing):
stupid, stupid life!
Isn't it romantic
Merely to be young...
Shut up and
leave me alone!
Hey, would you
cut me some slack?
I've had no formal training!
(mellow swing music playing)
Hey, there
Who?
You, with the stars
in your eyes
(womanly voice):
Are you talking to me?
Love never made
a fool of you...
Frasier, it's been two days.
I think it's time you stopped.
In the middle of my salute
to Adler and Ross?
I think not.
Hey, there
You on that
high-flying...
It's a dangerous combination:
a karaoke machine
and an obsessive personality
whose parents used to play
Broadway cast albums
to drown out their lovemaking.
Still can't get
a hold of Miss Howe?
No. It's been busy for hours.
Well, she is getting married
tomorrow.
She probably had a lot to do.
Maybe... find something
to wear.
Yes. It's not like
Si and Effie Kupperman
left her a wedding gown.
(chuckles wryly)
(imitates cat snarling)
She hasn't been here
for two whole days.
Do you...
do you think I ought
to go see her, Lilith?
I'm going to tell you
what I tell all my patients:
"What do you think?"
They pay you for that?
What do you think?
Oh, I don't... I don't think
she wants to talk to me.
Wh-Why, why don't you go over
and see how she's doing, Carla.
Yeah, great, I'll do that!
And while I'm there,
you can take my kids
to go see Smurfs on Ice.
All right.
I'll go see her.
Woody, lock up for me,
would you, buddy?
All right.
Everybody out!
Closing up!
SAM:
Woody!
Not now.
Closing time.
Could you be
more specific, Sam?
I'm not a mind reader.
(knocking)
REBECCA:
Hold your horsies.
(glass clattering)
Here I come.
(banging)
Ow! Oh!
Oh, well.
You're not the pizza boy...
but you're cute.
SAM:
Ooh!
How do you see
anything in here?
REBECCA:
Oh, let me just
open those drapes
and let in a
little light, okay?
(exhaling)
Why don't I, uh,
turn on a lamp here, huh?
(switch clicks)
Come on, honey.
Click.
(switch clicks)
Boy, you're not
going to get
your security
deposit back here.
You drinking again?
Certainly not.
I never stopped.
There.
Now I stopped.
Now I'm drinking again.
So...
You want to talk?
Is this about getting married
tomorrow?
You gettin' cold feet?
Certainly not.
I am perfectly prepared
to marry Robin
and spend the rest of my life
with him.
I'm just not particularly
looking forward to it.
You know, I don't get that.
You know, all you've
done the last two years
is talk about getting
married to this guy.
Yeah, well,
I'll tell you,
it is one thing...
to love somebody
who's serving time for you.
It's another thing
serving time with them.
Sam, I haven't even begun,
you know, to taste life.
I mean, I just discovered
this drinking thing.
Sweetheart...
(chuckles)
I can understand
the temptation.
I mean, after all, I'm
a recovering alcoholic.
I'm just not ready
for commitment yet.
Well, doubt's
part of any relationship.
I mean, look at me:
I-I was divorced.
You know,
I drink for a couple of days,
and you were an alcoholic.
I have a little bit of trouble
with a relationship,
and you were divorced.
Do you retain water in the
middle of the month, too, Sam?
Look, I'm just
trying to help you.
I mean, everybody
gets cold feet
when they're about
to get married,
but it's a pretty weeny
reason to start drinking.
Why did you start drinking?
I lost my curveball.
I am not drinking
because I have cold feet.
I am drinking because
I don't know if I love Robin.
Oh, wow.
Do you think
maybe you don't?
I don't know.
I just wish I had a little bit
more time, you know, to decide.
You don't think
there's any chance that
that, um, parole board
could keep him in prison
just a little while longer?
Listen, listen, listen.
If you don't love the guy, why
don't you just back out of this?
Oh, I'm supposed to tell
the richest man in the world
that I don't want to marry him?
No, he's not rich
anymore, remember?
That's right.
What's his number?
Come on. Come on.
Stop that.
I'm being serious here.
I am being serious,
too, Sam.
It's just that
I can't stop remembering.
I can't stop remembering
that one time...
in my life...
it was just so exciting.
Oh, boy.
I know where this is going.
Oh, God, I loved it, Sam.
Honey...
It was just so thrilling,
and it was magical, you know?
I know, I know.
And like every single nerve
in my body was alive,
and I was glowing.
God, it was like
the first time in my life
I was one with another being.
Once you have that,
you just don't forget.
I'll never forget the night
we made love.
I'm talking about when I was ten
and won first prize
in that horse show.
You know, but that sex deal
was good with you, too.
I mean, even having sex with you
is better than Robin.
Even that, huh?
So that's it...
isn't it?
I don't want to marry Robin.
(sniffles)
Well, I guess I won't be needing
this anymore.
Right now...
I made my decision.
Robin is history.
There.
(sighs)
It feels good.
All right.
Yeah.
Let's celebrate.
No, no, we don't
need to do that.
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
There is a better way
to celebrate, Sam.
Drop your pants.
What?
You heard me, buddy.
I... want... you.
Oh, no.
Sweet... sweetheart,
we-we can't do this.
Oh, yes, we can, Sam.
The train is pulling
into the station.
No, no...
All aboard.
Whoo, whoo.
I'm sorry, I-I
won't do this.
Why?
Well, first of all,
you've been drinking
a little bit and...
you know, a gentleman
has rules.
And second, you're kind
of repulsive right now.
You can't take it?
I'm gonna go home.
No, Sam, Sam, we have all night.
We've got tonight
Who needs tomorrow?
Let's make it last, babe
Let's fi... nd
The way.
Sam Malone...
I want you to get ready...
for the most exciting night
of your life.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3q8m5
Help other users to choose the best subtitles