Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Young man, a beer, please.
Hey... you're on
Sunday morning TV, aren't you?
Indeed.
Are you, uh,
David Brinkley?
No.
Sam Donaldson?
Give me a break.
Oh!
Aren't you the guy
who keeps the Gorgeous
Ladies of Wrestling
from tearing each
other's hair out?
You could say that.
Oh, man! Your money's
no good here.
Actually,
I'm John McLaughlin--
I'm the moderator
of a political roundtable
called The McLaughlin Group.
Oh. Well, that'll be $2.50.
(theme song begins)
¶ Making your way
in the world today ¶
¶ Takes everything you've got ¶
¶ Taking a break
from all your worries ¶
¶ Sure would help a lot
¶ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ¶
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always
glad you came ¶
¶ You wanna be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ¶
¶ You wanna go
where people know ¶
¶ People are all the same
¶ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ¶
(applause)
¶
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
¶
(cheering)
Good evening.
Welcome to Cheers 200.
I'm John McLaughlin.
A little more
than eight years ago,
(phone ringing)
a pseudo-intellectual
college student
walked into a bar
and met a recovering alcoholic
ex-relief pitcher
for the Boston Red Sox.
Hello?
Sam?
Are you Sam?
(mouth full):
Yes.
Yes, he's here.
Someone named Vicky.
No, no, no, no, no.
No. She knows you're here.
I told her you're here.
Well...
Now, look...
(mumbling)
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
He had to step out.
Where?
Well, um...
I think what happened is,
he, uh....
He had t...
he had to go to mime class.
That week, America was
supremely uninterested.
Cheers ranked #77
out of a possible
77 television shows.
(laughter)
Last season,
it was the #1 television show
in America.
On this, the occasion
of the 200th episode of Cheers,
we will be showing
some of the many highlights,
and lowlights,
of the first 199 episodes,
as well as talking
to the originators, the cast,
and the current caretakers
of the little bar in Boston
where everybody knows your name.
We'll be right back.
It's like I'm
in complete control
of people's destinies.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, like, I can make
their drinks too strong
so they get sick.
Uh-huh.
Or, uh, I can water 'em down,
so they're paying for nothing.
Yeah.
Or if I don't like
their attitudes,
I can spit in it.
(laughs)
Carla, you're not still upset
about that little argument
we had the other day?
You tell me.
Oh, uh, hey, Carla, listen,
I'm sorry about this morning
when I called you
a "sawed-off witch."
PEOPLE:
Norm!
George, you want to tell us
about Norm Peterson?
Well, uh, he hangs out in a bar.
(laughter)
He, uh...
he's got darned good writers.
Afternoon, everybody.
ALL:
Norm!
What's up, Norm?
My nipples--
it's freezing out there.
What are you up to, Norm?
My ideal weight,
if I were 11 feet tall.
Hey, Mr. Peterson, Jack Frost
nippin' at  your nose?
Yeah. Now let's get Joe Beer
nippin' at my liver, huh?
What's going on, Mr. Peterson?
Let's talk about what's
going in Mr. Peterson.
Hey, what's happening, Norm?
Well, it's
a dog-eat-dog world, Sammy,
and I'm wearing
Milk Bone underwear.
Norm's a very loyal guy.
Unfortunately, his priorities
are a little bit out of whack.
(clears throat):
He's loyal to the bar first,
and, uh, you know,
to his marriage...
somewhere down the line,
but he is loyal.
You can't go sneaking out nights
on somebody you love.
Woody, you have
to believe that truth and...
Norm, it's Vera.
I'm not here-- honesty are
the cornerstones of a marriage.
I promised Vera
I'd pick up some Chinese food.
Oh, that's nice
of you, Norm.
Well, I spilled it
on the floor this morning.
Sheesh! Women.
You can't live with 'em.
Pass the beer nuts.
Hey, Norm, how come you and Vera
never had any kids?
I can't, Coach.
Gee, I'm sorry, Norm.
I look at Vera, I just can't.
See you in the morning,
I guess, huh?
Yeah, I may be a little late.
Oh, that's okay.
I had a key made.
I came, I drank...
I stayed.
(laughter)
(deep groan)
What's the matter, Norm?
Aw, nothing.
Just my shorts are
binding up on me.
Just, uh, you know, stand up
and straighten 'em out a little.
Nah. I'll give 'em five minutes.
Sometimes they self-correct.
CARLA:
I've been down this road
a few times myself,
and take it from a pro:
there is one thing
you always have to do
before you tell a guy
you love him.
What's that?
Lose the mustache.
Rhea, tell us about Carla.
Well, she's, um, a survivor.
She's a realist.
She's very fertile.
(laughter)
I cannot let any man
touch me, talk to me or see me,
or I'll be shooting out kids
like a Pez dispenser.
Do you think that she's mean?
No. I don't think she's mean.
I think that she's honest.
Frasier, you're brilliant!
That is one of
the most brilliant ideas
you've ever had, and you've had
a lot of brilliant ideas.
Thank you, Carla.
See, Woody? It works.
Bonehead bought it.
Nothing wrong
with sweating.
I myself have perspired
once or twice.
We could grow rice.
Give me a little something
with hair on it.
Here I am.
So, uh,
you married?
Yes, quite happily.
Too bad. Could've been
my first Englishman.
Oh, no, no, no, wait.
There was that one other guy,
but he was so white,
I kept losing him
in the sheets.
Does everybody
like Carla?
Oh, yeah.
You have to.
(laughter)
Did Carla like Diane Chambers?
(laughs):
No.
No?
Suffice it to say,
he insists on making mountains
out of molehills.
He wants you to wear
a padded bra?
I can no longer
hold my tongue.
Want me to do it?
He has saved hundreds,
nay, thousands
of troubled marriages.
It's even rumored that he had
a hand in helping Chuck and Di.
Speaking of that,
why don't you upchuck and die?
Do you like Cliff?
No.
McLAUGHLIN:
You don't like Cliff?
No.
It's a little known fact that
42% of all deaths in America
are caused by accidents
in the home.
So were you.
Yeah, you'd never catch
a woman of mine
leading me around
by the nose.
No, but you might catch her
sunning herself on a rock.
What a pathetic display.
I'm ashamed God
made me a man.
I don't think God's doing a lot
of bragging about it, either.
CLIFF:
If you go back in history
and, uh, take every president,
you'll find that
the numerical value
of each letter
in their last name
was equally divisible
into the, uh,
year in which they were elected.
All right.
CLIFF:
See,
I figured it out,
and by my calculations,
uh, our next president
has to be named...
Yelnick McWaWa.
Who is Cliff Clavin?
Well, Cliff,
according to Cliff, would...
he'd be the wing nut that holds
Western civilization together.
(laughter)
He, uh...
according to me,
he'd just be a winged nut.
You know, you've got
a big mouth, Clavin.
Hey, he happens to be
right, you know.
Yeah, it's a genetic quirk
in the, uh, Clavin family
that we all have
two extra teeth.
Uh, you see, that's the
only way that we can prove
that we are the rightful heirs
to the Russian throne.
Hello in there, Cliff.
Tell me, what color is
the sky in your world?
You know, I, uh...
I happen to be a bit
of an expert on tapeworms.
It all goes, uh,
it all goes back
to my eighth-grade science fair.
You know, everybody else had
rabbits and guinea pigs.
I, uh, had a tapeworm.
Really?
Yeah, so I couldn't go.
Or was that, uh,
was that a ringworm?
Check, please.
Yeah, boy, boy, boy...
Me and parasites--
don't get me started.
John, is there, is there
a part of you in Cliff?
Oh, yeah, I, I, I am fascinated
by fascinating facts, yeah.
Is there a part
of Cliff in you?
Uh, I wear white socks.
(laughter)
NORM:
Well...
CLIFF:
Yeah...
I tell ya...
Is that, uh,
Cliff Clavin or is
that Don Ho, huh?
Ah...
Where ya been, buddy?
Some, uh, faraway
island resort?
Oh, easy mistake,
Norm, but, no,
I got this tan right
here in Beantown.
Is that at the new, uh,
Tan and Wash I've been hearing
so dang much about?
That's right, Normie.
And by the way, did you realize
that the tan first gained
popularity
in what is now known
as the Bronze Age?
Great, great,
well, I'm sold.
Oh, and, by the way, uh,
look how white I used to be.
McLAUGHLIN:
During the course of
the history of Cheers,
you lost a character.
You lost a man.
Right.
Nick Colasanto,
who played the part
of Ernie Pantuso,
the Coach.
Uh, Nickie was like a father.
I mean, he came...
He was the father
and Woody's the kid.
I mean, that was, uh...
Nicky was the... the sage.
He used to say
he used to play the character
like a 12-year-old.
He would sit and listen
to everybody like they made
complete sense.
I, I don't know
if you know the set,
but he's still,
he's still present.
We put a picture of Geronimo
that Nicky had
in his dressing room,
we put that on the upstage wall
of Cheers
so he's, uh, he's still present
and, uh...
He was a former coach
in professional baseball?
He was Sam's coach, yeah.
He had a record in the minor
league being hit by a pitch
more than any
other person...
(laughs)
I mean, what I'd do was,
I'd get up there
and lean my body
into the pitch, right?
And, well, sometimes I took one
right in the old melon, but...
I mean, I really...
I really made a science
out of it.
I became a master.
Well, here, try
to miss me.
Oh.
You ready?
Okay, here we go.
I'm not gonna get it
anywhere near him.
That's the whole point.
(soft thud)
(gasps)
Oh!
COACH:
I'm on my way
to first!
Whoo!
Nicky was amazing.
He was a director...
Accomplished director,
teacher...
A very, very bright man,
and he would, like,
he would drive on the lot,
and he, he'd say
that he'd get out of his car
and he'd, psst, turn that off.
And then, pshew, he was...
he was Coach from then on.
Cheers.
Yeah, just a sec.
Is there an Ernie Pantuso here?
SAM:
That's you, Coach.
Speaking.
Boy, oh, boy...
The damnedest thing.
I've been shivering all the way
over here.
Well, Coach,
you don't have a coat on.
It's 30 degrees outside.
Oh, thank God!
I thought I had malaria.
Whew!
Uh, Coach, I'm
having blackouts.
Kind of a nice break in the day,
isn't it, Sammy?
Do you remember
Nick, Shelley?
Dearly.
He was really Diane's only
friend, real friend.
He would listen to Diane,
and he would counsel her
and-and offer her a kind
of support and friendship
that didn't really
come out clearly
from many of the other members
in the bar.
DIANE:
Coach?
What do you do
when you are so furious
that you have to do something?
Well, I know you'll think
it's kind of crazy,
but, uh, I bang my head
on the bar.
Doesn't sound crazy to me.
It might do me
a lot of good right now.
Well, okay.
No! No, oh, don't!
But, uh, uh, you're so,
you're so beautiful, so...
Beautiful?
Daddy, you have been saying
that I'm beautiful
ever since I was
a very little girl.
But look at me!
Not as my father,
but like you're lookin' at me
for the first time,
and please, try to see me
as I really am.
Oh, my God! I...
I didn't realize how much
you looked like your mother.
I know.
I look exactly like her.
And Mom was not...
...comfortable
about her beauty.
But that's what made
her more beautiful.
Your mother grew
more beautiful
every day of her life.
She was really beautiful.
Yes! And so are you.
You're the most beautiful
kid in the whole world.
Thanks, Daddy.
LES CHARLES:
We wanted to create,
uh... there are...
there are in America
great neighborhood bars.
But not everybody has one,
and so we thought we'd give--
uh, for all those poor, deprived
people-- we'd give them one.
And that included ourselves.
We didn't have one.
So we created one--
a place that we would like to go
and spend time and, uh,
where everybody could go
one night a week and,
and be with friends.
(shrieking)
(shouting)
(all clamoring)
Come on! Carla!
Easy!
Yeah, I got her!
Let go! Oh!
Let go of me!
You get your hand out!
Just stop it!
You had the gall! Oh!
Just get...!
Whoa!
SAM:
Stop that!
Come on, you guys.
(shouting)
Whoa, whoa...
Oh, no! No!
CARLA:
Whoops!
(screaming):
No!
(groaning)
Oh, no!
(Diane shrieking)
Stop this immediately!
I have never been witness
to such a silly, soph...
Sam Malone...
kiss your butt good-bye!
(all yelling)
(Diane screams)
McLAUGHLIN:
When you conceived
of the relationship between
Diane Chambers and Sam Malone...
what was it?
I think that there
was an intensity
with the Sam and Diane,
uh, affair that was, uh...
McLAUGHLIN:
Dominating?
Yeah, very much so.
A really intelligent woman
would see
your line of BS a mile away.
You think so? Huh?
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Yeah, well, uh,
you know,
I've never met an
intelligent woman
that I'd want to date.
On behalf of the intelligent
women around the world,
may I just say... whew!
Well, I'll be darned.
What?
Nothing. I just, uh,
noticed something.
What?
Well, I guess I've, uh, I've
never looked into your eyes.
Something wrong with them?
No, I, uh... just don't think
I've ever seen eyes
that color before.
As a matter of fact,
I don't think
I've ever seen
that color before.
Yes, I have.
Where?
I was, uh, I was on a ski
weekend up at Stowe. I...
I was comin' in late one day,
uh, last person off the slope.
The, the sun had just gone down.
And the sky became
this incredible color.
I, I usually don't, uh,
notice things like that,
and I found myself kind of
walking around in the cold,
hoping that it wouldn't change,
wishing that I, I had somebody
there to share it with me.
Then afterwards I tried
to convince myself
that I'd imagined that color,
that...
that I hadn't really seen it.
That nothing on this earth
could be that beautiful.
Now I see I was wrong.
Wouldn't work, huh?
What?
An intelligent woman
would see right through that?
Oh? Oh!
In a minute.
Damn.
SAM
You are the nuttiest,
the stupidest, the phoniest
fruitcake I ever met!
You, Sam Malone, are the most
arrogant, self-centered son...
Shut up!
Shut your fat mouth!
Make me.
Make you?
My God, I'm, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna bounce you off
every wall in this office!
Try it and you'll be
walking funny tomorrow.
Or should I say funnier?
You know... you know, I always
wanted to pop you one.
Maybe this is
my lucky day, huh?
You disgust me!
I hate you!
Are you as turned on
as I am?
More!
Bet me.
Wh-Whenever you think
too much about something,
it loses all its sense.
I mean, obviously the only
reason why I'm with you
is because I lo...
What, Sam?
I said the reason why I'm
with you is 'cause I lo...
You lo...?
Well, you know,
you know what I mean.
Well, what's the matter?
Can't you say it?
Oh, of course I can.
I lo... I lo... I lo... I lo...
DIANE:
Do you know what the difference
is between you
and a fat, braying ass?
Nope.
The fat braying ass would.
Speaking of fat,
braying asses,
you're about to get
dumped on yours.
How dare you slap me!
Don't you ever hit me again!
Like hell.
You always think you
gotta get the last one in.
Oh, come on.
All right, all right, fine!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
All right, come on.
SAM:
All right, please, come on.
Let go.
Oh, what the hell?
Will you marry me?
No.
Oh, Diane, will you marry me?
(sobbing):
No, Sam.
Diane, will you marry me?
That didn't sound very sincere.
I'll be back here.
I will.
I'll see you in six months.
Okay?
Okay.
That's better.
(door closes)
Have a good life.
(piano playing "What'll I Do?")
¶
JOHN:
Frasier Crane--
what does he do for a living?
He's a psychiatrist.
What is Frasier's
philosophy of life?
He hopes he can heal
the human condition.
Come on, man!
Tell Diane you love her.
Let some fresh air and sunlight
in there!
Frasier?
What, Sam?
I don't like guys
touching my head.
Well, there's our next session.
Is there, uh,
some of you in him?
Sure.
I would like to heal
the world, yeah.
Have you notified
the world?
Uh, in my small way,
yeah.
(chuckles)
Is there some
of him in you?
Uh, well, we do walk the
same streets together now.
I am running with scissors!
You see, it's been
psychologically documented
that all human animals have a
neurotic hair-trigger response
to, uh, at least one of
the five sensory stimuli.
Well, it could be
anything, actually.
Well, let's see, sound of the
surf pounding against the shore.
The smell of honeysuckle
on a warm summer night.
The taste of a vintage
Chateau Neu d'pais.
Fire-red fingernails dancing
through your chest hair.
A black-lace teddy...
straining against
its fleshy cargo.
Frasier, man,
snap out of it.
In a minute, Sam.
Did psychiatrist
Frasier Crane
provide services
for Diane Chambers?
No.
No, that was,
that was my job.
When Diane left Sam,
and he started drinking again,
he was filling the void
that Diane left.
And Diane filled her emptiness
by toying with
and... destroying...
a man who's her cultural
and intellectual superior
in every way!
REBECCA:
Okay, kids, you say hi
to Binky!
KIDS:
Hi, Binky!
Binky, do your act.
I don't have an act.
I'm a psychiatrist.
NORM:
Uh-oh, frost warning.
Good afternoon,
Dr. Crane.
Dr. Sternin.
(clears throat)
What a lovely surprise.
I hope I can regard that
as civility
in light of today's situation,
rather than sarcasm
at my expense.
No, that was completely
at your expense.
What these two people, who are
such geniuses at romance,
are trying to do is to get you
to take your hair down,
thinking that it
will stimulate me
like some sort of
Pavlovian dog.
So why don't you
just oblige them,
get this silliness
over with
so we can get on
with our lives?
(sighs)
You mean like this?
Precisely.
You know what?
What?
I'm going to kiss you.
I'm gonna kiss you hard
and I'm going
to kiss you long.
But make no mistake
about it,
I am going to kiss you.
In fact, I'm going
to kiss you
like you've never...
WOODY:
Oh, boy, my Aunt Edna's
killer fudge brownies.
Oh, killers, huh?
Yeah, they're called that
because the first time
my Uncle Ford ever
smelled them baking,
he came running in from the
field and got hit by a combine.
He hung on
for a few days.
At the end,
he was just praying to die.
Well, eat up, everybody.
Hey, I don't know
about Indiana,
but around here,
when guys get together
to send another guy
off to his doom,
things can get
a little raunchy...
(chuckles)
You fellas ever
dress up farm animals
in women's clothing?
No.
Well, then
I'm one up on you.
Woody Harrelson,
tell us about Woody Boyd.
Uh, he likes other people,
you know,
and he, he likes connecting
with people,
and he doesn't really, uh, care
to, uh, own the bar
or anything one day.
He just wants to be a bartender
and live in the big city.
Woods, she likes to do her
cushion pushing on four wheels.
Miss Howe...
really?
You know, uh, back
where I come from,
we used to say something
about girls like that.
What?
Let's date them.
(chuckles)
Well, actually, Carla,
as a student of the theater,
I have to correct you.
What you were doing there
is not called acting.
It's called improvising.
Shut up, Woody.
Now, that would be directing.
I take it that there's a big
part of you in Woody Boyd.
Yeah, I would say
the virtue in me is, uh...
(laughing)
(chuckles)
No, I mean,
we're both very honest.
Miss Howe, I don't mean
to insult you,
but you're looking
kind of puny.
Have you lost weight?
Is this a setup?
Did Sam tell you to say that?
No, ma'am, I told myself
to say it.
Thank you, Woody.
That's the nicest thing
anyone said to me all week.
Your hair's been looking
kind of ratty, too.
Some people say that they...
they thought in your
last couple of episodes,
that you've been a little bit
harsher than you normally are.
Yeah, I agree,
by the way.
Shut up!
What's the use?
I don't care anymore.
Don't be bitter.
I'm not bitter, Sam.
I'm just consumed
by a gnawing hate
that's eating away at my gut
until I can taste the bile
in my mouth.
Well, I guess
I am a little bitter.
Either that or I'm coming down
with something.
Does anybody have a Tic Tac?
WOMAN:
I was wondering
if Woody could perhaps
recite the lyrics
to "The Kelly Song"?
Let me get in the right key.
Okay.
¶ Kelly, my darling,
you are my sunshine ¶
(piano plays)
¶ When we're together,
I feel fine ¶
¶
¶ Your smile is so lovely,
your hair is so clean ¶
¶ You make me feel that
the whole world is mine ¶
¶ Kelly, Kelly, Kelly, Kelly
¶ K-E-L-L-Y
¶ Why?
Because you're... ¶
¶ Albania, Albania
¶ You border on the Adriatic
¶ Good night, ladies
¶ We're going to leave you now ¶
¶ Time to rap
about a controversy ¶
¶ Gonna take a stand,
won't show no mercy ¶
¶ Lotta folks say
jocks shouldn't be ¶
¶ Doin' the sports news on TV ¶
¶ I don't want to hear
the latest score ¶
¶ From a punchy old broadcasting
school board ¶
¶ So get your scores
from a guy like me ¶
¶ Who knows what it's like
to have a groin injury ¶
¶ G-g-groin, g-g-groin
¶ G-g-groin injury
Boola!
The first night of the show,
I mean, I really realized--
they introduced
the cast members--
and I felt the void
from the audience.
It was sort of like
a silent, horrible void...
to me, I mean,
maybe I was the only one
seeing it, hearing it.
But it was...
it was for Shelley.
So right when I...
after I came out,
and they, you know,
they were nice to me,
yeah, yeah, you know.
"Big deal, we're not gonna
like you no matter what you do."
(laughing)
I will prove it to you.
I will dispel the myth
that you turn my stomach.
I will give you a little kiss.
Here.
There.
Now, what category
am I in?
Yes? No?
Oh, jeez, boy, why do I
even bother with you?
Whew!
Definite maybe.
I heard that.
You said "maybe."
We had an idea for a scene
where she's in the office
and Sam comes in the office.
They've got a bet that if
he catches her with a cigarette,
she will go to bed with him.
A-ha!
Oh, uh, hey, uh,
where's the pool table?
Oh, wrong room.
She put a lit cigarette
in her mouth,
and all of a sudden we went,
"This woman has hidden talents!"
Oh, Norm, I need your help.
Oh, you just started.
You're gonna do fine.
Things are gonna turn around,
I swear.
No, you idiot,
my hair's stuck to the wall!
It's a huge risk.
Take it.
I'm moving to Tokyo.
I'm gonna take over
the Japanese division.
I leave tonight.
Yes, darling, yes!
Oh...!
Can I have my drink?
You know, you men
are all alike.
Yeah, so where was I?
Uh, you were engaged to one of
the richest men in the world.
Could I just have my check?
Are you a man?
Sure.
I'm gonna have to break it off
with Robin.
Well, it's the
right thing to do.
I'll just say to him, um...
"That's it, sweet baby."
I think the two of us are
cut out of the same cloth.
I think that we,
perhaps, have a...
a friendship in the,
in the making.
We may not see it yet,
but I think we have
a deep, deep friendship.
I think we're
very similar.
Do you think you
share value systems?
Well, I think
we're equally shallow.
Mr. Colcord.
Rebecca, I'll be brief.
You were very
understanding about that
little incident
back in my limo,
and I think that kind
of understanding
should be rewarded.
So, I'd like you to have this.
(scoffs)
(whispers):
It's gorgeous!
No!
I should like to point out
that if I had offered
this bracelet
to my chargé d'affaires,
she would have snapped it up
in a blur.
Heh, I admire your standards.
You know,
this definitely
puts you in the lead.
Must go.
Would you care to join me?
Did you hear that?
I am winning!
I'm winning!
No! Hey, come...
listen!
Listen to me
for a second here.
Come on, you've given up
something very valuable
and very important.
You're gonna regret this
the rest of your life.
Oh! You're right.
I will take that bracelet.
SAM:
Oh, it's not just
losing the job.
It's that I was, you know,
taken advantage of.
I know. I know.
You know,
that I was used.
That I was just...
you know, manipulated
by somebody who just
cynically wanted to get
something from me.
Malone, what are you doing?
I'm feelin' bad.
No, you are feeling
pretty good.
Okay, I admit it.
I'm not a sad guy.
I'm a happy, horny guy.
What is Sam's
philosophy of life?
Service the queen bee,
you know, to...
Look at the two of you!
No, look at the three of us!
Let's look at the two
of you again.
Can we get a couple
of piña coladas over here?
Sure thing. Let me just
finish makin' this margarita.
So, anyway, Margarita...
All I can think about is getting
home and jumping into bed.
Need anybody to break your fall?
Guess who.
Uh-oh.
I'll give you a hint.
Vermont ski lodge,
a roaring fire and baby oil.
Uh... could you, uh,
be more specific?
Great.
What time will you
be getting off?
You've been with a lot of women.
No, I have not.
There have not
been that many women.
Uh, that gets exaggerated
here in the bar.
There haven't been
that many, really.
How many have there been?
Well, I don't know.
Maybe, uh, four hun...
(gasps):
Oh...!
Honeys, honeys.
Four honeys.
You know, Sam,
the church does
recommend chastity
to unmarried people.
(chuckles)
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're serious, uh...
For the sake of our friendship,
I am just gonna resist
my sexual urges
and that's all there
is to it.
Now, come here.
There.
All right.
You know that
I loved Evan Drake
since the first time
I met him.
I'm sorry. This is not working.
Hot fire below.
I can't imagine
not doing this... show.
Um...
I think the thing
I notice is that, uh,
when I walk around,
the incredible, uh, the faces
of the people that look back
when they recognize Cheers.
That, that look
and that face is, uh...
coming back at you.
Uh, it's such a privilege
to walk around
in that atmosphere
that it is, uh...
it's... it's magical.
¶ Making your way
in the world today ¶
¶ Takes everything you've got ¶
¶ Taking a break
from all your worries ¶
¶ Sure would help a lot
¶ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ¶
¶ All those nights
when you've got no lights ¶
¶ The check is in the mail
¶ And your little angel
hung the cat up ¶
¶ By its tail...
¶ And your third fiancé
didn't show ¶
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always
glad you came ¶
¶ You wanna be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles are
all the same ¶
¶ You wanna be where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ You roll out of bed,
Mr. Coffee's dead ¶
¶ The morning's looking bright ¶
¶ Morning's looking bright ¶
¶ And your shrink
ran off to Europe ¶
¶ And didn't even write ¶
¶ And your husband
wants to be a girl ¶
¶ Be glad there's one place
in the world ¶
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always
glad you came ¶
¶ You wanna go
where people know ¶
¶ People are all the same
¶ You wanna go where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ Everybody knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always
glad you came ¶
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ Everybody knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always
glad you came ¶
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ Everybody knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always
glad you came. ¶
I'll tell you what you do.
Why don't you...
Hey, would you
get out of here?!
Go on!
Cheers to Cheers on your 200th.
Looking forward
to Cheers' 400th.
(coughs)
Bye-bye.
(theme song playing)
(chattering)
Thank you all for coming.
Thank you.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/wzfn
Help other users to choose the best subtitles