Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Hey, Cliffie.
What you doing?
Uh, writing a letter
of application for the Eco pod.
What the heck's the Eco pod?
It's a totally
self-contained environment
located in a mile-wide bubble
underneath the desert floor.
Yeah.
It's gonna be inhabited
by the best and the brightest
of the, uh, human species,
so I-I thought I'd apply.
They're gonna have a zoo
in there, too?
Yeah. Yeah, very
funny, Carla.
You'll be laughing out of
the other side of your face
when they make me Postmaster
General of the Eco pod.
Actually, the Eco pod
does have some scientific merit.
It was designed
by a colleague of Lilith's,
Dr. Louis Pascal.
It will serve as a prototype
for the colonization of space.
Plus which,
the grant money is incredible.
I hear
Pascal's driving a Lexus.
Boy, I sure hope I get a shot
at being sealed
up in that thing.
Say, would a petition help?
It might.
Hey, I'll sign that.
No! I'm first!
Okay...
Boy.
(weepy): You guys are the best
friends a fellow ever had.
(theme song begins)
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Sammy, when is Woody getting
back from his honeymoon?
I've been working
a double shift for two weeks,
and I'm exhausted.
Oh, thank you. Come again.
Oh, my God, who am I?
Uh-oh. Isn't that Henri,
that jerk who's always trying
to steal Kelly from Woody?
You know, I just
don't like that guy.
Con artist.
Yeah, Mister Frenchie
Two-Face.
Hello, fellows!
Hey, Henri!
How's it going?
Hey, Henri,
what can I do for you?
Uh, I need a favour, Sam.
I need you to tell
the Unemployment Office
that I applied for a job,
and you turned me down.
(laughs) Sammy, come here.
What?
Listen, why don't we hire the guy?
That would help me out a lot.
Oh, I-I don't know
about that.
Henri, did you ever tend bar?
Well, yes, but...
CARLA: You're hired.
No, no,
but you are missing the point.
You are to turn me down
and send me on my way so that
I might spend my afternoon
watching television.
I'm sorry, man,
but I need the help.
Thanks.
(speaks French)
Okay, give me an apron.
Oh, mon dieu.
I am filling Woody's shoes.
Oh, the pressure.
Well, Henri, let me be
your first customer, okay?
I would like a beer, please,
and put it on my tab.
Aren't you supposed
to pay when served?
Well, as long
as we're bringing up the matter
of debt, Frenchie,
let me bring up a
couple little things
called World War I
and World War II, okay?
Now, why don't we
subtract the cost of my puny little beer
from the enormous
debt that you owe us?
Okay, okay.
Hey, uh, you came down pretty
hard on him, didn't you, Norm?
Damn it, Cliffie.
My dad was almost in the army.
(whistling)
(indistinct crowd chatter)
Say, can I bum a cigarette?
Yeah, I got one right...
Oh, God! Sam,
I swear, I swear.
I can't believe you...
No, this is the only
one that I've had!
You promised me you would
not smoke in the office.
We had a little problem
with that, remember?
Ding-a-ling-a-ling.
Whoo! Whoosh!
I know, I know, and
I've tried to quit,
but it's too hard-
I just can't!
Yeah, well, you need
some professional help.
Oh, wait a minute.
Yeah, here we go.
"Smokers Anonymous,"
"Smoke Beaters."
Oh, yeah, yeah.
"Doctor Kluger's
No-Mercy Clinic."
Wait a minute.
Let me see that.
Here we are.
Sam, he doesn't even have
an ad; it's just his name.
How about going with this one
with the cute
little smoking kitty?
Yeah, uh, is this,
uh, Dr. Kluger?
Well, my name's Sam Malone,
and I have an employee
that needs to stop smoking
right this very minute.
Can you help me out?
Yeah, tell me
about your program.
Oh! Ow!
Boy, I bet that hurts, huh?
Wow, I bet you really
have to be a doctor to do that, don't you?
Uh, no, no.
It sounds terrific.
Yes, I can.
All right, great!
Thank you very much.
Sounds good.
Oh, yeah.
I'll fit it in
in my spare time.
Maybe I'll stop by next week.
No, you don't understand, hon.
We got to get you up
to the sidewalk right now.
They're sending
the, uh, Kluger van.
Oh, yeah.
Van?
Oh, yeah. Come on.
Kluger van?
It'll be good for you.
You'll be all right.
(distant phones ringing)
So,
you're the girl
who likes to smoke.
You don't intimidate me.
I've been to a million
of these places,
and they don't work.
I'm out of here.
Oh, well, fine. Go.
You're free to leave.
No doorknob.
(laughs)
Yeah, that's right, Miss Howe.
Because you have the key,
and the key is discipline.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm scared.
Why don't you just save
yourself some time
and unlock the door?
Uh... all right,
Miss Howe.
Relax. Have a seat.
(chuckles)
Why don't you have a cigarette?
In fact...
why don't you have,
a thousand cigarettes?
Now...
you are going to smoke
until you can smoke no more.
But I predict you will
not get past 50.
No one has ever gotten past 50.
I had 50 in the van.
Oh, well,
I can see this is going
to be a challenge.
All right, hold my calls.
And so you can
imagine my embarrassment
when I made two dates
for the same night.
Uh, what happened when
your two lovelies arrived?
Was there a cat fight?
Oh please, tell me
there was a cat fight.
Of course.
There was a big cat fight.
They were very, very naughty.
I don't even know why I kept
letting them up on the bed.
Henri, where was the strangest
place that you ever...
Oh, that would have to be, uh,
ah, during a performance
in the balcony
at the Paris Opera.
And believe me,
it wasn't over
until the fat lady sang.
Very impressive.
(chuckles)
And what about you, Sam?
You're supposed to be
a great ladies' man?
All right, let's see,
the strangest place,
that'd have to be,
uh, the back of a car.
Well, that's not so strange.
The car's on an
assembly line, Henri.
You played with me, Sam.
Hey, I like you.
It's nothing personal.
As a matter of fact,
I think of you
as kind of a...
young Sam Malone.
Uh, don't you mean, you're
kind of, uh, an old Henri?
No, I don't.
Well, but why should
we argue the point
when we can settle it in battle?
(chuckling):
What do you mean?
I suggest a little competition.
All right, here's what we do.
We shall collect phone numbers
from beautiful women.
Whoever has the most phone
numbers at midnight
will be acknowledged as the
world's greatest ladies' man.
That's a great idea.
Hey, take him, Sammy!
Yeah, put him in his place.
Don't listen to this.
It's a stupid idea.
HENRI:
Oh...
Do I hear a scaredy-cat's tune?
Would you grow up, Henri?
Scaredy-cat, scaredy-cat,
scaredy-cat.
Hey, hey, stop that.
Hey, please, will ya?
Maybe ten years ago I would
have taken this silly bet.
But I'm, I'm older,
and I'm a little wiser.
Oh, well, maybe
you're right, Sam.
Maybe we don't need to compete.
(sighs)
I'll simply be king of ladies' men
and you'd be the mayor
of Scaredy-Cat Town.
You'd better hurry.
I am about to get
my first number.
Yeah, well, he can get
all the numbers he wants.
I'm not going to
stoop to his level.
Bravo, Sam.
You handled that very well.
It's good to see that
you've evolved
beyond the playboy mentality
of bedding every woman you meet.
Times have changed and you've
wisely changed with them.
I applaud that.
Oh, well, I appreciate that.
Thanks. Thanks very much.
Well, the king
of babes is dead.
What the hell are
we supposed to do now?
Norm.
Yeah.
Tell the bartender
I need a vodka-rocks.
Sammy, Carla needs a
vodka-rocks and a beer.
Carla, will you cut it out with
this "tell the bartender" stuff?
It's me, Sam.
Sam is dead.
He died, when he wouldn't take
the challenge from Henri.
You know, that's just childish.
Can we please just talk
about anything
besides this damned bet?
Yeah. Okay, how about this?
What would, uh, Metropolis
be like if Superman retired?
Oops! One thing wrong
with that scenario.
Superman gives a damn.
I've got two more numbers, Sam.
Yeah, well, I'm not
playing, Henri.
You will, Sam, you will.
Yeah? What makes
you think so?
Because I know you, Sam.
Deep down you're a, uh-uh,
babe-hound just as I am.
Admit it.
With every phone
number I catch, you die a little inside.
You can deny what you are to
the others, but not to me.
Come, Sam, come over
to the dark side!
Just go fill
a pretzel bowl, will you?
Okay. Okay.
But after they're filled-
come to the dark side!
Normie, now that Sammy's dead,
you realize we're gonna
have to live vicariously
through Henri?
No, Cliffie.
Just say we stopped living
vicariously through others, huh?
What do you say we get
off our duffs for once,
and live ourselves, so
that some other poor slubs
can live vicariously
through us? Huh?
What do you say we...
(laughs) Oh, shoot!
Damn, I nearly got
through it, too!
You were good.
Yeah.
I thought you were gonna do it!
You are the most
beautiful woman
I have ever seen.
It would make
my life worth living
if only I could have
your phone number.
WOMAN:
Sorry.
Nothing personal.
I just don't like French guys.
Oh...
(coughs)
(with American accent):
Well, uh, that's, uh,
that's just an affectation.
I'm Chuck from Portland.
I-I just figured
you're so sophisticated
that you-you wouldn't
have anything to do
with plain old me.
You should have more
confidence, Chuck.
Maybe this will help
your self-esteem.
(with French accent):
I got another one.
Thank you.
Sammy!
I am thrashing you soundly.
You better hurry!
You'll never catch up!
Look at Sammy
just standing there.
Maybe Henri's right.
Maybe he is a...
(French accent): scaredy-cat.
You guys don't get it, do you?
You know, it's...
I've done all this
babe-chasing stuff.
All right, here-here's
what it is.
It's like- it's like watching
The Three Stooges.
You know?
You watch the early ones
with Curly,
and they-they were magic!
And then- then you watch
the later ones, you know,
where they're using the same
jokes with Curly Joe,
and it just breaks your heart!
See, what I'm saying is...
I guess, you know,
you-you've got to move
with the times.
That's all.
Well, listen to the scaredy-cat
knocking Curly Joe.
I got another one, Sam!
Hey! Hey! The whole issue
is closed, Henri.
I'm not taking the bet.
Oh, very well, I give up.
I won't bother you again.
After all, what can I expect
from an American?
You are all fat, lazy,
stupid.
All you want to do is watch TV,
eat fast food
while your easy women
are scooped up
by handsome foreigners
like myself.
That tears it!
You've just drawn blood
on the US of A, pal!
Cliff, calm down.
Calm down, nothing!
Sammy might be missing
in action,
but on behalf of
this great nation,
I'm gonna go out there
and collect more
telephone numbers
than that sleazy Frenchman!
What about it, men?
Are you with me?
You know,
I'm usually afraid of girls,
but it's for America!
Me, too!
Then let's go!!
Hey, fellows, fellows, fellows!
All right, please,
take your seats.
Okay, Henri, you're on.
Carla, get the babe kit.
(gasps)
Not the babe kit!
Sam, are you sure?!
Yeah.
Oh, but, Sammy,
he's just a kid!
He didn't know!
Maybe it's time
he grew up, Carla.
Oh, but Sammy,
you told me never to get the babe kit!
Henri, you shouldn't have
brought America into this.
Ooh! The babe kit!
I'm shaking!
(laughs)
What is this babe kit?
Tell me.
Tell me!
ALL: Scaredy-cat, scaredy-
cat, scaredy-cat, scaredy-cat!
Okay, Carla, I'm ready.
Bring in the kit.
Before you open this thing,
I want you to know
this is a one-shot deal,
tonight only.
In this box
is the Sam Malone I used to be.
Sammy, if you've outgrown
all this stuff,
why do you keep it?
I thought maybe one day
I'd have a son.
(gasps)
Sam! Oh!
Sam!
The first edition of your
little black book.
Yeah.
Oh!
(gasps)
Your Members Only jacket!
Oh, Sammy, a picture
of you and Elvis!
Yeah, yeah.
The chicks really love that.
What kind of cologne is that?
It's a special blend;
Old Spice, Hai Karate
and something that takes spots out.
I'm not really sure.
Well, I'll leave
you to prepare.
Yeah.
Every time I think I'm out,
they pull me back in!
So, I wanted to be an artist.
The old man wouldn't have it.
Off to medical school.
I could never please him.
Aw. Not you, with all
the important work you do?
Well, it was never enough.
You poor, poor man.
Mm.
Oh, watch it.
Don't get ashes on my diploma.
Oh.
Hey, guys!
Hey.
All right, Fras.
Say what's the, uh,
tote board for?
I thought Sam wasn't gonna take
that bet.
Well, he wasn't,
but then Henri turned it
into a big grudge match...
France versus the USA.
At the last hour,
Sam stepped in for our side.
Damn, and I missed it!
I was home teaching
my kid to read!
I could kick myself!
Thanks a lot, sweetheart.
I-I'll give you a
call next week.
You know, I think
the two of us could be
very special
together, Michelle!
Or should I say,
uh, number eight? Yeah!
(bell dings)
ALL (chanting):
USA! USA! USA! USA!
Wait-wait-wait.
Oh, my God!
Is it really you?
Uh, yeah.
Hi.
How long has it been?
Oh I love what you did
with your hair! It's great!
Thank you.
Are you still going
with, uh... Oh, shoot.
Steve?
Yeah. Steve, right.
No, no,
apparently, he wasn't ready
to make a commitment.
Is that Steve or what?
(both laugh)
That's right.
God, you look wonderful!
Hey, give me a hug.
It's great to see you.
Great to see you.
Wait, this is crazy!
This is crazy!
Here, look, give
me your number.
I don't want to lose
touch with you again.
You know, I really meant
to call you a couple of times.
Here.
Well, shame on you for not.
Give me another hug.
All right.
Bye.
Bye-bye. See you later.
Sammy, who was that?
How the hell should I know?
ALL:
USA! USA! USA!
So how many orphans
did you save?
Oh, 15, 16 if you include
their little puppy.
You went back in
to save a puppy?
Well, he was an orphan, too.
Oh!
My card.
HENRI: Oh, thank you.
Uh, could you push
that down for me?
Oh, sure.
How am I doing, Carla?
Well, it's all tied up
with, uh, two minutes left.
No sweat.
Oh, that's what I like to hear.
The old Sammy's back!
Oh!
I can't believe it!
Excuse me, miss, have you seen
a, an Olympic gold medal
from the decathlon?
I hate to lose it.
It was part of a set.
But I'll tell you something,
I would give them all up
for a shot at your phone number.
Look, I find you very amusing
and, uh, I appreciate
all this flattery,
but if this is just some bar
pick-up, I wish you wouldn't.
I'm just coming off
a bad relationship
and I'm very vulnerable
right now.
Oh, well, I'm, uh, I'm sorry.
I didn't know that.
Uh, actually, I'm, I'm
not an Olympic athlete.
(softly):
Sam, hurry!
Uh, I'm a secret agent.
Uh... I'm sorry.
You were right the first time.
It's a sleazy bar pick-up.
Yeah.
Forgive me.
It was very childish.
Good luck to you.
Thanks.
Yeah. Sorry.
(clock rings)
Aw, shoot.
I guess Henri wins.
I win! I win!
France has won!
There's something
you never hear.
Well, Henri, you won
fair and square.
Congratulations.
Yes, I did, Sam,
and on behalf of Frenchmen everywhere,
let me just say...
(blows raspberry)
(laughs)
Well, thank you.
How very gracious of you.
Shame on you, Sam.
Shame on you!
You threw back the tying babe
just because she
was vulnerable.
The old Sammy would have kept on
pushing till he got the number.
Well, maybe I'm just
not the old Sammy anymore.
No, I guess you're not.
Uh, excuse me.
Yeah?
Listen, I just wanted
to tell you that
I, uh, appreciate you being
such a gentleman back there.
Oh, well...
You know, I don't meet
many men who are like that.
You're welcome.
Good luck to you.
Hey, what are you doing
later on tonight?
Uh, I thought you wanted
to be alone.
What about all that
vulnerable stuff?
Oh, that was just a line I use
to find out
what kind of man I'm dealing with.
(laughs) Good for you!
Hey, you guys, you
have to meet this guy.
He is such a gentleman.
Oh, hi.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, yeah, and he's cute too.
Oh.
Listen, we're gonna go out.
Do you want to come along?
It's a lot more fun with four.
Yeah.
Look, there's one thing
that you should know.
We do everything together.
Everything?
Everything.
Yeah.
Well!
Ladies, ladies.
Uh, Carla, uh, would you close
the bar for me?
Uh, oh, Henri, uh,
congratulations on that, uh,
that, uh, phone number
thing we were doing.
Okay, ladies,
right foot!
(laughs)
ALL:
USA! USA!
USA!