CARLA: Hey, Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Afternoon, Woody!
Oh, hiya, Mr. Twitchell.
If it isn't Walter Q. Twitchell,
the man who put the "nie" in weenie.
You South Central Branch types
are all alike--
wisenheimers.
Good Lord, Miss Agnes!
You're wearing your postal keychain
and you're not on active duty?
Well...
That's a direct violation
of postal regulations.
I'm filing a report on you.
Oh, yeah? Yeah.
I'd love to see the supervisor's face
when he calls me out on the mat
and I whip out this little baby.
Heh? Care to take a peep
at the old French peeper here, Twitch?
I warn ya, it's, uh, pretty hot stuff.
You're a sick man, Clavin.
(all laughing)
What are you...?
Oh, nice shiner there, Twitch.
Yeah, they could never pass up
a chance to sneak a peek
at Natalie in her nightie.
TWITCHELL: Nightie?!
Wasn't wearing anything I could see.
Huh?
TWITCHELL: Revenge is sweet.
Here's your mail.
Have a nice...
(piano plays)
♪ Making your way in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like to get away♪
♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always glad you came ♪
♪ You want to be where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You want to go where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
(sighs)
Are you developing a slow leak, Diane?
No.
I have a problem.
I just don't know who to talk to.
Oh.
Well, how about me?
I don't think that would
be appropriate in this case.
You see, it's a romantic problem.
Oh.
Considering our past, I don't think
you could possibly
maintain your objectivity.
Oh, come on.
Give it a shot.
Very well.
As you know, last week,
I was substituting as
a teaching assistant
at the college and...
it seems that one of the students
has fallen in love with me.
Marry him. See!
Sam,
in this case, the smitten youth
is particularly good-looking.
Ah.
No, make that
exceptionally good-looking.
All right.
No, make it
Greek-god-like.
The problem is that he's very persistent
and with his beauty and youthful ardor,
I find myself inexplicably
drawn to him.
He's asked me out several times.
Now, I don't want to encourage him,
but on the other hand, I'm tempted.
What do you think I should do, Sam?
I'm sorry. I got sidetracked there.
I was looking at my foot.
Sam, please.
As you know, I'm one who prides herself
on her attraction to the inner man,
but every once in awhile,
someone comes along that
makes you go, "zowie."
Oh, stop it, will ya?
You're just trying to make me jealous.
Your being jealous was the
farthest thing from my mind...
...although,
now that you bring it up,
any sane man would be jealous
of Lance Apollonaire.
Oh, come on.
If you're gonna make a guy up,
at least give him a name
that doesn't sound
like a bad aftershave.
I knew it was a mistake to talk to you.
I'll just have to deal
with this on my own.
Rest assured, though,
that the last thing I need
is to become that young
man's "Mrs. Robinson."
Wouldn't that be Mrs. Apollonaire?
No, Woody.
Mrs. Robinson was a... Yes, it would.
Well, top of the day, everybody,
and what a fine day it is, too, huh?
Why the good spirits, Mr. Clavin?
Well, uh, you guys ever hear
of the Knights of the Scimitar?
Yeah, it's one of those lodges, right?
The lodge, Sammy.
You know, it's always,
uh, been a dream of
mine to become a member.
Well, yesterday, I made it.
You guys are looking at a Knight.
Hey, that's great, man.
Thanks... Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You know, uh, Dad himself was a Knight.
When I was a kid, I used
to sneak up into his room
when he was out at work and,
uh, try on his turban and sword.
And unless I miss my guess,
you completed the outfit
with your mother's bra and high heels.
Carla, this is serious.
It's no easy task
getting into the Knights.
Oh, sure, as the son
of an alumnus, I was,
uh, guaranteed full membership,
but, uh, well, hey, my oath does
not permit me to say any more.
Thank God.
Yeah.
But the best part is...
Your oath, Clavin, your oath.
No, no, this stuff's permissible, Carla.
Oh, shut up, anyway.
Well, oh, well, so don't listen!
Hey, look, uh, listen, you guys.
The best part is that, uh,
you know, now that I'm a member,
I can get all you guys in.
Huh? You know,
of course it's gonna
have to be one at a time.
Now, uh, I figured out a fair
way to do the choosing, okay?
Now I'm thinking of a number
between one and ten.
Whoever has the closest wins.
Uh, Norm, you first.
Two million and 12.
Two million 13.
Two million 14.
Well, the number was four.
Norm's closest with two million 12.
Darn! I was gonna say four.
I shoulda stuck with my first instinct.
Cliffy, uh, thanks a lot,
but I-I'm just not interested.
You know, I guess I'm an example
of the old adage, "I'd never join a club
that would have someone like you
as a member," you know?
That's great.
Hey, Normie, Normie,
you know, the Knights,
they got a lot of, uh, you know,
bankers, lawyers, and assorted
captains of industry down there.
Yeah, so?
Well, so, they're
gonna need accountants,
and, uh, God knows
you could use a few clients.
Yeah, I've heard those places
are great for making contacts.
Yeah.
My business has been down just a bit
this past year.
There you go.
Woody, give me the horn, will ya?
Oh, boy. Hey,
you're gonna love it down
at the lodge, you know.
After a hard day's work,
it's a great place to unwind.
Yeah, wearing those turbans,
you probably need a place to unwind.
You know, unwind.
(laughs)
Turbans?
How they're all wound
up around your head
and you gotta unwind 'em?
Hey, uh... good one, Woody.
I was voted class clown.
You should be proud.
Yeah, I was only running
for class president.
Oh, Diane, will you do me a favor
and run up and get some change
from Melville's, please?
Oh.
What, what are you doing?
Lance is definitely taller than you are.
For a while there, I
thought you were taller,
but I see why I was mistaken.
Your shoulders are less broad,
thus giving you
the illusion of greater height.
I promised not to bring up
this Adonis-like
creature, didn't I? Sorry.
No, no, hey, don't be sorry
about a little fantasy.
I mean, I'm not sorry about the fantasy
I had a couple of hours ago.
By the way, how many nurses
do you think can fit in
a standard-size hot tub?
Sam, I assure you, Lance is not a fantasy,
and the feelings he inspires
are very real, too.
Change.
Not for you or any man.
No, no, Diane.
Change: Nickels, dimes, quarters.
Can I ask you a question here, Carla?
Mm-hmm.
Who's the handsomest man you know?
Robert Redford.
No, no, he's a movie star.
I mean someone you really know.
Robert Redford.
You don't know Robert Redford.
Yes, I do.
How come you never mentioned it?
If you were the only woman in Boston
he was messing around with,
would you tell anybody?
Okay, all right, besides Robert Redford.
I mean, some... somebody
you see in the city here.
Who's the handsomest
guy you see in the city?
Um, Dwight Evans.
No, not-not an athlete.
Somebody that you see every day.
My butcher.
In this bar, Carla.
Well, uh...
Standing next to you,
getting very angry.
Well, that would be you, Sam.
Well, why do you
put me through this stuff?
Put you through what?
Oh, hey, uh, Woody.
Come here for a second, will ya?
Uh, let me ask you a question.
Who, uh, who's the
handsomest guy you know?
Oh, that's easy--
Carla's butcher.
Evening, everybody.
ALL: Norm!
What's the latest, Mr. Peterson?
Zsa Zsa marries a millionaire.
Peterson drinks a beer.
Film at 11:00.
Hey, uh, Normie, you're supposed to be
at your interview down at the lodge.
Oh, yeah, I've already been, Cliff.
Already... That took what, 15 minutes?
Yeah, something like that.
CLIFF: Oh, uh, so,
did you get to meet
the, uh, High Sultan?
Good guy he was. Yeah.
Oh, well, so tell me,
what'd you say to him?
Uh, something like, uh, "Hi, High."
CLIFF: That's great, Norm.
I told you to be friendly, not flippant.
You know, frankly,
this just doesn't bode
at all well for you.
(telephone rings)
Cheers.
It's for you.
Hmm. It's probably those guys.
They said they were gonna call.
Yeah, like they called Joan of Arc
before they turned
her into French toast.
Now look, look.
Just treat this guy
with respect, all right?
Hello.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Hi, High.
Yeah.
Great.
Oh, no, no, no. No apology necessary.
That's okay. Sure.
All right, bye.
Here. You blew it.
You got nobody to blame
but yourself, Norm.
No, Cliffie, he just, uh, apologized
for making me wait so long.
I'm, uh, I'm a Knight.
Oh! Great!
Congratulations.
How's that for the old Clavin clout, eh?
Evening, Sam.
Hey, Frasier.
What's with your voice?
Oh, I spent the afternoon
screaming at a patient.
Oh.
What, what kind of therapy is that?
No, it's not therapy.
He burned a hole in my carpet.
Anyway...
how you doing, Sam, old man?
You know, Frasier, I, uh,
I don't like that
phrase "old man" anymore.
Uh, I-I prefer "buddy."
Oh, well, how you doing, Sam, old buddy?
Look, is, uh, something bothering you?
Well, yeah.
Diane's made up some guy who's supposed
to be great-looking,
just to get me riled.
Only I could care less
about the whole thing.
Well, good for you, Sam.
You know, the old Sam
would've rambled on and on
about how jealous he isn't,
proving only that he really is.
Right.
I mean, I could give
a rat's rear what Diane does
or who she does it with.
And I certainly am not jealous
about some college punk kid.
And even if I were,
which I'm not...
Call me at the office.
Hey, Sammy, you want to see a sap?
Sure, why not?
That's me, Carla. Uh-huh.
But a great-looking sap, right?
Not bad. Why?
Not bad?
He's a killer.
And I can't believe,
with a mug like that,
you're letting Diane do a number on you.
What are you talking about?
Oh, come on, she's just trying
to make you jealous,
and you're sucking it up
like a Hoover deluxe.
No, I'm not. I mean, first of all,
I don't believe this Lance guy exists.
But if he does exist, I don't
believe he's crazy about her.
And even if he exists
and he's crazy about her,
he's got to have a face like a fish.
Uh, excuse me.
Is Diane Chambers here?
Uh, she'll be right back, Mister...?
Apollonaire.
Check out what Diane thinks
is great-looking, will you?
(laughs)
Carla?
(thud)
Is she gonna be all right?
Yeah, of course she's
gonna be all right.
Are you all right? You okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm-I'm fine.
I just had this dream that
I saw the handsomest man.
(gasps)
(thud)
Would you stop that, please?
Oh, nice going, Sam.
I was hoping he'd
give me mouth-to-mouth.
You still can, you know.
Diane's upstairs.
She'll be right down.
Can I get you something?
Yeah. How about a beer?
Oh, dear, now, I'm sorry,
I'm gonna have to ask you for an I.D.
(laughs)
Yeah, sure.
(chuckling)
Is something funny?
Yeah, yeah, it says here
you're six two and a half.
So?
Ha! I'm six three.
Oh, Diane, your little
friend's here to see you.
Lance, what are you doing here?
Well, I brought these for you.
Six two and a half. (chuckles)
Oh, thank you. They're beautiful.
They must have cost you a fortune.
Oh, no, I... I picked them all myself.
And arranged them, too.
I was hoping they might change your
mind about going with me to Vermont.
Lance,
I've already told you,
I don't think it would be
a good idea for you and
me to go away together.
Will you at least think about it?
Okay...
I'll...
I'll think about it.
Fair enough.
Talk to you on Friday. Uh-huh.
Oh, dear.
Things are beginning to get complicated.
Lance is becoming more insistent
that I go away with him this weekend.
So, Sam, should I go or not with this...
figment of my imagination?
Well, if you do, just make
sure he doesn't eat first.
Children tend to get car sick.
I know I shouldn't even
be considering it, but...
when I look at him, I consider it.
Excuse me, but what
happened to the woman
who said it's the inner man who counts?
That woman just pictured Lance
gathering flowers in his bikini briefs.
So did this one.
MAN: Thank you, Brother Tanner,
for reading the minutes
of last week's meeting.
Now, Brother Foley, what is
the next order of business?
According to the agenda, High Sultan,
we're to welcome
our newest member into the
Knights of the Scimitar.
Ah, yes.
Stand up, Norm Peterson,
and be welcomed.
Norm, uh, Norm,
why don't you tell us a
little bit about yourself, huh?
Well, there's really
nothing to say, guys.
Now...
don't be modest.
No, I mean it. There's
really nothing to say.
Uh...
Let's see, I was born in Chicago, uh...
I moved to Boston and
became an accountant.
Are you married?
Yeah.
To?
Long.
By the way, uh, in case you guys need
a good accountant, you
know, I did happen to bring
some of my business
cards along, so, uh...
Oh, sorry,
Norm, I-I guess you
didn't get the word.
It-it's against the
rules to do business
with fellow lodge members.
You know, Cliff said...
My fault for listening.
HIGH SULTAN: Well, Norm,
the time has now arrived...
for you to undergo
the initiation ritual.
Stand, please.
Approach me.
Are you prepared?
Yeah.
(gong sounds)
Congratulations.
Just, uh, just like that, huh?
Yeah, that's it.
Uh, grab a hat and sword
out of the bin, hmm?
Great. Yeah, my God, the pageantry, huh?
Okay, our, uh, next order of business
is our third annual...
Hey, uh, Normie, look, I'm sorry
about that business rule.
I, uh, I didn't know, I guess.
Great time to find out, Cliff.
Oh, hey, if it's any consolation,
these guys give great parties.
Hoo-hoo-hoo,
hey.
Oh, I'll tell you, I thought this was
going to be really stupid,
but these are a good bunch of guys,
I tell you. Yep.
Well, have I ever
steered you wrong, Norm?
Oh, yeah; that's why I thought
it was going to be stupid.
But, uh, you know, it's too
bad about the business stuff,
but I-I feel pretty
comfortable with these guys.
Yeah. Really, thank you
for sponsoring me, buddy.
Mm-hmm. I can't wait for
some of these parties.
Bang, zoom, eh?
HIGH SULTAN: Oh, uh, before I forget,
the, uh, referendum that we ban beer
at all lodge functions has been passed.
Good-bye!
So, what time's Peewee coming in?
If you're referring to Lance,
I'm expecting him shortl... soon.
And I don't appreciate
these constant attempts
to denigrate him.
Let me ask you a question.
What do you see in him?
(laughs)
You mean... besides a young,
brainy, stunningly gorgeous man
with many interests similar to mine
who's fawning over me and
giving me all the attention
I could ever ask for?
Yeah.
I see what I used to see in you
before you decided to
spend the last few months
flogging me with your apathy.
Well, I'm sorry, Diane,
but that's all I had handy.
Hi, Diane.
Have you made a decision?
Have I, Sam?
Send me a postcard.
I don't think I can go,
because it would upset someone too much.
Diane, go with someone's blessings.
Excuse me.
May I speak with you for a moment?
Hop up on a stool there, Lance.
Carla, why don't you pour him a beer?
I know you're still smarting
from my turning down
your proposal of marriage,
but how long can you drag this out?
You're hurting me, but
you're also hurting yourself
with this feigned indifference.
Well, while we're talking
about hurting people,
how do you think Lance is going to feel
when he finds out that
you're using him to get to me?
I am not using him.
I like him.
He treats me wonderfully.
And I don't, so go with him.
(scoffs)
Mr. Malone, I'm about
to call your bluff.
I'm going to go with him,
and I'm going to have a great time,
and it will leave you
a hollow, broken man.
All right.
Just watch while I give you
a little preview of
our weekend together.
I'm going to kiss him
in front of you and the whole bar,
and it's going to kill you.
Lance...
this is for the flowers.
Now, Mr. Indifference, are you going
to tell me that doesn't bother you?
Well, I have to admit for a while there,
my life passed before my eyes...
...but the funny thing
is you weren't in it.
Right.
Lance, let's go.
Diane?
Yes, Sam?
It would've bothered me
if he had done this.
Yes, I can see where
that might have given you
cause for concern.
(clears throat)
Uh, so, Diane, are
you about ready to go?
Uh...
Lance. Thank you.
Um... Lance,
I-I-I just
remembered
I have to work this weekend.
That's okay. I understand.
Bye. DIANE: Good-bye, Lance.
Well, kid, you blew it.
You know what would've
really have bothered Sam
would be if you had
kissed her like this.
Carla, you're not involved in this.
I am now.