Cheers is filmed before a live
studio audience.
( babies crying )
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
( babies cooing and crying )
( no audio )
( piano playing )
Making your way in
the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break from all your
worries sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go where
everybody knows your name
And they're always
glad you came
You want to be
where you can see
Troubles are all the same
You want to be where everybody
knows your name
You want to go where people
know people are all the same
You want to go where everybody
knows your name.
So, did you get a chance
to see Carla's babies?
Oh, we sure did.
There are two of the cutest
little guys you've ever seen.
Ah, who do they look like,
Carla or Eddie?
Well, they're twins.
They kind of look
like each other.
What's this?
"Carla's Tips."
Yeah, it was Carla's idea.
She does some of her best
thinking in labor.
This is ridiculous.
How does she expect to be tipped
if she's not even here?
Well, actually,
she's doing a lot better
than she usually does.
Hello, Samuel.
Hey.
Well, pardon my appearance,
everybody.
We always do.
Sorry. I was covering for Carla.
Oh, hey, you're doing
a fine job.
The reason why I look like
I've been up all night
is because, well,
reading that little opus.
All right,
Lust for Justice.
Yeah, Vera talked me
into reading this.
Oh, is she a fan?
No, no. When Vera's
talking, I'll read
just about anything.
Yeah. I almost
ruptured a disc
delivering those
Book of the Month club copies
and I decided to see
what all the hooha was about.
Yeah, two thumbs
up, right?
Oh, yeah.
Finest piece of trash
not written by a Junta or Jackie
in modern literature.
Good Lord. Another piece
of salacious mind candy.
God, this is over
600 pages long.
Who could imagine
he'd know this many words?
Yeah, well I checked.
He uses a lot of them twice.
CLIFF:
Yeah, well, Frasier,
you want to
borrow it then?
No way you'll find me
reading it.
Just look at these reviews.
Suit yourself.
"I couldn't put it down."
( scoffs )
( phone ringing )
Cheers.
Oh, yeah, she is.
Miss Howe, Mr. Drake.
Mr. Drake?
I wonder what he's
calling about.
Woody, how did he sound?
Happy, mad, pleasant, annoyed?
Well, he sounds
kind of weird.
Like an old woman with a lisp
and a thick German accent.
Woody, that's his secretary.
Oh, well, then she sounded
pretty happy.
Hey, Anthony, Annie, what's up?
Sam, I'm swallowing
my Tortelli pride
to ask if
I might borrow five bucks.
That was very difficult
for him.
Is it okay?
I want to get a present
for my mom and the twins.
Sure.
What are you going to get them?
Five bucks.
She'll like that.
Thanks, Sam.
Hey, I don't know when I'll be
able to pay you back.
Job market's
been really bad lately.
I haven't been able to
find a job anywhere.
Actually, we have an opening
for a temporary waitress
to sub for your mom.
What do you think?
Ah, I don't want
to be a waitress.
No, I was thinking about her.
No, I don't want my
wife to work.
I could do it if I want to.
Nuh-uh.
Nuh-huh.
W-Why don't you two
talk about it.
Of course we will.
Communication is
the cornerstone of our marriage.
Nuh-uh.
Nuh-huh.
Well, well, well.
Hey, Normie,
look who's developed
a lust for justice.
Yeah.
Do you mind?
Lorenzo is hemorrhaging.
Oh, he dies.
Don't tell me.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
We don't want to spoil the part
where Monica first comes in.
Were you shocked or what when
she turned out to be a man?
CLIFF:
Oh, no, no, I saw...
I wish I was
in the land of cotton
Old times there
are not forgotten
Look away, look away,
look away...
You know, sometimes I like
to play little guessing games.
Do you like to play
little guessing games, guys?
( all agree )
Let's play a little
guessing game.
I just spoke to Mr. Drake
and he suggested that I hire
a young girl he knows
to cover for Carla.
Now, why do you suppose a busy,
important man like Mr. Drake
would take time out of his day
to get a simple cocktail
waitress a job?
Oh, oh, oh.
Uh, she's, uh...
Norm.
She's a friend of the family.
Possible.
He's, uh, paying off a debt.
I like that.
He feels sorry for her.
He does have a soft heart.
Maybe she's
sleeping with him.
Of course that little tramp
is sleeping with him!
Do you think
I'm stupid?
Is this still part of
the guessing game?
No, no, no.
This is just too perfect.
Evan found a nice little bowl
for his goldfish to swim in.
Safe, out of the reach of
the other executive sharks.
Obviously, he forgot about
the Great White Sammy.
( all snicker )
Well, we've reached
a compromise, Sam.
I'm taking the relief
waitress job.
SAM:
Great.
What's the compromise?
I'm letting her.
Wait a minute.
I am in charge around here
and it is my responsibility
to hire people,
and I have just be informed
that I am hiring someone else.
They're going through
a tough time right now.
Why don't you let Annie
work just for tips?
Tips?
!
Yeah.
If I'm gonna work here,
I demand a set salary,
plus tips, plus
two coffee breaks,
plus weekends off.
That is completely
out of the question.
Okay, then I demand
that tip thing.
It's a deal.
I need a Scotch, rocks,
two white wines and a draft.
Okeydokey.
Come on, corn cob. Arriba.
Boy, I tell ya,
Annie's getting to be
a real pro, huh?
Yeah, she's sure rattling off
those drink orders, huh?
That's nothing.
How about the way
she puts me in my place?
Can you believe it?
Her first day on the job and
Evan's little tart is late.
That's because she
knows I can't do
anything about it
because her lover boy
is the big boss.
Isn't she just
the queen of gall?
Oh, no, that was Charlemagne's
wife, I think.
Well, you know,
if memory serves,
I think her name was Cathy.
Listen, have you ever thought
that you're reading
this whole thing wrong?
That maybe she's just
a four-eyed little geek
that Evan Drake
is trying to help out?
Right. And Cliff is leaving
his brain to science.
I guess, you're still covering
for Carla, huh?
Guess again.
Okay, uh, here's
another possibility.
Instead of
firing someone,
you send them to
the worst job in
the organization.
Usually the poor schlep
just gets fed up and quits.
They've tried that
on me a bunch of times.
Works like a charm.
You know,
you might be right.
She's probably just some
pathetic little dishrag
whose last great hope
is working here at Cheers.
I got to stop
jumping to conclusions.
Excuse me. Is Miss Howe here?
Mr. Drake sent me.
Oh, you must be the slut.
Excuse me?
Slot. You're here
to fill the slot.
Welcome to Cheers.
Why don't you just
follow me in to my office
and we'll fill out
your W-4 form.
Great.
And I'll need a phone number
and a job history,
and a number we can call
in case you meet with some
horrible disfiguring accident.
Sam?
What?
Could I ask your opinion as
a passionate macho stud horse?
Sure. I may have to stamp out
the answer with my foot,
but go ahead.
Well, it's bad enough
that Anthony's lost
all his ambition
and can't get a job.
Right.
But ever since I
started working here,
he's become insanely jealous.
Why am I late?
When am I coming home?
Why am I dressed
like such an ultra-fox?
I mean, if it weren't for
the six times a day we make love
he'd be no fun at all.
Six?
Whoo!
Can't think of anything
that I can do six times a day.
Hit me again. Will you, Sam?
Listen, it's kind of
tough on a husband,
you know, to have his wife
supporting him.
It's a...
It's a pride thing.
It is a pride thing, Sam.
I remember once when I was out
of work, Vera had to support us.
I tell ya, the day that woman
left to deliver phone books...
The proudest day of my life,
actually.
What do you want
me to do?
You want me to
talk to him?
Would you, Sam?
Thanks.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're welcome.
Hey, I saw that!
Anthony! I can't believe
you're spying on me.
Suddenly,
everything makes sense.
You're taller than me.
You have a Corvette
instead of a bus pass.
And your hair does
that cool blow-dry thing.
And now you've got my wife.
Well, aren't you gonna stay
and fight for me?
What's the use?
Hey, Anthony,
come on, now, don't...
Have you ever had to defend
Vera's honor?
Well, no, not per se.
But on more
than one occasion
I've held her place in line
while she parked the car.
Could you believe that?
After I gave that man
the best 28 months of my life.
Well, why don't you go
catch up with him
and patch things up.
Forget it. He's a wimp
and he can't get a job.
And his jealousy
is ruining our marriage.
Not to mention that he left
the cap off the toothpaste
for, like, the kajillionth day
in a row.
I had no idea
that the wounds
were so deep.
Well, as far as I'm concerned,
he can just go and...
Oh, God!
I've just lost the only man
I've ever loved.
Oh, no, wait.
Sit here, will ya?
Listen, he'll come back.
Don't you worry about that.
Now, he's not gonna leave
a beautiful girl like you.
You really think so, Sam?
Oh, absolutely.
He'll be right back.
I mean, do you really
think I'm beautiful?
Hey, anyone see the conclusion
of the White House Murders
last night?
No! Don't say anything.
I've got it on tape.
Did you believe it was
the vice-president?
Please!
How about where the First Lady
popped out of a pool
of her own blood
and strangled
the Russian ambassador?
No... No...
Yeah, that
was my reaction exactly.
Well, thank you,
one and all,
for ruining yet
another plot for me.
I'll be off, now,
but before I go...
there's something I'd like
to share with you.
In Citizen Kane. Rosebud
is the name of his sled.
In Murder on
the Orient Express,
everyone did it,
and Luke Skywalker's father
is Darth Vader.
Ha!
Ah, why doesn't
the guy tell us
something
we don't know, huh?
Darth Vader is Luke's father?
See you soon.
Bye.
"Bye."
How dare she put on
that sweetness and light
when it's so obvious
she's nothing more
than a sordid
little harlot.
Hypocrite.
Doing a great job,
Laurie. Keep it up!
I need a couple of drafts, Sam.
Okay.
But, oh, you, uh,
You and Anthony
still not talking?
Talking? I can barely stomach
necking with him.
He's a wimp.
Not like my Sam.
Tell me,
how do you feel
about moonlit walks by the beach
and dinner by a roaring fire?
I hate them.
I-I can't stand them. Bleah.
Yay! Me, too.
No, no, no.
I was kidding. I love them.
Too late.
You know, if someone
ran over Laurie
in the parking lot, I bet it
would look like an accident.
Do you want to
make 500 bucks?
Just, don't...
Listen to yourself.
You're going crazy here.
We both have a problem
with these new waitresses.
Why don't we help
each other out, here?
Oh, like I scratch
your back...?
And I'll scratch
your front.
What do you propose?
Well, all right, uh...
now, we don't know for sure
that Laurie is
Evan Drake's mistress,
so why don't you
let a guy
who knows women
better than they
know themselves
find out, all right?
Okay.
Laurie, you got
a second here?
Yeah.
How do you feel
about, uh...
moonlit walks on the beach with
a dinner by a roaring fire?
Oh, I love those.
Well, would you
like to join me?
Oh, no, no, but...
thanks for asking.
She's his mistress.
How do you know that?
She turned me down.
That just proves
she has a weak stomach.
I'll handle this myself.
Oh, wait a second.
Wait a minute.
What about my little
problem here, you know?
Sam, I don't have
time to handle
some silly little
teenage crush.
It is not silly.
Oh, yes, Miss Howe?
Laurie, my, you are
such a busy little bee.
I bet you just
won't have an ounce
of energy left for
your leisure time.
Oh, that's okay.
I've lots of energy.
I'll bet you do.
You know, you and I
really haven't had
a chance to get
to know each other.
What do you like to do
in your leisure time?
Well, I, uh, I like to read.
In bed?
Sometimes.
What else do you
like to do...
in bed?
Sleep.
Oh, well.
Let, let's imagine here,
that you are asleep in bed,
and you roll over.
Did you fall
on the floor,
or did something
impede your progress?
Excuse me?
Oh, nothing.
It's must my warped,
wonderful, wild
sense of humor.
By the way,
how do you
know Evan Drake?
Well, he's uh...
a friend.
Oh. Well, then maybe
you could help me out.
I was gonna buy him a gift.
Perhaps you know
what size he wears
in slacks or shirts
or jockey shorts.
Oh... sure,
but he doesn't
wear jockeys.
He wears boxers.
Never mind, then.
I'm gonna pop her.
I'm gonna pop her
right in the kisser.
I'm gonna pop her!
Pop, pop, pop, pop, pop!
That's good.
Now-Now do, uh,
bacon frying.
You know, Darth Vader cannot be
Luke Skywalker's father.
They don't have
the same last name.
That's right, Woody.
I'd better call out
the Imperial Guards.
( inhaling and exhaling deeply )
Stop it, Mr. Peterson.
You're scaring me.
ANNIE:
You know, Sam,
I was just thinking
about us last night
as I was in the tub
shaving my legs
and pumicing the dead skin
off my knees and elbows
and waxing my...
Uh, is-is there
a point to this?
Do I have to say it?
Can't you just feel it?
Would you stop that?
This is silly.
Now, just...
Of course it's silly,
but love is silly, isn't it?
Romeo and Juliet were silly
in a mad, passionate way.
Are we silly, Sam?
Are we?
Y-You maybe,
but I'm not.
Listen, young lady, I happen
to be a very close friend
of your
mother-in-law,
and out of respect,
I'm ending this conversation
right now.
You can end the conversation,
Sam,
but you can't end the feeling.
Honey, I'm flattered,
but this is nuts.
I mean, I...
You know, I'm old
enough to be your f...
a youthful
uncle, all right?
I mean, when-when...
when I'm 60,
you're-you're
gonna be 22.
Oh, my God, that
can't be right.
Uh...
all right, uh...
All right, when
I'm 60, uh,
well, you'll be
looking pretty
good, actually.
Um...
so, why don't you
call me when I'm 60?
I can't wait that long.
Oh, don't. Just...
( Sam grunting )
Hey, knock it off!
All right, you, outside.
You're gonna get
what's coming to you.
I am not going outside
with you, Anthony.
Not you. Her.
I mean, come on.
You're twice as big as me.
Hey, but you stay away from her,
if you know what's good for you.
Thank you for the warning.
Come on, Annie. Let's go.
Why should I
listen to you?
Because I happen to be the new
Assistant Night Manager
at Burger Burger Burger.
You got a job?
Hey, an important job.
When I tell people
to chop lettuce,
they say, "How high?"
And now, I am telling you,
Missy,
if you don't come with me
this instant,
we're through forever.
I am so totally
turned on right now,
I could spit.
NORM:
Well,
I guess it's true
what they say:
power is the ultimate
aphrodisiac.
A uniform doesn't
hurt, either.
Can you wear it
all night?
Oh, maybe the hat.
Ooh.
Boy, Sam, lucky
for you, he got
that job, huh?
Lucky, hell.
I got him that job.
I traded in a few favors
and got him in.
Wow.
As a matter of fact,
are you interested
in buying a secondhand car
with this giant hamburger
on top?
Five-speed
or automatic?
Uh, Miss Howe?
Yes, Laurie, dear?
Well, uh,
Mr. Drake is dropping by,
and I was wondering
if I could just break away
for a... for an early lunch.
Lunch.
Is that the fashionable
term for it these days?
No, I think
I've always called it lunch.
Well, you just run
along with Mr. Drake
to your lunch,
and don't eat so much,
you can't walk back.
Okay.
Excuse me, Sam.
What did she mean by that?
Oh, she's, uh,
under a lot of
pressure nowawdays.
I volunteered
to help her release
some of it, but she...
( sighs )
Probably didn't help,
by asking for an early break.
Mm.
I better apologize.
CLIFF:
Oh,
Normie, do my eyes deceive me,
or is this the start
of girl-fighting season?
Luckily, we
have our, uh,
luxury box seats
just in time.
That's right.
They cost a little bit more,
but they're worth it.
Miss Howe,
if it's more convenient,
I'll just take my lunch break
one hour...
Listen!
Let's just cut the
crap here, all right?
I know how you
got hired here,
and I know what
your relationship
is to Mr. Drake.
You do?
Well, give me credit
for having an
ounce of a brain.
You can tell me
to go to hell,
but there's something
I have to know.
Do you love
Evan Drake?
Well, yes.
I see.
( voice cracking ):
And does he
love you?
Does he love you?!
Well, of course he does.
Well, then there's only
one thing left to say.
Oh, my God. Oh!
( shrieks )
Oh, damn, it's
a knockout.
Didn't even get
to any hair-pulling.
( door opening )
Uh-oh, uh-oh,
uh-oh.
What the hell's going on?
Mr. Drake.
Daddy.
D-Daddy?
Daddy?
Daddy.
What happened?
Oh, I think she hit me.
You hit my daughter?
No, I'm fine.
Yes, I did,
but it was
an accident.
I have a nerve
disorder.
A nerve disorder?
SAM:
Yes, she...
Yes.
She was dropped
as a child on her...
REBECCA:
And-And you better
stand back, because
I just never know
when it's gonna go off.
Ooh.
Oh!
Aah!
See?
I'd better get back
on that medication.
Are you all right, baby?
I'll be all right. Thank you.
I mean her.
Yes, Daddy.
Oh.
REBECCA:
So, uh,
Laurie's your daughter.
Why didn't you
tell me, kiddo?
Well, Daddy
said not to.
I didn't want her
to have any special treatment.
I want her to know
what it feels like
not to be the boss's daughter.
What a fabulous idea.
And so smart of
you not to tell
anyone who she was.
Do you have
any cotton in
your office?
Yeah. Let's put some food
in my baby, huh?
Again, again,
please accept
my apology,
and it was so nice
to see you, Mr. Drake.
If you don't mind, I'll wait
till after
you've had the medication.
Do you think he bought
that nerve disorder thing?
I think he bought
that nerve disorder thing.
Is it getting
darker in here?
Oh, Sam, stop being
such a big baby.
Yeah, well...
Here, let me look
at your nose.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
( gasping ):
Oh, my God!
What?
Oh.
( grunts )
Huh?
What-What...?
Hey, everybody, I'm back.
Hey, Carla.
All right.
Anything new
since I've been gone?
( baby cooing )
NORM:
Mm, no, not much.
CLIFF:
Uh, well, nothing special.
( baby cooing )
Yeah, yeah.
How about yourself?
The usual.
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.OpenSubtitles.org