Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Man, how about all that stuff
that's going on over at Cheers?
What's that?
You don't know about that?
Well, Rebecca, the babe
who runs the place,
you know she's been
dating Robin Colcord,
the multimillionaire.
Uh-huh.
Well, he tried to pull
a hostile takeover
of her corporation and she
was implicated in the deal.
So the corporation dumped her.
Guess who ended up
owning Cheers.
Sam Malone.
You're kidding.
Wait, you haven't heard
the best part.
Now, Colcord
skipped the country,
so Rebecca's ended up
having to take a waitress job...
at Cheers.
Wow.
W-Where do you get
this stuff, anyway?
I got my sources.
Another round on the house,
Mr. Peterson?
Thank you very much.
(theme song begins)
¶ Making your way
in the world today ¶
¶ Takes everything you've got ¶
¶ Takin' a break
from all your worries ¶
¶ Sure would help a lot
¶ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ¶
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always
glad you came ¶
¶ You wanna be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You wanna be where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ You wanna go
where people know ¶
¶ People are all the same
¶ You wanna go where everybody
knows your name. ¶
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Is Rebecca in her office?
I thought you ditched her
and skipped the country.
I did, but I've come back.
I finally realized what
Rebecca means to me.
What use is my money
or my freedom
if I don't have the woman
I love?
Rebecca?!
(gasps)
I'm back.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Rebecca, what is going
on in here?
Robin, I can explain.
Wait a minute.
My button's caught
in your zipper here.
Robin, I can't explain.
It's my own fault.
For all you knew, I was
never coming back again.
I left the way clear for
something like this to happen.
But Robin, nothing did happen.
Nothing?
No, nothing.
Okay, something almost happened
but I would never betray you.
I love you.
We didn't do anything.
Did we, Sam?
Yeah...
(clearing throat):
...what she said.
(knocking)
Hey, jailbird,
your lawyer's on the phone.
Your lawyer?!
Yes, I've made arrangements
to turn myself in.
Oh, Robin.
Oh, I'll wait for you.
I won't have any money
when I come out.
That doesn't matter.
I'll help you rebuild
your fortune.
Yeah, just look at what
she's done with this bar.
Oh, shut up.
Boy, just because you
lose a few billion bucks
is no reason
to cop a 'tude.
I guess I should go see
if Robin needs any help.
Sure.
Sam?
Thank you for lying about...
you know.
It's okay, sure.
Thank you for... you know.
I just think it was the
right thing to do.
The lying, I mean,
not the, you know...
Well, that, too.
Yeah.
Anyway... (clears throat)
well... see ya.
See ya.
(tiny object clattering)
Oh...
Your button.
Yeah. Thank you.
Well, my attorney's
spoken to the prosecutor
and I... I have to go.
Can't we at least wait
till morning?
Well, my attorney says that
if I turn myself in now,
I can avoid a media circus.
Do you have any idea what
these sleazy tabloids would pay
for a picture of Robin Colcord
the fugitive?
(gasps)
Okay, let's try
another one,
only, this time, look
a little bit more guilty.
Guilty?!
SAM:
What do you guys
think, huh?
I'm finished.
With, uh, with what, Sam?
With putting my old stuff
back on the wall.
It was gone?
Yeah, it was gone--
three years gone, man.
Rebecca had her stuff up there.
Ah.
Are you so taken
with your own lives
you don't notice the
changes going on around here?
Sammy, we notice the important
things, all right?
By the way, is Diane
coming in today?
Hey!
Give this man
a drink-- whoo!
Sammy, I just realized,
I forgot to call Ma and
tell her the good news.
You know how
she loves you.
Boy, she's gonna be
tickled pink
when she hears you got
the bar back.
Hello, Ma!
Guess who the new
owner of Cheers is.
No, it's not me,
it's, uh, it's Sam.
Well, I'm, uh, still
a mailman, Ma.
Well, I know you had
high hopes for me, Ma,
but I couldn't finish college
and that's all there is to it.
She was thrilled.
SAM:
Hey, Woody.
It says here that
you and Carla
haven't had a raise
for over two years.
That's right, Sam.
I guess that's why I been
so darn moody lately.
Well, that's one of the things
that's gonna change around here.
Starting tomorrow, you guys
get a $20-a-week raise.
Wow, thanks.
Another thing here,
while I'm at it,
to celebrate the new management,
I am wiping out
everybody's bar tab.
Sam Malone, I am not a man
for mushy sentiment,
but I want you
to know something--
if you ever need a liver donor,
I've got one like yea big.
Woody, round of drinks on
the house for everybody.
All right!
(cheering)
Hi, Sam.
Oh, hi.
I didn't expect to see
you waitressing here today
with your billionaire
boyfriend back in town.
Well, it's only temporary
until I find a good job.
You know what they say--
better a temporary dead-end
stupid job than no job at all.
Ah, just what every
employer wants to hear.
Excuse me.
I'm gonna, uh, take
these plants of yours
out to the woods
and give them their freedom.
So, what's new, Miss Howe?
I just got back from
visiting Robin in jail.
They're not going
to let him out on bail
since he jumped
bond earlier.
They're gonna charge him
a huge penalty, even if
he pleads guilty.
I don't think they're gonna give
that poor guy any breaks at all.
I got a raise.
You deserve it, Woody.
I deserved it two years ago.
Who was the boss then?
Let me think.
Hi, guys. Sorry I'm late.
Boy, of all days for my kids to
handcuff me to the water heater.
Why, uh, what's the big deal
about today?
Didn't Sam tell
you what happened
in the office last night?
No. What?
He and Rebecca were in there
for for a mighty long time
and that place was wrecked.
He didn't mention a thing.
Really?
Maybe he's saving all
the dirty details for me.
He's such a gentleman.
(watch alarm beeps
three times)
Well, fellows, that's the bell
announcing Clavin's midmorning
brain twister.
Oh, you going to get up
and try to walk again?
Is this going to be along
the same lines
as yesterday's little pearl?
If the Lennon Sisters,
the Maguire Sisters
and the Andrew Sisters
all came to a four-way stop,
which would have
the right-of-way?
No, no, no, no.
This one is, uh, based on
historical fact.
Now listen up.
How would the Civil War
have changed
if Lincoln had had octopus
tentacles instead of a beard?
For God's sake, Cliff.
There is no practical
answer to that question.
Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Now we can assume that
the Gettysburg Address
would have been written on
the back of eight envelopes.
Very good.
Very good answer, Normie.
Also, he could have disarmed
John Wilkes Booth
and still applauded the play.
Now, in a related query,
what if Herbert Hoover was
able to expand his face
like a blowfish?
What were you guys
talking about?
Former presidents with
fish parts in their faces.
Come on.
Do you really expect
me to believe
you were talking about
something that stupid?
Where have you been
all these years?
Hello!
I know what you
were doing.
You were trying to
cover up the fact that
you were gossiping
about me.
REBECCA:
And, as soon as
I turn my back,
you will go on about Sam and
I in that office last night.
Didn't I tell you?
I knew something happened.
Ooh, guys, do you think Sammy
finally bagged Rebecca?
MEN:
Yeah!
Oh, hey, Rebecca,
I'm sorry.
This is, you know,
just guy talk, you know.
Carla, you think he
finally bagged Rebecca?
Yeah!
There he is.
Why don't we ask him?
Sammy,
last night--
you-- the Howitzer
in the office.
Come on.
NORM:
Come on, Sam.
Come on.
Guys, guys, that's tacky.
Sam, we know that.
It says it above
the door. Come on.
All right, if you must know--
nothing happened.
End of story.
I guess nothing did happen.
I guess not.
Sammy would never withhold
information like that.
No. He lives to talk
about that stuff.
And we live to
hear about it.
Aw, it's a symbiotic
relationship.
Mm-hmm.
Much like that between the shark
and the tiny pilot fish
that constantly swims
around its mouth
picking out the little
bits of meat.
I suppose you're now
going to tell me
that if George Washington
had had a pilot fish,
he wouldn't have
needed wooden dentures.
Now you're getting
up to speed, Dr. Crane.
Yeah. Yeah.
And then he could have, uh,
swum across the Delaware
to defeat the Hessians.
(laughing):
No Dr. Crane,
try to understand.
It's only the president's
face that changes.
It's not like he grew fins
or something.
(silly gibbering)
(knocking on door)
Sam.
Oh, hi.
I wanted to thank you
for your discretion.
What do you mean?
Well, not telling Robin
about us was one thing,
but not telling all
those goons out there--
I know that was
a real sacrifice.
No, no big deal.
Yes, it is.
I know how much you love
to crow to all
your friends
about your great
romantic encounters.
Rebecca, believe me,
it was nothing.
Wait, wait-- not telling
them was nothing,
or the great romantic
encounter was nothing?
What?
Oh, uh, the not
telling, of course.
No, the... romantic
stuff was great.
Wasn't it?
You know, I don't mean to be
disloyal to Robin or anything,
but... it was one of
the most powerful things
that's ever happened
to me in my life.
Really?
You need to get out more, hon.
What?
You mean you didn't like it?
No, I said I did,
didn't I?
No, it was great.
I liked... I really,
really liked it a lot.
But what?
Uh... I don't know.
It's, like,
maybe I was looking forward
to it too much, you know?
Like when you're really
excited about a new movie.
Like The Bad News Bears.
Remember that?
For weeks, people kept
coming up and telling me
what a great movie it was.
But when I finally
went to see it...
So it wasn't that great.
No, it's just Tatum O'Neal
throwing a ball around.
Not that.
Oh, you mean us?
I told you really,
it was fine, honey.
Fine?!
But it was a letdown,
like The Bad News Bears.
No, it was... (sputters)
much better
than The Bad News Bears.
Maybe I was a little off.
I don't... you know?
I mean, I knew
that I'd been depressed
and I'd been crying
for a couple of days and...
Wait a minute.
What?
I know what you're doing.
You are trying
to convince me
that I was not good in bed,
so I will go to bed
with you again
to prove how good I can be.
I swear to you, Rebecca...
No, wait a minute.
We did it once and that's
all we're gonna do it.
And no matter how much
we might want it
and no matter how great
it was for both of us,
we're never doing it again.
Fine.
I mean it, never again.
Gotcha.
You should listen to me--
there is no more.
I hear you
and I agree with you.
It was a terrific moment that
you and I had together,
but the truth is,
you know,
I can see that you love Robin
and Robin loves you,
so, truthfully,
I'm liberated.
I feel, I feel good.
But I just hope we can,
you know, remain friends.
Get your mind out of your pants.
Hey, wait-wait-wait!
Come back here.
I wasn't trying to
do anything there.
Oh, stop caressing me.
I have had it
with this constant
sexual harassment!
I am quitting this job
and I'm never
coming back here.
Me too, man.
20 lousy bucks after two years.
Man, I'm out of here.
Wait up, Miss Howe, wait up...
Woody, that was a personal thing
between me and Rebecca.
It had nothing to
do with your raise.
Well, still, 20 lousy bucks...
Well, that's fine--
25. Now, let's get
back to work.
Come on.
Hey, keep your hands off.
Wait, wait, wait
a minute, Sammy, look,
Rebecca just said
she was leaving here,
and never coming back.
Yeah, that's right.
Oh, man.
This is terrible.
What?
Sammy finally struck
out for real.
Ooh.
(customers muttering,
murmuring)
What are you talking about here?
We all knew that it
was taking a long time,
but we thought that,
eventually,
you two would be doing
the horizontal hokeypokey.
But I guess that's it, huh?
Lower the flag.
The end of an era.
First, the Communist
bloc crumbles,
and now Sammy's studhood.
Yep. Guess that's it.
SAM:
No, it's not.
Come here.
Come on,
all of you.
I want you to step in
the office there,
and I'll show you where we...
uh, where we, uh,
decided to put up
some, uh, some shelves, uh...
Tall ones, you know,
it'll be great for books
and uh, some of my videotapes
and everything...
It'll be nice.
Breaks your heart, doesn't it?
What I can't figure
out is why,
why I don't want to tell
any of my friends.
No, that's not true--
I-I do want to, but I can't.
Why? That's...
That's...
You know, maybe
it was such a letdown
that I didn't feel like
bragging about it.
Or maybe it was not a letdown
and I was just ticked
that she dumped me
as soon as her boyfriend
walked in.
Or maybe she's right
and I'm just trying to get
her in the sack again.
I don't know.
God! I-I just...
I-I'm just a simple guy
trying to deal with
this complex problem.
Or maybe...
maybe I'm a complex guy
trying to deal with
a simple problem, I don't know.
What do you think, Father?
Am I to understand that
you had relations with a woman
who is not your wife?
Yes. That's, uh...
that's correct, Father.
Uh, what do I need to do?
Say three Hail Marys...
...four Our Fathers
and nine rosaries.
Thank you, Father.
Nine rosaries? That's a lot.
We're cracking down.
You mean that I...
I have to do that
for each one of these beads?
Hey, it's not a
religion for wusses.
CLIFF:
You know, uh, Sam,
we all feel kind of bad
about what you're
going through and...
as much as we live
vicariously through you
when you score, we...
also feel vicarious pain
when you strike out.
So what's the deal?
Are you gonna snap out
of this by the weekend
or do we have to go
rent a Matt Helm movie?
I'm fine.
Can we just drop
the subject, please?
Sam, is something troubling you?
Do you need to talk to someone?
Yes, as a matter of fact, I do
need to talk to someone.
I need to talk
to everybody here.
I don't know why
it's taken me
so long to get this out here,
but last night, in that office,
Rebecca Howe and I had...
uh, a disagreement about those
shelves I was telling you about.
Uh, you know, I'm gonna
put them up anyway.
You know, what the heck.
They'll be good for knickknacks
and everything.
I think they're gonna look,
uh, fine.
Matt Helm never had
to build shelves.
(knocks on door)
Hi, Sam.
Hi.
I didn't expect to see you here.
I just came back
for my final paycheck
and there seems
to be some mistake.
It's only for $16.
Oh, darn those computers.
How can they make
a mistake like that?
It was supposed
to be for six.
You got a ten on you?
This isn't about
a silly check.
Give me the check.
This is about us.
What about us?
Sam, we have been friends for
too long to let it end this way.
And I just came
back to say
that I'm sorry I ran out
earlier in a huff
and that I knew you
weren't coming on to me,
and that when you
said I wasn't good,
that it wasn't just some trick
to get me back into bed,
it was because you were
being honest,
because I am a lousy lover.
No, sweetheart,
you're not lou...
No, Sam,
it's all right.
It's not like I haven't
heard it before.
I have to learn to accept it.
You know, some people
are bad at math.
Some people can't skip.
No, no...
You're a fantastic lover.
I am a dud and I know it.
Robin just didn't realize it
because he's English.
Listen, I wouldn't say you
were good if you weren't.
Maybe I just, you know,
wasn't too enthusiastic
this morning because my
feelings were hurt.
I mean, the minute
he comes in here,
you act as if
nothing happened.
No... no, no.
Sam, that doesn't wash.
You have been after
me for three years.
And you finally got me.
I mean,
if I was even adequate,
I know that you would
have run out there
and told every bozo
in the bar.
You don't think I wasn't
dying to do that?
It was making me crazy.
It's just that I thought that
I'd be betraying our friendship.
I never really had
a friend before.
You have lots of friends.
No, no, I never "had"
a friend before.
It's weird.
I don't know
how to behave.
I don't...
So you really, really did this
out of respect
for our friendship?
Uh-huh.
Sort of... sort of like
you were being noble?
Well, I...
Yeah, I guess so.
I guess...
And, uh, I wasn't lousy?
No. You were fantastic.
Look, you want me
to prove it to you,
I'll go out there and tell
them that we made love.
No, no, no, no, Sam, no.
It's enough
just knowing you're
willing to do that.
No, I think you need more.
No, no, no.
No, Sam, don't give
up your nobility.
Aw, come on.
Let, a noble guy
have some fun here.
Oh! I get it: you
want to tell them.
Yeah. It's a guy thing,
you know.
At least let me tell Carla.
Okay, go ahead.
Really?
Yes, yes, you've done
a lot for me; it's fine.
Yeah, this friendship stuff's
gonna to be fantastic.
Yes...
Hey, guys, guys,
listen up here.
(laughing)
Uh, last night...
Rebecca and I made love,
and she was fabulous.
(sighing deeply):
Well...
...this has got to be
the saddest day of my life.
What?
Sammy, you never had
to resort to lying before.
What, you don't believe me?
First of all, why would you
wait a whole day to tell us?
And second of all--
she was fabulous?!
Sammy,
come on, let's go
look at those shelves.
No, no, really,
I was being noble.
No, really, I was fabulous.
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/49gce
Help other users to choose the best subtitles