Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Here's something about
a show of impressionists
coming to Boston this fall.
Well, why wait?
I do one that'll knock your socks off.
He's talkin' about
French painters, doofus.
Yeah? Well, so am I.
Yeah, I do a great Cezanne.
Get outta here. No, I do. Watch this.
(French accent): Hosey,
posey, life is perfect.
(as John Wayne): Hey, ya better smile
when ya say that, Pilgrim.
(as James Stewart): Now, now, now, now,
just a-just a darned
second there, young fella.
(all chuckling)
Okay, okay, I got one. Watch this.
(with country accent): Hey, fellers.
I believe we might be
in for just a little rain
before this day's over.
Woody, who is that?
It's Dwight Womack,
mayor of Hanover, Indiana.
No, Woody, Woody, when
you do impressions,
you gotta do impressions
of famous people.
Well, if I could do somebody famous,
why would I be doin' Dwight Womack?
Yeah, good point.
Yeah, he's got a point.
(piano plays)
♪ Making your way in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like to get away♪
♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always glad you came ♪
♪ You want to be where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You want to go where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Hey, everybody.
(all calling out greetings)
Sam?
This is our first time
back in Cheers since,
you know, yesterday.
Don't you think we should
announce our engagement?
Oh. All right. Okay.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Oh, no, no, you do it.
You're the man.
All right, listen up, everybody.
I have an announcement to make here.
Uh, Diane and I decided to...
Oh, Sam, (clears throat)
what are you going to say?
Well, I was just going to tell them...
(speaks softly)
I see.
SAM: Well, what do you want me to say?
(Diane whispering)
Oh, come on, Diane, nobody
knows who the Lunts are.
Due to our desire
to be-- what?
Conjoined. Conjoined, uh...
hey, well, Diane and I, uh,
would like you to, uh, celebrate with us
by, uh, toasting our nuptials.
Ouch.
No, no, Woody, it's, uh...
What Sam so eloquently
expressed was that he and I
have officially become
engaged to be married.
(cheering and applause)
How about that Al, huh?
CLIFF: Oh, marriage, Sam.
I thought you'd said
you'd never marry Diane.
Well, I-I never, uh, said that exactly.
No, no, I think the exact
words were "I'd rather have
every hair on my body
pulled out simultaneously."
Well, that-that's just an expression.
I mean...
No, seriously, you know,
we all knew it was going
to happen sooner or later.
I just thought I'd get it over with.
Well, Diane, Sam,
congratulations to both of you.
Diane, I hope you're planning
to stay for the entire
ceremony this time.
Ours was... (laughs)
Ours was very touching, I thought.
Well, another one bites
the matrimonial dust.
I guess that leaves only one stud
to satisfy all the babes in this bar.
Yeah, I can handle it, too.
Hi.
I bet you never thought
you'd see the day, huh?
Nice shirt, Sam.
Is it new?
No, it's not. It, uh...
Did you hear what I said up there
about me and Diane getting engaged?
The beer distributor called.
He wants to know if he can change
the delivery day to Wednesday.
Carla,
I know that we haven't
always seen eye-to-eye,
but you could at least wish us well.
I need a draft.
Fascinating.
She's experiencing denial.
What's that mean, Dr. Crane?
Well, simply put, it
means that the human mind
blocks out that which it
cannot emotionally accept.
What's that mean, Dr. Crane?
It means that you don't understand this,
and you never will.
Oh.
I think perhaps I should get
personally involved in this.
After all, Carla is a good friend.
I think I could help her
alleviate her suffering.
Besides, there's nothing good on TV.
So I don't see any ring here.
What gives, you guys, huh?
Well, we're doing a little
window shopping. Yeah?
But she's got her eye
on a big ol' diamond
in the window of, uh,
Barton and Lyles. Yeah?
Oh, no, no, Sam.
Now that's much too expensive.
I would be content with any one
of the smaller stones we saw today.
Oh, now wait a second.
Hey, Woody, give me the
phone there, will ya?
Listen, you might as
well have the best ring.
You got the best husband.
Hmm?
Is it any wonder I love you?
I'm twice blessed.
I'm getting the most wonderful guy
and one helluva rock.
Yeah, let me, uh, let me find out
just how much this thing is here.
Yeah, find out there, Sammy.
Hi, uh, you got a ring in
the window there by the door?
It's a big diamond
with two little diamonds
on either side there.
Yeah, uh, that's the one.
Yeah, how-how much does that cost?
(laughs)
How much?
Fifty-two hundred.
(all laughing)
Boy, what am I going to do here?
Bruce. What?
Friend of mine in the jewelry business.
He buys diamonds and gold wholesale
and then you don't
have to pay the markup,
which is like a zillion percent.
Oh, you know, that-that's
kinda silly. No, no.
It's the same gold, same diamonds.
Well, if it's the same
ring, it's the same ring.
Absolutely.
Give me the phone. All right.
Yeah, I'll call the
guy. Yeah, do it, do it.
Uh, Sam, I don't think
that's a good idea.
Why not?
Diane's not the kind of
woman who'd like to find out
that her ring was bought from a jeweler
who begins every transaction
with, "Psst, buddy."
Oh, no, you make...
you're makin' it sound worse than it is.
I mean, I'm sure everything's legit.
All right, fine, Bruce. Great.
Psst, Sammy, come here.
Dee-daa. Huh?
Not bad for 1,200 bucks, huh?
WOODY: Wow, I'll say.
Hey, Carla, you, uh, see the ring
that Sammy got for Diane here?
You know, I'm thinking
about having my house texture-coated.
You have your choice
of 24 decorator colors.
Amazing.
Yeah, and surprisingly reasonable.
SAM: Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, you guys, you
want to see a classic?
Here, watch.
Hi, Diane. Hi, Sam.
Oh boy, hey, you know,
that finger looks a little warm there.
Maybe you should cool
it down with some ice.
(gasps): Sam.
What? What? What's the
matter? What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's beautiful.
Oh. Oh.
Just think, hours ago,
I was admiring this
magnificent ring in the window,
thinking it was an
unattainable treasure.
And now, here it is on my finger.
Yep, there it is, all right.
That's the one.
How about that, huh?
Oh, thank you, thank you.
Well, yeah... (chuckling)
Thank you. Yeah.
You're welcome.
NORM: Hey, uh, Carla, do you realize
that when Sammy and Diane get married,
uh, Diane's going to be your boss?
Nice shirt, Norm. Is it new?
Sam...
I felt that I couldn't
possibly ask you for this,
but now that you've actually gone out
and purchased it, I can tell you.
This is the only ring I ever wanted.
Mmm.
Where's the box?
Box?
Yeah, you know, the one it came in.
Oh, yeah, uh...
this, this one didn't seem to come
with one of those, did it?
Really?
Oh, I'm surprised they
didn't give you one,
especially considering how
much this must have cost.
Oh, well, they did, they did.
It's just that I told
them, uh, keep the box.
She'll just wear it.
That's what I said, all right.
(weak chuckle)
Sam?
Yeah.
This may sound frivolous,
but every woman wants to keep the box
that her engagement ring came in.
I already have a space reserved
for it in my memento drawer,
right between my French
Club pin and my retainer.
All right, all right.
I mean, fine, honey,
I'll just, uh, go on,
go back, and, uh... I'll get the box.
CLIFF: Uh, don't forget
your receipt there, Sammy.
Ah, they'll probably remember your face.
You can relax, everybody.
Got the box.
NORM: All right, Sammy.
They just, uh, gave it to ya, huh?
No, no, I had to buy something.
Oh, yeah?
Wha, wha, what'd you get?
Sterling silver corncob holders.
290 bucks.
Do you believe that?
Wow. Why'd you buy those things?
Well, everything else
seemed like such a rip-off.
I'm still way ahead, though. It's okay.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, sure.
Think about it.
Oh, Sam, there you are.
Yeah, and here you
are, my little darling.
One ring box, just your size.
How 'bout that, huh?
You happy?
Delirious.
Oh, good.
I just wish I'd gone with you
when you went back to Barton and Lyles.
I want to buy myself that dress.
Oh, which dress is that?
The one in the window.
Right next door in Justine's window.
Don't you remember?
I was admiring it as we walked by.
Oh, sure, sure, sure, yeah.
Yeah... oh, it's perfect.
I'd love it.
Well, you know, it's kinda slack now.
Why don't ya take off?
Do a little shopping.
Really? Yeah, go ahead.
Oh, Sam. Uh.
I'll get my purse.
All right.
So, uh, Sammy...
when Diane sees the ring
in the window of the fancy store
and also on her finger,
what do you think she'll say?
Well, I'm off.
Uh, no, Diane, uh, wait a second here.
Uh, I can't...
I can't let you go through with this.
What?
Well, uh, I, I bought
that dress for ya.
Sam Malone...
Yeah.
I don't believe you.
No, it's a fact.
It's in my car right up there.
Oh, you scamp.
Oh, go get it, please.
Uh, you know, I...
I was kinda hopin' to
surprise you with it.
Well, I already know about it now.
Right.
What am I standin' here for then, huh?
(laughing)
Oh...
Say, you know, that's, uh...
that was such an interesting dress.
How would you describe that color?
Pink.
Pink! Right.
You always know the perfect word.
Pink.
Who woulda thought?
I wonder what's keeping Sam.
He's certainly been gone a long time.
Where is Sam?
"Where is Sam?"
(quietly): I think she's starting
to relate to her environment again.
FRASIER: Well, I think
we've made great progress.
Carla,
can you tell me who Sam is?
Of course. He's my boss.
Did you know that he is
now engaged to be married?
Yes. I'm very happy for him.
See how well we've done?
Carla...
who is the charming soul
that has agreed to marry him?
Norm.
Well, I'm not the miracle worker.
Here we go.
The one you wanted and, uh, three more.
Oh, Sam!
What?
You impetuous fool. Oh, I love them.
(chuckling): Oh. Oh, thank you.
Uh-huh. Wait a minute.
You were gone an awfully long time.
I thought you were
just going to your car.
Well, I got a-a parking ticket,
and I, uh, I wanted
to fight it in court.
Do I, uh, detect a snafu there, Sammy?
Every damn dress in the window was pink.
Oh, boy, that must have,
uh, cost you a pretty penny.
That's all right.
I'll get some of it back.
She couldn't possibly
like all four of them.
Oh, Sam, I love all of them.
I can't decide which one
to wear tonight to dinner.
Oh, go... oh, boy, uh, right.
What did we say, uh, 7:00?
Oh, could we make it a little later?
I have to stop by the store
to get the ring appraised.
Pardon me?
The insurance man said
that there has to be
an appraisal on file
in order to have this
covered in my theft policy.
Boy, they, uh... they
don't make it easy, do they?
Uh, I'll tell you what.
Why don't you, uh, let me handle that?
I'll have it appraised.
Uh, why... yeah, why
don't you give me the ring?
Oh, no, Sam!
Just as our love is
forever, so is this ring.
From here on out,
it will never leave my finger.
Beautiful.
That's really beautiful.
Woody, you want to get
me some aspirin there?
Sam, I think this has gone too far.
You're caught in a quagmire of deceit.
You're just going to
sink deeper and deeper,
and to what avail?
To my butt's avail.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
Maybe I should just...
bite the bullet and be honest with her.
I mean, I really want
this relationship to work.
We do, too, Sammy.
Uh, Diane?
Yes.
I, uh, I have something
I want to say to you.
Uh, I'm afraid you're
not going to like it.
After receiving this...
beautiful symbol of
our relationship--
a symbol that has
touched me very deeply--
nothing you say could
ever disappoint me.
What is it?
I have to go to the doctor.
What for? No, it's nothing serious.
It's, uh...
I just figured that, you know,
we-we're getting married.
Uh, I might as well have a check-up
and make sure the old
Evinrude's still cranking.
I don't see any cause for alarm in that.
No.
In fact, I think it's quite sensible.
Good, good.
I love the dresses.
Oh, me, too.
Thanks so much.
Lovely.
So, uh, what now, Kemo Sammy?
It's no problem. It's no problem.
I'll just, uh... I'll
go back to the store
and I'll... I'll handle it.
Tell you, though... no way in the world
am I going to buy that expensive ring.
The ring is bought. Oh, yeah.
CLIFF: Oh, you shelled out
for the ring in the
window, didn't you, Sammy?
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
I got a real interesting price on it.
Full price?
Right around there, yeah.
As soon as I switch this one
for the... ring on her finger,
my problems are over.
Oh, Sam, what did the doctor say?
Same thing he always does: "Wow!"
But you're fine, yes?
SAM: Oh, yeah, no problem there.
No, uh...
You know, actually, I-I was sitting
in the, uh, waiting room there,
and I, uh, realized that, uh,
I had never officially put
that ring on your finger, and I'd...
well, I'd kind of like to.
Sam, you're just
sweeping me off my feet.
Um, okay, well, uh, close your eyes.
Why?
Uh, well, there, uh...
there-there's something
I want to say to you,
and, uh, I might get embarrassed
if-if you saw me... say it.
Okay.
All right. I can't wait to hear this.
Right...
Diane... you're really neat.
I think this big step we've taken
has made you positively goofy.
Well, maybe it has.
That's me-- just
one big goof.
(chuckles)
Yeah, they, uh... they
haven't found a chick
that can outsmart me.
All right, Sammy.
Did he say "chick" or "chimp"?
(phone ringing)
Cheers.
Uh, no, I'm sorry.
Norman is uncharacteristically absent.
May I... take a message for him?
Uh-huh.
Bruce wants to know about the ring?
Mm-hmm.
Uh-huh...
Yes, I think it's safe to say
that Sam's fiancée was
completely fooled by it.
Boy, I'm starved.
I hear it's a great restaurant.
You're quite the little
chatterbox tonight.
Oh, you want me to talk?
Well, it's not necessary.
Fine, I'll talk.
I don't appreciate
being given junk jewelry
and then lied to about it.
Oh, now, wait a second, that
is not junk jewelry, Diane.
Oh, Sam, please, no more lies.
How could you pledge
your troth with a paste ring?
Oh, that is not a paste ring!
All right, all right, there was...
there was another ring.
I... but I switched it
for the one in the window.
I swear to God I did, Diane!
Oh, please, don't bother swearing.
You have no idea what this day has...
I know this obviously
means nothing to you.
I'd rather go without than wear a lie.
SAM: No, no, no!
(tires screeching) (crashing)
Explain that part about
switching rings again.
Oh, there's something shiny!
No. Just another paper wrapper.
(sighs)
Oh, look at us. We're filthy.
Yeah.
By the way, I hate that dress.
Considering the circumstances
under which it was obtained,
it's hardly one of my favorites anymore.
Okay.
Then I can count on you not wearing it
when you visit me in the poorhouse
that you put me in.
Oh, Sam, get off it.
No, no, no, wait a second.
Le-Let's tally up the damages here.
The first ring was $1,200.
The box was $290.
Four lovely pink frocks was a mere $950.
The, uh, damages on the car
will be at least a grand.
And let's not forget
about the $5,200 bite
I was hoping to avoid
in the first place.
Bringing it to a grand
total of $9,000...
for a ring I no longer have.
Well, I hasten to add that this
was all of your own volition.
SAM: Ah...
$290 for the box?
Yeah.
Do you like... do you
like corn on the cob?
Well, I guess I'm just stupid to think
that I could make someone like you happy
on a budget of someone like me.
I'm sorry.
Well, you should be.
All right, I said I was!
Give me a bit of slack.
(sighs)
Even... had that been
the... bargain ring,
it would've been
sinfully impetuous
of me to cast it away.
Well, here's the bargain ring right now.
Why don't you give it
the old heave-ho, too?
Hmm...
Hmm.
I'm somehow reminded of a fable penned
by an anonymous 18th century author...
concerning the young mistress
of a great feudal estate
and a woodchopper who
worked on the estate...
Diane... not now, please?
Could I just tell you the moral?
What?
You're really neat.
Hardly a rich soul, I know.
The fact remains that...
no matter what the cost...
a ring is, above all else,
a symbol of the feelings
that two people have for each other.
So, truly, Sam, this is the ring I want.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, here.
Let me do this.
Uh...
But nothing says we can't keep looking.
(screaming): No!