Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
(bell ringing)
Oh, here you go,
pal. Let me, uh...
(laughs) Sorry.
I don't have any change on me.
That's all right.
God bless you anyway.
FRASIER:
Hey, Sam.
Hey, Frasier, how
you doing, man?
I tell you, I used to
have change all the time,
but things are tough now.
The bar burned down, you know.
This is the place right here.
Yeah, burned down,
and I've been spending
every dime I have
just to rebuild the place.
I don't have anyone to
blame but myself really.
And women. Oh, God.
(laughs)
Me and women.
Oh. Yeah, I tell
you, I think...
I think it first started for me
when I hired this really bright,
blonde waitress, you know.
Her name was Diane.
Maybe you heard about her.
Used to come in and out
of here all the time.
Five years ago,
books under her arm...
And then Rebecca, you
know, finally admitted,
"Yeah, I burned
the bar down."
I forgave her.
Good night, Sam.
Yeah, good night, Fras!
And then, listen to this.
Rebecca finally
admits to me, "Yes, I
burned the bar down."
(whoops) Was I mad, I tell you.
But what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna stick her
with guilt the rest of...
Sam?
Yeah?
There you go.
Thank you.
Come this way. Oh.
Here you go.
You earned it.
(theme song begins)
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Hey, guys.
Oh, hey, Sam.
Hey, listen, uh,
my folks sent me
a Christmas ham, and I wanted
to surprise Kelly,
so I'm putting him
in your office till the last
minute. Is that all right?
Fine with me.
Sure it will keep?
WOODY:
Oh, sure.
(squealing)
Unless some city boy
lets him out.
(squealing)
Oh, Woody, look.
He's so cute.
(baby talk):
Yes, you are. You're so sweet.
Oh, he's shivering.
Should we cover
him with something?
Well, not really.
Maybe with some honey glaze
and a little pineapple.
That is disgusting.
I can't believe
you'd even think
about killing
something this sweet.
Rebecca, where do you think
hams come from?
Big, funny-shaped
cans on aisle six.
(squealing)
Actually, I'm something
of an expert on that subject.
Big, funny-shaped cans?
No, Carla.
I happen to be a swine buff.
You see,
your porcine mammal is known
for his superior intelligence.
Well, that's true.
You know, back in Hanover,
they say pigs are smarter
than the people.
Actually, it's usually
the tourists who point that out.
(door opening)
Excuse me.
I'm looking for Sam Malone.
I'm Sam.
What can I do for you?
Oh. I'm, uh, Susan Methany.
My husband Kirby
bought your Corvette.
(liquid pouring,
glass clinking)
You... You've seen my Corvette?
Is it parked outside right now?
Wait. Oh, how is she?
How's she doing?
Wait a minute.
Let me... Let me get my shammy
from the office here!
No! Mr. Malone,
it-it's not here.
I just came here to ask
a few questions about it.
SAM:
Oh. Oh.
I'm sorry. I got a
little carried away.
You see, um, Kirby passed
away a couple months ago.
Oh. Well,
that is bad news.
It wasn't a car crash, was it?
Oh, no, no.
It-It was a
heart attack.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I mean, thank God that he's,
uh, not suffering anymore.
I'm sorry.
That came out wrong.
Let me... Sit down. Let me...
Let me buy you a
coffee or something.
Thank you.
Um... boy, that must be really
tough on you right now, huh?
Well, it's been a little rough,
but I'm getting over it.
Yeah.
And part of getting over it
is dealing with all
the details, like the car.
Oh.
My lawyer says I need
the vehicle ID number,
and I can't find it.
That's U510593947-D.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What am I doing?
Let me... Let me write
this down for you.
Although I, uh, do have
kind of a cute way of remembering this.
Uh, I made up a little song.
Want to hear it?
Yeah. I-I'm a kindergarten
teacher.
I get my fill
of cute little songs.
All right.
Maybe you could
just write it down.
Sure.
So, Susan.
So, what are you
gonna do with the car?
Um, I don't know.
I-I was just keeping it
in the garage.
I'm perfectly happy
driving my Volkswagen.
Excuse me.
Is that garage heated?
Oh, yes, yes.
Kirby insisted.
He was a little nuts
about the car, sweet as he was.
Okay, there you go.
Oh, thank you.
Do you have a pay phone?
Uh, my lawyer said I should
call him with the number.
Oh! Uh, here. No.
As a matter of fact,
use this one right here.
There you go.
Hey, guys...
I'm sorry. I'm just
a little excited
about your husband, uh...
(quietly):
Hey, fellas.
(laughs)
You know that guy Kirby
who, uh, bought my Corvette?
Dead.
Yeah.
Sorry, I can't be
happy for you, Sam.
I didn't know
him like you did. No, no, no.
No, no. No, I'm not happy
that the guy had a heart attack.
It's just that this is a chance
for me to get my Corvette back.
Oh, so, how do you figure
you're gonna get the car?
Oh, uh, that lady right there...
that's, uh...
that's the widow.
So, I figure, what?
You know, I just take her out
to dinner a few times,
let her get
to know me, you know,
pour on the charm,
and then, boom.
I'll lowball her, you know?
Well, this calls for a round
on the house, huh? Come on.
I don't have my car yet, man.
You, uh, kind of jumped the gun
on that one, huh, Norm?
Thank you, Mr. Monday
Morning Quarterback.
Thanks, Mr. Malone.
I won't bother you anymore.
Oh, uh, hold on
one second, there.
Let me just, uh...
Don't know how
to say this, but, uh,
I can only imagine what
you're going through
and everything at this point.
I just want you to know that
if you ever want to talk,
I'm a bartender, and that's
what I'm paid to do. I listen.
Well, thank you.
That's nice of you.
Yeah. Actually, you
know, what the heck.
I got a break right now.
You want to
take a walk in the park,
maybe, and just... talk?
All right, I'd like that.
Great, all right.
It'd be nice talking to someone
who's not six years old.
Yeah, I'll bet.
I'm getting my car back!
You are such a good boy.
(snorts) Yes, you are!
Yes, you did,
you used your litter box again!
Oh, he would make the best pet.
Hey, Woody,
would you consider selling him?
No, but I'll share him.
You will?
Sure. The day after Christmas,
I'll bring you some sandwiches.
Woody, why would you
say things like that?
Miss Howe, I think
you're getting a little
too attached to this pig.
I am not, am I, Snuffles?
No, I'm not getting
too attached to you.
Whoa, Sammy, what's up?
You're breaking out
the good stuff.
Yeah. Susan's coming over again.
So, Sam, how are things
between you and Susan?
Oh, uh, you know,
pretty good, pretty good.
You know, I take her out,
we talk.
We talk about school,
about Kirby, life.
You know, everything
under the sun.
Funny thing is,
the more we talk,
the more she likes me.
The more she likes me,
the more she trusts me.
And the more she trusts me,
the closer I get to
snagging that car.
Did anyone else's blood
just run cold?
Oh, come on.
I'm not doing
anything wrong here.
Give me a break, man.
You know, I'm helping her
out, as a matter of fact.
She's going through some
pretty difficult times.
I'm taking her mind off of it.
In other words,
you deserve that car.
Well, I didn't want to say it,
but I'm glad someone
sees it my way, yeah.
All right! Well,
let's celebrate, huh?
This calls for a round
on the house.
No, no, no, I haven't gotten
the car quite yet, Norm.
You're severely
off your game, my friend.
Game? You call this a game?
Sammy, I don't know why you're
going to all this trouble.
She told you that she keeps
the car in a garage, right?
You say the words, my kids
are over there in 20 minutes.
In 25, your car
is speeding down the highway.
Worse comes to worse,
they put them away
for a couple of years.
I mean, it's not like
I'm rattling around
in an empty house.
You're very sweet.
I appreciate that,
but, you know,
I've put a lot of energy
and time into this plan.
I think I'm gonna
stick with it.
(door opening)
(singsongy):
Where is Aunt Carla?
There's Aunt Carla.
Isn't he the cutest
thing you've ever seen?
Yeah. He's gonna make
a nice football.
(whispering)
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna save a life.
I'm gonna drive Snuffles way out
in the country
and give him his freedom.
He'll be free!
Free, I tell you!
And he'll always remember
the person who gave him
his freedom- Rebecca Howe.
This is the best thing
I've ever done.
I don't mind saying,
that is one screwed up broad.
Hey, Susan.
Hi, Sam.
Can I get you something?
Juice and cookies?
Uh, it was arts
and crafts today.
Make it bourbon and water.
(laughs)
Sam?
Yeah.
I've got to tell you,
this past week has been great.
You've really pulled me
out of my shell.
Well, I'm glad to hear that.
Guess what.
What?
I brought the Corvette.
Oh!
Oh, my old car, right.
Yeah, I almost forgot.
Yeah. Uh,
it's blue, right?
No, red.
Red, red, right.
Right, right.
Flame red, actually, but...
It felt kind of weird
driving it.
Oh!
Well, yeah, of course
it did, of course.
Why didn't I think of that?
Yeah, it reminds
you of Kirby. Yeah.
You know, it's
none of my business,
but I'm gonna say this anyway.
I think you should sell it.
I'm having a thought here.
Maybe...
No, that's crazy, that's crazy.
Well, what? What?
Well, I-I was just
gonna say that,
you know, if-if you're gonna
sell it, and, like we said,
we think you should,
then, um,
why don't you sell it to me?
Oh, Sam.
No, you don't have
to do that for me.
No! No, I
insist, I insist.
See, my-my only problem
is that I don't think
I can afford the
fair market value.
You know, maybe only like
ten grand over the
next two years?
You know what?
Let's do it.
I-I-I never drive it,
and-and you love it,
so it's yours.
Great. I think
this is a great idea.
I tell you what- let me, uh,
let me go get a check,
and, uh, we'll go out to dinner
and we'll celebrate.
Oh, what are you guys
celebrating?
I just sold Sam my car.
Oh, that's great.
That's all he's been
talking about.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
Well, he's had his eye
on that car
since the day you walked
in the door.
Okay, here we go.
Here's the check.
Uh, do me a favour,
do not cash this right away.
You know, Sam,
if you wanted my car so badly,
all you had to do was ask.
I mean, you didn't have to, uh,
waste a week pretending
to be my friend.
Here- take it.
How about that.
I got my car back.
Didn't cost me a penny!
(chanting):
Sammy! Sammy!
Come on, come on. Sammy!
Come on, you'll have fun.
Sammy! Sammy!
Woody, we're running
low on pretzels.
I know, Miss Howe.
I set them all free
to live in the wild.
Woody, I let your pig
go three days ago
and I've apologized every day.
Let's just drop it.
There is a quarter
of an inch scratch
on the right fender.
You can't miss it.
No!
It disfigures the entire car!
Listen, I want you to send
your tow truck over right now.
Are you laughing at me?
You know, fine, I'll
tell you something.
I'm gonna take my business
some place else.
Sam, may I have a beer please?
And let me guess-
you dinged the Corvette again.
Yeah.
Boy, I don't know, it's weird.
It's the fourth scratch
I've had in a week.
I don't know what's going on.
Maybe I need to check my eyes
or something.
Yes. Your eyes.
Oh, what's that
supposed to mean, huh?
Sam, this is not
a personal attack.
I am trying to help you.
Look, the way you got that car
back was shameful.
It went against
your better instincts.
Now, deep down,
you don't think you deserve
to have that car,
and I submit
that subconsciously
you are trying to destroy it!
Hey, you know, take your
business someplace else!
Go on! Get out of here!
NORM:
Sammy!
Sammy, settle down now!
Frasier could very well
have a point there!
You know something?!
Or maybe not, okay?
The guy's a quack.
Sammy.
Sammy!
You scammed a poor, innocent
widow out of her car.
Now, on many levels,
I can respect that.
But somehow, this one
crossed the line.
I know, you're right.
Yeah, and another thing.
Remember what I told you
about hitting the customers?
Yeah, I know.
I-I forgot.
That's-That's your turf.
It's-It's just that
I have so little.
I know.
I'm sorry, you...
I'm sorry, Frasier.
I'm-I'm under a lot
of pressure here.
I mean, I should be having fun
with that car, and I'm not.
It's driving me crazy.
Do you really think
there's something to that,
you know, subconscious
guilt and shame stuff?
It depends.
Yeah? On what?
Are you going to hit me again?
Oh, no.
I'm sorry, man.
No, of course not.
I... I know you're right.
I've been feeling
like a real heel
ever since she gave
me the keys.
I mean, she's so sweet
and so innocent,
you know, and I was just
making her believe
I was her friend so I
could snag the car.
Sam, you must find Susan
and beg her forgiveness.
It's your only hope.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, thank you. You're right.
I-I'm out of here.
You know, Sammy, another way
you could go is just
to get rid of the object
of your guilt.
Cliff, you can't have the car.
Okey dokey.
(phone rings)
Cheers. Hello.
Hello?
Cheers.
Turn the phone around.
Right side up.
Right side up!
Yeah. That's much better.
Ah.
Woody, it's your dad.
Hi, Dad.
Hello?
I can't hear...
Dad!
You're kidding.
Oh, my God.
That's unbelievable.
Wow! Well, that's...
I'm relieved.
Well, say hi to Mom, okay?
All right.
Bye.
Miss Howe, you aren't
gonna believe this.
Guess who showed up in my folk'
back door last night?
Who?
Snuffles.
Yeah, I guess he found his way
onto the back of a truck
that was headed that way.
I-I told you he was smart.
I can't believe this.
You see, he travelled all
that distance to get home
where he was safe and sound.
This is a Christmas miracle.
I'll say.
Mom said he was delicious.
Now remember, tomorrow
we're going to visit the zoo,
so everybody bring
your permission slips.
What's a zoo again?
Uh, it's a place where they have
a lot of animals.
Even tigers?
Yes, they have tigers
at the zoo.
What if the tigers eat us?
That's why you need
your permission slips.
Uh, quiet time, everybody-
hit the mats!
Come on.
(knocking on glass)
(overlapping chatter)
Shh!
I am teaching class.
Yeah, I know.
This'll only
take a second, please.
Why are you here?
I tried to call you at home,
but you-you didn't
answer the phone.
I-I've got to get
something off my chest.
What? I mean, you got
your precious car.
What else do you want from me?
Susan, please, let me just try
to explain something to you.
That-That car...
used to be my entire life,
you know, and when you...
when you got it,
I-I just went crazy
for a second.
I'm sorry.
I really hurt you
and I'm sorry,
and I-and I want to make it up
to you. Here...
and I want to give you
the fair market value
of the car.
This check is just
the down payment.
Please, I-I'm sorry.
Well, you did hurt me.
But I guess I understand.
I mean, the car was
your whole life.
Oh, thanks.
So you forgive me?
No, I don't forgive you.
I'm sorry, what...
You heard me...
I don't forgive you.
I mean, my whole life
I-I've let people walk
all over me.
And-And the minute
that they start to feel
a little bit guilty,
I-I let them off the hook.
Well, no more.
For the first time in my life,
I'm not going
to forgive somebody.
Yeah!
(giggles)
It feels good not forgiving.
Yeah, well, not to me
it doesn't.
I mean, listen,
why-why don't you forgive me
and not forgive some other guy.
You know, an every other thing.
Sam, if you feel
guilty, I'm glad.
You deserve it.
Now excuse me. I have
a class to teach.
Oh, no, listen, I'm not leaving
until you forgive me.
Sorry.
I'm serious.
Listen, this is very
important to me, Susan...
Oh, my God.
What did you do to those kids?
(quietly):
It's quiet time.
Now go.
No, hey, I...
I'm sitting right here
until you forgive me.
All right, then you're
just gonna have to be a part of class.
Whatever.
All right.
All right, quiet time is over.
Everybody up.
Back to your chairs.
Boys and girls,
I would like you all
to meet someone.
This is Sam.
ALL:
Hi, Sam!
Yeah, hi, boys and girls.
Listen, I'm gonna
be sitting right here
until your teacher forgives me.
So you just carry on.
Go ahead.
Class, do you remember
when we were talking
about telling the truth?
ALL:
Yes.
Well, Sam here told a fib.
ALL:
Boo!
And what
kind of people tell fibs?
ALL:
Bad people!
Oh, wait.
Hold on a second.
So, I did a bad thing.
Please, just can't you
forgive me?
And where do fibbers go?
ALL:
In the doghouse!
I'm sorry.
In the what?
ALL:
In the doghouse!
Oh, come on, Susan,
not the doghouse.
This is...
Oh, come on, this is stupid.
I've already given
you the check.
What more do you want?
Can fibbers buy their way
out of the doghouse?
ALL:
No!
So, why don't you just sit there
and think about
what you've done?
The rest of us will get
out our art supplies.
ALL:
Yay!
This doghouse is stupid.
And it's made out of cardboard.
I-I could get out of
here anytime I want.
I could.
Good-bye. Don't forget
your permission slips.
Okay.
Bye. Bye.
Sam, I've got to say,
you're quite a sport.
You made it through the morning
and the afternoon classes.
Yeah. Well, I'll
tell you the truth.
I was going to leave
a couple hours ago
but my... my legs
kind of froze up.
Oh, boy!
Listen, uh...
I, uh... I've
been mulling it over,
especially during the,
uh... quiet time,
and I... I think that...
I think you should
take the car back.
What?
Yeah. Come on.
I-I'm never going
to enjoy it.
I... I think
you should drive it.
And please,
once again, I'm sorry.
I acted like a real jerk.
I forgive you.
You what?
I said I forgive you.
I just won't
forgive the next guy.
Hey, thank you.
That means a lot to me.
Say, uh...
this may not be
the right time or anything,
but you want to
go out and grab something to eat?
You serious?
Yes. Yes. I-I...
You know, I owe you one.
You know, we spent a lot
of time together last week.
I kind of miss it.
All right.
Why don't we take your car?
My car?
Are you serious?
Yeah. But if you
miss one payment...
Yeah. I know, I know.
In the doghouse.
You'll wish.
You know, for a minute there,
when you were asking me out,
I thought maybe you were
trying to get to Kirby's boat.
Oh, come on.
Kirby had a boat?