Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Woods, refill, please.
Yeah, sure.
Whatever you want.
Hey, hey, hey.
Why so down
in the mouth there, bud?
Well, I'm understudying
another play,
and I know I'm never gonna
get to go on,
because the star
never gets sick.
But, darn it, the part
is perfect for me.
Yeah?
What is that part?
Moses.
My theater group
is doing an original play,
An Evening With the Prophets.
Mm.
I got more lines than any
of the other Israelites.
( chuckles )
But I managed to jam
them all in,
right up here.
Mm.
Yeah, your head
looks packed, all right.
Go on, test me.
Give me a cue.
All right.
( muttering )
Well, what's the first line?
"And I have said
I will bring you up
"out of the affliction
of Egypt
"under the land
of the Canaanites
"and the Hittites,
and the Amorites
"and the Parasites,
and the Hivites."
Wait, wait, wa-wa-wait.
What, uh, what happened
to the Cellulites?
NORM:
They, uh,
settled in the land of Vera.
( laughing ):
Did you hear what he said?
( piano plays )
¶ Making your way
in the world today ¶
¶ Takes everything you've got
¶ Taking a break
from all your worries ¶
¶ Sure would help a lot
¶ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ¶
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You want to be
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ You want to go
where people know ¶
¶ People are all the same
¶ You want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name. ¶
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Here we go.
Thank you.
Boy, what a day.
Yeah?
Yeah, I can't wait
for it to end.
All I can think about
is getting home
and jumping into bed.
Need anybody to
break your fall?
Hi. Sam Malone.
Hi. Suzanne Porter.
How do you do?
Sam, you done picking
up on this lady?
( clears throat )
Not quite, Woody.
Well, I'm sorry to
interrupt you, but, uh,
Denise called.
Oh, Denise.
Who's Denise?
Um... uh,
my brother's kid.
Uh, Denise.
Yeah, I have to say hi
to her, and De-nephew.
( both laughing )
Very smooth, Sam.
Very funny.
Uh, so who's
this Denise?
Aw, she was somebody...
we had quite a thing
going there a while ago.
And then we both realized
that sex wasn't anything
to base a relationship on, so...
six months later,
we broke up.
NORM:
Uh-huh.
Yeah, she must be quite a dish
if you're willing to pass up
on door number
one over there.
Well, it's kind of
like avocados.
One of them's ripe,
and ready to be squashed
into guacamole.
And the other one needs
to stay on the shelf
a little while longer.
( both laughing )
WOODY:
Well, anyway,
call her back--
she says it's urgent.
Ah, with the accent
on "urge," huh?
Hmm!
Actually, you know,
I think, uh,
this is a call I should
return in person.
Aw, Sam!
Whoa, hey!
Where are you going?
Uh, to my niece's house.
Her grandma's sick.
If it's your niece's grandma,
wouldn't that be your mother?
My mom's sick?
Oh, my God!
Excuse me. Why don't
you stick around for
a little while?
My mom bounces right back.
Hey, Sam, hey, uh,
back from the Denise
decathlon, huh?
( Cliff chuckles )
Got a, uh, another gold medal
in the "broad" jump?
You know,
you got a big mouth, Clavin.
Hey, he happens
to be right, you know.
Yeah, it's a genetic quirk
in the, uh, Clavin family
that we all have
two extra teeth.
Yeah, you see,
that's the only way
that we can prove
that we are the rightful heirs
to the Russian throne.
Hello in there, Cliff.
Tell me...
what color is the
sky in your world?
What's wrong?
Carla, I just want to be left
alone for a while, all right?
You got it.
Thank you.
Hey, everybody,
Sam wants to be left alone!
Okay, Sammy,
spill your guts.
What's the matter?
Carla, I just said
that I-I want...
Yeah, but
you're gonna end up
telling me eventually,
so you might as well
get it over with.
Go on,
make you feel better.
Just keep this
to yourself.
Remember how I went
over to Denise's house?
Well, she... she didn't invite
me over for a good time.
She wanted to
show me something.
What?
My child.
Seven pounds,
ten ounces,
a baby boy.
( laughs )
( laughing continues )
What's so funny?
Sam Malone finally got caught
with his hand in the cookie jar.
( laughs )
Carla, come on.
This is serious.
Oh, of course it is, Sam.
But I really think
you're gonna be okay, you know?
Yeah?
Just remember this.
This little piggy
went to market...
( laughing )
Would you...?
This is not funny.
I'm sorry.
You sure it's yours?
No, it's between me
and another guy.
But the kid's a real looker,
so, you know,
you figure it out.
So when are you
gonna find out, Dad?
Soon.
I mean, she dragged me down
to a lab
to have a blood test.
Well, what's
the big deal, you know?
You can just do
what all the other jerks do.
You pay a little money
for support,
and you get off the hook.
No, Carla, it means a lot more
to me than that.
I'm telling you,
if this, if this kid is mine,
then... then I want
to see that he's fed,
that he's clothed,
and that he's educated.
You know,
I'm-I'm gonna take
him to, to
Little League games, too.
I'm gonna be the
best damn father
you've ever seen.
Please don't let
him be mine!
Oh!
I tell you, if I get
out of this, I swear to God,
I am through fooling around
forever.
Sam, don't swear to God.
No, I mean it, I mean it,
if I get out of this,
I swear to God,
I'll never have sex again.
You?
Never?
Yeah, not ever.
I mean, for the rest...
Well, three months,
three months.
Well, I guess the amount of sex
you have in three months
is what most people
have in a lifetime.
Huh.
If they're attractive, I guess.
You have a phone call
from Denise.
( sighs )
Oh, and Carla,
you know that, uh,
pitcher of beer
you left on your tray?
Some guy from table six
came and drank it.
We don't have a table six.
I knew I should have said
table five.
Hello.
Oh, hi, Denise.
Um, what'd the doctor say?
Oh, thank God,
oh, thank God!
Oh, thank God! Oh!
Oh, I'm so happy.
Well, I'm so happy
for the other guy.
Yeah.
Congratulations, huh?
All right, we-well,
I'll call you
some other time
then, all right?
Bye-bye.
Doctor, Sam?
Uh, yeah, uh,
Denise and I and this, uh,
other guy
share the same doctor
and she just wanted
to let me know
that he had gotten
some new magazines
in the waiting room.
You lucky dog!
Must be the
Sports Illustrated
"Swimsuit Issue."
Say, uh... Suzanne,
uh... what do you say,
you want
to help me celebrate here?
I'd love to.
Great.
What are we celebrating?
I have no idea,
but whatever it is
we're overdressed.
( Carla clears throat ):
Sam?
Yeah?
Uh, Sam, aren't you
forgetting something?
I know, I know, I'm gonna
drop by the old drug store.
Don't worry,
I learned my lesson.
Could you wait just...?
What?
Does the name "God"
ring a bell?
Yeah?
The guy you
made a vow to?
Oh.
Yeah, boy, I almost
forgot about that.
Uh... it's no big thing.
"No big thing"?
Come on, God's a sport.
People make promises
like that all the time,
but if God had to collect
on all of them,
He wouldn't have any time
to create
natural wonders like that,
for instance.
I'll see you...
Oh, boy.
Give me a minute here.
CARLA:
Listen, Sammy,
I don't want to tell you
how to run your life,
but I want to tell you this:
don't mess with God.
Look at all the people
in the Bible who did.
The entire population
of Sodom and Gomorrah.
Lot's wife-- turned into
a salt lick with boobs.
Come on, what...
What's He gonna do--
reach down from the clouds
and snatch me up?
You know, you...
Halt, infidel!
Hey, sorry, Sam.
Uh, I was just at
an understudy rehearsal.
I thought you might get
a kick out of my costume.
( panting ):
You ought to warn people
before you go around
pretending to be God.
You thought I was God?
Thanks.
I was only trying to be Moses.
Hey, guys, he thought I was God!
Sam, can we go now?
Yeah, you bet.
No, no, Sam!
He has sent
His messenger.
Me...? What messenger?
That is just Woody.
You think it's a coincidence
that Woody came in
just at that very moment
dressed as Moses?
I mean, of all the plays he
could have been in, Sammy.
He could have been
dressed as Auntie Mame.
Would that have
scared you?
Yeah, a little.
Let's face it, Sam,
that was a warning,
and you'd better
take heed.
Oh, come on,
what's He gonna do?
Well, my cousin Tino...
Yeah?
...swore he'd
give up meat.
That night,
he ate a burger.
The next day,
his teeth fell out.
Oh, come on, Carla.
There's no connection here.
I swore I would
not have sex, so...
( shudders )
Listen, I-I-I'm not
really in the mood anymore.
Why not?
Carla's cousin Tino's
teeth fell out.
Yeah, well, maybe
some other time.
Uh...
Why don't you
give me a call?
Yeah. I-I don't
have your number.
Perfect.
Oh... are you satisfied,
God's Little Helper?
Oh, listen, Sam.
Uh, in the interest
of authenticity,
you think there's anyway
I can sound
less like God
and more like Moses?
Yeah, stop going
around scaring people.
That's good.
That's good,
now, how 'bout the voice?
Now sit down.
Now...
how can I be of help?
Well, I would like
your advice, Father.
Actually, it's for
a friend of mine.
He, uh...
got himself into kind of a bind,
and so, in desperation, promised
God he'd give up something.
And what did he promise
to give up?
Sweets.
Oh.
I see.
( chuckles )
Yeah...
but my friend
really likes sweets a lot.
You know, and sweets
like him a lot.
And he hasn't had sweets now
for about two weeks,
and if he doesn't have sweets
soon, he's gonna explode.
I see, and God's
contractual obligation
was to get your friend
out of this bind you spoke of.
Yes, sir. Which He did.
Well, then, what is the problem?
Well, m-my friend was wondering
what the penalty would be
if he, say... you know, had a...
huge box of chocolates.
Sam, I think this is between you
and your God.
Yeah, right.
Oh, how did...
How'd you know it was me?
In all the years people
have been coming here
for their friends, I have never
met one of their friends.
Oh, well, yeah,
as long as I'm busted,
I guess I might as well tell you
the truth here.
I-I didn't promise
to give up sweets.
I promised to give up sex.
Ah...
that is a tough one.
You know, Sam, the Church
does recommend chastity
to unmarried people.
( chuckles )
Oh, I'm sorry.
You were serious. Uh...
How do you do that?
I mean, what do you do?
How do you not?
I mean, a-are there
special tricks, or a
certain way
of sitting, maybe?
Well, yes, but we are strictly
forbidden to reveal it.
You're kidding.
Yes.
Oh.
You know, Sam, I think
you're looking for someone
to tell you it's all right
to break your vow,
but I can't
do that.
You know, I've found that people
who come here
looking for answers usually
know what the answer is,
and I think you do, too.
Yeah, maybe.
Well, thank you.
Oh...
Oh, no, no, no.
SAM:
Carla, Carla?
Oh, great.
Look. I think I got it.
God's gonna have
to accept this one.
"With the Lord, one day
is as a thousand years,
and a thousand years
is as one day."
So?
So that means
I've been out of action
for 21,000 years.
Come on, that's got to
be good enough for Him.
You know, Sam, I-I'd
like to agree with you--
( sighs )
since you're so
pathetic it's annoying--
but no sale.
All right, all right,
I still got Deuteronomy here.
Don't look, Sammy.
Temptation at 12:00.
Oh...
Oh... Oh, God.
Man, they're coming in waves.
( phone ringing )
Cheers.
Yeah, this is him.
You're kidding.
Moses has an ear infection.
Yeah, all right. Yeah.
I'll be right there.
So, Woody, they gonna
let you go on?
Uh, no, I got to stop
by the drugstore
and pick up some antibiotics.
So, believe it or not,
I've given up sex entirely.
But you got to promise
not to tell anybody.
Well, Sam,
confidentiality
is the bedrock
of my profession.
Besides, who'd
believe me?
You were saying?
Well, I was just wondering
what you think I ought to do.
Well, you need to find
another outlet for
your sexual energies.
Mm-hmm.
For example,
during six painfully frustrating
months of my adolescence,
I built a submarine
in our basement.
One of those
little plastic models?
No, life-size. Slept six.
The happiest hours
of my youth were spent
down there in the dark
shouting, "Fire one.
Fire two."
Well, enough about me.
Let's address
this problem, Sam.
Well, I don't know
anything about submarines.
Well, surely you
have other interests.
Sports, sailing, music?
Well, yeah, I had a
piano lesson once.
Actually, I had
the piano teacher
and it was twice, but...
I liked it.
Well, I'll tell you.
If you were to sit down
at the piano today
and channel your energies
into it,
you would find
all your sexual tensions
pouring out
through your fingertips.
Yeah, fingertips.
Yeah, right.
And best of all, Sam,
no matter how badly you perform,
a piano never laughs.
Never stomps out of the room
and refuses to let you
play again for three days.
Well, I'm off to Lilith.
( yawning ):
Sam?
Would you please
lock up?
Uh, yeah.
I'm going home to bed.
Okay, good night.
Did you hear me?
I said I'm going
to go to bed.
Well, I hope you, uh,
get a good night's sleep.
Thank you.
Carla, I just left myself
wide open
for one of Sam's sleazy remarks,
and nothing.
I mean, not that I want to,
but what does it mean
when you can't turn on the
horniest guy that ever lived?
I am really getting old.
Oh, Rebecca, would you
stop being ridiculous?
You're still a young,
beautiful, vibrant woman
with her whole life
ahead of her.
Oh, you're just saying that.
Yes, I am.
I was taught to humor old folks.
Carla, I ca...
I can't take this anymore.
I mean, I tried everything.
I've stopped eating oysters,
I'm taking cold showers,
I even started stuffing ice
in my pockets.
I tell you, I'm not going
to make it.
Oh, Sammy, buck up.
You only have
nine more weeks to go.
I'm talking about tonight.
Guess who?
Uh-oh.
I'll give you a hint.
Vermont ski lodge,
a roaring fire,
and baby oil.
Uh... could you, uh,
be more specific?
Gravity boots.
Oh, Rachel Patterson.
( laughs )
Oh, look...
Hi, Sam, how are you?
Oh, boy.
I tell you, honey,
you're the last person
in the world I want
to see right now.
Nice to see you, too.
Uh...
Listen, I have got
an 18-hour layover,
and I'm not
the least bit sleepy.
How'd you like to help me
kill some time?
Listen, what, um...
Actually, I hear, uh,
movies are good for
that kind of thing.
Why don't you, uh, why
don't you take in about
two or three
right in a row, there?
I know-- smell.
I'm wearing that perfume
that always drove you so crazy.
Oh, Devastation, huh?
Uh...
Actually, I got this, uh,
this head cold.
Uh, I wouldn't want
you to catch it.
Um, I'm sorry, uh...
what do you say,
some other time, huh?
Well, okay.
Oh, Sam?
Yeah?
A friend of mine
snapped this
of me on a beach in Ipanema.
I thought
you might like a copy.
Oh.
Would you excuse me
just for a
minute here?
Look at this!
I mean, this is not fair.
I mean, I'm going for it.
It's-it's not
like I'm murdering anybody.
I-I'm just going to bring
a great deal of pleasure
to two people.
So, if in Your,
uh, infinite wisdom,
You feel You have
to smite me down,
then please
make it quick and painless.
And if You could give me
about three hours,
I'd appreciate it.
Okay.
Sam?
( sniffing )
Devastation.
The hound is loose.
Please, go easy on him.
Sammy, now you've done it.
There's nothing
in your future but
frogs and locusts.
Why'd you have to
go and do it, Sammy?
I didn't do it.
What?
We went to the hotel,
she got into bed,
I got into bed with her.
Then I was folding up my socks,
and I was...
You fold up
your socks?
Sure. I'm not an animal.
Anyway, all of a sudden,
for no reason,
I went over and I,
and I opened
the nightstand drawer.
And there it was,
staring right up at me.
The Bible.
Can you imagine that--
a Bible in a hotel room?
So, we... we got out of there
real quick,
and we got another room, and...
there it was again.
I mean, we... we went
from hotel to hotel,
and it just followed us
wherever we went.
Then it dawned on me.
This was a bona fide miracle.
God was speaking
to me directly
through hotel nightstands.
He works in mysterious ways.
Amen. Amen.
Excuse me,
Sam, but, uh
in all the years
you played baseball,
traveling
throughout the country,
all the hotel rooms
you stayed in,
didn't you ever once notice...?
Uh, Frasier,
Sam was just telling us
about a miracle
that affected him
very deeply.
Now, what was it
that you were noticing?
Well, th-they always put
those little strips of paper
across the toilets.
Just an observation.
Sammy, I'm so proud of you.
( chuckling ):
Yeah.
If you could hold out
last night,
you can make it
the whole three months.
Sam, I'm late for a party.
Can you help me
with this zipper?
Sam? Sam?
Sam...!
Piano. Piano, Sam.
For God's sake, piano!
Carla?
( playing "Chopsticks" )
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/64sv
Help other users to choose the best subtitles