Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Oh, hi, Dr. Sternin.
Dr. Crane isn't here.
I know. He's at home,
and that's why I'm not.
CARLA:
Whoa-ho!
Trouble in Casa de Wacko?
Not really.
Scotch, Woody.
I'm just not looking
forward to going home.
Frasier's giving me
every indication
that he expects me
to indulge in another one of his
silly little fantasies tonight,
but it's really rather personal.
I know just
what you mean.
Husbands can drive you nuts
about stuff like that.
Take my Eddie.
He borrowed this
fairy princess costume
from the ice show.
Really.
Every Friday night,
I have to dress up
and put a magic
sex spell on him.
Well, as long
as we're sharing,
here's what I have
waiting for me.
Every so often,
Frasier likes
to regress
to his childhood.
First, he insists
on calling me Mommy.
I fix him cinnamon toast
and strawberry milk.
Then it's bath time--
one of my favorites--
followed by my
tucking him into bed
and singing "All the
Pretty Little Horses."
After that,
we make love until
the windows rattle.
Men! They're really
something, aren't they?
Oh, by the way, about all
that fairy princess stuff?
I was just kidding.
So was I.
Oh, right, Mommy.
Hey, guys, get
a load of this!
Oh! Carla! Carla!
( piano plays )
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You want to go where everybody
knows your name. ¶
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Afternoon, everybody.
ALL:
Norm!
Hey, Mr. Peterson. There's
a cold one waiting for you.
I know. And, if she calls,
I'm not here.
You're just the man
I want to see here.
Listen, I want you taste
this Bloody Mary for me.
Oh, please, Sammy.
Not again.
We did this
all day yesterday.
And we're going to do it all day
today until we get this right.
Now, listen up, everybody.
I am not losing
the Bloody Mary contest
to Gary's Olde Towne Tavern
again.
Now, please.
I got Rebecca out there.
I got Carla out there.
They all got their
little jobs to...
The least you can do
is taste this for me.
All right, all right.
There you go.
Huh?
What do you think?
Not bad, Sammy.
Yeah?
Yeah. I mean,
it's a little thick, but, uh...
All in all,
I'd have to say it was...
( choking )
That's great. I get the point,
man. That's very funny.
No, no. I actually...
I rather liked that one.
Hey, hey. Whoa, whoa.
Would you guys stop
horsing around here?
I'm serious. I want
this guy Gary,
and I want him bad.
I am tired
of having him
do everything
better than we do.
He's got a better
softball team,
a better
tag football team.
Better T-shirts.
They have T-shirts?
Here. I'll show you.
NORM:
Oh, yeah.
I've got that one in red.
Ooh! They have
them in red now?
CLIFF:
But you got
to preorder.
They're 100% cotton.
All the sizes
are very true.
I'll order one
this afternoon.
Listen, you guys
are not taking
me seriously.
I mean it. I want
to hurt this guy
where he lives.
Speaking of that,
have you seen his house?
He's renovating this
beautiful old Victorian.
It's on the cover
of Boston magazine.
I saw that.
I hear he's coming out
with a new T-shirt of it, too.
You guys are
not helping me.
Sammy, I'm back.
Well, what took you so long?
I just spent the last two hours
wandering through the streets
of Chinatown,
thanks to your
brilliant directions.
What? What?
"Look for a shop
with a dead duck
hanging in the window."
I defy you to find
a shop in Chinatown
without a dead duck
in the window.
Anyway...
I got it.
You are looking
at the last ounce
of black cardamom on
the Eastern seaboard.
Ooh...
Nice. Sammy, let's
see that stuff, huh?
Sammy, you really
think that stuff
is going help us
win the contest?
Are you kidding me?
Wait until you see
what this does
to the taste of a Bloody Mary.
Whoo, boy!
This is pretty pungent stuff,
huh?
( chuckles )
( sneezes )
Oh, my God! My allergy.
Did someone bring some
black cardamom in here?
CARLA:
Woody! It's all gone!
Great. There goes the contest.
Well, big deal.
In about 20 minutes,
I'm going to swell up
like a blowfish.
Well, what... what
are we supposed to do now?
Usually, I pack
my face in ice.
Sam, guess what
I've got under my coat.
If I guess right,
can I keep them?
No, you idiot.
I've got some of Gary's
top secret Bloody Mary mix.
Hey, way to go,
Rebecca!
Baby, how did you get it?
How do you
think I got it?
You did that dorky twirl,
and, when he laughed,
you grabbed it and ran.
Okay, fine. Forget it.
I'm not going to tell you.
Oh, come on.
We won't make fun of you.
All right.
That thing Carla said.
Well, I'm the one
that got it.
Well, that's good.
That's good.
Now I'm going to take it down
to the company
pharmaceutical division
and have it analyzed
to find out
Gary's secret ingredient.
CLIFF:
No, no. No need
to do that, Rebecca.
Sammy, pour me a shot
of that concoction.
I'll tell you
exactly what's in it.
Oh, man, I don't know.
No, no, no. I've got very
sensitive taste buds.
As a matter of fact,
in medieval times,
Clavins were
the royal tasters.
I heard they
were royal something.
Well, I don't know
what's in it,
but Gary makes the
best Bloody Mary
I've ever tasted.
NORM:
All right, Sammy,
set me up with
a shot of that, huh?
Let me have
some of that.
Hey, hey, you guys,
don't drink it all.
I have to take
some to the lab.
This is great.
Gary deserves to win
this contest every year.
It's almost worth cramming
myself into this dress.
Hey, I'd dress up
as a hooker
to get some
of this stuff.
Oh, come on, you guys.
It can't be that special.
I suppose you're going
to tell me
that Cheers has never made
a Bloody Mary this good.
Sammy, Cheers never
made anything this good.
I wonder what's in it.
( sneezes )
( jar breaks )
Well, we know
there's black cardamom in it.
Damn it, Woody!
Ah! Cheers...
where good times go to die.
CLIFF:
Well, well, well!
If it isn't Gary from
Gary's Olde Towne Tavern.
Look, pal,
didn't I tell you
if you step one
more foot in here
you'd have me
to answer to?
Yeah, and I told you
if you got in my way
you'd wind up
in the next zip code.
Then we have had
this discussion, huh?
Now, I brought a little present
to my friends at Cheers.
Oh, yeah?
What's that, Gary?
Towels for you to cry into
after I win
the Bloody Mary contest.
You know what I'd like
to do with that towel?
I'd like to shove
that up your nose,
pull it out your mouth
a couple times,
and buff up your
sinuses for you.
Oh, as if you could.
Oh, I could.
You could not.
Could too.
Could not.
Could not!
Could too!
Way to go,
Sammy!
See me slip that
"could too" in there?
Well, you won that one, Malone.
But that's
the last thing
you're going to win.
Hey, big shot,
we won this contest
the first two years they had it.
Well, since I opened,
I've won the last four.
All that proves is
that you've won it
twice as much
as we have.
How did you
like that, Sam?
Let me handle this, Woody.
Just get going.
Get out of here, would you?
Is this
the thanks I get
for my
heartfelt gift?
No.
This is.
Oh, that's nice.
I see you're still hiring
the cool Grace Kelly type
for waitresses.
Choke on it!
Okay, okay, I'm going back
to the Olde Towne Tavern,
where
my exclusive satellite coverage
of the World Welterweight
title fight
is about to get underway.
Hey.
Hey, wait. Hey, come on.
Where the hell
do you think you're going?
Uh... just taking
a little stroll.
Ah! That was refreshing,
wasn't it?
Hey, Doc.
What's going on?
Well, for one thing, I find
myself baching it again.
Lilith finally
blow her brains out?
No. But thank you
for asking after her, Carla.
So where is
the lovely Dr. Sternin?
Well, she's in Albany
for a few days
attending a conference
on gender stereotyping.
Gender stereotyping?
Yes. It's unfairly attributing
certain modes of behavior
exclusively to one sex.
That sounds
kind of boring.
Why did she
go to that?
Who knows?
You know women.
I can't tell you
how honored we are
that you've
chosen our bar
as the site of the
Bloody Mary contest.
Well, we were
going to hold it
at Gary's
Olde Towne Tavern,
but they're just so
darn crowded in there.
Well, you know,
you'll never have
that problem here.
Well, I better be going.
I have to drop off
a set of rules
at Gary's Tavern.
So long.
Bye.
What the hey?
That's Gary on the TV.
GARY:
We hid a secret camera in
a competitor's establishment.
Let's hear what they have to say
about Gary's Bloody Marys.
Boy, I don't know
what's in that,
but Gary makes the best
Bloody Mary I've ever tasted.
GARY:
Really?
Gary deserves to win
this contest every year.
Thank you very much.
And you'd be surprised
what some people would do
to get a hold
of my Bloody Mary mix.
Hey, I'd dress up
like a hooker to get
some of this stuff.
GARY:
But you can get
a pretty good Bloody Mary
just about anywhere in town.
Isn't that right?
Cheers never made
a Bloody Mary this good.
If you say so,
Sam Malone of Cheers.
Anybody know
the way to Gary's?
I'll give you a lift.
I can't believe
that weasel filmed us!
Oh, that stunt tears it.
Now I'm mad.
Yeah, I can tell.
How?
That little vein
bulging in my forehead?
No.
My nostrils flaring?
My jaw is clenched?
No.
Well, then,
how can you tell?
You just said,
"Now I'm mad."
Yeah, well, now I'm really mad.
Yeah, I can tell.
How?
I'll tell you something.
This is war. This is total war.
No prisoners, no truce,
no amnesty, no nothing.
Only one of us is going
to walk out of there standing.
Well, what are you
going to do, Sam?
Well, for one,
to really mess him up,
we're going to have
to infiltrate his bar.
CARLA:
Yeah.
Oh, let me do it, Sam.
Please. Let me do it.
You know, I've taken
a lot of makeup classes.
I can... I can
put on a disguise
and get in there without
anyone knowing about it.
Woody, I don't think so.
Oh, come on.
Let me do it.
I feel responsible.
I'm the one who
blew away the spice.
I'm the one
who broke the jar.
I'm the one who broke
the door in the men's room.
What?
At the bus station
downtown.
Come on. Let me
make it up to you.
Woody, you just...
you don't know
what you're getting
yourself into.
I mean, those guys
at Gary's are vicious.
They could
strip you naked,
paint you red and
put you on a subway.
They wouldn't do that.
They did it to me.
But I got
the best of 'em.
How's that?
I loved it.
Wait a minute, Woody,
come here, come here.
Woody, Woody, Woody,
I've got a plan.
Listen up.
Shh!
Gary had a camera in here
the other day.
He could have a spy
in here now.
And the whole place
could be bugged.
Come on, you guys.
Whoa, whoa.
Don't take off in a clump
like that.
It'll look suspicious.
Everybody split up.
We'll hook up outside.
No, no, no!
You're clumping up again.
Spread out.
No, you're clumping up again.
Cliffie, you got
the time, pal?
Right, time check.
2200 Zulu.
Agent Hoosier is overdue.
Abort Operation Red Dawn.
Cliff...
What in God's name
are you talking about?
Spy lingo, Norm.
Woody's not back
from Gary's yet.
It's time to mobilize
our forces. Let's go.
I'm just the man for it.
Actually, I considered a career
as a spy when I was young,
but in the end, I decided
not to go into intelligence.
That seems only fair.
None of it went into you.
Hey, guys, guys, guys.
What's the big rush here?
Give him a chance.
He's only about
five minutes late.
Actually, I think we might be
underestimating Woody.
You know, something tells me
he might actually
pull this thing off.
Hey! Hey!
Wait, there's a note.
What's it say?
( moaning )
"Compliments of Gary's.
We deliver."
( muffled speaking )
What?
What are you
trying to say?
He's trying to say
something.
What are you...?
Don't rip off the tape!
( screams ):
Ahh!
That's it, Cornmeal.
You blew it.
I'm telling you,
I was doing fine.
I borrowed this great costume
from my theater group.
I really looked
like a nun.
I went in there...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You dressed up as a nun
and went into a bar?
Well,
it was either that
or one of
the von Trapp children.
This is the stupidest thing
I have ever heard of.
Hey, I don't see
anybody else volunteering
to go over there
and get roughed up
and hung by their heels.
I did it 'cause
I was trying to help.
Okay, you were trying to help.
Why'd you have to be
so stupid about it?
And that's another thing.
I'm sick and tired
of hearing that word.
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
If I hear that word
one more time,
I'm walking out of here
and never coming back.
Oh, come on, man.
That's stupid.
That's it, I quit.
Cool down.
No, no, I'm serious.
I've had it with this place.
I'm not appreciated here
anymore.
Oh, Woody, come on, man.
That's not true.
Leave me alone!
( chuckling )
Well, look who's back.
Sister Mary Woody.
( laughing )
I'm looking for a job.
Oh, right.
I heard you quit Cheers.
I'm never going back
into Cheers again.
Well, except to get
my last check and, uh,
the only key to my apartment.
So where'd you stay last night?
Well, I just walked around.
Down to the Commons,
over to the river,
across the river
to Cambridge,
back over the river,
took a right at the
Prudential building,
stopped at a newsstand,
thought about buying a paper,
didn't...
Okay, okay, okay.
I get it.
So you're coming to me
for a job?
I don't owe Cheers diddly.
Well, you're
a darned good barkeep.
And I could use
an extra hand.
There's always
an upsurge of business
every year after I win
the Bloody Mary contest.
Why not?
Grab an apron
in the back.
Oh, gee,
you won't regret this.
Wait till
I tell my mom I'm working
for that weasel Gary.
Are you crazy?
He's the enemy.
No, I think he's okay.
I was in Cheers
when he quit.
It was real ugly.
I don't know. Uh, you
think we can trust him?
Gary?
Well...
Yeah?
I found a nickel in
the pocket of this apron.
You know who it belongs to
or should I put up a flyer?
I think we can trust him.
Afternoon, everybody.
Hey, hey, Gary.
Well, this is it!
The day of the big contest.
Hey, Woody, come here.
Yes, sir.
Woody, I'm gonna
be honest with you.
I had my doubts about you
having worked at Cheers and all,
but after the way you've worked
out here this last week...
you're really one of us now.
Thank you.
By the way, here.
What is it?
It came for you a few days ago.
I forgot to give it to you.
"This is to inform you
that the contest
has been moved up
two hours to 12:00 noon."
You forgot to give this to me?
Is it important?
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Damn it, boy.
You and Malone set me up.
You knew about this
time change two days ago.
Well, don't just stand there
like a bump on a log.
Say something.
Got you, Gar.
( clicks tongue )
That means the contest
started five minutes ago.
Gee, boss,
I don't think
you're gonna make it.
I think you're gonna lose.
I think you're gonna fall
flat on your face.
I think...
I'm gonna be hanging
upside down again.
Get him!
Come on. Get him!
Well, I wish I could
give all of you an award,
but there can only
be one winner...
Surprise, Malone.
I made it.
Hey.
No, he's disqualified.
He's late.
( booing )
You were late, man.
I didn't get the message
about the time change.
They tried to keep me away,
but it didn't work.
Yeah, right!
It didn't work.
That's a lie and you
should be disqualified
for making a
slanderous remark
and for wearing that
shirt with those pants.
( laughing )
There's still time
for another entry.
All right!
( cackles )
Here.
Try a real Bloody Mary.
Hands down, the winner.
( cheering )
All right!
Olde Towne Tavern!
Hey!
Hey, hey, Sam...
here's a little bit
of advice for you:
give up while you got
a shred of dignity left.
Oops, too late.
( giggles )
All clear?
All clear.
( cheering )
Oh, my man Woody!
That's good, man.
Take that makeup off.
( cheering )
Well, now just a minute.
That's Woody?
My God.
This is amazing makeup.
This is just incredible.
This was part of
some elaborate ruse, huh?
Yeah, we set
the whole thing up.
Yeah, that way we can
get Gary out of here
before the real contest starts.
And when you made such a fool of
yourself pretending to be a nun?
That was part
of the plan.
When you went
to work for Gary?
Part of the plan.
When you told Gary the time
of the contest had changed?
All part of the plan.
Hey, guys...
I'm ready for the real contest.
Not part of the plan.
And the winner
of Boston's annual
Bloody Mary contest is...
Gary's Olde Towne Tavern!
Yeah!
( groans )
Where have I heard that before?
You know, Sam,
that was a stroke of genius
having Li'l Abner there
playing the judge.
And I got to admit I fell for it
until I got
within about 20 feet.
Very funny.
You know, we're gonna
get you next year, Gary,
and it's not going
to be very pretty.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Don't try to outfox me
because you can't.
Every time you think
you got me fooled,
I'm one step ahead of you.
But I got to admit,
this time you came...
that close.
( laughs )
Very funny.
I can't believe he did it again.
Uh, 45... 50.
Carla, what are you doing?
I mean, you usually pay off
a judge after you win a contest.
If the contest that
had just happened
were the real contest--
which it wasn't--
and if this guy
were the real judge,
which he's not.
You follow any of that?
This is my next-
door neighbor.
The real judge is some
old lady from Cambridge.
Thanks for helping
out, Larry.
Any time, Carla.
Wait a minute.
If this wasn't the real contest,
when is the real contest?
In about a half an hour.
Are you telling me
we still have a chance
to win this thing?
We sure do!
Carla! Carla!
Carla! Carla! Carla! Carla!
Carla...
How long have you
had this planned?
Since about...
a minute after we lost
last year's contest.
This is unbelievable.
What?!
That I could come up
with a great plan?
No, that you'd pay
this guy money
out of your own pocket.
Get real.
I lifted Gary's wallet
when he was leaving the bar.
Thank God you are on our side.
And from here on in,
whether we win or lose,
what's really important
to remember--
and I'm saying this
in the spirit of true sportsmen
everywhere--
is Gary won't win!
Yeah!
Gary won't win!
Hey, guys...
I am on to you.
Oh, man, I give up.
Now hand over my wallet.
Your what?
Come on.
Somebody took my wallet.
Yeah, someone
handed it in.
You must've dropped it
when you were
leaving the bar.
Yeah, yeah. Thanks.
So long, chumps.
( chuckles )
( whispers ):
Gary won't win.
( whispering ):
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org