SAM: Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Why don't you wait? I'll get our coats.
Mm. Okay?
Hope to see you again soon.
Thank you, Miss.
Oh, great.
I can't even read that check.
Well, I'm so sorry if my handwriting
isn't up to your high
and mighty standards,
but some of us don't get to sit around
on our buns all day and
practice our penmanship.
Some of us
have to go out and earn a living!
Here are your glasses, dear.
You left them in your coat again.
Oh, thanks.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let's go.
Oh, hey, um... I'm really sorry.
I-I...
I don't know what to say,
except I had a really bad day.
Oh... yeah, sure, Carla, bad day.
Bad life is more like it.
House full of kids, this crummy job.
If I keep treatin'
my customers this way,
I'm going to lose even that.
Uh, uh, here you go.
I hope things'll start looking up.
Oh, no, no, no, no, I
couldn't, I couldn't.
Not the way I treated you.
No, please, please, please, we insist.
(sighs)
Ten bucks?
Excuse me, Miss.
You forgot to, uh, give me a napkin.
I'm so sorry!
I don't know what to say,
except I've had a really bad day.
Bad day? Bad life is more like it.
A house full of kids...
(piano plays)
♪ Making your way in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like to get away♪
♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always glad you came ♪
♪ You want to be where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You want to go where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Yep! Hey, everybody, guess what?
Today marks the beginning
of my seventh year
as a U.S. postal carrier.
Well, all right.
Woody, I think that calls for
a little drink on the house.
What do you think, huh?
I think you're right, Mr. Peterson.
Yeah? Hey, what the hell,
give Cliffie one, too.
Hey...
This guy, huh?
Oh, yeah, imagine that.
Seven years carrying the old bag around.
(snorts)
Yeah, I know the feeling.
That's, uh...
that's quite an
achievement, though, Cliffie.
Oh, yeah? Look who's talkin'.
Oh, okay, all right.
I know some people around
here don't exactly think
that I'm an overachiever,
but, uh... I'll tell you,
I don't plan to go to my grave
until I've made some sort
of impression on this world.
I'd say you've already made a deep one.
You know,
I plan on leavin' somethin' behind
for the world to remember me by.
Yeah?
And here it is.
(sighs)
It's a glass of Windex, Woody.
No, it's a drink.
And Woody Boyd is going to
become the next Jim Sheehan.
Who?
Certainly you've heard of the inventor
of the Fish House Punch?
I can't say we have,
Wood, but then again,
we don't get out that much, you know?
Well, I'm callin' mine
the Blue Boyd of Happiness.
Can I tempt you?
Not bad.
Really.
Oh, hey, that's delicious.
Now all I got to do
is fill out these forms
and register with
Bartender's Monthly Magazine,
and my name will be a household word.
Yeah: doorknob.
Hey, Sam, you want to try my new drink?
Woody, I can't touch that stuff.
I'm an alcoholic.
You are?
Oh, I... I'm sorry.
I-I thought you knew.
Yeah, I drank myself out of
baseball and out of a marriage.
Gee, that's hard to believe.
Well, it's true. Right, gang?
Yeah... Guy had a face full of booze...
No, no, no, I believe
you were a drunk, Sam.
I just didn't know you'd been married.
Mmm, pretty good Blue Moon.
You mean it's already a drink?
Aw, don't feel
disappointed there, Woody.
Every combination in the world's
been done to death by now.
You couldn't possibly
invent anything new.
(phone rings)
DIANE: Hello, Cheers.
Hey, Woody, gin and tonic.
Oh, uh, somebody's
already invented that.
No, you horseshoe, I'm ordering one.
Oh, no! Really?
Tonight? Oh!
Oh, I can't wait!
Yes, thank you.
Oh! I have the most
exciting news, everyone.
Tonight I am eating dinner at The Cafe.
Ah, gee, that's pretty exciting.
Tonight I'm driving home in The Car.
No, you see, um... actually, Sam,
The Cafe is one of the
trendiest restaurants.
Eating there is considered,
uh, to be rather a coup
among certain, oh...
self-important and pretentious circles.
Congratulations, Diane.
If this place is so hot,
how come they can't think
of a better name than The Cafe?
Oh, Carla, if you had
any sense of style,
you would know that
a simple name connotes
the very best of taste.
Hey, you're right about that, Diane.
There's this joint out
on Route One called "Eat".
Don't miss it. It's great.
Say, you know, Darlene and
I can't make up our mind
whether to have some
chili or a hamburger.
Maybe this Cafe joint
sounds just like the ticket.
Well, you got the number there?
(laughing)
What? What's the number? What?
Pardonne mon laughteur, Sam.
This is not the sort of place
you just call and make a reservation.
My dinner companion is a Brundage,
and even with that pull,
he had to wait three months for a table.
Ooh, geez, I wonder how long
he had to wait for the chairs.
Look what I'm dealing with.
You consider food as a fuel
to be salted down heavily,
covered with ketchup,
stuffed in your mouth,
and on a good day, chewed.
What I'm trying to say is, Sam,
you couldn't possibly get a
reservation at this late hour.
Diane, I can get a reservation
in any restaurant I want.
The name "Sam Malone"
still carries a little
clout in this town.
Right. Hey, hey, hey.
Very well, Sam.
Let's give it a try.
Allow me to call The Cafe.
Well, now, li-lis...
I'm not even sure I want to go there.
Afraid, Sam?
They have not built the
restaurant that can scare me.
Come on. Um, yes, hold on, please.
Um, hello, uh, I'd like to
make a reservation, please.
Nothing tonight?
Well, this happens to
be Sam "Mayday" Malone,
formerly of the Red Sox.
Well, yeah, that'll be fine.
8:00? Well, let's say 8:00.
Thank you very much.
Hey, all right, Sammy. You got it, huh?
Sure did.
When, next March?
No, next February.
Well done, Sam.
God, I hate it when she's right.
Ah, you didn't want to
eat there anyway, Sam.
The waiters pride
themselves on rudeness,
the portions are too small, and
it's exorbitantly overpriced.
Oh, you couldn't get in either, huh?
Not till April.
Well, I certainly hope
Diane had a big lunch.
Hi, I'd like to, uh,
cancel a reservation
for tonight, please.
The name is Brundage.
Party of two.
Yes, that Brundage.
Thank you.
Uh-uh,
uh-uh, Sammy.
Canceling Diane's reservation?
CLIFF: Ooh, heart of stone.
I love it.
Yeah, hi, this is, uh, Sam Malone again.
I'm just wondering if you might've had
a surprise cancellation for tonight.
What do you mean, you don't?
You must have. I just...
No, no, n-never mind, never mind.
Boy, I'd sure love to waltz
into that joint tonight
just so I could see
the look on her face.
Well, if it's that important
to you, Sam, give me the phone.
If Julian Weinstein, my good friend,
can't get you in, nobody can.
Ooh, the heart transplant wizard?
Oh, one and the same, yeah. We
went to prep school together.
He's a well-known gourmet.
Yeah, well, wh-why would he
want to do this for me, though?
He'd love to do me a favor.
See, we dissected our
first frog together.
Hello, Julian. Julian, hi.
Frasier Crane. How are you?
Crane.
C-R-A-N-E.
Yes, yes, Dr. Frasier
Crane. All right, fine.
Uh, listen, I was wondering
what you know about, uh...
No, it's A-N-E!
Oh, skip it!
I'll tell you, you know,
you open a few thoraxes,
you forget who your friends are.
Oh, it's beautiful.
A feast for the eyes
as well as the palate.
Ah, that must be our table.
Uh, the Brundage party.
Brundage?
Ah, Brundage.
You canceled.
(laughs)
That's impossible.
I-I made the reservations
over three months ago.
Well, obviously, there's
been some mistake.
The best we can do is give
you the next available table.
And when might that be?
If all goes well, perhaps... tonight.
Perhaps?
Jordan, don't make a fuss, please.
We'll straighten this out.
He's sorry.
(laughs)
Dr. Weinstein, your table is ready.
Excuse me, Miss.
I don't believe it.
Oh, neither do I.
I was this close to
Dr. Julian Weinstein.
That's not Julian Weinstein.
That's the man who
stole our reservation.
That's not Julian Weinstein.
That's an imposter.
Ask him for his I.D.
Ask him to spell I.D.
Do you know how to order
in a place like this?
Oh, yeah, yeah, my, uh, friend Frasier
read a review about the menu.
He coached me.
No problem.
Dr. Weinstein.
Uh-uh,
uh-uh.
You swine.
It's one thing to pretend
to be somebody else on the phone,
but convincing others that
you're a sophisticated gourmet
is a little bit more
than you can handle.
You're going to blow it, Sam.
You're going to be
embarrassed in front of some
of the most important people in Boston.
And then you're going
to slink out of here
with your curly little
swine tail between your legs.
You don't think I can handle this?
Well, just watch.
Excuse me, we'd like to start off
with Bouchées Parmentier au Fromage,
followed by a salade maison,
and for our entrée,
we'll have Tourte Froide
D'Anguille Rabelais.
Thank you so much.
Good, Sam; that was your busboy.
I knew that.
He's got lips.
He can tell the waiter, can't he?
Bon appetit, Dr. Weinstein.
Who's Miss Grumpus?
Excuse me, uh, you aren't, uh,
Dr. Julian Weinstein, are you?
Uh... yes.
(chuckles softly)
This is really an honor.
I'm, I'm Dr. Peter Fisher.
Oh.
Uh, nice to meet you.
Yeah. You know, I had no
idea you were so young.
Well, I, uh, skipped a
few grades in med school.
(laughing)
You got to have a sense of
humor in this line of work.
Say, if you'll indulge
in a little shop talk,
uh, where did you come
up with that concept
of combining antithymocyte globulin
with, uh, cyclosporin A
to combat tissue rejection?
On the beach.
(uncomfortable chuckle)
Nice meeting you.
Excuse me, Dr. Weinstein.
Oh, uh, yeah, here we go.
Our chef Claude would like to say hello.
He met you while he
was a chef at La Ronde.
Do you mind?
Oh, uh... well, actu-actually...
It won't take but a moment.
Maybe, uh... Grab your purse.
We've got to get...
Dr. Weinstein, so good...
You're not Dr. Weinstein.
Yes, I am.
Perhaps you hadn't
heard about my accident.
Why, no, I didn't.
Oh, yes, yes, uh... terribly disfigured.
Uh, thank God for plastic surgery.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
But they've done a wonderful job.
Hmm...
You look much better.
And taller.
Traction. It, uh...
Well, nice to see you again.
You, too.
Boy, you pulled it off.
Mm. That's pretty smart.
Yeah, well, of course I'm smart.
I'm a doctor.
(laughing): Oh! Right.
All right, whiskey,
vermouth, bitters--
that's a Paddy Cocktail.
Gin, vermouth,
grapefruit juice--
that's a Palm Beach.
Oh, wait a minute.
How about gin, vermouth
and black coffee?
That's paint remover.
All right, I'll try something else.
Oh, great, I'm out of limes.
Don't panic.
Sam always keeps some extras around.
Where?
Call the doctor
and find out.
Telephone for Dr. Weinstein.
Oh, um...
It's a Dr. Woody.
He's in the middle of surgery,
and he says he needs your opinion.
Thank you.
Hello?
Wha-what? You're out of them?
No, look, just, just check in the box
right next to the scotch...
...uh, tape.
The scotch tape.
We, uh...
Sometimes we run out of stitches
and have to improvise.
Thank you, Dr. Woody.
Dr. Weinstein?
My date needs medical attention.
Can you help?
My food just arrived.
Well, I'm a doctor.
Sit down.
I-I want the world-famous
heart surgeon,
Dr. Julian Weinstein.
Well, of course; I bow
to his greater skill.
No, no, no, uh,
why don't you go ahead there,
Fisher, and give him a shot?
He's having chest pains, Doctor!
Oh, well, uh, why don't you time them
and see how far apart they are?
All right, I'll, uh, give
him a look-see, I guess.
Right this way, Doctor.
Everything'll be all right. Don't worry.
What are you doing?
You're ruining my dinner.
Ruining your dinner?
Ruining your dinner?!
Everybody, now...
Sam, this is the cruelest
thing you've ever done!
Yeah, what about the crummy thing
you did to me earlier today,
making me feel like a big nobody?
I apologize.
I spoke irrationally.
You're not a nobody.
(sighs)
Now, will you
and your date kindly leave
so that Jordan and I can
have our rightful meal,
and the two of you can
sashay over to the Colonel's
across the street?
Will you excuse me?
My meal is getting cold.
Now...
Well, we may have a
long wait ahead of us,
but we are going to
stay until we get seated.
No, you're going to
stay until you get seated.
Right about now a bucket of extra
crispy doesn't sound half bad.
Okay, Dr. Crane, just drink up.
Woody, please, you promised you'd stop
after the rum and trail mix.
That wasn't a drink.
That was just something
to cleanse your palate.
Now come on, here.
My God, Woody!
That bad, huh?
No, no, it's terrific.
Here, try this.
I've never had anything like it.
All right!
Oh!
Oh, yeah!
This one gets you
in the cocktail hall of fame!
So, what's in it, Wood?
Yeah, what's the secret recipe?
Well, it's, uh, two parts...
(crying)
Your change, Dr. Weinstein.
Ah, thank you very much.
Whew, boy, remember the good old days
when you could spend $200 for a meal
and then still have enough change
to buy a mint patty?
Ah, Paul, memorable.
Aw, gee...
(cries out)
Madam, we've had our last seating.
I'm afraid we won't be able to
accommodate you this evening.
Oh, Paul, uh... could I
speak to you for a minute?
I'll meet you outside.
Listen, it, it would be a
great personal favor to me,
Dr. Julian
Weinstein--
in fact, to the entire Weinstein family,
and pretty much to doctors
all over the world-- if...
if you could, uh, make
sure she gets some food.
Well, uh, if you'll agree to honor us
with your presence again, Dr. Weinstein,
I'll see to it personally.
SAM: Well, I appreciate that.
Enjoy, Diane.
Thank you. I intend to.
Thank you. This will do nicely.
Would you like to hear our menu?
Thank you, no.
I've memorized it.
I'll have the Tournedos Rossini.
I'm sorry, we're all out of that.
Uh, then I'll have the
Jambon Farci et Braise.
Once again, I'm sorry.
Let's attack this
from another direction.
You tell me what you have left.
Fricadelles de veau a la Nicoise.
Great, I'm in a Fricadelle mood.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
Well, I'm still hungry, actually.
What happened to, uh, Darlene?
Oh, I put her in a
cab and sent her home.
Well, you don't have
to do me any favors.
No, I'm not doing you any favors.
I-I'm really hungry.
May I, uh,
join you?
I don't care what you do.
Well, thank you.
Thank you, Sam.
You're welcome.
Doctor. Ah, Paul.
Can I get you anything else?
Uh, what do you have?
Anything for you, Dr. Weinstein.
Ah, well...
You know, I just can't make up my mind.
Why don't you have my dear friend Claude
mix me up something special?
Very good.
(chuckling)
I really do appreciate
your coming back, Sam.
It was sweet.
No, no, it's not sweet.
I... I did it for myself.
I was feeling guilty out there,
and I don't like to feel guilty.
Well, that's sweet in itself.
Well, we'll see how
sweet you think it is
when I have you pay for your own meal.
Madam. Doctor.
Everything was delightful
and well worth the wait.
Ooh, yes, I enjoyed it very much.
I'll be right with you.
Say, uh, I seem to be running
a little short on cash.
You know, Sam, I think it
was a really good idea you had
about us going Dutch.
See, this way, we don't feel
that we owe each other anything.
This is not funny.
This could be very embarrassing
for both of us. Please.
Why? I've already paid for
my meal, and I'm leaving.
Good night, Dr. Weinstein.
See you in surgery.
Hey, I'm serious.
Hey, come on, don't do this!
MAITRE D': Is there a problem, Doctor?
No, no, no problem at all. Um...
I'll just use my credit card here.
Mm, very well.
Uh, Dr. Weinstein, this appears to be
the credit card of a Mr. Sam Malone.
Let me see that.
Well, I'll be darned.
You know, I must have,
uh, switched wallets
with this Malone character.
You know, I bet it happened at the club.
Yes, it did; I remember him now.
A baseball player. Malone.
You, uh, you ever heard of him?
No.
Oh, well, why don't you, uh, put it on
this credit card anyway,
and I'll take this Malone guy
out to dinner some other time, hmm?
I'm afraid not.
Well, all right, I don't suppose
you take a personal check, do you?
And whose name would be on that?
Okay, well, uh, why
don't we try this, then?
Oh, my God, look at
the size of that cat!
Hey, you, come back here!