Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
What are you
doing, Cliff? What?
Well, I'm, uh, leaving
a tip there for Carla.
Yeah?
Yeah, one of the oldest
bar tricks
in the book there, Normie.
Look, you see I filled
the glass with water.
I'm gonna invert it on top
of this dollar bill.
Put it on the bar, right?
Looks... Looks, uh,
empty now, doesn't it?
Mm-hmm.
Well, watch what happens
when she comes to get her tip.
Fasten your seat belts
and wait for the fun to begin.
Oh.
Thanks for the tip, Cliff.
Uh, joke's still
on her.
She's the one that's got
to mop up all this mess.
(laughs)
Thank you, Carla.
Your apology's
accepted.
(theme song begins)
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always
glad you came
You wanna be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You wanna be where
everybody knows your name
You wanna go
where people know
People are all the same
You wanna go where
everybody knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Hey, guys.
Hey, Wood.
Hi, Wood.
Mom finally sent out
Grandma Meg's pressure cooker,
so last night I whipped up
a batch of chili.
Oh.
Do you want
to try some?
Yeah.
Sure.
It's from an old
family recipe.
Oh, your
grandma's?
Nah, this old family
that lived down the road.
Mmm!
Woody, this is
excellent!
Mmm!
Normie, what
do you think?
(belches)
He likes it!
Normie likes it!
Woody, I'm sorry. It seems
we've eaten all your chili.
I still got plenty left
in the thermos.
Great.
I didn't have breakfast today,
all right?
(door opening)
Quick, Normie,
turn on the Weather Channel.
You know, I wonder
if that sentence has
ever been spoken before.
(female voice on TV)
Oh, yeah, there she is.
Who?
Weathergirl Dorothy,
my favorite.
Isn't she dreamy?
Cliff, everybody
looks sort of dreamy
when they have giant clouds
floating behind them.
No, no.
Listen, listen.
She's got the cutest
little lateral lisp.
Oh, I always get a giggle
when she tries to pronounce...
(lisping):
...stratocumulus.
So you, uh... you watch this
a lot, do you?
Huh? Oh, yeah, yeah.
You get, uh,
kind of a fatherly feeling
about these, uh, weather anchors
after a while.
Yeah, well, besides,
it's on all night.
You're a very lonely
man, aren't you, Cliff?
Not as long
as I got my Weather Channel.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Sammy's back!
(all shouting greetings)
Hey, how was
your weekend
up in the mountains
with Natalie?
It was so great.
Nothin' like shushing down
those fine white slopes.
NORM:
Yeah.
Oh, you went
skiing, huh?
No, no, no.
You're a dog!
Oh!
Goodie. Sam, you're back.
Hey, that's
what Natalie said.
No, actually,
actually, she said,
"Oh, goodie, Sam, your front."
(laughter)
I have a very, very
special surprise for you,
so just close your
eyes and come with me.
This is deja vu of
the whole weekend.
FRASIER:
Oh!
Okay, you can
open your eyes.
(chuckling):
Okay.
Well?
I can't tell you
how much better
Natalie's surprise was.
What, you
don't like it?
Well, it...
It's-It's just...
Boy.
I mean, it's-it's
really...
Boy.
No, that's...
that's not...
That's not the
right word.
It's not
boy at all.
It's, um... It's...
It's a tearoom.
Thanks for not making me guess.
Well, so what-what do you think?
Well, you want my, uh,
honest first impression?
My gut reaction?
Yes, I do.
I hate it. I hate it.
I hate it!
Now how could you
do this without
asking me first?
Without asking you first?
Wait a minute! I happen to have
paid $25,000 to John Hill
to get this poolroom back.
If it hadn't been for me,
you wouldn't even have
this poolroom!
I don't have a poolroom.
I have a tearoom.
Ish!
Oh, oh, oh.
Look what you
made me do.
You made me
say "ish."
(scoffs)
What's that on the floor?
It's a throw rug.
Oh.
Oh, hey.
Look at that.
It works.
Wait.
This wouldn't happen to
be a throw table, would it?
No. Sam, wait!
You know, if you're gonna
take my money,
I think my ideas deserve
a little bit more respect.
All right.
You're right.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Uh, this just came
as a little bit
of a shock to me,
that's all.
Tell you what, why don't I,
uh, just, uh, go outside here
and come back in
and start fresh?
That would be good, Sam.
Thank you.
I hate it. Hate it. I hate it!
Ish!
I'm putting that room
back the way it was!
As soon as I find
my pool table.
CLIFF:
Three ball,
corner pocket.
Thanks, Sam.
A little too much
English on that.
REBECCA:
Sam,
please, now I know... I know
I sprung this on you, but
please give it a chance.
I think it
could work.
My marketing survey showed
that this neighborhood was
in need of something like this.
People want to go
to a place where
they can just relax.
You know, a nice,
quiet, pretty little place
where they can
just sit and talk.
(belches)
Good one.
Honey, you're crazy.
I-I have people coming in here
just to shoot stick. I mean, I
bet that poolroom makes me
an extra hundred
bucks a night.
Yeah, well,
I bet with my tearoom,
I could make 500 bucks tonight.
500 bucks
in one night?
Yes.
What else are you selling
back there?
Sam, it's my grand opening.
I've been promoting
all over town.
You make 500 bucks in one night,
and-and that tearoom is yours.
It's a bet.
Okay, it's a bet.
(chuckles)
But I want you to know
there's no losers here
because I'm gonna share
half the profit with you.
Oh ho! Ooh!
Half the profits
of a tearoom!
Oh!
Oh, boy,
why didn't you say so before?
Let's figure
this out here.
All right, let's see.
We'll, uh,
start with your profits.
That'd be... ooh!
Wait, wait, wait.
Now I get half of this.
(muttering):
Let me. Hmm...
Ooh, another... ooh!
Fellas, fellas, look.
I get a great
big zero,
and I don't have
to lift a finger!
Oh, thank you,
thank you.
I can retire! Ooh!
God, he's a butthead.
DOROTHY:
Now, let's take a look
at the regional map.
(lisping):
The southern sectors
will experience scattered clouds
over the Mississippi Basin.
Boy.
(chuckles)
Don't you just
love how she says
(lisping):
"Mississippi Basin"?
It just melts your
heart, doesn't it, huh?
Mm-hmm.
You know, I, uh,
sent a fan letter to my Dorothy.
Hmm?
Yeah, I wonder
if she'll ever even read it.
I mean,
they must get so many. Hmm.
You know, I don't
think so, Cliff.
I don't think that
many people watch
the Weather Channel.
Seriously,
I don't think
that many people know
there is a Weather Channel.
Hmm. Boy, Norm,
are you out of touch!
Hey, Fras, Lilith.
Get you a drink?
No, Sam, we are not here
for libation this day.
We are here for the grand
opening of Rebecca's tearoom.
Oh, yeah? Yeah?
What, you gonna go back there
and, uh, make fun of her?
No, we're-we're going
to go have some tea.
Oh, yeah, yeah,
then you're, what...?
You're gonna spit it
on the floor and laugh at her?
We're just going to order it
and drink it down.
Well, what's funny about that?
We're not trying
to be funny.
We're just here for some tea.
Is that so hard to believe?
Yeah, seein' how
she's been open all day,
and you're the first customers.
(chuckles)
Oh, well, maybe the word
hasn't gotten out yet.
Although, she did send
us this lovely invitation
hand-calligraphed
on a lace doily.
Didn't anyone else
get one of these?
Very funny.
Could have put someone's
eye out, you know.
Let's go, Frasier.
Wait, wait,
wait, Fras.
You're not really
gonna go in there
and drink tea,
are ya?
Come on out here
and sit at the bar,
you know,
with the guys.
Have a beer.
Yeah.
Well, I guess I-I could.
(clears throat)
No.
I mean, you're-you're tellin' us
you're just gonna go back there
and sit with your wife
and sip tea, huh?
Yup, that's me.
Whipped and proud of it.
Thank you.
Here you are.
Please allow me.
All right, there.
Now you'll notice on the menu
that we have a...
a wide selection of sandwiches
and delectables, and, uh,
many, many varieties of tea.
So, what can I get you?
Just some tea, please.
That's it? Just tea?
Well, perhaps
I could tempt you
with some tiny
little sandwiches or
fresh biscuits?
Scones?
We're both watching our diets,
so two pots of Orange Pekoe
would be lovely.
FRASIER:
Hon,
maybe we should split a pot.
Well...
Per-Perhaps one of my slightly
more expensive herbal teas?
Uh, no, thank you.
You guys cannot just have tea.
Tea is a
loss leader.
I lose money
just boiling the water.
And, Lilith, look.
(blows through lips)
You are hardly fat.
You are borderline anorexic.
Just
pig out!
Order some strawberry tarts.
Strawberries make me break out.
Well, at least that will put
a little color in your face.
Perhaps we won't have
anything at all.
Fine!
I don't really care. Get out!
Thanks for coming.
Tell all your friends.
Frasier, Lilith,
oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm
just desperate.
I don't understand
why nobody wants
to come back into my
beautiful tearoom.
Well, Rebecca,
a restaurant should be...
like a mistress.
You see,
one shouldn't feel that
she's overeager to please.
It's far more enticing
if you need her more
than she needs you.
Who is this "she"
you're talking
about, Frasier?
Purely hypothetical.
Well, it's a
little strange
for a happily
married man
to go prattling on
about a mistress.
Oh, come on, hon,
give me this one.
You already heard me
admit I was whipped
in front of the boys.
That was good.
You were right, Sam.
Nobody's gonna come
in here
and have high tea
and crumpets.
Oh, don't give
up hope.
(Cockney accent):
Maybe a carriage
will break down
in front of the pub
and everyone'll come
in for a cup of tea.
Have a cup of
tea, please.
Have a cup of tea.
God, I hate you!
Okay, guys.
Just made up a fresh new batch
of chili.
(cheering)
Now all I ask
is you please
leave me some this time.
You guys really like
that chili, don't you?
Mmm.
Well, do you
think that
if I sold that kind of
chili in my tearoom that,
uh, I could make
$500 a night?
Easy. But, uh,
why would anyone want
to go back there?
We got a free pot
of chili right here.
Good point.
Chili in the tearoom!
Sammy, kiss that poolroom
good-bye, pal.
Sam, she's sellin' an awful
lotta chili in there.
She must be gettin'
pretty close
to that $500 mark.
Oh, come on.
So she's sellin' a
couple of bowls.
I mean, how much chili
can a guy eat?
Boy, I can't eat another
mouthful.
Uh-huh, see
what I mean?
Thank goodness they sell
these gallon buckets
for take-out.
Oh, man,
I'm gonna lose
my poolroom.
I've gotta think of some
way to stop her.
I agree with you,
Sammy.
Go for the jugular.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Whatta ya mean, like
sabotage her?
No, go for her jugular.
I mean, you can't
sell chili
when her throat's
all ripped out.
Well, she could,
but who'd wanna buy it?
No, I got it,
I got it.
Let's call the fire
marshal on her, huh?
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no,
that'd be below
the belt.
I can't do that.
Sam, can I talk to you a minute?
You know, I
just realized
that the closer I'm
getting to my goal,
the more all I'm thinking
about is winning,
and that's not right.
I mean, I wasn't even
considering your feelings.
You've had that poolroom
for many, many years
and, well, I guess what
I'm trying to say is...
(singsongy):
Ha-ha-ha-ha, ha-ha!
I'm gonna win
your poolroom!
Call the fire marshal!
Glad that dinner rush is over.
Give me time to
put up a new pot
before the after-theatre
crowd gets here.
Sam, I'm takin'
a break.
Me, too, Sammy.
I'm down to the last notch
on my belt.
Yeah, I had to make a
new one with a nail.
Hey, Cliff, you got somethin'
in the mail.
Huh?
That reminds me.
Did I ever take you out back
and kick the hell out of you
for that postal increase?
Uh-huh.
Good.
Just goin' over my checklist.
Well, look at this!
It's a reply from my
Weathergirl Dorothy.
Oh, look at that,
the sweetheart.
She sent a little photo
of herself.
No, no, no, Cliffie,
I believe that's
a satellite photo
of the entire
Eastern Seaboard.
Oh, yeah,
but she's in there.
I mean, I'm in there.
We're all in there.
The letter says,
"Dear Cliff,
"Thank you so much for
your sweet letter.
"You did not mention
what grade you're in,
"but from the handwriting
I guess
"that you're a big
boy of 11 or 12.
"Maybe when you
grow up,
"you can be a
weatherperson, too.
Yours truly,
Dorothy Borsik."
CARLA (whispers):
Sammy, the
fire marshal.
Sam,
we got a tip that Cheers
is operating a kitchen
without a permit.
Anything to that?
Oh, gosh no.
I don't think anything that
would concern you, you know,
just a couple
of exposed propane tanks,
unventilated
hot plate.
I mean, but that...
oh, now wait a second.
Gee, that's a,
that's a potential fire hazard.
And you, you're a fire marshal.
What was I thinking?
I think I'll just
take a look-see.
Maybe I shouldn't have called
the fire department.
Maybe that was wrong.
Don't chicken out
now, Sam.
No, no, no,
maybe I shoulda...
put a mouse in the
chili and called the
health department.
That would have
been funnier.
(laughing)
Sam,
you should
be ashamed of yourself.
Do you realize
everything that Rebecca has
attempted in her life
has resulted in failure?
Yeah.
This is her first
success, and you're trying
to take it away from her.
That's my poolroom!
But it's her life.
But it's my poolroom.
Come on, you guys, understand
that, don't ya?
Yeah, Sam, we
understand.
We understand you made a fair
bet, you saw that you
were gonna lose,
and you started cheatin'.
Well, I-I-I didn't want
to be a bad sport.
I just wanted to do anything
I had to to win.
But that's no reason
for you to be a cheater.
But you were the one
who told me to cheat!
No, I said
to kill her.
Cheating's wrong.
I'm, I'm sorry.
What, do you all hate me now?
Is that...?
Well, kinda, yeah.
I'm afraid that's some
list, Miss Howe.
NORM:
Great,
now he's writin' her up
a citation.
So it's beans,
tomato paste,
onions, peppers
and ground beef.
No, that's ground chuck.
Oh, ground chuck.
Serves eight?
Uh-huh.
What're you gonna do,
share with the other guys
at the firehouse?
Why should I?
What have they ever
done for me?
Sam,
why do you suppose
the fire marshal would
come by my chili room
tonight, of
all nights?
Kismet?
No, because you
tipped him off.
Sam, you could've
gotten me shut down.
Thank God that dear
man loves his chili.
I'm sorry.
I got carried away.
Yes, you did.
Listen, I, I gotta
make this up to you.
How, how, how, how
close are you
to getting that $500?
About $20.
I'll tell you what.
Let me, let me, uh,
buy a bowl of
chili for $20.
No.
No, Sam, you don't
need to do that.
No, listen, I wanna prove to you
that I'm not a poor loser.
Come on, give me
my bowl of chili here.
Thank you, Sam,
this is nice of you.
Go ahead,
just put on Woody's hat
and get the chili yourself
because I want to get
my camera and get a picture
of you pouring
that bowl
of chili that put me
over the top.
Oh, you got
to warm it up, Sam.
You know how to
turn on the flame?
It's kind of tricky.
Yeah, I'll
figure it out.
(loud explosion)
Yep, that's how I
figured it out, too.
It was a accident.
Sammy, are you okay?
You ever had a pot of chili fly
by your face
at the speed of light?
No.
Don't.
Look at the hole
in that wall.
Who could miss it, huh?
No, I'm talking
about the brick wall
across the alley.
Man, that pressure cooker
really wanted out of here.
Okay, everybody
out of here, out.
Come on,
everybody, out!
Go back to the bar,
please.
Not you.
I want to talk to you.
Don't you think maybe I should
go to a trauma center first?
S-Some of this
could be me.
Oh, come on, I know what
you're thinking here,
but I-I didn't do
this on purpose.
I swear to God I didn't
do it on purpose.
You did it just because
I started doing really well
back here and you're jealous.
Y-You're just a big baby.
I am not.
Yes, you are.
You want everything for you
and nothing for me.
Well, yeah, if that's being
a big baby, okay,
but... but I'm a,
I'm a guy.
I'm supposed
to be a big baby.
And you're a woman.
You know, you're supposed
to be like a nice mommy
and tell me everything's okay
and, and pat me on the head.
I would like to pat you
on the head with a pickax.
Oh, I, I know how you feel.
I mean,
I'm sorry.
This is crazy, I...
I feel so sorry.
No, you don't.
Yes, I do, I really do.
I just feel terrible.
I... feel like I could cry.
Okay.
Okay what?
Cry.
What do you mean?
I mean, make water come
out of your eyes.
And that way I will know
that you are really sorry
for what you've done here.
Just cry?
Yep.
Does it count if, you know,
if you really want to cry,
but you can't?
No.
Cry, Sam.
Huh.
(mock sobbing)
No onions.
I want real tears.
Now, just cry.
Give me a break.
What am I supposed to--?
I mean, isn't this enough?
A guy, a guy
who can't cry?
I mean, that is
heartbreaking.
Honey, there's nothing sadder
than a man who can't cry.
No, Sam.
It is not enough.
Wait, maybe I can
help you out here.
(glass breaking)
(footsteps
approaching)
There.
Now we can go.
Come on.
What was that sound?
Oh, that was the sound
of me breaking all the windows
out of your Corvette.
(Sam sobbing)
REBECCA:
There, now there
are those tears.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org