Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
E-leven and
holding.
Hey, that's a personal best.
Uh-huh.
What's going on?
We're trying to
count how many
Spanish peanuts
Cliff can...
fit up his nose.
(nasally):
And, uh,
11's the limit.
I know my nostrils.
Let's see, now, who had 11?
Uh, Norm Peterson.
Hey.
Oh, yes,
I know Cliffie's
nostrils.
Here you go, Norm.
Thank you.
Cliff, are you crazy?
You've really been stuffing
peanuts up your nose?
That's dangerous.
You could puncture your sinuses,
you can even get brain damage.
Oh, come on, I've been doing
this kind of stuff for years.
It's no big deal.
Yeah, Cliffie, but,
uh, but never 11, pal.
Uh, yeah,
you're right, Norm.
Uh, hey,
uh, Rebecca,
I'm gonna mosey
into the poolroom
and, uh,
pry some of these out.
Give me the corkscrew,
will you?
Thank you.
Hey, Norm, that's quite a little
sum of money you've got there.
Yeah, well...
Maybe you'd like
to apply
some of this to your bar tab.
(laughing)
That's very good.
(chuckles)
You know, you're
starting to fit in here.
That's great.
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
(door opens)
Sam, let me have a Scotch.
Oh, make it a double.
Oh, what the hell?
Just pound me over the head
with the bottle.
Whoo!
Tough day, huh?
No, I'm not unwinding, Sam,
I'm, I'm bracing up.
You see, Lilith's mother
is coming up from the city
for our fifth
wedding anniversary,
meeting me here.
I thought I'd come in a
little early and... marinate.
Yeah, mother-in-laws,
man, they're tough.
Oh, she's demanding, Sam.
She's unreasonable,
cold, sarcastic, bitter.
Nothing is
to her liking ever.
Yeah, we know.
What's her mother like?
Ah, I suppose it's wrong of me
to blame Betty
for all our problems.
I'm sure I'm not the way
she wants me to be either.
Well, how does she want
you to be, Dr. Crane?
Well... dead.
The thing
that really drives me crazy
is the unrelenting tension
between Lilith
and her mother.
You know, Lilith
just holds it all in,
she has to unload it
somewhere,
and guess who gets
to listen to it endlessly.
Apparently me,
Dr. Crane.
Oh, that's wonderful.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, yes, thanks.
Guess what.
I just won
this radio contest.
I get a weekend trip
for two to Atlantic City,
all expenses paid.
Oh, congratulations.
Who are you going to take?
Uh, I don't know.
I just moved to Boston
and I don't know a soul.
Yeah, yeah, I heard, I heard.
Oh, thanks very much.
That's incredible.
I can't believe that.
Hey, guys, guess what.
I just won
a radio contest.
You're kidding.
I did, too.
Really?
Yeah, you know, Atlantic City,
free trip, the whole works.
That's the same here.
Really?
Isn't that incredible?
Well, it, it could be.
Only problem is
I don't know who to take,
you know, two tickets
and everything.
I wonder what I should do.
About what?
You have kind of a short
attention span, don't you?
Well, I like that,
I like that.
(mumbling indistinctly)
We're talking about
my two tickets and...
Oh, yeah, you know,
I've got the same problem.
Yeah, uh, well, you
know what we ought to--
I'm Sam, by the way.
Oh.
Sam, I'm Debbie.
Hi, Debbie, uh...
maybe we should,
you know,
instead of wasting
four tickets,
we should just use
yours and go together.
That's a super idea.
Yeah, all right.
Hey, guys,
I'm off to Atlantic City.
Boy, those Japanese that say
we've lost our ingenuity
and the ability
to get the job done
ought to come to Cheers
and have a gander at Sam Malone.
Sammy.
Yeah.
I'd like you to take this,
uh, Cliff nostril money
and put it on black 17
at the roulette table.
Black 17--
you got it, pal.
Okay, we're ready.
But, now, what are we going
to do with your tickets?
Oh, I'll probably
just, uh,
give them away to
some strangers.
Oh, I'd do that, too,
but I don't know
any strangers.
This is going to be
a great weekend.
Uh, how come, uh,
black 17, Norm?
Oh, uh, well, 17
is 'cause, uh,
Vera and I were
married on the 17th.
Oh.
And black is because Vera and
I were married on the 17th.
Another one,
Dr. Crane?
Um, no thanks, Woody.
Uh, one ought to do it.
(door opens)
Mother and I have arrived,
Frasier.
Hit me, Woody, need some juice.
Thanks for helping me
with my bags, Frasier,
but I see you've got that big,
heavy drink to lug around.
Hello, Betty.
So this is where you spend
all of your time,
while my grandson
crawls around
in open stairwells
and electrical outlets.
Well, actually,
Frederick is walking now.
If my daughter had any sense,
so would she.
Is there a bathroom
around here?
Oh, yes, Mother, right
down that hallway there.
Frasier, I have
to thank you.
You seem to be trying
harder than usual
to be pleasant
to my mother.
Want to tell me what
the hell is going on?
Well, darling,
for the past few months,
I've been agonizing
over what to give you
for our fifth
wedding anniversary,
and, uh, I thought about
jewelry, a trip, a car.
But this... this
cost me even more.
"I promise not to fight
with Betty during her visit."
Happy anniversary, my love.
It's very thoughtful,
Frasier.
Exactly how do you intend
to pull that off?
Well, I've been working
at this for some time now
and whatever Betty says,
I shall let this
smile be my umbrella.
Well, get ready
to smile.
My mother has never
gotten over being upset
about missing
our wedding.
She wants us to renew
our wedding vows on Saturday.
But, darling, I...
I think the whole
idea is just...
wonderful.
(door opens)
Hey, waitress, you want to
turn up the heat in here?
I am not a
fish stick.
Or maybe I should ask someone
who can reach the thermostat.
Hey, hey.
Lady, you can't just waltz
in here, insult people,
and start ordering
everyone around.
Why not?
'Cause that's
my job.
I would have thought your job
was to live under a bridge.
Yeah?
Well, unless you want
some bridgework,
you just better shut up!
Look,
she rattled me, okay?
Betty, I-I think
it's terribly sweet
that you want us to reenact
our wedding, but...
have you given any thought
to a... a little cocktail party?
I-I think
that might be more pleasant
and perhaps a bit more intimate.
Well, you're wrong.
Very wrong.
You couldn't
be more wrong
if your fanny was
screwed on backwards.
That wrong, huh?
Thanks for dropping
me off, Debbie.
NORM:
Hey, Sammy,
how'd it go in Atlantic
City? You get lucky?
Yeah, you bet I did.
So, uh, how much
you win?
Not a cent.
I'll call you
tomorrow, all right?
Okay.
Thanks.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
Sammy? Huh? Huh?
CLIFF & NORM (high-pitched):
Huh? Huh?
So, you remember
to put that, uh,
50 bucks down on
that black 17, buddy?
Yeah, you know,
about that Norm...
Yeah?
...you know,
the strangest thing happened.
I put all your money...
Right.
...on black 17.
And lost, right?
No, no, no,
it hit, it hit.
It hit?!
All right!
But Debbie got so excited,
she started jumping
up and down and...
and by the time,
she was finished, I, uh...
I, uh, had accidentally
let your winnings ride.
I could kill you!
You did that?
And it hit again.
Whoa! What are
the odds on that?
Pretty damned
steep, buddy.
(laughs)
I don't
believe it!
(overlapping shouting)
All right! Sammy!
I'm rich!
Look at this.
(whooping)
All right!
Sam, Sam, Sam?
What, what,
what, what...?
Now that Norm's come
into all this money,
don't you think it's time
that somebody reminds him
that he has a pretty
hefty bar tab?
Oh, sweetheart,
he's my friend.
I can't mention that.
He'll come through.
I don't know, Sam.
Hey, hey, trust
me, trust me.
I've known the guy
for a long time.
He'll do the
right thing.
Sammy, this calls
for a celebration.
Let's have a
round on me, okay?
(crowd chatter)
NORM:
Drinks for everybody!
Sammy, put it on
my tab, please.
Sam? Sam?
Now, about the cake--
do you like butter cream?
Yes, Mother.
Good, because
that's what I ordered.
Now, how
about flowers?
I like roses.
Do you like
cascading lilies?
Sort of.
Good! Because
that's what I ordered.
Now...
why don't you go
and learn your vows?
I've written them out.
And I'm going
to go call the caterer.
Looking at Frasier's
friends,
I know I'm going
to need to order more.
I don't know what.
Just more.
She's written vows?
Yes.
Apparently with the
recurring phrase
"shiftless alcoholic."
Darling, for the
hundredth time,
why are we going through
with this ridiculous
wedding re-enactment?
Because every time
I try to say "no,"
it comes out "yes."
My behavior is solely
to please my mother.
Why does she always
try to turn me
into something
I'm not?
Maybe, deep down,
she always wanted a girl.
Hey.
Hey, rich guy,
mind if I do a little
reading here?
Oh.
Oh, Sammy, my tab.
Tab? Oh!
Thought it was
the Yellow Pages here.
Yeah.
Boy, we've had that thing
a long time, haven't we?
Sure have, buddy.
Look at that,
we go all the way back
to when we didn't
even know your name.
"Skinny guy
at the end of the bar."
Yep.
It's gotten
awfully big.
Kind of a
disgrace, really.
That it is, Norm.
That it is.
NORM:
Tell you what
I'm gonna do.
Since I've come into
all this money,
I'm gonna buy you
a new book.
Whenever I'm
in her presence,
I revert to being
a little girl again.
But you're not.
You're a grown woman.
You have a
successful career
and you're well respected
in your field.
Now, darling,
you must go over there
to your mother,
look her in the eye,
and, for God's sake,
tell her
that we're not going
to reenact our damn wedding!
You're right,
Frasier.
Incidentally,
why do you always refer to
it as our "damn wedding"?
One hurdle
at a time, Lilith.
Now, I'll be with you
all the time.
I'll be your support.
Lean on me.
Is anyone else hot
in here?
Say, waitress,
do you mind?
I'm not a rotisserie
chicken.
Yeah? Well, you...
you look like one.
Sam.
Huh?
I just gotta take a couple
of days sick leave.
Mother,
Frasier and I have spoken,
and there's something I have
to tell you about my wedding.
Oh, I just can't wait
to see my little
girl married.
I am so sorry I missed
it the first time!
I can't wait either,
Mommy.
Come along.
We've got a lot to do.
I'll be right
there, Mommy.
A lot of help you were,
you spineless bastard.
All that money, huh?
Yeah.
Sure will come in handy.
You could probably
pay off all your
outstanding debts, huh?
If I had any, Sam.
Not me.
Own my own house,
own my own car,
no plastic,
do not believe in debt.
So I'm beginning
to find out.
Rebecca Howe?
Why yes.
And who are you, stranger?
You wouldn't
remember me.
I was a customer here
many years ago.
I had a couple of beers
and couldn't pay for them
and this bar was kind
enough to run me a tab.
Two beers?
And you did not pay for them?
That's right, Miss.
And I'll tell you why.
Shortly after that,
I committed a crime of passion
and was sent to Devil's
Island for life.
Oh, my!
Go on, stranger.
For years, rotting
in those cells,
I was kept alive
by but one thought,
the knowledge that
I owed a debt to Cheers.
So under the light
of a tropic moon, I escaped
and fashioned
a crude raft
with vines
and coconut husks.
The rest is
unimportant.
Suffice it to say,
here's three dollars.
God bless you,
stranger.
Norm, did you hear that?
How could anyone help
but hear that?
Blah-blah-blah-blah-blah.
Could you keep it down?
I'm trying to watch some TV
over here!
How could you
even think
that someone would
be stupid enough
to take a hint
like that?
Miss Howe,
here's that dollar I borrowed
for lunch yesterday.
You know you could
have come right
out and told me
instead of having that guy
come all the way here
from Devil's Island.
Sam, let me have a quick one,
will you?
I'm showing Betty
the sights.
Oh, yeah?
Where is she?
Well, I gave her
a little shove
into Filene's Basement
and yelled "Sale!"
With any luck, she'll
be trampled to death.
Your wife's waiting
for you up there.
Oh.
Oh, hello, dear.
You caught me.
I'm hiding.
Yeah, well, this is as
good a place as any.
This is where I always come
to hide from my problems.
I mean, my-my work
problems, of course.
You know, my-my domestic
life is just, well...
Things are looking up, Frasier.
I've been researching
the problem
of how to deal
with an overbearing mother.
I think you'll be delighted
to learn
that I've hit upon the perfect
course of action.
Oh, darling, how exciting!
A breakthrough!
What's the plan?
To acquiesce totally.
Yes, I'm going to let my mother
run roughshod over me.
It's time
to cut our losses.
I'm at the third
from final turn in the maze
and unbeknownst to me,
the researcher has
removed the cheese.
Your analogies always
bring it home, dear.
Yeah, still can't get your
mother off your back, huh?
It's very difficult for me
to relate to.
Really?
Oh, yeah. Ma and I don't have
any problems.
You know, in fact, most people
find it's hard to tell
that we're even related.
Folks down at Club Med
are very surprised
when they find out
we're mother and son.
Shocked even.
You know, Dr. Sternin-Crane,
I always heard
that you should tell your
mother exactly how you feel.
Is that what you do, Woody?
Yeah, right,
like I want a whopping.
Well, thank you
very much, Woody.
I appreciate that.
You know, I have another idea.
Thank you very much, Woody.
I appreciate that.
You didn't let me
tell you the idea yet.
Woody, in certain company,
when someone says,
"Thank you very much.
I appreciate that."
It means, "I don't thank you.
I don't appreciate that.
And I want you
to shut your mouth."
Oh, thank you very much,
Dr. Sternin-Crane.
I appreciate that.
(doorbell rings)
So glad you could
come, Sam.
Oh, thank you.
The gift table's
over there.
We were, uh,
supposed to bring gifts?
Don't give it
a second thought...
Mr. Trump.
Hey, man, I'm so sorry.
I didn't realize we were
supposed to bring gifts.
Oh, that's all right, Sam.
Your presence here
is more than enough.
Paul, you scamp,
is this a toaster oven?
So you see,
that's why Shamu
cannot really be considered
a killer whale.
Hello, I'm Dr. Bramwell,
a colleague
of Frasier's.
I couldn't help overhearing
your conversation.
You must be one of his patients.
No, no...
I'm one of his friends,
uh, Cliff Clavin.
Oh, well, then I wouldn't
be poaching if I...
Well, uh... here's my card.
Huh.
Uh, thank you.
Thank you very much.
That's the third one
I got tonight.
I must have a sign
on my back or something.
Sam, there's Norm.
This might be
a good chance
No, no.
to ask him about
the bar tab.
Come on...
You can do it.
This is not--
he'll get upset.
No, he won't get upset.
This is the last place
in the world
he'd make a scene.
Just be discreet. Norm.
Norm, Sam wants to ask
you about your bar tab.
Oh.
(laughs)
I, it's just, you know,
she thinks, you know,
you came into some money,
that maybe it'd be appropriate,
you know, to pay off
some of your bar tab.
Well, sure, if I had
any money left.
Wait a minute, you spent
all-- every cent?
Yeah.
What the heck, you know,
easy come, easy go, Sammy.
It was found money, I figured,
so why not do something that
I always wanted to do with it.
So, I went down,
and I bought a boat.
Isn't it a beauty?
I can't believe that, man.
What?
You spent it?
Hah...
After all those years
of me carrying you
while you were
unemployed?!
Well... yeah, but...
You're my friend?
I-I listen to all your stupid
little comments every day?
I-I let you run up the largest
bar tab in history,
and then you come
into some money
and you tell me
you don't pay me back?
You-you spend it
on a stupid boat?!
Well, I hope you and
the stupid boat sink!
You big deadbeat!
Sammy, I, I bought
the boat for you.
See, it's, it's
the Mayday Malone, see?
I mean, thank you.
You know, I know how bad
you felt when your boat sank
and, well, it's something
I always wanted to do, big guy.
Oh, man.
That's the nicest thing
anyone's ever done for me.
Yeah.
Hey, listen, about
that bar tab...
Yeah, I know...
I've broken it down
into 36 easy payments.
Now I want you
to stand up straight
when you're out there.
All eyes will be on you.
Yes, Mommy.
And for heaven's sake, speak up.
I want to hear
every word clearly.
(louder):
Yes, Mommy.
Not now, when you're out there.
(knocking)
May I see the bride
before the ceremony?
Oh, no, Frasier.
I don't want you
to see me like this.
Oh, nonsense, dear.
Oh, my Lord.
Is this my Lilith,
so... so beautiful?
"Beautiful"?
And your hair.
It's so gorgeous.
My face is beautiful?
My hair is gorgeous?
What's next, I have a cute,
little caboose?
Watch your mouth, Lilith.
You know how much
I hate this.
I wouldn't have put
this horrid paint on my face
or worn this atrocious hairdo
if my mother
weren't emotionally
blackmailing me into doing so.
"Blackmailing" you?
How could you?!
Shut up, Mother!
It's bad enough I have to be
your little girl,
I don't have to be his, too.
Now, for once in your life,
keep your mouth shut
and butt out!
(crying)
I'm sorry, Mother.
Oh, no.
It's so beautiful!
I said the same thing
to my mother on my wedding day.
The tears,
the unhappiness...
I wouldn't have
missed this for the world.
(knocking)
Uh, Fras, you going
to be much longer?
'Cause I hit that
punch bowl kind of hard.
Are you going to be
all right, Mother?
Yes, I'm fine.
I want to be ready when
they ask if anybody objects.
I've written it all out.
We love you, too, Betty.
Frasier, I apologize
for yelling at you.
Now be honest.
Didn't you say that I was
beautiful and gorgeous
only to force a catharsis?
Guilty as charged.
Then help me get
this junk off my face.
("Wedding March" begins)
Oh, darling.
We don't seem to have
time for that right now.
As much as I hate it,
you'll have to keep it on.
Oh.
Now listen,
let's go out there
and say our "I do's"
and then I'll haul
your cute, little caboose
up to the bedroom.
Thank you, Frasier.
("Wedding March" continues)
Oh, the hell with the "I do's."