Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
MAN (on TV): ...so grab your rod
and reel, and join us next week
when Jim takes us trolling
on Lake Winnebeshaki.
Nice show, huh?
Well, if you ask me,
there's something wrong
with watching televised fishing.
Not the same impact
as watching it live, huh, Woody?
Hey, you know something?
I got a great idea.
What's to stop us
from taking a little
fishing trip ourselves?
We don't want to?
Oh.
Come on, it'd be fun.
You know, we could go
this very afternoon,
head out to Lake Winthrop, huh?
What do you say? NORM: All right.
Okay. All right, let's get
organized here, uh, Woody.
Uh, I'd like you to be in charge
of bait and tackle, okay?
Got you.
Cliffy in charge of, uh,
food and the transportation.
Okay.
Well, what're you in
charge of, Mr. Peterson?
Finding a reason not to go.
Ah, here we go.
Huh? Gladiator film
festival at the Majestic.
CLIFF: Yeah, that's a good one.
♪ Boom, boom, boom, boom ♪
(humming dramatic fanfare)
De gustibus non est disputandum!
(humming continues)
(piano plays)
♪ Making your way in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like to get away♪
♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always glad you came ♪
♪ You want to be where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You want to go where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Hi, Sam.
Hi.
Oh, uh,
some customer was in
with some tickets to some concert,
sounded foreign and dull.
I thought you wouldn't want to miss it.
Thank you.
(gasps)
Jean Pierre Rampal!
It was just some customer. I
didn't really catch his name.
Oh.
He's a flautist.
Nothing less than brilliant.
No other player could so
eloquently fuse the world of
classical music to that of modern jazz.
What a perfect performer for us to see
on this, our first
official date together
in our new-found relationship.
What should I wear?
Something long or tea length?
Why don't you wear something
you can stretch out in?
Oh.
The seat next to you's gonna be empty.
Sam!
Come on, please.
Can't you scrape somebody
else up to go? Please.
And the operative
word there is "scrape."
There's only one man I want to be with.
No, no, I'll go alone.
And it'll be fine. Mm.
Miss Chambers,
I might be back from my fishing trip
in time to take you,
if I don't stop to clean up first.
No, thank you, Woody, that's very sweet.
Maybe next time.
Okeydoke, but I don't know
when I'm gonna be going fishing again.
Cliffy, it was not ten.
I had 11 of 'em. 11!
You're wrong, Normie,
you're wrong, wrong, wrong.
How was the Gladiator film fest, fellas?
CLIFF: Not now, Sammy.
We're awash in controversy.
You had ten, Norm,
just like me.
Ten what?
Anachronisms. Huh?
Oh, you know, those things that, uh,
aren't in the time period
in which the film is set.
Normie and I like to see
who-who gets the most.
Today it was me. 11!
Normie, you had ten just like me.
There was no way
it was Caesar Augustus wearing Reeboks.
Hey, so you guys ready
to go fishing? Uh...
we got to... You know,
Woody, uh, couple beers first.
You know, I work up a
powerful thirst watching,
uh, Thoracian dogs smite
Spartan pigs, you know.
Greetings, everyone.
Hey, Frasier.
How about a beer?
Oh, well, no, Sam, just
make it a club soda.
I've got to appear on TV today,
and I want to keep my wits about me.
Oh my! SAM: No kidding?
What's the TV show?
FRASIER: Well, it's a
local talk show called
Psychology This Week.
Oh.
Oh, maybe you heard it. I don't know.
I know all about that show.
It's where once a week a couple
of shrinks get together
and debate certain aspects
of the psychological condition.
That's right. NORM: Oh, man,
we had to pick today to
go fishing, huh, Cliff?
Well, I'm surprised.
I didn't know you were a fan.
SAM: Hmm...
Well, he was, but he stopped watching
when they lost the hostess
with the big Hindenburgs.
It's on at 4:00.
It promises to be very cerebral,
and, uh, I might add,
uh, darned entertaining.
Well, uh,
unfortunately, Frasier, it interferes
with another highly
cerebral event--
the, uh, Raiders
- Patriots game.
SAM: Yeah, right.
I realize that football
is a rarity on television in the fall,
but don't you think we
could spare half an hour
to see our friend, Frasier?
Do you have any idea how
much action you can miss
in a half an hour of football?
About 18 seconds.
Oh, all right, all right.
I guess it won't hurt... much.
Thank you, Sam.
(phone ringing)
Cheers. Yeah, hold on a second.
Oh.
You want to tell me what
the taxicab was doing,
uh, parked in front of
the Temple of Athena?
Yeah... all right,
uh, it was, uh... uh...
it was, uh, probably taking
Demitrius to the airport.
Well, thank you.
(clearing throat)
Well, as it turns out,
you can now watch your game
with a clear conscience.
I won't be doing that show after all.
What changed your mind, Frasier?
Well, Dr. Foster had
to cancel, and, uh...
Dr. Sternin is going to take his place.
Lilith Sternin?
You mean that-- uh,
pardon my French--
woman you once dated?
That's a rather charitable
description, Cliff.
Well, I just hope they can find someone
to replace me as readily
as they did Dr. Foster.
Can't handle debating a woman, eh?
A woman, yes.
An ice cube in heels, no!
Look, I have no intention
of entering a debate
with those cold, gray eyes and
those clever, smirking lips.
I'd rather clip my nails in a Cuisinart.
Oh, my.
What's wrong?
Oh, don't you see?
Frasier's in love.
He's what?
Oh, come on, Sam.
You're forgetting I was once
romantically involved with Frasier.
I know when he's enamored of someone.
Didn't you see his nostrils flare?
And everyone knows that hate
is not the opposite of love.
Indifference is.
Well, whatever you say.
I really don't care.
Touch?, Sam.
Let's be honest.
Quite often you've expressed
feelings of antagonism toward me,
and we both know how much you love me.
I...
I do not love you, Diane,
and I have the nostrils to prove it.
And you...
You're wrong about Frasier.
I mean, I know
psychobabble when I hear it,
and I also...
Wait. Uh...
Frasier? There's a theory
going around the bar
that you're ticked off with Dr. Sternin
because you're in love with her.
What do you think?
Well, that sounds like someone
who doesn't know shortcake from Shinola.
Hey, good guess,
good guess-- Diane.
FRASIER: Oh, well, hmm.
That's nothing but mere
cocktail-party psychology.
Believe it or not, Sam,
it's actually possible
to have hostile feelings toward someone
without being in love with them.
You mean I can actually hate Diane
without having it mean
anything more than I hate her?
Feel free. Ooh!
Oh, I better cancel
that appearance before it's too late.
Hang on. There you go.
CLIFF: Uh-oh!
Frost warning.
Good afternoon, Dr. Crane.
Dr. Sternin.
What a lovely surprise.
I hope I can regard that as civility
in light of today's situation,
rather than sarcasm at my expense.
No, that was completely at your expense.
You know, I wasn't
going to do today's show
when I heard you were the other guest,
but then I realized I'd relish
proving my superiority
over you in public.
Yes, that appeals to me, too.
So, I felt we should at least discuss
some procedures of conduct.
Ah, well...
Don't you dare.
My mistake.
So, am I to assume that
you just naturally thought
that I'd be at this
drinking establishment?
Actually, knowing your
obsessive-compulsiveness,
I checked with your service,
and indeed, you'd left them
a very complete itinerary of your day.
I trust all went well
at the dry cleaner's.
Thank you, yes.
And I can assume from your questioning
that you're attempting
to make idle conversation
rather than articulating
some control dysfunction
with my personal habits.
That's correct.
Are they fighting?
LILITH: First of all,
I think any mention of
our past relationship
could tarnish the objectivity
factor of the show.
You call that a relationship?
I mean, we dated one time.
The closest we came to physical contact
was when you closed
the car door on my hand.
Are you repressing? Oh!
Forgive me. Actually,
you're quite right.
Yes, I should be
straightforward in telling you
that you are passionless,
stoic and emotionally numb.
Apology accepted. Merci.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
they're fighting.
He just asked for mercy.
Secondly, I think perhaps we...
Look, Dr. Sternin, if you'll excuse me,
I have to cash a check and fill up
my gas tank before the show.
Yes, I know.
Have the attendant make sure your tires
aren't as inflated as your ego.
You know, you perplex me.
Oh?
Yes, normally people of
your limited physical appeal
make up for it with
an actual personality.
Dr. Sternin, excuse me.
I overheard Dr. Crane's remarks.
If it's any consolation,
I can empathize with your hurt feelings.
If you'd like to share
any of them with me
as a fellow woman, I
would consider it an honor.
Who are you?
(chuckles softly)
Diane Chambers.
I'm an old friend of
Dr. Crane's, a student,
and until my imminent marriage,
an employee here at Cheers.
Please, let's sit down.
Well, I suppose I am
just a little sensitive
when it pertains to my appearance.
Well, if I may be so bold
as to step into your arena,
I believe that
Frasier's hostility
is masking a deep attraction to you.
(subdued chuckling)
Thank you, Diane.
It's been a long time since
I've had such a good laugh.
Why would Frasier Crane
be attracted to me?
I'm not that kind of woman.
But you can be.
It just takes a little
softening of the edges.
Perhaps loosen the bun a bit
to relieve some of the
tension in your face.
I'm afraid it's not as easy as all that.
Oh, that's nonsense. Look...
I'm not far from here.
Why don't you come over to my place,
and I'll show you what I mean?
We'll just put a little
more makeup on, or...
some.
I really don't think I can do that.
Oh, come on, Dr. Sternin.
You're going to be on television today.
A little refinement of your appearance
might give you an edge in the debate.
Well, I suppose it wouldn't hurt.
Good, good! Let me get my things.
Sam,
may I have my purse, please? Oh,
and I'm going to be taking my lunch hour
a little early today.
Thank you for showing up at all.
You're welcome.
Shall we go?
You know, I've always
envied women like you
who could simply tumble
out of bed each morning
looking blonde and perky.
Oh, well, I must admit,
in my case, there is a
little labor involved.
A little labor?
She's calls in Local 416.
(TV plays) Yeah.
Oh. Yeah?
Come on, guys.
CLIFF: Yeah, I think they...
Okay, the tank's full,
and the gear's all loaded.
I got everything you could possibly need
for a fishing trip.
Uh, Woody, look, uh, we're right
in the middle of the game, huh?
I got a battery-operated
portable TV in the car.
We got a few beers to
finish here yet, buddy.
I got a cooler full
icing down in the trunk.
Yup, I think
the kid's outlasted us, Norm.
WOODY: Hot dog!
Look out, trout! (laughs)
Hey, if you guys don't
mind, I'll do the driving.
All right, I got shotgun.
Wouldn't it be more sporting
to use a fishing pole?
Oh, this is gonna be great!
ANNOUNCER: It's a
fumble. Davis picks it up
for the Patriots, He's
got a clear field...
Come on, come on, come on...
(all shouting)
(theme music plays) Aw, come on, Diane.
It's a great game. What're you do...?
Now let's all check our watches.
Did we not promise to watch
Frasier's show at 4:00?
All right, everybody see it?
ALL: Yeah.
(fans cheering on TV)
(affirmative shouts)
(indistinct voices)
All right, fine!
I'm not gonna play cat-and-mouse
with a silly remote control box.
You know, all you people ever see
of Frasier Crane is an ordinary Joe
sitting at the bar
being one of the guys.
You should see him in his métier.
He's a brilliantly perceptive man.
Does anybody have a
box that'll shut her up?
No, but I'd be glad to do it manually.
SAM: Oh!
Come on, you guys. We made a promise.
MAN: Aw, Sammy! Thank you, Sam.
HOST: First I'd like to introduce
Dr. Frasier Crane.
Dr. Crane is an eminent psychiatrist
here in the Boston area
specializing in treatment of phobias.
(applause)
Joining Dr. Crane in this discussion
is Dr. Lilith Sternin.
Dr. Sternin is a member
of the psychiatric staff
at Boston General Hospital.
(applause)
(crowd murmuring)
Welcome, Dr. Sternin.
Thank you. Dr. Crane.
You really made her
look beautiful, Diane.
Physician, heal thyself.
HOST: You've made many
excellent points, Dr. Sternin.
How do you respond to them,
Dr. Crane?
Oh, excu... What was the question?
Oh, uh,
yes, of course.
Excuse me, uh...
Yes, my method of...
flooding, uh,
seeks out the patient's,
well, most sensitive and vulnerable spot
in the defense system, and, uh...
penetrates...
probing deeper and deeper
into the patient's psyche,
thrusting over and over.
And thereby uncovering the reality
behind the irrational fear.
Thank you, Dr. Crane.
Anything to add, Dr. Sternin?
Yes.
Uh...
(clears throat): Although
Dr. Crane's method is faster...
a slow and methodical approach
can be much more rewarding.
Gentle stroking of the psyche
will bring about a far more
intense release of emotion
building until the patient
quite often will literally
cry out in a release of
satisfaction and joy.
(gasping): Point well taken.
This intellectual stuff's
getting me all hot.
This is embarrassing.
We shouldn't be watching this.
Mm.
Well, maybe just a little while... Yeah.
...and that concludes
this afternoon's program.
Aw! Oh, no, no, hey.
Boo! Come on!
HOST: Dr. Sternin,
Dr. Crane, thank you for joining us.
Oh, excuse me.
For a written transcript
of this afternoon's show,
please send a self-addressed,
stamped envelope
to Psychology This Week, Box 84037,
Boston, Massachusetts,
0220...
5.
What was that box number again?
Uh, 02205.
Hey, fellas, how was the fishing trip?
Geez. It would have been a little better
without Cliff's jabbering.
Guy catches one fish,
turns into Ernest Hemingway.
Oh, congratulations, Cliff.
Thank you, Sammy.
Yeah, it was man against fish.
The rest of the world was shut out.
It was a good fish, a clean fish,
a strong fish.
A little fish.
Get that stinking,
slimy thing out of here.
And take your fish with you.
Oh, Frasier, I didn't expect
to see you here.
Thought you'd be exchanging
psychological positions
with Dr. Sternin.
Please, Sam.
I made a complete fool of
myself today and Dr. Sternin.
If they'd had a hose at the studio,
they would have turned it on us.
Actually, that sounds kind of fun.
I'll never be able to
look her in the eye again.
The only consolation is
that nobody ever watches that show.
Way to go, sex machine!
I'm ruined.
Half of New England saw me today
as a rutting pig.
Come on, Frasier.
You're not in rut, you're in love.
Oh, nonsense!
I don't think that because
two people breathe heavily
on a TV show is any cause for them
to declare their undying love.
Breathe heavily?
I thought you were gonna
suck in a chair there.
Listen, a TV station
may not have been the
best place in the world
to sprout antlers, but it happened.
Go with it.
DIANE: Dr. Sternin, you're...
back.
Diane, I'd like to thank you
for your Pygmalion-like efforts.
I'd like to, but I can't,
because they led to disaster.
Good evening, Dr. Crane.
Dr. Sternin.
It's, uh, nice to see you again.
And you.
I apologize for my overzealous
behavior this afternoon.
And for making fools of us both.
Yes, well, I would also like
to apologize for my completely
unprofessional attitude, and
I promise you that
that sort of thing
will never happen again.
Fine.
I've already penned a letter
to the American Psychiatric Association
apologizing for my behavior.
I would suggest that you do likewise.
Of course, of course.
And I think
perhaps for the sake of our
professional reputations,
it's best we put this matter behind us
and go on with our lives.
Oh.
That is probably wise.
You see, I've already
lost three patients
as a result of today's fiasco.
That's odd.
I picked up three.
While we're on the subject,
Dr. Crane, I suggest
that your behavior indicates
an unacceptable level
of sexual frustration.
You strike me as a man who
needs professional help.
Or perhaps a girlfriend.
And you strike me as a woman
who could use a good cuffing.
Good day, Dr. Crane.
Good day, Dr. Sternin.
Uh, just a moment, Dr. Sternin.
Um...
Sam, isn't the refrigerator
door stuck again?
I don't think so. Oh,
I think it is.
And we need a hairpin
to open it up. Dr. Sternin,
could we borrow a hairpin?
I don't see how a hairpin will help.
Strangely enough, it does.
FRASIER: Oh, well,
don't you see?
What these
two people who are
such geniuses at romance
are trying to do
is to get you to take your hair down,
thinking that it will stimulate me
like some sort of Pavlovian dog.
So, why don't you just
oblige them, get this
silliness over with
so we can get on with our lives?
(sighs)
You mean like this?
Precisely.
You know what?
What?
I'm going to kiss you.
I'm going to
kiss you hard, and I'm
going to kiss you long.
But make no mistake about it,
I am going to kiss you.
In fact, I'm going to kiss
you like you've never...
(sighs)
Yes, like that.
Now listen, Lilith, I think
you and I have just been
too articulate for words.
We talk and we talk, and
what we really want to do
is show how we feel.
I think, Dr. Crane...
Look, I don't care what you think!
We both want to be animals.
Now I'm going back to my tastefully
decorated townhouse
and prove it.
Well, I-I suggest you come with me.
I think I see what you're trying
to do, Dr. Crane, and I
just want you to know...
it worked.
Let's go.
Isn't it exciting to see the blush
of new-found love on their faces?
Do you realize
we've just seen the birth of
a new ro... Don't you
have someplace to go?
Oh, yes.
The concert.
By myself.
I'll go.
And sure, I'll be
alone, but I don't care.
Because I'm in love.
And no one who's
truly in love can ever be alone.
And I know my fellow loves me.
He just doesn't know it yet.
So I'll go to this concert,
listen to the music, and
dream again of the day
when he'll be sitting beside me,
holding my hand,
sharing the moment.
That's my dream,
and mine alone.
And no one can...
Get her out of here!
I'll go.
Only if you really want to.
But this is not a date.
The fact that we sit together
has nothing to do with anything.
We're gonna take separate cabs.
I will not talk to you
during the intermission.
I'm not gonna take you
anywhere afterwards,
and we will not mention
this ever again, okay?
Fine.
Okay.
Is that love, or what?