Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
(cheering)
(static hissing)
NORM: Hey, wow, Sammy!
Woody, Woody, Woody, jump up there
and fix the TV. again, will you?
(patrons complaining)
Whoa, whoa!
Perfect, Perfect!
Don't move!
Oh, wait a second,
Woody-- uh, just a...
just a minor adjustment.
SAM: That's it!
Oh, I sure hope this game
doesn't go into overtime.
(piano plays)
♪ Making your way in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like to get away♪
♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always glad you came ♪
♪ You want to be where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You want to go where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Sam, here's your change.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, dear.
What?
I can't remember whether
or not I left my stove on.
Oh, boy.
No, it's off.
A-ha. I think.
It's off. Of course it's off.
It's on. My apartment's on fire.
Still...
Go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, wait, uh, before you go,
uh, while you were
up there at Melville's
a Madame Likova called.
Something about showing up tonight
with, uh, a videotape and analysis?
Here? Madame Likova? Yeah.
Well, we've got to get
this place cleaned up.
Everyone, out!
What's the big deal? Who is she?
What?
Well, she...
Promise me, all of you, that
you won't make fun of me.
Yeah, right.
Hey... Carla, come on.
No, we, uh, we won't make
fun of you, we promise.
I've been studying ballet.
(laughing)
Sam!
You laughed.
No, no, we just, uh,
all thought of a joke.
What joke?
You in a tutu.
Come on. What is this?
Come on. Tell us all about it.
Madame Likova has been visiting Boston
and she consented to teach
a class at the college.
On a caprice,
I decided to enroll and I was accepted.
Our final session entailed doing
a solo performance on videotape.
Oh, I get it--
that way she could
puke in the privacy of her own home.
NORM: Diane, uh,
why the sudden interest in ballet?
Oh, Norman, it's not sudden.
I've had an on-again,
off-again love affair
with the ballet since
I was seven years old.
I studied for a while, then gave it up.
Regrettably, of course.
Although I was blessed
with a swan-like neck
and natural grace...
I abandoned my dream of
becoming a prima ballerina
and concentrated instead
on my career as a novelist.
Which explains why you're
here in a bar pushing beers.
Oh, I remember the first time
I ever put on my toe shoes...
Excuse me, Diane. Isn't
your apartment on fire?
Oh, my God!
I completely forgot!
My poor kitty.
Wait a minute.
I'm sure I turned it off.
(sizzling noise)
(coughing)
(meowing)
Hi, Cliff.
Hey, Diane. Hi, everybody.
Sammy? Hey!
Mind if I put one of these up
on the old, uh, bulletin board?
Go ahead.
Ah, better take this old
one of mine down, huh?
Boy, oh, boy, nobody was interested
in my singles potluck séance.
What's going up this time?
Well, you know, for years
I've been saving up
and, uh, finally made it.
I bought myself a snazzy
Italian sports car.
Yup.
As of tomorrow I'm going to be the owner
of a brand new Alfredo.
Hey, all right.
But first I got to, uh,
sell off the old Cliff-mobile.
Wait a minute.
Now you own a 1965 Chevy
station wagon, right?
Yes, sir.
This is a picture of a Rolls-Royce.
What are you doing?
Uh, read the copy there, Sammy.
"Chevy, the Rolls-Royce
of station wagons."
Oh, come on.
Smart.
Um, ex... excuse me.
SAM: Yeah?
I'm looking for Diane Chambers.
Oh, she's not here right now.
Oh, I'll bet you, you're
Madame Lik... Likova.
Oh! Oh, goodness no.
No.
How Madame would laugh
if she heard you say that.
And then she would strike me.
No, I, I am Leeza, her assistant.
Oh, Sam Malone, hi.
Hello. Hello.
Frasier Crane.
Hello.
Uh, well, is Madame
going to come here
later on tonight?
Oh, no, no, Madame Likova
would never come to a tavern.
No, I am bringing by
the tape and analysis for Diane.
Normally the students
pick them up themselves,
but, well, Madame Likova
can be very... harsh,
so I wanted to soften the blow
by bringing them here myself.
Her dancing's that bad, huh?
I am afraid so.
That is why I, I, I
wanted to come here myself
and, and tell her not to dance anymore.
Uh, but I, I have to go now.
Uh, we are checking out tonight.
And an impatient Madame Likova
is a dangerous Madame Likova.
Oh.
Uh, give her this
videotape and this envelope
and tell her I'm so sorry.
Well, I will. Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you.
Do Svidaniya.
"Do Svidaniya", huh?
Those Russkies can never leave
without slipping in
some Soviet propaganda.
Hey, you guys think, uh, Diane
is really that bad of a dancer?
CARLA: I don't know.
Guess there's no way of
ever knowing, is there?
Yeah, none that I can really think of.
CLIFF: Me, uh, neither.
And who knows if that VCR
in Sammy's office even works, you know?
There's, uh, there's only one way
to find out, you know. How's that?
Get a tape and, uh,
slip it right in there.
Talk about luck.
Here's a tape right here.
That's extremely insensitive.
No, it's not. No, it's not.
It's like driving by
the scene of an accident.
You don't want to look,
but you just can't help yourself.
Yeah, and in this case you get
to play it over and over again.
(piano playing)
Is it working?
(laughing)
Guess so.
Hey, that's Miss Chambers.
Oh, boy.
Why is she hopping around like that?
Well, she's dancing, Woody.
Get out!
I don't know, guys.
You know, maybe this isn't funny.
Sam, are you looking at the screen?
I-I-I'm sorry.
I'm just...
(groaning, complaining)
Being laughed at is
going to be the least
of Diane's worries.
If she ever reads this analysis,
she's going to be shattered.
Take a look at this thing.
Oh, boy.
"Poor, poor,
poor, terrible..."
Ooh, how was her attendance?
What... I mean, what are we gonna do?
She thinks her teacher's
going to show up tonight.
Uh, what are we going to tell her?
We're not going to tell her anything.
Madame Likova is going
to write her a splendid analysis.
Can I borrow your office?
Oh, hey, now wait a second now.
Do you think this is
the right way to do it?
Oh, listen, what harm can it do?
I mean, she said this
was a one-shot deal.
Why not let her leave it a winner?
Uh, why would you, her favorite doormat,
want to make her feel
better about herself?
Oh, I hear what you're saying.
Yeah, sure, she mocked me, debased me,
humiliated me, ridiculed me,
finally left me at the altar,
but you never really can
forget your first love, can you?
Back again.
And you'll all be happy to know
that my oven was off.
Ah!
But I had left the milk out,
so it wasn't a wasted trip.
Uh, Diane,
while you were out,
your, uh, dance teacher's
assistant came by.
Oh, poo.
Madame Likova didn't come?
No, no, uh, she got hold
of a bad bowl of borscht.
Uh...
but she, she, uh, told us
to make sure you got this.
Here it is.
Yeah.
The moment of truth.
Mm...
Oh, I can't.
Oh, oh, come on.
You, you're going to
have to open it sometime.
"Technique: very good.
"Strength: very good.
"Emotional response: outstanding.
Flexibility: average"?
Well, I always thought
I was very flexible.
"Excellent natural instincts."
"Soul of a dancer."
"If not for the late start,
could have had a career in dance."
Oh, my.
Oh, I'd love to call her and thank her.
Maybe I can still
catch her at the hotel.
Oh, no, no, Diane, I don't
think that's a good idea at all.
Why not?
Why not...?
Because, uh, because...
Well, uh, you know,
she's probably packing
and if you disturb her right now,
she'd probably put, uh, her,
her work clothes in one bag
and her regular stuff in another bag.
Then if the airline
lost one of those bags,
then she, you know,
either she wouldn't be able
to work or she'd look real
goofy out there on the street.
That's why not.
Is there something
you're not telling me?
No! Ha! No.
We're just, uh...
What are we doing here?
Uh, well, we're, ha,
we're horsing around.
Horsing around, huh?
(laughing)
FRASIER: No, listen.
The fact is we're all just
thrilled to death about the report.
Now you go ahead and call
her. I'm out of here, fellas.
Sit.
Ah, yes, Madame Likova, please.
Oh, boy...
DIANE: Oh, I see.
She's busy, huh?
Well, maybe...
Oh, Madame Likova!
Madame Likova!
Yes, yes.
This is Diane Chambers.
I'm, I'm so glad I caught you.
I...
Yes. Yes, Madame Likova.
I read it. I...
Did you really mean everything you said?
Ah, yes, I'm sorry.
I know you always mean what you say.
(line disconnects, dial tone buzzes)
Hello?
She hung up.
Well, she was never one to chat.
This is unbelievable.
Mmm.
I never thought I was this good.
Maybe I've been too critical of myself.
I really don't think that's possible.
I must view my tape again--
through Madame's eyes.
Would any of you mind, if...?
Mind?
We'd be angry if you didn't.
Oh, my friends.
I'm, I'm so glad you're all here
to share this moment with me.
I tell you what.
What don't you come and stand
right up close to the television here?
Oh, okay.
So you get the best possible viewing,
and we'll just sort of surround you
behind you so we don't
distract you, all right?
CARLA: Hit it!
(piano playing)
Yes, yes. Look at me.
(muffled laughter)
Ever since I was a child,
I wanted to dance so badly.
Ooh, looks like you got your wish.
Norman, don't you think it's time
you got home to your beloved?
No, no, it's, uh, Vera's
night to howl tonight.
She's, uh, hosting a Tupperware party.
I'd say, uh,
right about now they're
probably knee-deep
in lettuce crispers.
Vera's really into Tupperware?
Are you kidding?
She wants to be buried
in one of those things.
I can just, uh, see the service.
You know, they lower
you into the ground,
somebody burps the corner
and you're sealed fresh
for eternity, I guess.
Oh...
Was that a sigh, Diane?
I don't know.
Come on. What's the matter? Come on.
Nothing. You mentioned eternity, and...
it got me to thinking.
"For of all the sad
words of tongue or pen,
The saddest are these:
It might have been."
Yeah.
I wonder what might have happened
if I had pursued my dream.
Who knows?
I might have ended up an
accomplished ballerina.
Now I'll never know.
Yeah, that is tough, but, uh, well,
that's what you get for dreaming.
Didn't you ever have a dream, Norman?
No.
Not at all? Nope.
You never wanted something
that was out of reach?
Well, uh... beer nuts.
Norman, I'm serious.
So am I. Could you just...
Yeah.
Everyone has dreams, Norman.
Everyone except me.
I learned
early in life not to have 'em.
Oh...
Yeah! I figure they're useless.
They don't come true anyway.
Norman...
Yeah, life's tough enough
without getting yourself all worked up
over something that's not gonna happen.
Mm-mm.
Dreams-- they just
give you heartache.
But isn't the real heartache
knowing that you had the
potential to do something
and you never tried?
Listen to me.
Listen to me!
Do I have another choice?
I have the potential to be a dancer.
I still have a fighting chance
to make my dream come true.
I'm gonna send my tape to Boston Ballet.
You know... In fact, I am
going to drop it in the mail tonight.
I, uh...
Oh, Norman...
Diane?
Oh, this is so wonderful. Well...
Thank you so much. (smooches)
Um...
I'm too excited to stick around.
Anyway, you know how to
lock up, right, Norman?
You kidding? I'm the one who taught you.
Right.
Good night.
Yeah.
Well.
Ah, alone in a bar.
Maybe Diane is right.
I guess dreams can come true.
Hello, everyone.
My!
Don't you look the ballerina.
Thank you, Carla.
Now, why don't you take a flying leap?
Sam, the reason I came early
was to tell you that I'm
going to be a little late.
You're not early. You're right on time.
Oh. Well, then, I'm
going to be quite late.
I'm auditioning for Boston Ballet.
Would you mind
if I warmed up?
This seems a tad high, but
it might serve as a barre.
Well, it is a bar, Miss Chambers.
No, Woody, when a dancer warms up,
they hold onto a barre.
That is a bar.
FRASIER: If I might
interrupt here, uh...
Please.
Diane, what audition?
Well, you know I sent off my tape
to Boston Ballet.
Yeah. What audition?
Well, they had the nerve
to send it back unopened.
They never even looked at it.
I think that's patently unfair.
Is that giving art a chance?
Well, uh, Diane, do you think,
uh, maybe you're just not ready
for the Boston Ballet? Hmm?
Yes, I am.
I know it.
Madame Likova knows it.
The only people who don't know it
are the people at Boston Ballet,
and they're about to find out.
They're rehearsing now.
They're going to see me
if I have to do a grand
jet? over the gate.
Uh, Diane, I think
that might be a mistake.
Why?
Don't you think I'm good enough?
Oh, no. Oh, hey, are you kidding me?
I think you're wonderful.
Heh. So what's the point?
Um, Frasier, the point?
The point is...
You know...
you two have been behaving
very mysteriously lately.
Oh...
Are you planning a surprise party?
(laughing): You're onto us.
Darn! Oh...
Well, I will try to act surprised.
Oh.
Well, that's great, but
as I was saying, Diane,
the point is... well, not to make
a big scene about this thing.
You see, I-I'm sure the Boston Ballet
must have, uh,
open auditions, you know,
from time to time.
Why not, uh, wait till then?
I've wasted enough
time already. Thank you.
No, wait, Di-Diane, wait a second here.
Uh, oh, boy.
Listen, I-I'm going to...
(laughs)
I-I'm going to have
to tell you something,
and, uh, you may not like it.
You see, the-the truth...
the truth is that...
Sam, I know what it is.
You're afraid of losing
me to the world of ballet.
No, no, see, that's...
See, that's not what
I'm afraid of at all.
Oh, my plucky little man.
I-I-I...
Whoo, boy!
I'm just going to have to come
right out and, uh, say this.
Uh, I-I hope I don't hurt
your feelings here, um...
Please, please, please, don't do this.
Help me here, Frasier.
Diane, please, please,
please, don't do this.
Sam...
this is one of the most
genuine displays of affection
you've ever shown me.
With love like this in my corner,
how could I possibly fail?
Yeah, well...
Hmm...
Frasier, she's not going to believe me.
Tell her. Come on, tell her.
Diane, Diane, just a second.
There's something I've
got to get off my chest.
Uh... Yes, Frasier?
Knock 'em dead.
Thank you.
What?!
(classical music playing on piano)
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Excuse me!
Miss, we're in the
middle of a rehearsal.
Yes, yes, and-and you're
all very wonderful,
but I have something I'd like to say.
CHOREOGRAPHER: Miss, please...
This will only take a second.
Hold it, everybody.
(piano playing stops)
Oh, you may put her down.
Kirby, please show
the lady to the wings.
Oh, no, no, please.
I must prove to you that I indeed belong
in your fine fraternity. Kirby!
I'm sorry, miss,
but we just don't have
time for this right now.
I don't have much time myself.
A dancer's career is not a long one.
I'm sorry, but it's true.
I have a dream: to be a dancer.
And in order for it to come true,
you must see me dance.
Oh, yes, my technique
is not quite as polished
as it should be, but is
that all there is to art?
Mere technique?
Or is it not the passion
and emotion and pain that
lie deep within our souls?
For I have that emotion.
I have felt that pain.
I... I am a feeling person,
and I can communicate those
feelings to you through dance,
so judge me not by what
my arms and legs are doing.
Judge me... by what I make you feel.
No, most importantly, judge me...
for I must dance.
Damn it, I must!
Well...
Oh! Thank you!
You won't be disappointed.
Oh, oh!
SAM (whispering): Psst! Hey!
(whispering)
Never mind.
(classical piano music playing)