Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
(wrench clicking)
Oh, no!
You got some car trouble?
Oh, yeah.
Every time it gets cold,
my stupid battery dies.
Gotta get a new one?
Ugh! No, that's
all right.
I got one
right here.
(grunts)
Here. Norm,
close the hood.
Start walking
real fast.
(theme song begins)
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always
glad you came
You wanna be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You wanna be where
everybody knows your name
You wanna go
where people know
People are all the same
You wanna go where
everybody knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Hey, guys, how do I look?
NORM:
Ooh!
Hey!
Major spiffy!
Oh, that's right! Today's
the big day, isn't it?
Yup. Kelly's coming back
from France.
Ah! She's hopping the pond, eh?
The what?
The pond. It's a reference
to the Atlantic.
Uh, the Atlantic is an ocean,
not a pond, Dr. Crane.
How many of those
have you had?
Apparently, not enough.
Boy, I am
really nervous.
It seems like
Kelly's been gone a year.
How long has she been gone?
A year.
Can I put some ice
in that drink for
you, Dr. Crane?
Hey, guys!
I just put a down payment
on immortality!
Oh, yeah? What are
you talking about?
I'm s... I'm sorry.
It just slipped out.
The miracle of cryogenics.
Oh, that thing
where they freeze you?
Yeah. Go ahead,
take a look.
You know, when my number
is up, uh, I'll be frozen
and preserved
in a subzero container
moments after a doctor
declares me legally brain dead.
Boy, that's a tough call.
You know, in this brochure,
the containers look
kind of small.
They don't freeze
your entire body.
No, just the brain pan.
They cut off your head
and freeze it?
Uh-huh.
What do they do with the rest
of your body, throw it away?
Well, it's a start.
NORM:
Cliff, uh,
this corporation
wouldn't be owned
by a dog food
company, would it?
SAM:
I want to get
this straight. So,
when it's time for you
to thaw out, what do they do?
They, like, uh, put your head
in a plastic bag
and plop you in some
boiling water for three minutes?
CARLA:
Sammy!
Sammy, this is science,
not Lean Cuisine.
Hey, Clavin on ice.
That's nice.
FRASIER:
Now, wait a minute.
Why is everybody
making fun of Cliff?
Now, I'm not saying
that I believe
that Cliff's severed head
will be brought back to life
in the year 2278 to
charm and delight
a new generation
of Bostonians,
but who knows?
I mean, who can
predict the future?
CARLA:
Hey,
look, everybody--
it's Clavin's family reunion!
That's it, I'm out of here.
I'll have real friends
in 2278!
NORM:
Oh, yeah.
You and the other severed heads
can go bowling or something.
(laughter)
Hello, Woody!
Kelly!
Boy, I've missed
you, Kelly!
I've missed you,
too, Woody.
Ah.
I brought you
a present.
It's a real
French beret.
Tada!
Oh, wow!
It was between this one
and the one
with the arrow through it.
Oh, well, this
one's nice, too.
Surprise! I got them both!
Oh!
This is gonna be fun.
This is gonna be
just like old times.
I can't wait.
So what do you
feel like doing?
I don't know.
What do you feel like doing?
Gosh, this is just
like old times.
Listen, maybe Henri
will know what to do.
Who?
Henri, my new best friend
from Paris.
Woody, this is Henri.
Henri, this
is Woody.
Ah, Woody.
Yes, I've heard
so much about you. Yeah.
Give me 40 bucks,
please.
I have to pay
for the cab.
Thanks.
I'll be right back.
Kelly, that guy just
take me for 40 bucks,
kiss you twice
and leave?
Woody, you're so American!
Henri is my photography teacher.
He's the greatest.
He showed me
all of Paris,
taught me all
about French food,
taught me not to be ashamed
of my body, and he...
he lectured me
in history and art.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
C-Can we go back
to that body thing?
Henri took some
art photographs of me.
They were very tasteful.
Now, hold on.
You-You guys aren't...
Ugh! No, of
course not!
He's just here on vacation.
Sure, he's always joking
about how he's gonna
steal me away from you,
but he's only kidding.
Are you sure?
Henri, you're
gonna love this.
Woody thinks
you really are...
(snickering):
...trying to steal me
away from him.
Oh...!
(laughs)
Oh, that's so funny.
I am, you know.
Right out from
under your nose.
(Henri laughs)
See how he is, Woody?
He really cracks me up.
(laughing):
Yeah, that's a good one.
Now, I got one for you, Henri.
Get your hands off
my girlfriend.
Henri, if you'll
excuse us a moment.
Woody, I think you
were a little rude
to Henri just now.
Yeah, well, I think
Henri was a little rude, too.
He's supposed to be
rude; he's French.
I'm, uh, Sam Malone,
by the way.
Oh! I've heard
about you in France.
Oh, yeah.
You follow baseball?
No. Stewardesses.
Oh.
Uh, when I first came in,
I was afraid that
you were Woody, uh, but
then when I saw the real thing,
I was most relieved.
Why's that?
Heh. No competition.
I could steal Kelly
with both hands
tied behind my back.
Ooh!
Listen, Kelly's
Woody's girlfriend.
I'm sure you could have
any woman you wanted.
I know, but, uh, Kelly
is so innocent and naive.
I love to change that.
Boy, I'm kind
of torn here.
I mean, Woody's my
closest friend,
but that is a real
solid argument.
You know, Woody may surprise
you there, you know.
He's, uh... looks
like a pushover,
but he's got his
way with women.
Oh, no, I've been shot
through the head!
I've been shot
I'll take my chances.
(Henri and Kelly laughing)
Come on, Woody.
Woody, how about
this one?
Knock, knock.
Who's there?
Henri, the guy who's going
to steal your girlfriend.
KELLY:
Now, Henri,
this is getting
a little tiresome.
Oh?
I'm kidding.
It's really cute.
Oh. Woody, why don't you
get us some drinks?
Three sodas, Sam.
You know, Woody,
I... I'd watch out
for that guy,
if I were you.
Oh, I know he's annoying, Carla,
but Kelly swears that he's just
joking around to get my goat.
I don't think
he's joking around there, Woody.
Yeah, I don't
think so, either.
I mean, the French
aren't exactly known
for their
sense of humor.
What do you mean?
Well, let me put
it this way:
Their, uh, comic hero
is Jerry Lewis.
What's your point?
Yeah.
Oh, Henri,
that's impossible!
No one can do that!
No. It's true.
I'll show you.
What are you guys doing?
Henri says he can
teach me to tie a knot
in a cherry stem
with my tongue.
Here, uh, we'll
demonstrate.
I'll be the
cherry stem.
Hold it. Hold it.
That's it, frogman.
Get away
from my girlfriend!
I know what you're thinking.
You're thinking you're more
sophisticated than me,
and classier than me,
and smarter than me,
and that... and that you got
better hair than mine,
and that you're taller
than me,
and-and you got
that strong jaw line.
What was my point?
Oh, yeah--
you get out of here
before I kick your butt
back to the Eiffel Tower!
Very well.
But I do feel I
should be allowed
to say something
in my defense.
Go ahead.
I'm going to steal
your girlfriend.
I can't believe
Kelly would be so mad at me
just 'cause
I stood up to Henri.
It's like
she's starting
to like him
better than me.
Hey, Sam, you don't
think that...
maybe they've
been to...
To the back of the barn?
I was gonna say
to bed together.
What-What is the
back of the barn?
What does that mean?
That-That's-That's where
the compost heap is.
I can't think of any
place less romantic.
I don't think they've
slept together yet, Woody,
but I-I would be concerned
about Henri.
I mean, I know
guys like this.
I mean, I am
a guy like this.
Well, what can I do, Sam?
Well, how's-how's
your love life?
I mean, the physical part?
Well, I can't
speak for Kelly,
but I'm looking
forward to it.
You're-You're telling me
that-that you and Kelly
haven't slept together?
Well, uh, we-we did once,
when we went to
see Old Gringo,
but the whole
row was snoring.
Well, I... You know,
I think this may be
your problem here, Wood.
Well, I always figured
we'd wait until after
we were married.
That's-That's the
way everybody in
Hanover does it.
Except for that couple
that teaches art at
the high school.
I think waiting for marriage
is a wonderful idea.
REBECCA:
I wish I had.
I also wish that I had
studied harder in college
and maybe gone
for a different career.
Maybe engineering.
And, you know,
Boston was a bad move.
And then, I mean, of course,
you can't choose
your own parents.
But if I could have,
I would have chosen two
that were more supportive,
you know, like Brian Keith
and Maureen O'Hara
in The Parent Trap.
Woody, is this helping you?
Well, even if it isn't,
just thinking about
The Parent Trap
for a moment
made me feel good.
What do you think about
premarital sex, Mr. P?
Well, Wood, there's an
old saying, you know, uh...
"Why buy the cow when you can
get the milk for free?"
Then of course,
you, uh, you get married,
you wake up one day and realize:
"Oh, my God.
I've married a cow."
Thanks, Mr. P.
Hey, uh, Sam,
what if we do it
and it becomes
like a crutch,
and we rely on it for
the rest of our lives?
Well, then you know
you did it right.
But you better hurry
or Henri's gonna
beat you to it.
All right.
I'm gonna go
through with it.
All right!
WOODY:
Yeah, right.
But if it's gonna happen,
it's gotta be wonderful.
Where can we go?
We can't go to her place,
'cause her Dad's home.
Well, then why don't you
go to a motel?
This is all second nature
to you, isn't it, Sam?
Look at him.
Walking out of here a boy,
and he's gonna come back...
a happy boy.
Everyone!
This is Dr. Eugene
Eckworth,
a renowned scientist
and surgeon.
A man who not only
believes in cryogenics,
but has just performed
the procedure
you all scorned
so zestfully.
Yes, I'm in the process
of transferring
one of our thermostatic clients
to a storage facility.
My good friend, Frasier, asked
me to stop by for a drink.
You-You telling me you brought
a severed head into the bar?
Oh, man, we gotta have a policy
against that, don't we?
CLIFF:
Hey.
Don't worry, it's,
uh, it's frozen.
It's not like it's gonna
go bad or anything.
Hey, a game of pool, Gene?
You can leave the head there.
Oh, that's just fine.
Ooh, weird-looking box.
What's in there?
Um, I don't know.
Why don't you look?
Okay.
No! No-no, don't do that!
There's a frozen severed
head in that thing.
Oh, give me a break, Sam.
She's right.
There's no head in there.
Then why doesn't
somebody open it?
Yeah, you're kind of in charge
of all body parts around here,
aren't you, Sam?
All right, we'll--
I'll open it up
take a quick look, see that
there's no head in there
and then I'll just shut it
up again, all right?
Okay.
(chuckles):
This...
Well?
I can't see anything
in there.
MALE ELECTRONIC VOICE:
Help me.
(all screaming)
CLIFF:
Ha! Ha! Hey!
Hey! Well, look who's
laughing now, huh?
ELECTRONIC VOICE:
Help me... Help me...
(switch clicks)
Ha! You guys were running away
from a tape recorder!
Cliff, I must admit
that was funny.
Thanks a lot, Gene.
No problem, Fras.
FRASIER (laughing):
Take care.
Hey, Doc, that was great.
Congratulations.
We make a good team,
you and me.
Ah, we showed them.
Hey, how would you like
to play a trick like that
on somebody else
tomorrow, huh?
Wouldn't that be great?
Lot of people I'd like
to get even with.
Guys down at the post office.
All the people in
my apartment complex.
Ma! Ooh, I'd love to nail her!
Help me!
Well, here's your room,
Mr. and Mrs. Malone.
Well, thank you.
The wife and I really enjoy
getting away from the kids
for a relaxing evening.
By the way, honey, shouldn't
we call the babysitter
and tell her there's
some chicken in the fridge?
The little woman
is a great cook.
Almost makes putting up
with the mother-in-law
worthwhile.
You two aren't married, are you?
No.
(flatly):
Gee, you really had me going
there for a while.
(door closes)
Well, this is it.
Just you and me alone together.
So, uh, what should we do first?
We could kiss.
Yeah, we've done that
lots of times.
Yeah.
Boy, I've never felt
this self-conscious
about kissing you.
My lips feel huge.
Well, they've always been full.
Really?
They feel like two
big pieces of liver
slapping together.
Oh, no, I can hardly talk.
Woody, I think we're both
a little bit nervous,
so why don't we
lie down and relax.
Okay?
(sighs)
Oh! Hey, this is one
of those vibrating beds.
I always wanted to try this.
(coin clinks)
Oh, darn, I dropped the quarter.
I have another quarter.
No, no, I'll get it.
(coin clatters into box)
(electric motor
rattles and whirrs)
(loudly):
I'll turn it off!
Boy, I don't know
why people like this thing.
Let me kiss
your head, Woody.
Does that feel better?
Yeah, that feels a lot better.
(knocking)
Oh, no.
It's the manager.
He figured out
we're not married.
But, Woody, you told him
Then I guess it was easy
for him to piece together.
(knocking)
CARLA:
Woody, open the door!
Carla, what are
you doing here?
Oh, good,
you're still dressed.
Thank God I'm not too late.
I knew I would
find you guys here.
I gotta talk to you guys
before you make
what could be the worst mistake
of your lives.
What's she talking
about, Woody?
I'm talking about
you two getting together
in this motel room
for all the wrong reasons.
She's talking about
the two of us getting together
in this motel room
for all the wrong reasons.
Kids...
...making love...
is a very special thing
between two people.
You don't want
to throw that away
just so you can beat
some Frenchman to the punch.
Believe me.
I came to this motel
when I was 16 years old.
You know what happened?
I got knocked up.
And, uh, here I am,
eight kids later,
trying to talk you kids
out of making the same mistake.
Carla's right.
When it happens,
it has to be special.
It has to be the most
meaningful thing
in the whole world.
You know, if...
if it were up to me,
I... I think
we should wait.
You mean until
we're married?
No, until I can
afford a nice room
at the Four Seasons,
instead of some
cheap motel.
No offense, Carla.
I know this place has
sentimental meaning to you.
Let's go.
Boy, I'm glad I could
help you guys.
Yeah, I don't know
how to thank you, Carla.
Yeah, that's okay.
See, I told you
I could get us a vacancy.
Come on, Frenchie.
Here's your big chance.
Steal me away from Woody.
Hey, Doc.
Where is everybody?
Have you seen Norm?
Well, Cliff,
Norm was pretty upset
about our little severed head
gag this afternoon.
He's been moping
in the pool room all day.
I... I don't know.
Really? Gee, uh, it
was meant to be a joke.
Hey, Norm!
Come on out here, will you?
I didn't mean to scare you.
No, let me, let me
go see if he's okay.
Oh, my God!
Cliffie!
(screaming)
(screaming continues)
(both guffawing)
Very funny, Fras.
Hey, I go where
the thrills are.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ae7w
Help other users to choose the best subtitles