Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Not again.
Every day this week!
If I find out who
this N.R.P. creep is,
I'm really gonna
let him have it.
Hurry up, Norm.
Sammy's getting
a lot faster at this.
Got it.
Hey, Norm.
Listen, I uh...
I know the N.P.
Stands for Norm Peterson.
What's the "R" stand for?
Resourceful.
(theme song begins)
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Mail-gram for you, Fras.
CLIFF:
Well, I'll be darned.
Yeah, what's that?
Well, it says here if you walk
with a quarter wedged
between your knees
your, your posture
will be a lot better.
Hey, give me a couple of bits
here, Norm, I want to try it.
Tell you what, Cliff...
here's a buck
to not try it, okay?
Fair enough.
(groans)
What's the matter?
It's from Lilith.
Oh, that's awful.
What? What's awful?
"Dear Frasier, life in
the Eco-pod is wonderful.
"Googie and I are happier
"than we've ever been.
"Please start divorce
proceedings.
Our marriage is..."
Made in heaven?
"Our marriage
is over."
That burns my hide- Lilith
sending that Mail-gram.
Well, thank you, Cliff.
Well, all of a sudden
a first class stamp isn't any good anymore?
I mean, people,
I've been telling you,
I mean, our success rate
is almost 50%!
Well, you know,
unless it's raining,
'cause then the tires...
I'm sorry to hear that.
Sorry.
Oh, thank you, Sam.
Divorce, Lilith
wants a divorce.
You know, I, I know
we've been separated
and I've been saying
some pretty bitter things,
but... I guess deep down
in my heart of hearts,
I'd always hoped for some
sort of a reconciliation.
Now I just don't
know how to feel.
Hey, you know, Fras,
I went through this same
thing when Nick left me.
And the way I look at it,
here's what you can do.
You can get angry and bitter,
learn to hate the world,
snap at people.
Or?
Or what?
You want to talk about it, make
yourself feel a little better?
Oh, I appreciate what
you're trying to do, Sam,
but, uh, I think I'd just, uh,
rather be alone right now.
Try to figure out how
I'm gonna carry on now that,
I know that Lilith
is never coming back.
Boy, oh boy.
That must be rough, huh?
I've never been married,
but, uh, I remember
how depressed I was when Ma left me.
You referring to the time your
mother moved to Florida
when you were 37 years old?
It still hurt.
Poor Fras.
Boy, I'm never seen him so sad.
And it's too bad.
You know, he's always
there for us.
He's always helping us out.
What can we do to cheer him up?
I don't know.
Oh, I've got it.
Oh! We'll throw
him a party.
What?
A divorce party.
You know, then that way he'll
know that all his friends
support him and, and maybe it'll
brighten his day a little bit.
We'll, we'll have it
for him tomorrow when he usually comes in.
I don't know, you know,
a party for a guy
whose wife just left him...
uh... it seems
kind of strange.
Makes perfect sense to me.
Look out, everybody,
here he comes.
Okay, what do we yell
when he comes in?
Just yell, "Surprise!"
Surprise, surprise, surprise...
okay, I think I've got it.
ALL:
Surprise!
♪ For he's a jolly
good fellow ♪
♪ For he's
a jolly good fellow ♪
♪ For he's a jolly good
fellow... ♪
♪ Which nobody can deny. ♪
(cheering)
Is this for me?
Yes, I thought it would help
you get over Lilith.
Do you like it?
Oh, very much. Thank you.
Well, it was my idea.
The guys fought me
at every turn.
Okay, everybody,
let's lift our glasses here
and toast Frasier's
new-found freedom!
Yeah!
Woody, you having a beer?
Why not?
I'm a grown man, I'm an adult.
I can handle my alcohol.
Plus we're out
of chocolate milk.
(glass clinking)
I want to make the
first toast to Frasier.
Lilith stinks!
ALL:
Profoundly put.
But I really don't want
this to degenerate
into a "bash Lilith" party, so,
look, what's done is done.
It's about time I got over it.
Oh, well, then you're
not going to like
what we did to the dart board.
Dah!
Well, maybe just one throw.
(cheering)
Nice shot!
All right, Frasier!
Well, I've got one at home.
Oh, dear, dear, dear.
Woody, uh, exactly
how many beers
have you had there,
young fellow?
Just one... Mom.
Wood, you got to be
careful there, buddy.
You never know how liquor's
going to affect you, you know?
Sometimes you
can get depressed.
Sometimes you get giddy.
So, Norm, when're you gonna get
off your butt and get a job?
Sometimes you just
get brutally honest.
Frasier, you know
how I feel about you.
But I'm not
any good with words,
so I'm gonna let this
do the talking for me.
(tawdry trumpet riff)
(strip tease music playing)
(patrons hooting and hollering)
Oh, Lordy, look at that!
Yeah!
Cake!
All right, huh? The world
of the exotic dancer.
A little sleazy if you ask me.
Almost as sleazy as the types
who frequent those joints.
Oh, hey! It's Cliff!
Hey, uh, I must
look like a Cliff.
Uh, excuse me, miss,
could you move the veil,
you're blocking
the mocha creme, here.
You're kidding, right?
No, you see, uh, sweetheart,
over the years
our priorities change.
Yeah? How so?
Hey there, Miss Krapence.
That's Mr. Krapence.
That's not what I heard.
Say, Woody, why
don't you sit down
right here for a
while, all right?
What's with this
"Miss Krapence" stuff?
I mean, who's been
making cracks?
I've got an ex-wife,
you know.
Whoa, what-what-what
are you doin' man?
Why, why, why are you taking
shots at, at Paul, huh?
Well, come on, Sam,
use your head.
The guy's in his 40s,
he's not married.
He's always braggin'
about his sex life
and yet he's always here.
It all adds up, Sam.
Or should I say, Samantha?
Would you guys do
something with him?
Look at that, Norm.
He's fast asleep.
Hmm?
Oop!
Oop! Look at this legs-
they're twitching.
I bet you he's dreaming
he's chasing rabbits.
Don't be ridiculous, Cliff.
Only dogs dream about
chasing rabbits.
(barking)
Frasier, are you
enjoying your party?
Yes, I am, very much.
Uh, friends,
uh, I just wanted
to say thanks.
Really, thank you very much.
Aw.
Okay.
It's just terrific you
guys tried to cheer me up
and, uh, I just think it's time
I was shoving off now, okay?
Frasier, you're going home?
Well, yes, and, uh,
thank you again, Rebecca,
for putting all this together.
Frasier, are you going
to be all right?
I, I just get a little emotional
when I, when I drink too much.
(laughing):
Look at me.
Fras, you know what?
I think I'm gonna
drive you home.
Oh, I would really
appreciate that, Rebecca.
I sent Frederick
to his grandmother's,
and I just don't want to go
home to that house alone.
Frasier for what it's worth,
I think that Lilith
made a big mistake. Well, thank you.
And for what it's worth,
I think that Evan Drake
made a big mistake, too.
Thank you, Frasier.
And, well, uh,
while we're at it,
so did Sam, and, uh,
Martin Teal,
and Robin Colcord and that...
that cousin of Woody's
that used to play the piano,
and Mark Newberger.
And those are just
the ones you know about.
Ah.
I hope you didn't mind my
pouring my guts out to you.
I didn't mind a bit.
I was glad to help.
So I'll see you
tomorrow at work?
Uh, Rebecca, why don't
you come on in for a bit?
I'll make some coffee.
Sure. Okay.
Great.
All I've got's instant.
Oh, instant's fine.
You know, come
to think of it, Fras,
you have a really hard job.
You listen to other people tell
you their problems all day long
and you never really have a
chance to talk about yourself.
You're a very sympathetic
person, Rebecca.
Thanks again.
Frasier, would you
quit thanking me?
That's what friends do,
they help each other.
You really are
my friend, aren't you?
Well, of course I am.
Fras, I think I better go.
Oh, oh, God.
Rebecca,
I'm-I'm so sorry.
Uh, this... this is
entirely unintentional.
I-It wasn't premeditated
or anything.
I, uh, oh, God, uh...
Frasier, I understand what
you're trying to say.
Let's just forget
it ever happened, okay?
Rebecca, wait, wait.
I've always found you,
you know, rather attractive.
Well, very attractive really.
Well, thank you very much.
That's sweet of you to say,
but I really think
I'd better be go...
It's just that seeing you
now in my home,
looking into
your beautiful eyes,
I just wanted to,
I had to...
Oh, God, what am I doing?!
This is not romantic,
this is just weird!
Frasier, y-you're my friend!
I've known you for years!
First Sam, now you.
Who's next- Cliff?
Oh, God!
Oh, Rebecca, you, you have
to admit,
there's always been some
sexual tension between us.
There has?
Yes. It started the first day
you came into the bar.
I heard your sexy, smoky voice.
I, I looked up and I thought,
"My God!
Who is that woman?"
Really?!
Really.
Your turn.
What did you think
when you saw me?
I thought...
Well, you know, Fras, I met
so many people that day.
Well, I mean, through the years
you must have at least found me
a, a little attractive.
Well, I, uh...
Oh, come on!
I mean, surely
for as long as we've known each other,
there has to be some
sexual tension!
Why?!
Well it's been proven
in scientific journals!
People who spend any amount
of time with each other
do experience some sort of
subconscious sexual attraction!
Are you sure?
Do you want me
to get the book?!
No, no, no, Frasier,
Frasier, Frasier,
Frasier, forget the book!
Frasier,
listen to me. I...
You are a very attractive man.
And you're funny, you're witty,
and you're very charming.
And one time,
you came in the bar
and you had on these pants,
and they made your buns
look really cute.
What colour were they?
I could go put them on.
No, Fras...
Fras, you don't need to put
those pants on.
My, my point here is that, for
all the years I've known you,
you have been married.
So, uh, I just, I never
really took notice.
Well, I'm not married now.
No, you're not.
Yeah, he's still out cold,
Normie.
Mm.
Think we ought to wake him?
Well, we could.
You know, we could take him
over to his house
and, uh, get him undressed,
put him in bed,
let him sleep it off
in peace and quiet.
Yeah, we could do that.
But we're not going to, are we?
No, sir, my good friend,
we are not.
What we are going
to do, though,
is, uh, get a pan
of warm water,
put his hand in it,
and, uh, step back
and watch the hilarity ensue.
Guys, am I the only one here
who's concerned about Frasier?
I think so.
You know, this could be
a depressing night for him,
you know?
We're his friends,
and here we are
just playing stupid camp games
with Woody.
Wait a minute.
The hand in the pan of warm
water a stupid camp game?
I don't even know who you are,
Sam Malone.
I'm serious.
Remember the last time
he got this upset?
He ended up on a ledge.
Yeah, you're right about that.
All I'm saying is maybe he
shouldn't be alone.
Yeah, yeah, maybe
we ought to go over there with
some chips and a pizza.
Thank you.
Yeah. I'll get some videos
or something, right?
Well, yeah, it feels good
to do something nice
for somebody sometimes, yeah?
Yeah.
This is Cheers, right?
We, we stick with each other.
NORM:
That's right. We take care of our own.
Hey, guys,
you'd better take an umbrella.
It's starting to mist.
Mist?
Oh, man, that, uh,
that really messes up my hair.
It's not gonna help the tickle
in the back
of my throat either.
And this, uh, sweater
is sure to pill.
Well, now what are we gonna do?
I'll get the pan.
You heat up the water.
Now, Rebecca, you're,
you're sure you're okay with this?
Because I wouldn't want
to do anything
to compromise our friendship,
and I know you're in a very
delicate state right now.
You ready to hit the sack?
Right upstairs.
You get some champagne
and I'll go upstairs
and get ready.
Right. Okay.
Take your time.
This is not a drill.
This is not a drill!
(humming)
(doorbell rings)
Damn!
Hey!
There you are!
(laughs) I didn't want you
to be alone and depressed
on a night like this.
So what I did was
I brought over
some Three Stooges
tapes we can watch.
Whoo! Gloomy in here.
There you go!
Listen, Sam, uh...
Yeah, I know, I know, I know.
My hair's all frizzy.
But what the heck?
You're worth it, buddy.
Sam...
You know, I was thinking
about not coming here.
Then I thought about how,
you know,
how you'd feel to see
a friendly face around,
so here I am.
(both chuckle)
Sam, uh...
Yeah?
I, I appreciate all
this, but, you know,
that you're here in
my hour of need and all,
and I just want to tell you
I think I'm okay with it now.
I think I'm just
gonna head upstairs
and you know... (yawns)
put my head down, you know?
I, I...
Hi, Fras.
Carla!
Hey!
Oh, Fras, sorry about your wife,
blah, blah, blah.
Well, brought some pizza.
I'm just gonna dig right in.
Give me a piece, there,
will you?
Uh, Sam, this is such
a wonderful gesture.
It shows a sensitivity that I...
(Sam and Carla laugh)
Geez, doesn't that
hurt Curly's nose?
Well, of course it does.
That's what makes it funny.
(laughs)
Nyuk-nyuk-nyuk-nyuk.
Woo-oo-oo-oo!
You got anything
to wash this down with?
Yeah. How about
some napkins?
Um, sure.
I'll, I'll get some.
They're, they're upstairs.
That's where we keep them.
I'll be, I'll be back in, oh,
15 minutes or so.
(doorbell rings)
Are you guys expecting anyone?
Uh, yeah, Norm and Cliff.
Aha! Tell him what
he's won, Bob!
Whoa! Pizza!
Beer.
Norm, Norm brought beer! Well.
No, no, no, I need a beer.
I'm a little thirsty.
Sure.
I'll, uh, I'll get you one.
It's, uh, it's upstairs.
You keep your beer upstairs?
Uh, yeah, in the bedroom.
You, too?
(doorbell rings)
Paul! (chuckles)
Are you, uh, alone or did you
bring some friends, Paul?
What's that supposed to mean?
Well...
Nothing.
Come on in.
Thanks for cheering me up.
I didn't come here
to cheer you up.
I, I came to say something.
Everybody, there's, there's
something I've got to say.
Uh, Woody made some comments
earlier,
and at first I was angry,
but then I got to thinking.
I took a long hard
look at myself.
I'm 45 years old, my mother's
dead, what am I waiting for?
I, I guess what I'm trying
to say is "World..."
Hey, Paul,
this is Frasier's night.
Do you mind?
You're right, Sammy.
I'm sorry.
Is there any pizza left?
I don't think so, Paul.
Just, uh, make yourself
at home, Paul.
Say, my God, is it
still raining outside?
You know, I'm, I'm gonna
go upstairs
and close those windows.
Okay? I'll probably be
a little while.
Oh, no, no!
Hold on!
Whoa, no, you don't, buddy.
You're not gonna go up there and
brood and be all alone by yourself.
No way. No way.
We're here to make sure
that you enjoy yourself.
Well, then let me
go upstairs and close the windows!
I beg of you!
It's been a long time
since I've closed the windows!
They're wide open!
Don't you be silly, you big lug.
Hey, look what we did here.
We made a little space
for you on the sofa.
Yeah, you can be the meat
in our best friend sandwich.
Hey, Fras, we got six hours
of The Stooges for you, man.
Nyuk-nyuk-nyuk.
Oh, God, look at that, fellows.
You big lug,
you got a tear in your eye.
FRASIER:
Okay, guys...
SAM:
Take care, buddy.
Thanks again.
Good night.
CLIFF:
Nyuk-nyuk-nyuk.
Yes, yes,
nyuk-nyuk-nyuk.
SAM:
We'll watch these again some other time.
Okay, bye-bye.
(door shuts)
(quick footsteps on stairs)
Oh, Frasier, I'm sorry.
I must have fallen asleep.
What time is it?
Well, it's pretty late.
Uh, I guess I'll go
downstairs and, uh, sleep on the couch.
Maybe I should just go.
No, no, you don't
have to go home.
You don't have
to sleep on the couch.
Just a second.
(door opens, shuts)
Frasier, what was that?
What was what?
I thought I heard a door slam.
You don't think those guys
are back, do you?
No, no impossible.
I locked and dead bolted it.
They'd need a key to get in.
Now where were we?
Let's make this a night
we'll never forget.
(door opens)
Frasier?
Lilith!
Rebecca?!
Lilith.
Am I the only one
who feels awkward here?