Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
( low, indistinct chatter )
( sighs )
Oh, Fras.
You make it
home okay last night, buddy?
Yeah, thanks for putting me
in that cab.
I figured
you had a little too much
when you started making fun
of that longshoreman's mother.
Oh, Lord,
I don't remember a thing.
What-what did I say?
Something like, uh,
"Unions are for mommy's boys
who can't get their own jobs,"
I think.
Oh, why didn't he kill me?
Well, you-you said
you wanted to wait and
take him on when
there were more people here.
So, uh,
you said you'd meet the guy
back here today,
about, uh, right about
now, actually.
No, wait. Whoa, whoa.
The guy couldn't make it!
Whoop, there he is.
Oh, oh!
No, no, no, no, no.
That's just a car.
Okay, why are you taunting me
like some sort of play thing?
It's just my little
hangover cure.
( sighs ):
Didn't help me a bit.
No, but mine's
gone completely.
( piano plays )
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always glad
you came
You want to be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You want to be where everybody
knows your name
You want to go
where people know
People are all the same
You want to go where
everybody knows your name.
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
How you doing, Woody?
Fine.
Is that a new shirt?
You mean the one I'm wearing?
Yes.
You look very nice today.
Very... cute.
Really?
You...
You mean it?
Me? I mean,
me-- you think me look cute?
Well, I did.
Hey, fella.
( laughs )
You a little sweet
on Rebecca there, huh?
Nah, get out.
No, come on.
You've got that
kind of dopey look.
Hey, get over here.
You can tell us, come on.
Well...
okay.
Uh, last couple of months,
I have kind of noticed her.
( laughs )
In fact, if it weren't
for Mr. Drake,
I really might go after her.
( laughter )
Come on, Woody.
CLIFF:
Hey, hey, that's
good, Woody, good.
What's so funny?
No disrespect,
Rhinestone Cowpie.
But I really don't think
her idea of a hot date
is a butter-churning contest
in Tobacci-flats.
Hey, you're forgetting
something.
Miss Howe said I was cute.
Yeah, but, Woody, I think
she thinks you're cute,
kind of like
she thinks a puppy dog is cute.
Yeah, I know.
Hey, is that a cut?
( patrons barking )
Oh, so you guys
really don't think
she'd go for me, huh?
I may just have to show you.
You couldn't get
to first base.
First base, nothing.
I can hit a home run with her.
( all voicing dissent )
Oh, come on.
Aah!
You can't hit a home run.
WOODY:
Can so.
In fact, by midnight tonight,
I can get a kiss.
A kiss, huh?
That-that what you meant
by home run?
Yeah, sure.
What else could it be?
I thought you meant
go all the way.
You mean marry her?
Sam, where
is your mind?
NORM:
All right.
Wait a minute now.
I got ten bucks says
Woody can
get that kiss.
CLIFF:
Come on.
Will you stop it, Norm?
I mean, Woody's got
about as much chance
of getting a kiss out of Rebecca
as Sammy here.
Yeah.
Hey, whoa, wait, listen,
sure, Woody can't do it,
but you think
I can't come through?
You know, rumor has it, Sam,
that, uh, the woman finds you
utterly repulsive.
Rumor? Heck, it's
in the newsletter.
Hey, would you guys give me
a break?
You're talking to Sammy here.
I am the king.
Well, when was the last time
that Rebecca said you were cute?
Yeah.
NORM:
Yeah, yeah, Sam.
Might be time
to hang up those
lips, buddy.
Hey, no, no, no.
Hey, listen,
I still got it.
And if you need proof,
then fine.
I will get that kiss from her,
and before Woody, too.
MAN:
Oh!
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Well, there's
an expression
we used to have
back in Indiana.
Yeah?
Same to you.
MAN:
All right,
all right.
I got ten bucks on Woody, huh?
( indistinct excited chatter )
Me, too.
I'll put, uh, 20 bucks down
on the kid.
You're putting 20 on Woody?
Uh, you're right,
Sammy, make that 50.
Come on,
you're putting me on here.
NORM:
No,
Sammy. I mean,
look at that face.
Okay? That sweet,
innocent face.
The kind of face we
all hate and resent,
but we will
cash in on it.
Okay, all right.
You know, I'm going
to teach you doubters a lesson.
I'm gonna take all bets.
Okay, let's set
the ground rules here.
( indistinct excited chatter )
MAN:
All right,
wait a second.
A kiss before midnight
tonight.
It's got to be a full one
on the lips,
all four lips touching.
For an entire...
three count.
Wait, wait,
wait, but, uh,
there's got
to be a bona
fide witness.
No, I'll do it, I'll do it.
You know, I think
this is gonna be better
than our contest
for the biggest spit bubble.
CLIFF:
Hey, well,
it's possible.
Explain this to me.
If, uh, the winner is gonna
get a kiss from Rebecca,
what does the loser get?
Well, uh...
a kiss from Norm.
( chuckling )
Then, of course,
there is no loser.
CLIFF ( laughing ):
All right, Normie.
( laughter )
So, when are we gonna
see some action?
Oh, what are you
worried about?
I got all day here.
I'll see you guys.
Oh, Sammy.
Anyway, I got
this sewn up.
I don't know, Sammy.
I'm on your side,
but you know, a lot
of women come into this bar
wanting to meet
the sexy bartender,
and more and more of them
are not talking about you.
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Listen, you're not
losing faith in
me here, are you?
I mean, you-you
still think
I-I got it, don't you?
Sure I do,
but you know,
you can't take this thing
for granted.
Get a little older,
you got to work harder,
or date uglier.
Well, you know,
come to think of it,
Woody is kind of
cute, isn't he?
Mm.
Oh, this is
not good.
( clears throat ):
This is not good
for my image at all.
I mean, if I let
Woody win here,
then every young punk
with a pair of lips is
gonna be challenging me.
All right, I got a way
to go here.
Watch this.
Hey, hey, these
go to table six.
And you owe 'em
some change.
Hey, boss.
What, are you
doing inventory?
That's right.
Boy, you know, it
is getting warmer.
Maybe we ought to
be ordering some
more rum and...
( choking )
Sam?
Oh, my God,
are you all right?
No. Not that.
Mouth-to-mouth.
Are you sure?
All right.
Oh, God, does anybody know
mouth-to-mouth?
I do, I do, I do.
( coughs )
It's okay, I'm all right,
I'm all right.
Works every time.
Low, Sammy, real low.
Not worthy of the king.
Entering Nick
Tortelli country.
Hey...
King Woody.
It does have
a ring to it.
Yeah. Yeah, I'll be right...
Yeah, say it Sam,
see what you think.
King Woody.
Your Grace.
Hey, hey.
Afternoon, Woody.
Oh, yeah, hi.
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah, sure. Great.
Oh, you wouldn't want
to know anyway.
Well, of course I would.
Really?
Very much.
You sure?
Yes.
Honestly?
When was the
last time
someone actually
struck you?
Well, see, I'm, uh, trying out
for this part in a play.
It's a really important part,
and it's a really
well-known play. Uh,
Bus Station.
You mean Bus Stop?
I'll never get it.
( snickers )
This is great.
He's gonna be
so worried about
his dumb play,
he's probably
gonna forget all
about the bet.
At least his memory loss
isn't from senility.
Gee, I'm so glad you're
on my side, Carla.
See, the thing is,
the audition's tomorrow,
and I don't have
a chance to work
with any of the other actors
to prepare my part.
Actors have to do that,
you know.
Say, Miss Howe,
do you think maybe
you could read with me?
Oh, gee, Woody,
I'm sorry.
I-I'm really busy
with this inventory.
Oh, yeah, sure,
I understand.
I'll just lose the part.
All right, Woody.
But you have
to promise to
make it quick.
Thanks, Miss Howe.
Hey, I hope you don't mind,
it's a love scene.
Did you hear that?
Love scene.
( laughing )
( clink )
Ow!
Love scene!
Sometimes
the little hamster
falls asleep in the wheel.
Okay, if you could
just sit here.
All right, Woody,
but I'm expecting
a beer distributor
in five minutes.
No problem.
Sell it, make me
believe it.
Carla?
Well, it
really helps
when you have
an audience.
Is there gonna be any nudity?
Not unless you're planning
something repugnant.
All right, so
what are we doing here?
Okay. The scene
is between
a wayward, young,
rodeo buff, Bo--
that'd be me-- and, uh,
the sexy showgirl,
Cherie.
That's you, I guess.
Okay, uh...
So where do we start?
Uh, right here before
it says, "They kiss."
Oh, oh, golly.
When you kiss
someone for serious,
it's kind of
scary, ain't it?
Yeah, it is.
Now I'm supposed
to kiss you.
Sorry, I, uh,
hope I'm not interrupting
anything here.
What is it, Sam?
Uh... we're out of vermouth.
So order more.
Uh, is that okay?
Yes, if we're out of it.
We are.
Then order more.
Vermouth?
Yeah! Sam, would you
excuse us, please?
( crowd chatter )
Okay, where
were we? Uh...
Wait. ( clears throat )
Oh, oh, golly.
When you kiss
someone for serious,
it's kind of
scary, ain't it?
Yeah, it is.
( door opening )
Sorry, I, uh...
I wouldn't interrupt
like this
except it's important.
What is it, Sam?
I ordered the vermouth.
WOODY:
Sam,
would you get
out of here?
We're right in the
middle of a scene.
Oh, a play!
Oh, I love good dramatic stuff.
What is this, uh,
Tennessee Ernie Ford?
Sam, get out.
Come on.
All right,
all right, all right.
Play fair.
All right, all right.
Play fair?
That's my opinion
of the play so far,
but with enough
rehearsal,
it might play great.
Okay, let's pick it up.
All right.
( clears throat )
Oh. Oh, golly.
When you kiss someone
for serious, it's kind
of scary, ain't it?
Yeah, it is.
Wait a minute.
I just ordered two cases
of vermouth yesterday!
Sam's crazy.
( crickets chirping )
Better make that
move, Sammy.
Time's getting short.
No, this is
how I like it.
Late innings,
game on the line.
Yeah.
The cool character
steps to center stage.
Well, I don't
know, Sammy.
You seem to be sweating
a little bit up there.
No, I'm not.
Yeah, that's okay.
Nothing wrong
with sweating.
I, myself, have
perspired
once or twice.
We could grow rice.
Oh, watch this.
Say, Rebecca.
Oh, excuse me for a minute.
Caroline, are you all right?
You look kind
of depressed.
( sighs ):
Oh, Sam, it's
the same old thing.
What?
I'm so in love
with my boss, and I
just can't get
him to notice me.
Well, have you tried
kissing him like this?
Oh, my God.
That was...
Oh, thank heaven
you showed it to me.
There's no way anyone could
possibly describe it.
If I kiss him like that,
he's bound to fall
in love with me.
Bye, Sam.
Bye-bye.
You two have a
great honeymoon.
Thank you so much.
Anything to get
my disc player back.
Hey, hey, hey...
By the way, Rebecca,
how are things between
you and your boss?
Anything, uh, I can do?
These lips remind
you of anything?
Yeah, I think the liver
in my freezer's gone bad.
What happened?
She couldn't possibly
have seen through
your little morality play.
Huh!
Oh... hey!
What's going on here?
Whatever do
you mean?
Sam and Woody are trying
desperately to kiss me.
Boy, someone's a little full
of herself, isn't she?
Come on, Carla.
What's the story here?
One woman to another.
Why would I tell
you something
about my two closest best
friends in the whole world?
I'll give you
a paid day off.
They got a bet.
They want to see who
could kiss you
by the end of
the shift tonight.
Why would they do such an
asinine, juvenile, thing?
Look at the contestants.
Actually,
Woody's doing it 'cause
they were razzing him.
Sam's trying to prove
he still got it.
Other than that,
just cheap thrills.
Don't tell them I know.
Wait a minute.
You're not
cooking up something
that's going
to humiliate my friends
and make them
look stupid, are you?
Well, yeah.
How can I help?
Oh, Miss Howe?
Can I ask you a question?
Sure, Woody.
What do you want to know?
Um... which key unlocks
the storage room?
I don't know.
Hold it still.
Look carefully,
very carefully.
You're getting sleepy.
Very sleepy.
Woody?
Very, very, sleepy.
You'll do
whatever I say.
Woody, go to sleep.
( snaps fingers )
Oh, no. I made
her disappear.
To recap,
sitting in the bar today,
we have, among others,
a man who was actually simple
enough to hypnotize himself.
I'd like to offer the suggestion
that we've seen it all.
Ten hut!
Happily, I stand corrected.
Well, it's time for me
to be all that I can be.
You enlisted in
the Army, you idiot?
Hey, we do more by 9:00 a.m.
than most people do all day.
And that's a
selling point to you?
Yeah, and I've had a bellyful
of that Ayatolah guy.
Quite frankly...
I don't like what's been
happening in the Persian Gulf.
So, I'm off to, uh...
I'm off to Persia.
I just wanted to shake
a few hands, say good-bye.
Kiss a few girls
for the last time.
Well, baby...
this is good-bye.
Yep, this may be
the last time
you ever see this dogface.
You can always take
a gander at this one.
Sam, I had no idea you
were this dedicated.
This is a wonderful
thing you're doing
for our country.
Well, thank you.
Kiss me, Sam, kiss me.
No, I can't kiss
another soldier.
Not after Kevin.
Kevin? Who-who's Kevin?
Kevin was my boyfriend
in high school,
and we really loved
each other,
and then
he enlisted in the Army,
and I never wrote,
and I never saw him again.
Well, he sounds like a creep.
Kiss me and make him jealous.
No, Sam, I'm sorry.
Come home safely, doughboy.
Damn!
I mean, what does it take?!
Well, maybe
you're being too subtle.
One hour.
I don't think
either of you heartthrobs
got the lips to win.
Serves you right
if you lose, Sam,
doing all
that weird stuff.
Me? What about you?
You-you and that
acting routine.
You know
something, Woody,
I'm getting a little
sick and tired of you.
You and your wholesome
farm boy bit.
You're not so dumb.
I resent that.
You're just upset
because you're not
king of the hill.
Well, that's too bad.
And I'll tell you
another thing.
I'm thinking about
not writing you
when you're overseas.
Oh, break my heart.
Sam?
Can I speak with you a moment?
You sure can.
( chuckling )
GUYS:
Over there
Send the word,
send the word
Over there...
Yeah?
Sam, I know what you
and Woody are up to.
I-I don't know
what you're
talking about.
I want you to win.
What?
All right!
( laughing )
And they said that
I was losing it.
Okay, so, uh, let's
get on with the
dirty deed here.
No, no, no,
we have to make this
look really natural.
Otherwise they'll think
the kiss is a setup.
Kiss, oh,
sweetheart, no, no.
Someone mislead you there.
Uh, we're supposed
to sleep together.
You're trying my patience.
All right, all right;
a kiss, a kiss, okay.
Uh... so, uh, how do
you want to do this?
All right,
here's the plan.
You go home and change.
and I'll tell the others
I'm really beat
and I have to go in
and take a nap in my office.
And you come back
and wake me,
and I'll act like I'm having
this really erotic dream,
and give you this long,
passionate kiss.
Oh, God, I love this.
I love this. Oh...!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
wait a minute. Uh...
Carla's supposed
to witness this.
Okay, bring her along.
Oh, and then I'll spit
and rinse my mouth out
to make it look
really legit.
Nice touch, nice touch.
Yeah, so long there.
Oh, wait a minute.
What do you got
on your lips there?
Oh, no one.
( laughing )
Can I talk to
you a minute?
Listen, I know
what you and Sam are up to,
and I want you to win.
Hey, Cliffie.
Hi, Sam.
Where is everybody?
Oh, most have gone home.
Carla's in the back.
Rebecca's asleep
in her office.
Rebecca's asleep?
Yeah. She said
she was up
late last night
doing the books,
or something.
Mm.
Oh, yeah, she said
she wanted me
to wake her up
right about now.
Better go do that.
Oh, no, no,
that's, that's uh, my job.
Oh.
Want to help me here, Carla?
( chuckling )
( clothes rustling )
( kissing noises )
SAM:
Mmm.
WOODY:
"Mmm"?
"Mmm?
SAM:
Mmm?!
WOODY:
Oh!
( laughter )
Sammy and Woody
sittin' in a tree
K-I-S-S-I-N-G...
( laughter continues )
You were supposed
to be Miss Howe.
That's a rotten thing you did.
Don't talk to me about rotten.
What about
all this kissing nonsense?
Yeah, that's different.
There's money involved.
Well, I am going to say this
once and once only.
I am a person
who cannot be used.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I've got to drive Mr. Drake's
valet to the airport.
( laughing and clamoring )
Call me a romantic,
but I always knew you two
would end up together.
( laughing )
I can't believe
I kissed you.
Yeah, well, you're lucky
I didn't punch
your lights out, man.
Yeah? You and what army?
Hey, hey, hey, guys.
Come on, now.
Relax.
Geez, you guys,
you were tricked.
It's no big deal.
I mean,
you're such good friends.
You mean a lot
to each other.
I mean,
don't walk away mad.
Go on,
kiss and make up.
Remember,
you both owe me a big wet one.
Ah...
Ah, I couldn't stay mad
at you, Sam.
You're just like
a brother to me.
Yeah, and if anyone ever does
knock off the king around here,
I guess I hope
it's you, man.
No hard feelings?
No hard feelings.
Listen, Sam,
now that everything's okay,
can I ask you something,
guy to guy?
Yeah, sure.
How was I?
Don't-don't do that.
No, I mean it's a question
you can't ask a girl.
I mean, is there anything
I need to work on?
No, see, I-I don't want
to talk about this, Woody.
I was nervous, so I might
have been a little dry.
Oh, for God's...! Yech!
No, I'm serious, Sam.
Hey, do you want to know
how you were?
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.OpenSubtitles.org