Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
WOMAN ( on TV ):
Oh, George, George, George...
George, George.
Oh.
George...
Honey, are you real?
Hot buttered rum
and an Irish coffee.
( laughter on TV )
Oh, no! Not
It's a Wonderful
Life again.
Mm-hmm.
How many times a day
are they gonna show
this golden moldy?
Six.
From now until New Year's
on Channel 13,
it's a wonderful month.
This flick is so
sweet, it makes
my teeth ache.
Uh-oh.
Stupid alert.
I can
guarantee you from my days
in accounting
that if you run short
at the bank, everyone in town
does not dash over, cash
in hand, to bail you out.
...auld lang syne...
Oh. Oh, here comes
the gooshiest part.
Oh.
Oh, have they no shame?
Oh, yuck, yuck,
yuck, yuck!
For auld lang syne
We'll drink a cup
of kindness yet
For auld lang syne...
( voice breaking ):
Can I have a Kleenex, Sam?
Must have got
something
in my eye.
( sniffling )
Yeah, me, too.
For auld lang syne.
( choked up ):
Must be... something in the air.
( piano plays )
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always glad
you came
You want to be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You want to be where everybody
knows your name
You want to go
where people know
People are all the same
You want to go where
everybody knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Hey, good afternoon, all you
warmhearted and generous people.
NORM:
Cliffy.
What's with the box?
Well, the, uh, postal carriers
are having a food drive,
and if you, uh, good samaritans
fill this box with canned goods,
I'll, uh, win a free trip
to Disney World.
Yeah.
Imagine that--
Pirates of the Caribbean,
Mr. Toad's Wild Ride and me.
( chuckling )
NORM:
So,
who are the cans for?
CLIFF:
Uh,
I don't know.
Poor, needy, somebody like that.
Boy, they make
such a fuss
about Mother
Teresa.
Excuse me
there, Doctor,
but, uh, do I, uh,
detect a wry note
of cynicism there
in your comments?
Cynical? Me?
How could I possibly
be cynical?
Living in a nation
in which we
celebrate the
holy birth
of a babe
in a manger
with Perry
Como in Hawaii.
Hey, boss lady,
what you all duded up for?
You mean, why am I not
wearing a sweatshirt
and plastic earrings?
Yeah.
'Cause I just came
from the company
Christmas party.
SAM:
Ooh! Did
you corner
Mr. Drake under the mistletoe
and make nice-nice?
None of your business.
Oh, Rebecca didn't
get her Christmas goose.
But I did have plenty
of time to make out
next week's schedule.
Whoa, whoa, wait
a second here.
You got us working
on Christmas Eve.
That's a holiday.
No, Christmas is a holiday.
Well, it's a
holiday eve.
I'm gonna pay you all
time and a half.
No. Hey. No,
forget it.
We cannot be bought.
I can.
Sweetheart, don't you want
to be home with your family?
Would you?
Good point,
good point.
Uh, Woody...
Uh, Woody can't work.
He has to go back
to Indiana, be with his folks.
Not this year, Sam.
I'm a big boy now.
I got commitments
in the city.
I landed a part
in our children's
theater production
of The Story of Snow.
I play the King
of the Flakes.
Hmm.
That'd be a stretch.
Listen...
We only have
a matinee
on Christmas Eve,
so I'd be happy
to work that night,
encores permitting.
Great. Oh, and just
so you guys know
I'm not pulling rank,
I'm scheduled
to work that night, too.
No. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Listen, no way am I
punching the clock
on one of the most sacred
of family nights
in the whole year.
Oh, and what do
you have planned?
An intimate little dinner
with one of your nieces?
She makes it sound so cheap.
Oh, joy.
Christmas Eve.
By this time tomorrow,
millions of Americans,
knee deep in tinsel
and wrapping paper,
will utter
those heartfelt words--
"Is this all I got?"
I hope you're not
hanging that there
for my benefit.
Are you kidding me?
Who'd want to kiss somebody
who makes everyone else work
on Christmas Eve?
Oh, all right.
The reviews are in.
We're a hit!
( patrons murmuring )
MAN:
Good for
you, Woody.
Let's, uh, take a peek.
MAN:
Congratulations.
Okay.
"The Story of Snow
was way excellent.
"I think any kid in
Miss Pedesta's class
who misses it is
a full-on goon."
And that from the kid
who panned Goldilocks.
Yeah.
WOODY:
Yeah. I'm gonna
call my mom
and read it to her.
Yeah?
Boy, I'll tell you,
I sure am glad
I stayed in Boston
after all.
If I was home right now,
I'd just be sitting around
listening to my aunt and uncle
talk about who's dead
and who's sick
and who lost part of their head
in a thresher.
Hello, Mom?
( crying ):
I miss you all so much.
Would you look
at the poor slob?
Forced to
humiliate
himself in
some stupid
outfit just to
make a few bucks
for the holiday season.
Yeah, why doesn't
he just wear a sign,
"Loser for hire?"
Hey, Peterson?
You're late again.
I'm not
covering for you this time.
No, no. I think you have
the wrong Peterson.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Well, when you find
the right one,
would you tell him not to sweat
in the hat so much?
Well...
guess I'm busted.
( tapping countertop )
Okay, I didn't mention anything
to you guys, 'cause I thought
that you guys just might razz me
a little bit
about being a Santa Claus
over at Nagle's.
That was you?
Mm.
That's what
my kid meant
when she says
that "Santa smells
like the place
where Mommy works."
WOODY:
A-Are you making the
stuffing bone dry,
the way I love it?
Ooh. Well,
can't you
freeze some and mail it to me?
Well, no, not the gravy.
That would be stupid.
My mother.
( Woody speaking
indistinctly )
Oh, God.
Can you believe Rebecca?
As long as one customer stays,
we all stay.
It's 10:30.
The guy's been nursing
the same drink for over an hour.
Yeah, I wish
he'd hurry
the hell up
so we could
get out of here.
WOODY:
Christmas
tree's okay...
Presents are
all wrapped.
Mm.
All the kids
are in bed.
And Eddie's
waiting up for me
so that we
could exchange
our goodies
in private.
You don't wait
until Christmas morning
to open your presents?
Oh, yeah,
but we like
to exchange our
goodies in private.
Hey, you know what?
Let's you, me and Woody
exchange presents right now,
and when he leaves,
we can leave. Come on.
Oh, good idea, yeah.
Ooh. Dad repainted
the Wise Men?
Well, is Balthazar
still black?
Hey, Woody, Woody,
as soon as you're finished,
we're gonna exchange presents.
Okay, Mom, got to go now.
Love you. Bye.
Here you go, Sam.
Here you go, Carla.
Oh, hey...
Oh, no, wait.
That Miss Howe's.
You...
you got something
for Rebecca?
Well, it's nothing special.
It's just an antique
silver frame
with a silhouette of her face
that I cut out in black velvet.
Wow.
Oh, I'm glad you like it,
'cause I got you the same thing.
Well, it's your face.
Yeah, I better give her
my present now, too.
You-you gave Rebecca
a present, too...?
You don't
even like her.
What are you doing?
It's a Christmas tradition, Sam.
It's called kissing up.
Yeah, and besides, I'd
sure feel like a doofus
if I didn't get
anything for Miss Howe,
and she got all those
wonderful presents for us.
Oh, man!
I didn't get her anything.
Oh, well, don't feel
bad, Sam. I mean,
just because everybody else
got her something.
The pretzel salesman, the beer
distributor,
the relief bartender--
that guy she fired
after one day.
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, wait a minute, though.
All those guys are just trying
to get her in the sack.
I got some shopping to do.
All right,
Happy New Year!
Merry Christmas,
Happy Hanukah.
Now get lost.
I can't.
Why not?
I'm expecting friends.
Oh, yeah, right.
Merry Christmas, Al.
Merry Christmas.
MAN:
Well, hello, hi!
Merry Christmas, Al.
Merry
Christmas, Al.
Hello. How
are you?
( loud chatter )
Buon Natale.
Feliz Navidad.
Joyeux Noel.
Merry Christmas
and shalom.
Ditto.
Now go home.
And take ten of these
deadbeats with you.
Oh, would
that I could,
Carla, but
Lady Bountiful here insists
on doling out
these obligatory gifts
so that people will pretend
they like us in the New Year.
My little Scrooge.
If he doesn't cheer up,
Santa's going to give
him a lump of coal
and make him sleep
on the couch.
Merry,
merry.
Thanks.
Happy,
happy.
All right.
Where's Sam?
I've got
a little
something
for him.
Oh, he went to buy a gift
for Miss Howe.
Oh, too bad
he didn't
wait around.
He could have
just given
her this.
I don't think so.
That's mentholated
preshave for
tough beards.
Oh.
Just as well.
That's what
I got her.
He did it again, damn it!
The third year in a row,
Walt Twitchell has cheated me
out of my rightful place
in the Magic Kingdom.
And he did it by one lousy
dented can of Spam.
You know, Clavin,
I know you're dying
to go to a place
where no one looks twice
at funny costumes
and big floppy ears,
but I think
you missed the point here.
A lot of food got
to needy people.
Isn't that
what it's all about?
Well...
I guess you're
right, Carla.
WOODY:
Oh,
Mr. Clavin, I'm
glad you're here.
I got something
for you.
Ah, thanks, Woody, but, uh...
Wait a minute.
Chow mein and leechy nuts?
Woodrow, think very carefully.
Were these in the bar
before 4:00 p.m. today?
Yeah, they were here.
I just forgot to
put 'em in the box.
Oh, that makes one more can
than Twitchell.
I win.
( laughs )
Deck the halls
with suntan lotion.
Disney World, here I come!
( laughs )
Well, I guess it's
true what they say.
Charity begins in Orlando.
( grunts )
Oh!
You... Yoo-hoo!
Hey, wait, no!
I see you in there!
Hey, come on.
Please, no.
Please, open. Oh, please!
( groans )
Hey, please open up.
Excuse...
Oh, great, listen.
Uh, is there any, uh,
store open around here
this time of night?
Oh, geez.
( groans )
( door bell jangling )
Oh, oh, bless you, sir.
Thank you, thank
you for being open.
Sorry, we're closed.
Oh...
Oh!
Merry Christmas.
( grunts )
( groans )
WOMAN:
Are you all right?
No.
No, I'm trying to get
a gift for my boss.
Everything's closed, I'm cold,
it's wet and I'm miserable.
Well, I've got plenty
of presents here.
Maybe you could
use one of these?
Well... you must be an angel.
You don't have wings
under there, do you?
Mm-hmm.
What?
I'm a stewardess.
Oh... oh...
oh, God.
Oh, bless your
heart. Hey!
Well, let's...
Whoo!
let's see what I've got.
Oh, thank you.
Okay.
Oh, well.
What's this, uh,
this one right here?
Oh, those are ear muffs.
But you don't want those,
they're too impersonal
and boring.
No, they'd be
perfect for her.
Your boss is a her?
Yeah, well...
rumor has it.
( chuckles )
Oh, well, I've got
some things that I bought
for myself she might like.
No, no, the ear muffs
are perfect.
Let me just write you
out a check here.
Oh, how 'bout
a nice silk teddy?
Mm, I love to lounge around
in my house with this.
Oh, yeah?
Mm. Mm-hmm.
Uh... what-what else did you
buy for yourself in there?
A black lace garter belt.
Ooh.
Trust me, you can never
have too many of these.
Ah...
Mm-hmm.
Let's see,
we have... baby dolls...
( chuckles )
...and a short kimono...
( chuckling ):
Merry Christmas, Sammy.
...and a satin camisole...
Mmm!
Evening, everybody.
ALL:
Norm!
Santa, what can I get you?
Finally, someone wants
to get me something.
I am so happy this holiday
season is over with.
The whining, the crying,
the screaming,
the temper tantrums...
Okay, I wasn't your
traditional Santa Claus.
NORM:
Come on in.
Right over there.
I'll get you
some beers.
I'll be right
with you.
What's with all
the bowls full of jelly?
Just having a little
get-together after work.
Kind of a class
reunion, you know?
Wow, you guys all went
to the same school?
Santa school.
It covered all the basics--
the hair, the makeup,
how to talk the kids into
asking for the big-ticket items.
( grunting ):
Okay.
Whoa, look who's
here, huh?
Oh, no, what if a little kid
walks in here?
Sweetheart, it's almost
midnight Christmas Eve.
What a time to find out.
Why don't you, uh...
yeah, grab a seat right here
and I'll go get us something
hot for our toddies, huh?
Thanks, Sam.
All right.
( chuckling )
Hey, Carla...
( clears throat )
I got a present for Rebecca.
See you picked up a little
package for yourself, too.
Hey, you, know...
Why not? I've been
a good boy
and it's just what
I asked for.
Sam.
Yeah?
Please accept this Merry
Christmas from Frasier and me.
Oh, hey, wow, that's great.
Thank you very much.
Listen, I got you
something, too.
Um, I left it over in my,
uh, other, uh, apartment.
Can, I, uh,
can I
get it for you next week?
Of course, whenever
you'd like, Sam.
Or whenever you get
a chance to buy it.
Ignore him, Sam, he has
a bug up his chimney.
Oh...
Merry Christmas.
SAM:
Yeah, uh,
let me have the ear muffs.
That's the, uh...
my boss lady over there.
Woody,
Carla, Sam.
These are just little
tokens of appreciation
from me to you.
Oh, my... you
got us presents?
Oh, wow!
REBECCA:
You know, there were
so many choices,
but I think I done good.
A coffee mug with
the corporate logo.
A night shirt...
with the corporate logo.
SAM:
Yeah, well...
Thanks.
That's great.
You're welcome.
Oh, and know that I don't
expect anything in return.
Oh, um, we got
you gifts.
Oh, uh...
SAM:
Yeah...
Yay!
Here, why don't you, uh,
open mine
first there?
"To Rebecca from Sam."
Oh, you shouldn't
have gone to the trouble.
Oh, just a little something
to keep your ears warm.
( gasps )
My God.
Diamond earrings.
I don't believe this!
I don't either.
( mutters )
I thought
I was a kiss up,
but Sammy wins
the pucker sweepstakes.
Hey, if he got her diamonds,
I wonder what he got us.
Yeah.
Oh, big whoop--
a wallet.
Thanks for
the soap, Sam.
Ooh, and
it's pink, too.
Uh, listen, I'm sorry
about the mix up here,
but my boss seems to really
love the diamond earrings.
Can I buy them
from you maybe?
Well, they were for my mother.
They cost $500.
$500?
Um, I'll be right back.
Rebecca?
Sam, uh...
I don't know what to say.
I'm really overwhelmed
by your generous gift,
but I think it's
inappropriate.
You mean... you're...
you're giving it back?
You don't... you don't
want to keep it?
I think I should.
Oh, well...
if that's the way
you feel, but I...
I want you to know
that I wouldn't have
bought these for you unless
I wanted you to have them.
Well, they
are pretty.
Thank you.
Is that "thank you" you're
giving them back to me,
or "thank you"
you're going to keep them?
I'm afraid that
I've misjudged you.
You're very sweet.
Aw.
Would you like
to come over
to my house tonight
for a late supper?
Well, that sounds
very inviting.
And I'll wear
my new earrings.
( to himself ):
And very little else.
Uh, damn! Oh!
That witch is gonna
make me work tonight.
Yeah, and after I gave her
the earrings, too.
I just can't believe it.
Oh, I guess that means
there's no lingerie
fashion show, then?
Well, maybe we could do it
some other time.
What do you think?
Well, I don't know.
It just seemed like
such a Christmasy thing
to do.
Yeah.
Oh, well.
Just write me a check for
the earrings and I'll be going.
All right, and that was
500-- and she better
be fantastic-- dollars.
And there we go.
All right, uh, well,
thank you very much.
You sure, uh, you sure
you're not upset about this?
No, I'm just going to go
over to my mom's house.
She's probably still up
getting everything ready
for tomorrow.
Yeah.
You know, baking the bread
and icing the cookies
and stuffing the turkey.
SAM:
Yeah.
Stuffing?
Oh, yeah, my mom
makes it from scratch.
Gee, so does mine.
Yeah, but does your mom
make it bone dry?
You could gag on it.
Hey, don't tell me.
Do you have a manger scene
on your
front lawn?
The biggest on our block.
Oh...
The Wise Men are my favorite.
Oh, I love Balthasar.
Oh, Balthasar's good,
but Melchior, he's the best.
( chuckles ):
Okay, well...
Listen, I'd
introduce you two,
but something tells me you've
known each other for years.
You driving, Carl?
No way, B.J.
I'm over my limit.
Don't ask me.
I'm gonna sleep
where I fall.
Yeah...
Doesn't that
just epitomize
the spirit of Christmas
in the '80s?
NORM:
Merry Christmas.
FRASIER:
A gaggle of pie-eyed
Santa Clauses...
You have a good night.
Take it easy.
...all trying to find
a designated driver
to take the sleigh
ride home.
MAN:
Well...
I hate to leave,
but, uh...
I've got a busy night,
and a long haul ahead of me.
Night.
Anyone remember that
guy from class?
No.
I don't, uh...
Beats me.
I thought
he was a friend of yours.
No, no, no. Not
a friend of mine.
No, he came over with you.
No, I could swear
that he came with...
Okay, wait, now wait.
Wait a second now.
You don't suppose...
( patrons chattering )
Did you
hear that?
Nah...
Suppose it could
be the wind,
but it sounded
like sleigh bells.
Oh, come on, guys.
I mean, seriously,
there must
be some explanation.
Well...
Geez, do you...
do you think
there actually could be a...
Oh, my wife's
gonna kill me.
I left the lights on in
the station wagon again.
Can one of you guys
give me a jump?
Eh...!
Lilith, that was a miracle.
Snowball, you've had
too much schnapps.
No, no, I'm stone sober. It's...
I mean, I know that's
just some fat old guy
with car trouble, but...
for half a second there, I
actually believed in Christmas.
And th-that hasn't happened
to me since I was...
born.
Come on, let's, uh,
let's sing some
Christmas carols
and roast some chestnuts
and all that treacle...
FRASIER AND PATRONS:
Deck the halls
with boughs of holly
Fah-la-la-la-la,
la-la-la-la
'Tis the season to be jolly
Fah-la-la-la-la,
la-la-la-la...
You know, Sammy,
I don't want to be
ungrateful or anything,
but this soap
sucks wind.
( chuckles )
You bought Miss Humbug
diamond earrings.
Oh, come on now.
There was a reason
for that, though.
She has invited me over for
an intimate late-night supper.
( chuckles )
Yeah, you, me
and half the people
in this bar.
Fah-la-la-la-la,
la-la-la-la...
Don't kid around
with me now.
I'm in far too fragile
a condition.
You mean you thought you
were gonna be the only...
( laughing )
You know, I wasn't too
thrilled about the soap,
but this makes up for it.
Fah-la-la-la-la,
la-la-la-la...
Hey, look-- It's
a Wonderful Life
is on again
and it's the very best part.
Turn it up, Sam.
Should old acquaintance
be forgot and never...
Well, I'm glad I can
finally say this to you
without having
my head bitten off.
Merry Christmas, Frasier.
It is, isn't it?
We have everything
that matters,
we're together, our loved ones
are safe and happy...
NEWSCASTER:
This just in to our news room.
Boston Airport has been
temporarily closed
due to the presence
of a berserk man on Runway Six
chasing an Orlando-bound plane
and throwing what appears
to be cans of Chinese food.
Stay tuned for further details.
...lang syne...
Oh, Cliffy, Cliff, Cliff...
( singing along with TV )
We'll drink a cup
of kindness yet
For auld lang syne.
WOODY:
God bless us, every one.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org