Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Watch this.
Okay...
What do you got, Wood?
Watch closely as I remove
my own index finger.
Uh-huh.
It's something I learned
from my uncle,
only when I do it, it's a trick.
Eh?
Uh, not bad but, uh,
I think Cliffy's still
ahead on points here.
And in what sophomoric
activity
are you gentlemen
involved now?
Our first annual tricks
with digits exhibition!
Of all the pointless wastes
of human energy.
Frasier's right.
You could sit here until
the end of time doing your
silly little finger tricks,
but none of you will ever
be able to top this.
Wow, she's right.
The king is dead.
Long live the queen!
NORM:
Yes and she's writing!
She's going for
bonus points.
CLIFF:
What's it say?
"My fist is stuck.
Call 911."
FRASIER:
Come on, hon.
You know, this
happens to her
more often than
you'd think.
(theme song begins)
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always
glad you came
You wanna be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You wanna be where
everybody knows your name
You wanna go
where people know
People are all the same
You wanna go where
everybody knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
How am I supposed to make
a drink around here?
We're out of gin, vermouth,
cherries and lime juice.
We gotta get into
that storeroom.
We can't.
Sam said to substitute.
Okay.
Here you go.
What the hell
is this?
It's clam juice.
I wanted a martini.
I wanted to be Princess
Carla of Monaco.
Drink it!
Sorry,
Mr. Krapence.
We can't get into the office
or the storeroom
because Miss Howe
locked herself in
since she decided not to marry
Mr. Colcord.
She's still
in there.
in the gown.
She won't talk
to anybody.
Doesn't move.
Doesn't eat.
Gee, that's awful.
I really wanted a martini.
Greetings all!
A pint of lager,
my good publican!
I'm of a Dickensian spirit
today.
I've just come from
the Antiquarian Book Fair,
where I managed to luck
into a handsomely bound
first edition of Charles
Dickens' Tale of Two Cities.
Wow!
If you don't mind
my asking,
how much does something
like this cost, Dr. Crane?
Well, uh, Woody, money
isn't really the issue,
but, uh, around $1,200.
(scoffs, snickers)
1,200 bucks?
Got something to
show you, Dr. Crane.
It's called a
library card.
Thank you for the advice, Woody.
Now may I have a scotch
on the rocks, please?
Okeydoke!
That'll be around
1,200 bucks.
Oh, Frasier, you know,
it's a good thing you're here
because we gotta
think of some way
to get that crazy lady
out of the office.
It's been two days.
Well, I realize that
you're concerned about Rebecca
and that you all look to me
as the solver
of all problems personal,
but, in this case,
I have to throw up my hands.
I mean, there's a limit
to what even I can do.
And we also know
how you pout
when we don't ask you.
Well... fine.
Maybe I'll just go home.
Okay!
I've got the tool box here.
I'm gonna get Rebecca out
of that office right now.
Rebecca!
I've got a screwdriver here!
I'm gonna take that doorknob off
and I'm gonna open the door
here.
Rebecca, I got a Phillips head
by mistake,
but I'm gonna...
I'm putting that down and
I'm picking up a flathead,
and then I'm gonna take that
doorknob off.
Rebecca, I don't have
a flathead,
but I have one of those
putty things
and I'm gonna put it...
Damn!
Okay, Rebecca, I just punctured
my thumb with that, uh...
putty thing and I'm gonna go
get a tetanus shot,
then I'm...
coming back here
and taking that doorknob off.
Here's a Band-Aid.
Hey, hey, guys!
Rebecca!
Hey!
Rebecca's out.
REBECCA:
No, no.
Don't say Rebecca.
Don't call me
Rebecca.
Rebecca doesn't live
here anymore.
Rebecca died two
days ago.
Oh! So that's
what that is.
Whoof!
I'm telling you,
a woman should never
sweat in taffeta.
Have a seat.
Come on.
Thank you.
Wow.
I've never sat
here before.
Here I am, sitting
on this stool,
knowing my life
is a mess.
I have no future, and...
I'm a totally
hopeless failure.
Yeah. Try it
with beer nuts.
It is all my fault.
I mean, I got
what I deserve.
And now I'm alone.
I... I have nothing
and I'm just a,
you know, worthless,
shallow person.
I'm telling you,
try it with the beer nuts.
Rebecca...
I realize you haven't sought
my professional advice, but
I think it's time
to get some perspective,
take a look at yourself.
Splash some water on your face
and get a fresh start.
I'd like to, Frasier,
but I seem to have lost
the will to move.
I just want to sit here
for the rest of my life.
Geez, maybe
it's the stool.
Come on,
Miss Howe.
Woody...
have you ever
had your whole life
cave in on you
all of a sudden?
No, but I have had
a cave cave in on me
all of a sudden.
You know, at the risk
of sounding insensitive,
I'm... I'm glad she's
getting out of here.
Her walking around
in that wedding dress
was just a tad too
"Miss Havisham" for me.
Who?
Miss Havisham.
Famous character
from Charles Dickens'
Great Expectations.
Spends the entire novel
walking around
in her wedding dress.
What?!
Yes.
Well, surely you know it.
It's Great Expectations.
Pip? Miss Havisham?
Magwich?
And, uh... and four...
pizza-loving turtles
who practice martial
arts in the sewer.
Oh, cowabunga, dudes!
CLIFF:
You know,
there's a lot of people
don't realize
that that was
a comic book first.
I'm gonna go for a drive, Sam.
SAM:
Oh, yes, sweetheart.
That's a good idea.
You know, get some fresh air.
Take all the time
you want.
Thank you.
Where did she get those clothes?
WOODY:
Hey, Sam, could you
dig some clothes out
of lost and found?
Here you go.
Woody, come on out here.
Let's take a look.
Hey, Sam, how long did
you say these clothes
have been in the
lost and found?
I don't know--
a while, I guess. Why?
(laughing)
Is that Woody Boyd?
Or is that
Keith Partridge?!
When is Miss Howe getting back
with my real clothes?
I can't go out like this.
I mean, I know it was
the '70s and all,
but who would dress in anything
this dumb-looking?
Those duds look familiar.
"Property
of C. Clavin."
Deep inside, didn't
we all know that?
(laughing)
These are your
clothes, Mr. Clavin?
Yeah, I guess.
Well, how'd they end up
in the lost and found?
How did they end up in there?
Well, it was the '70s,
(chuckles):
and I was a swinger.
Uh-oh.
I had some good times
in those rags, Woody.
Cliff, we don't want to
hear about it, please.
Huh? Oh, it was great.
You know, hey,
the disco scene,
grooving.
Ixnay, Cliff.
Yeah, it was
a great decade, huh?
Hot-tubbing every night.
I got rolfed.
WOODY:
Oh.
Please stop, Mr. Clavin.
Oh, now I remember
how I lost those clothes.
Oh, don't say it;
don't say it.
I was streaking!
Oh! I knew it!
I knew he was gonna
say it!
Of course, I was about
three pounds lighter then.
FRASIER:
Woody...
I think it was
a great sacrifice
for you to give
your clothes to Rebecca.
It puts me in mind
of another novel by
my favorite British author.
You know who I mean.
I'll give you a hint.
Charles...?
In Charge?
(laughs)
Are you people really
this ignorant
or do you just do this
to torture me?
Uh, sometimes the two
go hand-in-hand.
All right.
Gather around,
everyone.
I am going to right
a horrible wrong.
I am going to read to you
Dickens' classic,
A Tale of Two Cities,
and you will see
just how much fun
great literature can be.
(all groaning)
FRASIER:
"Book the First.
It was the best of times,
it was the worst of times."
Hey, wait,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Which was it?
Just stay tuned, Norm.
"It was the age of wisdom,
it was the age of foolishness.
It was the epoch of belief, it
was the epoch of incredulity."
Boy, this Dickens guy
really liked
to keep his butt covered,
didn't he?
"There was a king
with a large jaw,
"and a queen with a plain face,
"on the throne
of England.
"And... and..."
"...and there was
a bloodthirsty clown,
"who beckoned innocent
children into the sewer,
and swallowed them whole."
Ah!
That's a neat trick.
(phone ringing)
Wait-wait-wait a minute, Fras,
wait there.
Yeah, Cheers. What?
Hey... uh... Rebecca!
Where are you calling from?
I can barely hear you.
30,000 feet over Pittsburgh.
What?
I thought you were just
going for a drive.
I did.
I drove to the airport.
Listen,
will you tell Woody
that I left his car
outside the United terminal.
Or American.
It doesn't really
make any difference.
They all tow them
to the same place anyway.
Sam, is that Miss Howe?
Ask her if she
has my wallet.
I need my
driver's license.
Actually, you don't
have to worry about
that right now, Wood.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
I'm-I'm going home
to San Diego, Sam.
I want to try and forget Boston.
I want to erase
the last three years of my life.
It's been five, Rebecca.
Has it been that long?
Hey, Sam, does she
have my wallet?
You still have Woody's
wallet, don't you?
Yeah, sure, how do you think
I'm paying for this call?
Hell, how do you think
I'm paying for this flight?
Yeah, she still has it.
Honey, listen to me.
You can't run away from
your problems like this.
Sam, Sam, look,
the only reason I called
was to say good-bye
and thank you for everything.
It's really meant a lot to me.
Bye-bye.
Oh, miss, did you remember
your credit card?
Oh, yeah, thanks.
I'm gonna need this.
I need to buy a whole new
wardrobe when we land.
I'm gonna be good to myself.
As we recall...
from Monday's installment
of A Tale of Two Cities,
Sydney Carton was about to go
to the guillotine
and sacrifice himself.
The guillotine--
slice that neck.
(laughing)
"When suddenly,
an Apache attack chopper
"hovered above the guillotine,
pumping hot lead
into the crowd."
Get them Frogs, huh?
"As Darnay climbed
into the chopper,
"sweat streaming
from his bloodstained headband,
"he could be heard to mutter,
"'It is a far, far
better thing I do
"'than I have ever done.
"'It is a far, far better...
"'butt-kicking I give...
...than I have ever
butt-kicked.'"
All right.
Whoa!
What a book, huh?
Yeah, that was
great, great, Fras.
What, uh, what are you
going to read to us next?
Well, I was thinking about,
uh, David Copperfield.
What's that about?
Well, it's about
these, uh...
two coppers,
and this... field,
um... and they're found...
dismembered with their
body parts switched.
CARLA:
Man...!
Man, that Dickens
is one sick dude.
Have any of you guys
heard from Rebecca yet?
Normie.
Turn on the game,
will you, Sam?
No, no, no, come on,
let's, uh...
Let's give her
a call here.
I got her parents'
number here.
Let's just tell her that,
you know,
we're thinking about her
and that we care.
Ah, hell,
it's her parents' machine.
I hate these things.
I never know what to say.
Hi. This is Sam from Cheers.
Uh, this message is for Rebecca.
Um, hi, Rebecca.
We just wanted to find out
if you're okay,
and tell you
that we all miss you,
and I love you,
and I hope that...
Oh, oh, Sam.
Wh-What?
You love her?
No. No, I-I didn't say that.
Hold on a second.
No, I didn't say that.
No, no, I said-I said
we miss her and we love her.
You said we miss her
and you love her.
Yeah, but it was implied
that you miss her, too.
Well, shoot.
I-I-I don't want her to get
the wrong impression here.
Uh, hi, Rebecca, listen,
when I said that I love you,
you know I didn't mean
love love.
I, uh, you know, I meant more
like a friend, you know,
a buddy, a pal, uh,
like a partner, you know.
Like the two cops
in David Copperfield.
Okay, honey?
Well, anyway, bye-bye.
Wait, no...
Wait, hold on.
That was a little cold.
Yeah, you know,
listen, she's, uh,
she's feeling kind of low.
You can't just kick her
when she's down like that.
Yeah.
Sweetheart, when-when I said
that I love you, you know,
I meant that you're a-a very
important part of my life,
you know, along with a lot
of other people.
It-it's, uh, you know,
it's like my-my life
is this big jigsaw puzzle,
and you are
a very important part.
You know,
like a corner piece, huh?
All right.
Hold on. Oh...
I think the guys want to say
something here. Go ahead.
GUYS:
Sammy loves you.
Hey, any of you guys tried that
new steak house on Commonwealth?
No.
It's the greatest.
Beautiful waitresses
in tiny little wench outfits.
Yeah? What
did you have?
Beautiful waitress
in a tiny little wench outfit.
I'm going back, too.
Dr. Crane, when are you going
to read us some more Dickens?
(chanting):
Dickens, Dickens, Dickens.
LILITH: Oh, well.
Frasier, I'm impressed.
It seems your experiment
in cultural enrichment
has been a success.
Yep. We're waiting for Oliver
Twist: The Wrath of Fagin.
Excuse me?
Darling, I've done some
things the past few weeks
I'm not very proud of.
Just leave it alone.
Shoot, shoot, shoot.
Hey, guys...
listen to this.
(recorder beeps)
Sam, this is Rebecca.
I got your message.
Hearing your voice
made me realize
what I'm missing
in my life, and...
and I was such a fool
not to have seen it before.
My plane lands
at midnight tonight,
and I'm coming straight
to the bar to see you.
So will you please,
please wait for me?
(beep)
(snickering)
What am I gonna do?
I mean, do you think
that she's coming back here
because I left that message
on her machine?
Yeah.
Hey, will you be serious here
for a minute?
Just once I'd like to have
a serious conversation
in this damn bar.
Okay. Fine.
Mm-hmm.
Do you really think
that she's rushing back
because I said I love you?
Mm, yeah.
What do you know.
I'm gonna talk to somebody who
knows something around here.
What do you think?
You're dead meat
on a stick.
No, I'm not dead meat
You know,
and even if she does think that,
I've handled lots
of love-crazed babes
who want to become
Mrs. Sam Malone.
I got dozens of ways
of handling that.
You know,
even if they all don't work,
I still have Plan Z.
What's, uh,
Plan Z there, Sam?
Never you mind.
It's pretty drastic, I'll admit,
but I'll use it if I have to.
SAM:
I-I...
I don't want the same woman
hanging onto me
for the rest of my life.
I mean, can you imagine how
creepy that would be, Frasier?
I'll... answer that
question another time.
Okay, Leon, you just
wait outside there
and come running in when
you see the lights flash.
Right.
Carla, Sammy will
not tell us.
What is this Plan Z?
I'll tell you everything I know
for 20 bucks each.
All right.
It's called Plan Z.
When Sammy flashes the lights,
this guy Leon comes in
and executes it.
Okay, well, what...
what is Plan Z?
Beats me.
I didn't know that much
two minutes ago.
Give me the money.
I think it was worth it.
Oh, yeah.
Sam, it seems to me
you're going through an awful,
awful lot of machinations
to avoid dealing honestly
and directly with Rebecca.
Well, that's me,
you know, always thinking.
Besides, you know,
I don't think we're gonna
have to use Plan Z here.
I mean, what are we
talking about?
We're talking about Rebecca.
I mean, what's
the worst she can do?
Sam.
I hope you're ready to change
your life, because I am.
Ah...
Can you excuse me
just a second here, hon?
Sam, why are you flashing
the lights?
Oh, you know, it's just kind of
to welcome you back.
You know like, three cheers,
hey, Rebecca's back.
Rebecca's back.
REBECCA:
Sam,
get over here,
quit being silly.
I have to ask you something
really important.
Will you sell me this bar?
No. What?
Cheers-- I want to buy Cheers.
Running this place was the only
time I ever felt like somebody.
You know, people
looked up to me.
Who?
You mean you didn't come
back here to marry Sam?
Marry Sam?!
No, why would
you think that?
You didn't think that, did you?
Shoot, no.
That's why you've been doing
all this weird stuff.
Because you think I came
back here to marry you?
What weird stuff?
I can't keep
living a lie, Sam.
No, no, no, Leon.
Sam is my lover.
Boy, you...
you really did think
I was after you.
REBECCA:
I can't believe this.
You are a wussy little
fraidy cat.
I'm not a wussy
little fraidy cat.
Oh, then this is real?
You and Leon
are lovers.
Well, why don't you give
Leon a kiss then?
Because we've been
together for 14 years,
and we're no longer
demonstrative.
You know, the, uh,
the spark's gone.
I'm sorry, Leon.
I probably should have
said something sooner.
No, no, no, Sam,
you can't have it both ways.
You either give Leon a kiss...
on his lips...
or you admit
that you are
a wussy little fraidy cat.
Sammy, don't let her
make you look like
a wussy little fraidy cat.
I'm not a wussy
little fraidy cat.
(Carla meowing)
What are we
supposed to think?
Sorry about that, Leon.
You realize I'm gonna have
to slug you in the face now.
I wish you would.
(Cliff and Norm
groaning)
We, uh, still on for golf
on Thursday?
Yeah, you bet, Leon.
Great.
Oh, ow...
That hurt.
Sammy, look at you.
Your nose is bleeding.
Your eye is
starting to swell.
And you just kissed a man.
But you're not a wussy
little fraidy cat.
NORM:
You ain't afraid.
No, not Sammy.
NORM:
Good boy.
Good, Sam.
You know,
in the space
of the last 30 seconds,
we have witnessed deceit,
sexual turmoil
and sudden,
senseless violence.
It puts me in mind
of a passage from...
The Pickwick Papers.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org