Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
- All right, 1 955 AL MVP.
- Yogi Berra.
All right, height of the left field wall
at Fenway.
- The Green Monster is 37 feet high.
- Told you.
All right, here you go.
- lke Delock's lifetime ERA.
- 4:03. Had enough?
Give it up, Norm. The woman's
a lean, mean trivia machine.
- Unbelievable. You're the best.
- I know.
- Ask me something.
- Forget it, Zeke.
There aren't any questions
about wheat in there.
Oh, and I suppose you know
everything that's in this book.
- If it's in there, I know it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
What's the Library of Congress
card catalogue number?
Seven, eight, zero, three,
four, seven, six.
- That's not even close.
- What do you mean? Look there.
What?
That's it exactly.
Hey, everybody. Guess what
I grew in my greenhouse?
Not another potato that looks
like Richard Nixon.
No, I learned the error
of my ways there.
Yeah, I guess I was pretty
off the deep end then, huh?
No, but this is nothing like that.
Look at that.
A map of the Hawaiian lslands.
See the little bumps in the exact shape
and formation of our 50th state.
Come on, Cliff,
don't make me look, please.
Normy, Normy, this is one of nature's
fascinating little mutations here.
Resting in the hands
of one of her bigger ones.
All right, no skin off my nose.
I'll just put it in the bag
and take it on home.
Hey, guess what's in the bag.
"Human Sexuality"?
You don't have to broadcast it.
It happens to be assigned reading
for a required course.
You're blushing.
I am not blushing.
I prefer to maintain a sense
of decorum, unlike you
who brought in coloured slides
of your wedding night.
They were a big hit.
And your break was over
ten minutes ago.
Oh, Carla, please.
I have to come up with a topic
for my psychology paper by tonight.
I'm at a complete loss.
Of course I could turn out your
run-of-the-mill essay
on sadomasochism, bestiality,
bondage and discipline...
but I'm looking for something
with a little pizzazz.
- Hello, everybody.
- Oh, Sam.
Would you please see if you can
light a fire under the stick?
She's been goofing off
for an hour.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah. She's gotta write some paper
about sex and she can't think
of anything to write about.
You're kidding me. She studied
for a whole year at Sammy State.
Hey there. I hear you're
writing a paper on sex.
- Is there any way I can help out?
- Thank you, Sam.
This paper is on human sexuality.
No, come on, I'm serious.
I want to help.
Well, it had occurred to me
to use you as a case study,
but I lack the proper clinical distance,
so that's out of the question.
What are you talking about?
You got an A plus staring you
in the face, here.
Come on, we're pals, aren't we?
Come on, let me feel useful.
Well, you would be
an interesting study.
Great. Kind of slow in here, why don't
you step into my laboratory.
Well, all right. I am desperate.
Sam...
...this has to be done
in a professional manner.
I hope you'll take this seriously.
I'm only this far away
from a master's degree in--
Well, 37 different subjects.
But if I do well in this class, psychology
could well become my major major.
Wow, and we were here, huh, Cliff?
We're always here.
Sam, before we start,
I want to warn you.
This will be frank and candid.
We may be touching on some
highly sensitive areas.
I like the sound of it already.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Okay, why don't we start
with your parents.
Would you describe them
as physically demonstrative?
I'm here, aren't l?
They must have been.
But why are you asking me
about my parents?
I'm asking about your parents
to lay a psychological foundation
- for your later behaviour.
- Boy, this isn't as much fun
as I thought it was gonna be.
When are we gonna get to me?
Okay, why don't we jump to your
relationships outside the family.
Yeah.
At what age did you have your
first sexual encounter?
That's more like it. Okay.
"Trevor, a Case Study."
Who's Trevor?
- That's you.
- You're not gonna use my name?
Of course not.
So I do all the work
and this Trevor guy gets the credit?
Sam, this is not your résumé.
In a psychological treatise,
real names are never used.
Yeah, but at least I should be able
to choose my own name.
How about "Duke"?
- This is my paper, and I like Trevor.
- All right. All right.
Let's see where were we? You wanted
to know about my first time, right?
Yes. How old were you?
Boy, I'm not sure.
I know I couldn't get to her house
until the crossing guard showed up.
Wow. First time is kind
of hard to remember.
- What about your first time?
- I'm the scientist, Sam.
My first time has nothing
to do with this.
But just to lay the subject to rest...
...it was the summer of my 19th year.
He was a young man in uniform.
It was a brief encounter.
He left my arms and went
to his doom.
Oh, no, he was killed, huh?
No, no, he went off to boot camp
and came back
with the most God-awful haircut
I'd ever seen.
Now, may we get back to you?
And limit your responses to attitudes.
Please leave out the gory details.
Now, what about your
second encounter?
Well, that would be
the crossing guard.
So, Woody, ready to take on Carla
in the sports trivia contest?
Yeah, well, now, I've been studying
all week long, so go ahead.
- Test me.
- All right.
In what game did Ted Williams
break his elbow.
Ted who?
I'd take another quick peek
in the book, Woods.
- Diane?
- Dr Greenspon.
What on earth are you doing here?
I just wanted to come by
and tell you in person,
I've read your paper, and I think
it is absolutely extraordinary.
In fact, I wouldn't be surprised
if The New England Journal
of Psychology wanted to publish it.
Forgive me for losing my academic
demeanour for a few moments.
- I'm sorry. Sorry.
- That's quite all right.
- Would you like a drink?
- I'd love a beer, please.
Wonderful. Coming right up.
Of course I do have a couple
of reservations.
Well, the most significant concerns
your psychological subject, Trevor.
Since you seem to have found such a
near perfect example of Don Juanism,
there are bound to be those who are
going to doubt this paper's authenticity.
Doctor, I assure you,
every word is true,
although I understand your doubt.
It is hard to believe
that such a man exists.
Doctor,
have a seat over there
for just a couple of minutes.
I'll join you soon.
There are a few things I have to do.
- Sam.
- Yeah.
Would you mind
if I revealed your identity
to my psychology professor,
Dr Greenspon?
Mind? Yo, doc, Trevor here.
- Alias: Sam Malone.
- Lowell Greenspon.
That's an amazing case history
you have.
Yeah, isn't it? Knock on wood.
So you'd say that the paper
is accurate?
Well, now, we had to change a few
of the names to protect the satisfied.
- Well, it's been very nice to meet you.
- Yeah, you too.
- Thank you, Sam.
- Yeah. No, thank you very much.
What a find you have there, Diane.
So you really think it's publishable?
Well, that brings me
to my other reservation.
- What?
- In Trevor,
you've shown us the cause, yes?
What the paper lacks is the effect.
Now, if you could possibly find one
of these conquests to learn
why she's so gullible.
What gives her such low self-esteem
so that she could possibly
fall for this blatant manipulation.
I don't know.
Well, if you did, I don't see how
the Journal could fail to publish it.
Hey, Woody.
Come on, buddy,
get your nose out of that book.
How much more trivia can you cram
into that head?
Yeah, maybe you're right.
My brain must be filled up,
because my hair hurts.
Why don't you call Carla over
before I forget everything.
Carla, you got a brash,
young challenger over here who says
he's gonna boot you off the top
of sports trivia mountain.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
Well, he said it before and I've always
left him bleeding in the dust.
I say, Jethro goes down
in three questions.
Okay, everybody, gather around
for the sports trivia championships.
- Give me your best shot.
- Okay.
What was the lowest round
ever recorded
in a PGA-sanctioned
golf tournament?
- Fifty-nine, Al Geiberger.
- He's right.
All right.
Who was the oldest
heavyweight champion?
- Jersey Joe Walcott.
- Yeah. Bingo.
- All right, those were easy questions.
- Two for two.
You're gonna choke on this one.
Who was the only pitcher to ever lose
a one-hitter in the World Series?
- Bill Bevans.
- He did it.
All right.
New York Yankees, 1947,
against the Brooklyn Dodgers.
- All right. That's good, Woody.
- Goodwoody. Elmer Goodwoody,
shortstop, Boston Beaneaters.
It's all right, buddy, take a rest.
Take A Rest,
winner of the California Derby, 1 959.
Ten-eighty to win,
six-forty to place,
three-twenty to show.
- So you liked my rewrite?
- Oh, yes.
I just can't get over it.
I mean, who would have thought that
this "Colette" that you described
as "rapturously beautiful, intelligent,
indeed brilliant with an ethereal quality"
could be so easily manipulated
by Trevor.
Trevor is not without his charms,
crude as they may be.
Well, but they're so transparent.
The woman would have to be addled.
- She'd have to be totally lacking.
- Thank you. Your point is made.
Oh, hi, doc.
- Oh, my, is that the paper there?
- This is it.
You know, I still haven't had a chance
to read that.
- Mind if I take a look?
- You wouldn't enjoy it.
Oh, don't be modest, Diane.
I'm looking forward to your
presentation of it in class tonight.
- Thank you, doctor.
- Tonight?
Hey, you know, wait a second,
I'm the headline act of that thing.
- You mind if I sit in on class?
- Oh, Sam.
- You wouldn't enjoy the class, either.
- It's very dry and boring.
No reflection on you, professor.
I mean to someone
of Sam's limited intelligence.
No reflection on you, Sam.
What I mean is, don't you have
to cover for Woody tonight?
Oh, you're right. Darn it.
Well, too bad, huh? Doc.
Shoot,
and that did sound like fun too.
Wait a second, I've got an idea.
Why don't you bring them
all over here.
Kind of a field trip.
See Trevor in action.
We could hardly do that.
But I don't think some of the members
would mind coming by for a drink after.
It would give them a chance to meet
the clinical case in the flesh.
Oh, I'm not going to promise that.
We'll just see how the evening goes.
He's remarkable.
Sam.
- Sam.
- No, not now.
I'm going to prepare my lecture, here.
You know, it's about time
I gave something back to the sport
that's given me so much.
Sam, I think you should read this
after all.
It's not what you think.
If you change your mind
about the class coming here tonight,
call me at home. I'll understand.
"The Don Juan Syndrome
in Modern Culture: An Analysis of...
...Sat-- Sate-- Sater-- Satyriasis."
Oh, man, she did it.
She even made my sex life boring.
And not for the first time.
Excuse me,
is there a Cliff Clovin here?
It's Cliff Clavin, partner,
and you're looking at him.
Oh, hi.
I'm a reporter from the Chronicle.
You the guy that sent in this picture
of a squash
- with the Hawaiian lslands on it.
- Yeah. Yeah. What did I tell you guys?
This is one story
they couldn't squash.
There you go.
To be honest,
it's not the squash I'm looking for.
Actually, it's a part of a larger story
on eccentrics here in Boston.
You know, the lunatic fringe.
Lonely people desperate for attention.
Yeah, yeah, but where do I fit in?
You come right after the old lady
with the 84 snakes.
Okay, I'm insulted,
and I'll thank you to leave this bar.
They don't pay me enough.
Cliffy. All right,
you stuck up to that guy.
- You didn't let him exploit you.
- Yeah. Who the hell they think
they're dealing with.
I ain't giving my squash second billing
to a broad with a bunch of snakes.
Hey, how would you like to get a look
inside that old bag's head, huh?
Professor Malone, I think you've got
a little class in session there.
Hi, doc. Over here.
Welcome, everybody.
Why don't you come over
and take a seat anywhere over here.
There's no need to be so formal,
but if you have something prepared.
Oh, just a few things
off the top of my head.
Did you bring an apple
for the teacher?
- Sam.
- Yeah.
I didn't hear from you,
so I assume you read the paper.
Paper? Oh, yeah.
Couldn't put it down.
Are you sure you still want
to go through with this?
- Oh, absolutely.
- But, Sam, I don't feel this--
No, come on. Take a seat here.
Don't want to be late for class.
Okay, sit down.
Welcome, everybody.
Now, I realize you came here
to meet me and find out
what makes a guy like me tick.
So I asked myself:
"What makes you so different
from everybody else
when it comes to scoring big
with women?"
And I think it's--
I think it's this: I love ladies.
I love the way they smell,
the way they sound, the way they feel.
And by the way, that shade
of lipstick really compliments
that rosy glow on your cheeks.
- Unbelievable.
- Now, see, I'm not the only one
who thinks that.
Okay. All right, let's--
Enough about me here.
Let's open up this discussion
a little bit.
- What's your name, son?
- Barry.
Barry. All right, Barry.
Why don't you tell me what you do
when you meet a girl for the first time.
Well, I talk to her and I let her know
that I respect her as a human being.
I ask her out
without putting any pressure on her,
and I let the relationship
grow naturally.
Well, we all have some
pretty crazy ideas when we're young.
Okay, can anyone tell me
where Barry went off the beam?
Miss Chambers has a thought here.
All right. Well, all right, I guess so.
We can take five here.
Smoke them if you got them.
- You didn't read this, did you?
- Didn't have to, I lived it.
Sit down, please.
"Trevor is the image
of the arrested adolescent,
entirely self-oriented,
still intimidated
by the women around him
and attempting
to prove himself superior to them.
Through sexual conquest he can,
for a time, quell his constant fears
of inferiority and failure.
Indeed,
the idea of a nonsexual relationship
is completely foreign to him.
As the years pass and his physical
attractiveness diminishes,
he'll be doomed to a life
of loneliness and despair,
unable to give or receive love."
- Is this really how you feel about me?
- This is my clinical view of you.
As a woman,
I might have felt something different
than I feel as an academician.
It makes my life seem so cheap
and pathetic.
- Sam, you're reading things into this.
- Like here where it says:
"His life is cheap and pathetic."
Don't be hurt.
I hate it when you're hurt.
This is not a true picture of you.
I exaggerated in order
to corroborate my thesis.
Boy, I don't know.
Maybe I am gonna end up this way.
You're not listening to me.
This is a paper.
Theory and conjecture.
I was going for a grade.
I told the professor
what I thought he wanted to hear.
You're just saying that
to make me feel better.
I mean, everything in here is true,
including the part about I've never
had a nonsexual relationship.
Now, there, that's a good example
of exaggeration.
You and I have
a nonsexual relationship.
How can you say that?
Well, I think that the fact
that we don't have sex is a major hint.
That's just because we promised
to try to keep our distance.
And we have.
Our relationship has reached
the mature adult stage.
Well, I wish there
were some way I could...
...prove it to you.
Well, maybe there is.
Sit on my lap.
I'm just trying to convince myself
that I can be close to a woman
without it being sexual.
- This is the silliest thing I've ever--
- Hey, come on, Diane.
Well, if it'll help prove something
to you, all right.
- Boy, you're nervous.
- I am not.
- There, we did it.
- Hey, come on.
Come on, you can't just get up
like that. That doesn't prove anything.
Come sit here, and let's just try
to have a normal conversation.
There is nothing normal about this.
- What do you want to talk about?
- It doesn't matter. Anything.
- How about the weather?
- Okay.
- Nice weather.
- A little nippy.
Well, that's because we're in Boston.
Now, if we were in, say, Tahiti.
- We'd be lying in the sun.
- Getting a tan.
Maybe even a sunburn.
Well, not if we rubbed oil
all over each other.
What are we trying to prove again?
Something about that I can carry
on a normal conversation
- without it being sexual.
- Well, so much for the weather.
- Yeah.
- How about music?
- No, we don't like the same music.
- Well, we can talk about that.
- All right. I like rock 'n' roll.
- I like classical.
- Harmonies.
- Grandeur.
- The hot guitar licks.
- The strings washing over you
in a darkened concert hall.
The driving beat.
The low moan of the cello.
The drums, pounding,
pounding, pounding.
- But if we don't agree, we don't agree.
- Yeah, right.
- What's that leave us?
- Religion.
Religion. All right, the Bible.
- Adam.
- Eve.
- Fig leaves.
- Sin. All right.
- Okay.
- Well, I think we've proved our point.
Clearly we have
a nonsexual relationship.
And you are a fine human being.
- Well, thank you, Diane.
- So if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to go out there and tell them
my paper is completely invalid.
- There you go.
- Your knob.
Yes, I believe so.