Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Anybody seen my gum?
Left it around
here somewhere.
What'd you take
your gum out for?
To give my mouth a rest,
you know.
Dear Diary, today
it finally happened.
Wood, can I have another... Oh!
Cliff,
I think I found
your gum.
This is a new jacket, too, man.
Well, Norm, might I suggest
that you ice it
and then try to scrape the bulk
of it off with a razor blade,
and maybe that way
you can save it.
Oh, no, that's okay, Frasier.
I was about to get
a new piece anyway.
Sounds like a lot of work,
Frasier, I don't know.
Well, alternatively,
you could wait several years
for the resins to break down,
the gum to harden
and fall off by itself.
I seem to have
my full range of movement.
I can wait.
(theme song begins)
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Takin' a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always
glad you came
You wanna be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You wanna be where everybody
knows your name
You wanna go
where people know
People are all the same
You wanna go where everybody
knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Whoo!
Boy, did it just
get warm in here?
I hate Indian summers.
You never know what to wear
to work in the morning.
I mean, it's gonna get cold,
it should stay cold.
Then, who am I
to question the Lord?
What's with
the getup?
It's Indian summer, Sam.
I need these clothes
for protection.
Protection from what?
The eyes of men.
What are you
talking about?
Every time I've conceived a kid
it's been during Indian Summer.
That's when I'm at my most
fertile, Sammy.
I cannot let any man touch me,
talk to me or see me,
or I'll be shooting out kids
like a Pez dispenser.
Oh, come on.
I'm not kidding,
Sammy.
I've-I've gone over two years
now without having a kid.
Now that's a record for me.
I'm not taking
any chances.
I was gonna stay home,
turn off the lights,
lie down... but the
cable man's coming over.
Sweetheart, I promise you,
I won't let anybody
put the moves on you, okay?
Oh, no, you don't
understand, Sammy.
It's not them,
it's me.
When the mercury hits 95,
I can't be responsible
for my actions.
Oh.
Oh!
Who is that hunk over there
in the uniform
with the cute buns?
Oh, my God, it's Clavin!
Oh, this is, this is
worse than I thought.
Has he always had
that mustache?
Iced coffee will
cool me down.
REBECCA:
Hey, you guys,
listen to this.
"Rumor has it that the reason
jillionaire jailbird
"Robin Colcord gave up his
fortune and freedom
"was a mystery femme.
But so far our little caged
Robin isn't singing."
Boy, that writer really paints
a picture, doesn't he?
You know, I can just picture
Mister Colcord sitting
on his little perch in a cage,
sharpening his beak
on a cuttlebone...
Woody. Woody.
Pecking away
at a little bell
made out
of sesame seeds.
Yeah!
Sam!
Rebecca, this is kind
of a rip-off, isn't it?
I mean, they don't even
mention your name.
And don't think
I'm not grateful.
What do you mean?
You could have been famous.
Yeah, s-someday
I would like to be famous,
but not because I'm involved
with a rich man.
I mean, I would
like to be known
for some real
achievement.
Oh, yeah. How's that cure
for leprosy coming along?
You know what I mean.
You know how the girlfriends
of rich millionaires
are treated by the press;
like cheap sluts.
You know, I think it stems
from the envy
that the public feels
towards people
who achieve a certain level
of notoriety.
Well, also the fact that most of
those women have posed nude
in popular men's magazines.
But, you know, frankly,
I wouldn't waste my money
on publications like that.
I mean, those letters
are not real.
I just hope the rag
magazines don't find out
that I am
the mystery woman.
Who am I kidding?
Those bloodhounds
will ferret me out
the first chance
they get.
But at least I have my dignity.
Well, I'm off to change
the blue stuff
in the toilet bowls.
(sighs)
What's the matter, Wood?
I don't get The Far Side.
Woody, come on.
Hand it over here.
Come on.
Let's have a look.
Okay, Wood, now you see
here in the first panel,
the cows are standing
on their hind legs, right?
The second panel,
when the car goes by,
they're acting like
normal cows.
See, the idea here is,
Wood, that, uh, you know,
cows only act like cows
when, when we're around.
Other times they act
like people.
Now does that,
does that help you
clear it up
a little bit for you?
I just meant
I don't get The Far Side
in my newspaper at home,
but thanks for treating me
like a one-year-old.
Oh, every time we turn on
Robert Vaughn's
Amazing Discoveries,
we always get
the hair-loss episode.
I mean, it's like they,
they never did any others.
Well, listen, we don't have
to watch an infomercial.
We can choose
from any of 60
wonderful cable
stations here.
At the very least it's....
Well, there's Lyle Waggoner
talking about impotence.
Oh, people trying to whiten
their yellow teeth.
Singing in the Rain.
Oh, how to buy real estate
with no money down.
Wait, wait, wait,
you just passed by
one of the all-time
classics, Frasier.
Put it back on
the yellow teeth one.
Wait, wait,
go back.
There was a picture
of Robin Colcord.
Sources have confirmed
the identity
of Colcord's mystery woman.
Oh, God! They found me out!
Colcord's secret lover
revealed herself
in a press conference today
to be Jeanne Marie Beaulier,
Charges d'Affaires
for the French Consulate.
Miss Beaulier...
Excuse me?
I thought Robin dumped
that French babe
for you weeks ago.
Well, he did!
The nerve of that
cheap slut pretending
like Robin turned
himself in for her!
Don't worry,
Rebecca.
Your friends know who
the real cheap slut is.
Thank you, Norm.
Well, Rebecca,
don't be upset.
I mean, she's actually
doing you a favor.
You're off the hook.
The press is going
to tear her apart
and leave your relationship
with Robin unsullied.
I guess you're right.
I mean, the only thing that
really does matter is that,
that I am Robin's true love.
And it actually
makes it more romantic
because we're
the only ones who know.
Yeah, except for us.
And I kind of told my mom
in Hanover.
You know what I mean.
It's sort of like
a secret valentine
between me and Robin.
And us.
And my mom.
Woody, who cares
if your mother knows?
I mean, who is she
going to tell?
Are you serious?
She has choir practice tonight.
Once she gets
a cup
of coffee in her,
those old biddies
will bleed it out of her.
For a moist crumb cake,
she'll tell anybody
why you never see
Uncle Willie and Aunt May
in the same room
at the same time.
Why, uh, why would
that be, Wood?
I don't see any crumb cake.
(phone ringing)
Cheers.
Oh, hi, Mom!
It's for me.
Oh, yeah, yeah, I saw the news,
but don't believe everything
you see on TV.
That French lady, Jeanne Marie,
was telling a big whopper.
It was really Miss Howe
who was having...
well, you know,
with Mister Colcord.
Oh, all right.
I'm sorry. I will.
Where're you
going, Wood?
I have to go wash
my mouth out with soap.
I'm sorry, Woody.
Yeah, well, maybe next time
you'll think about the
consequences of your actions.
REPORTER:
Looks like no end
to the heat wave is in sight.
Today may actually break
a hundred.
Oh, man!
I'd better get the crib out
of the garage.
Hi, everybody.
I brought doughnuts.
Oh!
Gee, I haven't dunked
a doughnut in years.
Wood, give me another beer,
will you?
Oh, hey, did you see
the Midnight Tattler?
What?
Seems that, uh,
Jeanne Marie
sold her love letters
from Robin.
Yeah? Whoo-ee!
Look at the legs
on this chick!!
Hey, hey, guys?
Guys, guys.
Rebecca's standing
right here.
Try and to be
a little more polite.
Oh, uh, I'm sorry.
Thank you very much
for the doughnuts,
Rebecca.
Look at the legs
on this babe!
Are they continued on
the next page or what?!
Don't bother, Sam.
I've seen the article.
It's just a stupid,
pitiable act
of a desperate woman.
Those letters
are not real.
They never are.
Robin did not type
those letters.
I have seen his typewriter.
He doesn't even use
that font.
(phone ringing)
Cheers.
Oh, hi, Mom.
It's for me.
Um, yeah, yeah,
I-I saw the article.
Miss Howe says
it's not even his font.
What?
No, Mom, font
isn't a bad word.
No, it's not...
All right. Okay.
Thanks a lot, Miss Howe.
CLIFF:
Hey, Sammy, how about
turning up the sound?
Don't you care
about any of this?
I mean, it's got to be
bothering you a little bit.
I wouldn't be human
if it didn't bother me
a little bit.
But, I mean, what does
it really amount to?
I have Robin's love
and she has a couple of blurbs
in a cheap tabloid.
And it's not like she's some
national celebrity.
ARSENIO HALL:
Join me tonight as the stage
sizzles with my guests
Michael Caine, M.C. Hammer
and the woman Robin Colcord
gave it up for,
and I mean really gave it up
for, Jeanne Marie Beaulieu.
Watch her kick it
on the next Arsenio Hall Show.
Hey!
I'm the one who should be
kickin' it!
Hey.
This is getting
very serious.
Thank you for your concern, Sam.
Do you have any idea how much
that TV costs?
What?
The corporation owns this bar
for three years,
you don't break anything.
I have it for three weeks,
you yank my television
off the wall.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that.
It's just that
I didn't expect
this thing with Jeanne
Marie to go this far.
Before, nobody even
took it seriously.
And all of a sudden she's
getting national attention.
Tonight she's going
to be on Arsenio.
Yeah, I know.
And thanks to you,
I can't watch it.
Why hasn't Robin spoken out?
I mean, why hasn't
he denied this?
What if... what if he really
does love Jeanne Marie?
What would I do?
Hey. I know.
What?
I'll get my landlady
to tape Arsenio.
No, Sam.
No, no, no, you're right,
you're right, you're right.
Then I'd be obligated.
Sam!
You're not listening to me.
Well, all right,
I'm listening. What?
I mean I cannot just ask him
if he loves Jeanne Marie
because then he will think
that I don't trust him.
You don't.
I know, but I should.
But if I ask him,
"Do you love Jeanne Marie?"
and he says "Yes," I don't think
that I could handle that.
And if I ask him if he loved me
and he said "Yes,"
then he would know
that I did not trust him.
And trusting him is the one
thing that I really should do
since he gave up
his fortune for me...
if he really did
give it up for me,
which I can never know
because I can't ask.
Let me see if I can
put this in a nutshell...
What?
Sam, would you ask him for me?
No. No, no. No, I don't
want to do that.
I've never been to prison.
Oh, well, it's not
really a real prison.
I...
No it's like a
minimum-security deal.
It's like summer camp,
only Robin has to spend
seven to ten summers there.
No, really, and when you,
when you see him,
don't tell him that
I told you to ask, okay?
I mean, just make it
sound like, you know,
you just dropped by
prison, you know,
it's just like a real
casual deal for you.
Uh, no.
No, Rebecca, I'm sorry.
Okay.
Forget it.
It's just that, um...
whenever I think
that Robin might love
Jeanne Marie, you know,
I just get so darned mad,
you know?
Just feel like I could just...
Okay. Okay.
I guess I can...
swing by the prison,
on my way to the billiards
supply store.
Carla, uh, watch the bar
for me, will you?
I've got to go down
to prison for a minute.
Prison?
Isn't that where they keep
all the bad, lonely men?
Now, come on, Carla.
Don't.
Oh, Sammy, take me
with you, please?
No.
Smuggle me in
in your pants.
No!
Please?
I need a tattooed man!
Please, Sammy.
Carla, no!
Ah, yeah, there he is.
Thanks very much.
Hey, Robin.
Robin. Hey.
Hey, Sam.
What are you doing here?
I, uh,
I need to talk to you
for a minute.
Oh, yeah, certainly.
Grab a racket.
Oh, well, all right.
Yes, I'd stop to talk, only...
I just get three hours
a week on the court.
Prison, you know.
Excuse me, Sam,
weren't you
a professional athlete?
Well, yeah, I was a pitcher
for the American League,
but I never actually
had to hit anything.
I see, so basically you just did
what this machine is doing.
Yeah, but my arm got tired.
So, Sam, what have you
got on your mind?
I want to talk to you
about your ex-girlfriend.
Can you be, uh, more specific?
The one you were running around
with behind Rebecca's back.
Can you be more specific?
Jeanne Marie.
Oh!
Oh, dear Jeanne Marie.
Yes, I do hope her little game
with the press
isn't troubling Rebecca.
Yeah, well...
Yeah, it is actually.
You know this girl
is running around
getting exploited
all over the place,
but we all know
that it's Rebecca
that deserves
to be exploited.
Hey, these things are coming
pretty fast.
Can we slow them down?
Oh no, if they went any slower
they wouldn't remain airborne.
Yeah, yeah, Sam, look,
if Rebecca is really
getting troubled by this,
why didn't she make
mention of it to me?
Well, I don't know,
actually.
She, uh, tried to explain
that to me, but I, uh...
Yes, enough said.
Poor Rebecca.
Her insecurities have finally
got the better of her.
Well, perhaps I should, uh,
make an end of Jeanne
Marie's little charade
and go to the press
and tell them the truth.
Do you think
that would help her?
Sure, yeah.
Say, is your arm sore?
What?
My arm's sore.
Right here.
Oh, yes.
Well, we can take
a break if you like.
All right.
Maurice!
Thanks, Maurice.
Whoo!
Hey, Robin.
Excuse me, are you through
with the court yet?
Yes, Sherman.
It's all yours.
Thanks.
Maurice!
Hey, I voted for that guy.
Okay, guys, we got it.
You know, I think
Rebecca did us a favor
by breaking that old TV.
Yeah, I like
this new TV
a lot better
than the old one.
We're not talking TV here.
This is the latest
in video technology.
We've got Dolby sound,
black matrix, high resolution.
I mean, look at that.
It's almost as if Deputy Dog's
right in the room with us.
Yeah.
My God.
It's another scorcher out there.
I am sick and tired
of peeling patients
off of my leather couch.
I'll tell you,
the ones in shorts
scream like banshees
when I get them up fast.
Well, fortunately,
I'm a trained psychiatrist
and I've learned to tune out
cries for help.
Say, where's Carla?
She asked us to lock her
in the office
until the heat wave breaks.
For goodness sakes.
I mean this has gone on
long enough.
The human female doesn't have
an estrous cycle.
Someone is gonna have to tell
her that the weather
cannot affect human beings
this way.
Carla! May I have a word
with you, please?
Oh!
How is she, Fras?
Be afraid.
Be very afraid.
Has anyone seen
an afternoon paper?
Uh, what are you
looking for?
Well, because
Robin's statement
about me being his true
love is supposed
to be in the late edition.
I sent Woody out
for it hours ago.
You, you sent Woody out there?
It's a hundred degrees.
I'm sorry, Miss Howe.
I would have been here sooner,
but I think I passed out between
the newsstand and here.
Woody, man,
are you all right?
Yes, he's all right.
I bet I'm on the cover.
Heat wave,
heat wave...
heat wave.
children in sprinklers,
heat wave...
So it's a little warm out.
Grandma?
Is that you, Grandma?
Thank you, Grandma.
Here it is.
"Millionaire Robin Colcord says
that his true love
is some Boston bar manager."
What?
That's it?!
I thought I was gonna
be big news.
Such is the transitory
nature of fame.
You have missed
your moment in the sun.
I had three hours in the sun.
Would somebody shut him up?
This just isn't fair.
Robin gave it up for me.
Me, not Jeanne Marie.
Well, hey,
I wouldn't worry so
much about Jeanne Marie.
She's washed
up, too.
Look where they put her
on Hollywood Squares.
Center bottom.
Nobody's gonna
call on her there.
She might as well
be a Gabor.
MAN:
I'll take Robin Colcord's
lover to block.
No, no, whoa, whoa!
Come on, guys,
switch the channel.
Put a game on or something.
I'm trying, Sammy.
How do you work
this damned remote?
Oh, wait, you need this
one to work that one.
Damn!
Relax. Relax.
No, it was my turn, Sam!
Everybody in the world was
supposed to know that...
that I was Robin's
mystery femme.
I was supposed to be famous.
You know, that's not
what you said before.
You said the only thing
that mattered
was that Robin loves you.
Yeah, yeah, well...
that was back when
I thought Jeanne Marie
was gonna be laughed at.
But now, I didn't know
that she was gonna become
America's little sweetheart
and I was gonna become
America's little
stupid idiot nobody.
Honey, listen, from the
outside, fame looks great.
But when you actually
have it, it's not,
it's not all that
it's cracked up to be.
Oh, how would you know?
Well, I had a little bit
of fame, once upon a time.
Oh, yeah, right, that time you
almost got hit by that truck.
No.
No, no, no, come on.
When I was pitching
for the Sox.
Yeah, sure,
fame has its perks.
I mean, you don't have to stand
in line at restaurants.
That's very nice.
And cops let you slide
on a few traffic tickets.
That's... that's very nice.
Autographs, I mean, that's cool
and all of that.
But, basically,
it's just a hassle.
Really?
Yeah, sure.
Not being famous
is ten times better.
Really?
Yeah.
Yeah, you get treated
just like everybody else.
You can go to the
supermarket in peace.
Nobody crowds around you.
As a matter of fact,
they don't pay any
attention to you at all.
No, they certainly don't
let you cut ahead of them
in the ten-items-or-less line.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You have to wait behind
all the old ladies.
Some of them have
way beyond ten items.
'Cause believe me, you've got
all the time in the world
to count every little can,
every little loaf of bread.
Sam...
By the time you get to the front
of the line,
they're only too happy
to cut up your credit cards
right in front of your face
because you're nothing!
Sam...
Sam, are you all right?
I miss it so much, Rebecca.
Oh...
I know you do.
But we're both better
off without it, Sam.
Do you remember, remember
all the attention I got
when that truck almost hit me?
Well, there's no break
in this heat wave.
As a matter of fact, tomorrow
is going to be even hotter.
Let's look now
at the satellite...
(rumbling)
Oh, my God!
Clear out, everybody!
She's gonna blow!
(rumbling)
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org