Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Hi, everybody.
ALL:
Hey.
Hey, Sam.
Where is Rebecca?
In her office. Why?
Ah, today's the day a certain
chestnut brown-haired beauty
is gonna succumb to
the charms of Sammy.
( laughing )
Laugh if you will, but according
to my calculations,
the timing is perfect.
I waited long enough for her
to get over Evan Drake,
but not long enough for her
to build up
her resistance again.
The way I see it,
I got about a half-hour
window of opportunity
opening up here.
I'm telling you, boys,
Rebecca Howe is mine.
( men encouraging )
Sammy! Sammy! Sammy!
( mimicking trumpet )
Yes?
Ooh, he's got her saying,
"yes," already, ooh!
Not a devout
nun's prayer.
No, sir.
( piano plays )
¶ Making your way
in the world today ¶
¶ Takes everything you've got
¶ Taking a break
from all your worries ¶
¶ Sure would help a lot
¶ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ¶
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You want to be where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ You want to go
where people know ¶
¶ People are all the same
¶ You want to go where everybody
knows your name. ¶
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
So what you got there?
A Mercedes catalog.
Oh.
I'm thinking
of getting one.
Yeah, I hear good things
about those Cadillacs.
What, you got a raise
or something?
No.
I can only afford
the cheapest model,
and I have to give up lunches
until I...
Well, I have to give up lunches.
But it will still be a Mercedes.
Speaking of Mercedes.
I'm kind of known
as the Mercedes of guys.
Really?
I always thought you were
more of a cheap pickup
with a headlight missing.
Did you want
something, Sam?
Rebecca...
how long have we
known each other?
No, I will not
go out with you.
Hey, what...
what makes you think that
I was gonna ask you for a date?
You must really think
you look hot tonight.
Then why did you come in here?
Well, I was, uh...
gonna compliment you
on your blouse.
That's a very pretty blouse.
Well, we haven't seen each
other today until now.
How did you know I'd
be wearing this one?
I was hoping
you were gonna wear it.
It's always been
my favorite blouse.
It's brand-new; it's
the first time I've worn it.
I'm working part-time
in department store security.
I was in the store
when you bought it.
I bought it mail order.
I drove the truck
that delivered it to your house.
One date-- come on, please?
What, is this gonna kill you?
Men. You're all alike.
Nothing but users, and takers,
and big, stupid jerks,
who don't even know you exist
and then go running off to Japan
with someone else.
That is such a cliché.
Come on, please.
Forget it.
I'm concentrating on my career.
I happen to think I
have a real future
with this company.
No offense, but... why?
Because I think it's my time.
You know, Evan took a lot
of key people with him to Japan.
And the way I figure it,
everyone who knows
I'm a washout is gone.
Ooh.
Talk about sitting pretty.
You bet.
You know, the new executive
vice president, Mr. Stone
has been doing
a little housecleaning
at the corporate level.
From where I am,
it could be just a
short climb to the top.
Yeah, speaking of climbing
to the top,
the way I see it,
you haven't had a date
with a guy
for about two and half years.
Now, I think this date of ours
could be good for me,
but, sweetheart, I got to say,
it's looking real necessary
for you.
Sam, no.
We're starting to
become good friends.
Now, why wreck that?
Why not...
Friends tell friends who they
think they ought to go out with,
and as a friend,
I'm telling you,
you ought to give
this Malone guy a chance.
( choking back words )
( sighing )
All right.
What?
I'll go out with you.
That is great.
That's great, all right.
Um, I'll pick you up...
But just, uh, for future
reference here,
uh, what did I do right
this time?
It's just that
since Evan went away,
my expectations are low.
And with my stove on the blink
and nothing on the tube tonight,
I figured... why not?
Thanks.
Yeah, I'll have
to remember that.
8:00?
Okay.
Oh, a-and let's just keep this
between us.
I don't want
those bozos out there
turning this into a circus.
No, no.
I couldn't agree with you more.
( people yelling )
Lucky guess.
CARLA:
Whoa, yo-ho,
check it out.
( patrons whooping )
Sammy, you might as well
make that entry in
your diary right now
because no mortal woman
can resist this package.
No, no, we're
just having dinner.
Uh-ho!
NORM:
Oh, right, yeah.
Columbus was just going on
a little boat ride, huh?
Oh, it turns out
that's true, Norm.
He told the missus he was just
stepping out for lunch,
and, uh, took a left
instead of a right
at the Isle of, uh, Langerhans,
and before you know it,
uh, he's trading trinkets
for Miami Beach.
Cliff, you should write a book.
( laughing ):
Why, thank you, Carla.
No, I mean right now.
( laughs )
I mean it.
Look, here's a pencil
and some paper.
Go on in the back room,
and don't come out
until you have 60,000 words.
Go on.
REBECCA:
I'll be
right there.
Ah, look at that.
That really takes me back,
you know?
I remember my first date
with Vera--
the flowers, the candy,
the wine.
Sounds pretty romantic, Norm.
Yeah, it was.
You know, in retrospect,
I suppose I should have gotten
her something, but, uh...
I guess you can't
turn back that clock, can you?
( door opens )
Ah.
There you go.
I just, uh,
brought these in
so they could see what a real
long-stem beauty looks like.
( chuckles ):
Thank you, Sam.
Ah. Shall we go?
It's just dinner.
Yeah, dinner,
right, absolutely.
Uh, good night, fellas.
Uh, don't wait up for us.
( men whooping )
( gasps )
My God, it's him.
SAM:
Who's him?
It's him, Greg Stone,
the new exec VP.
I saw his picture in
the company newsletter.
Mr. Stone!
Welcome, welcome.
It's such an honor
to have you here.
Mr. Stone,
I'd like you to meet
Sam Malone.
Yeah, hi.
Pleased to meet you, Sam.
Yeah.
Who are you?
Rebecca Howe.
I'm the manager.
Ah, of course.
I'd like to use your
phone if I may.
You can do anything
you want with my phone.
Thank you...
For the moment,
I thought I'd just
speak into it.
Good choice.
Okay, come on.
Let's go.
Sweetheart,
we're gonna be late. Let's...
He could very well be
the most handsome man
I have ever seen.
( patrons groaning )
And did you see the way
he looked in my eyes
when he said,
"Who are you?"
I think he
really likes me.
We all do, honey.
Now, let's go.
No, Sam, you don't
understand.
He's the man I've been
giving my accounts to
the last couple weeks.
I think he could be
my ticket to corporate.
( door opens )
Miss Howe, I'd like to see you
in my office
tomorrow morning at 9:00.
Mm-hmm.
What'd I tell you?
What did I tell you?
Yeah, that's great.
Now, let's go celebrate,
all right?
Oh, excuse me,
excuse me, sir!
Listen, as long as you were
gonna tell me anyway,
why don't you just go
ahead and tell me now?
This is not the time
or the place.
Oh, please tell me.
You've been going
over my files?
Yes, I have.
And we're doing better?
Yes, we're doing better.
Well, then what's
the problem?
Just go ahead and tell me.
I really think we should
discuss this privately.
Pal, just between
us guys here,
do me a favor and tell her.
It'd kind of help
grease the old skids.
I really don't think.
Sir, excuse me, please?
Please?
Very well, Ms. Howe,
if you insist.
This, uh, quarter has shown
a slight improvement.
Did you hear that,
everybody?
"A slight improvement."
STONE:
But the records show,
unequivocally,
that the bar did better
under Sam's direction
than yours.
In view of this,
I'm hereby appointing Sam
the new manager.
And I regret to say
I'm forced to give you notice.
I'm sorry.
Okay, boys, dessert.
Well, what do you say we go
strap on the ol' feedbag, huh?
You coming?
Uh...
you guys want to help me
get her into the car?
I'll get the door.
This is gonna be a lot easier
than I thought.
Two Amstel Lights.
I don't know, Carla.
Either managing a bar is getting
a lot more complicated,
or I'm getting a lot dumber.
You couldn't be getting
any dumber, Sam.
Well, it must be
that other thing.
You know, having
you back in charge
really reminds me of
old times, you know?
I mean, real old times.
Even before the evil days,
when darkness
fell over the earth.
She means when
Diane was still here.
I know precisely
what she means.
( phone rings )
Cheers.
Sam, it's Mr. Stone for you.
Uh, put him on hold there,
Woody.
Damn, I'll bet
he wants those figures.
Hello, Woody.
Miss Howe?
Woody, where's Sam?
In his off...
Oh, I mean, in your...
In your...
I-I haven't seen him.
Hello.
Love your hairdo.
( knocking )
It's open.
( sobbing )
Sweetheart,
what happened?
I just had to knock
on my own office door.
Honey, I-I'm so sorry.
I swear to God
I didn't want
this to happen.
I know.
It's not your fault.
I know why it happened.
Because I'm a loser.
I always have been,
and I always will be
a big old, fat, old,
stupid loser.
No, you're not a loser.
Don't say that,
you hear me?
You are not a loser.
Okay.
You have a barrette
for this, or something?
I lost it.
Sweetheart,
don't worry about...
don't worry about that.
It'll be all right.
Hey, you know what might
make you feel better?
We never had that
date, you know?
Oh, God!
You just go
back over there
and do whatever it
was you were doing,
and I will get out
of your life forever.
Rebecca, I...
Sam, please.
It'll make it a lot easier.
You know,
I might just become a bag lady.
They're not all old, you know.
It could happen.
It really could.
I'll just send
for the rest of my things.
No, Rebecca,
wait a sec.
Honey, listen.
Sam, Stone
is still on hold.
He needs those figures
on the double.
( groaning )
( computer beeps )
Well, what the hell is that?
I'm no computer expert,
but it looks like Donkey Kong.
Oh, man, that,
that stinks.
You know, I, I...
It's not like it used to
be around here, Carla.
I mean corporations,
computers, reports.
I mean, I used to keep
track of inventory
in a spiral notebook,
for God's sake.
No, you didn't.
Well, I always meant to.
You know, I-I just
hate being in charge.
I'm not good at it.
Rebecca wasn't good at it
either,
but at least she enjoyed it.
You know,
I'm going to go back to Stone,
and I'm going to beg him
to give her this job back.
No, wait a minute.
You're quitting
because of this machine?
Carla, I hate that machine.
John Henry hated a machine, too.
Do you know the story
of John Henry, Sam?
He went toe to toe with a
steel-driving machine,
and he refused to admit
that that machine
was better than him.
And do you know what happened?
Yeah, the machine
beat him.
His heart exploded;
he died.
He did?
Yes.
Well, go get her job back
before you lose your ticker.
Go on.
Whoa, how'd it go?
Oh, Woody, Woody, give me
a seltzer there, will you?
Mr. Stone is dead set
against rehiring her,
and I hate to beg
when sex isn't involved.
So, what happened?
Well, I had to promise
that she'd agree
to a whole list
of conditions,
but he finally said yes.
I left a message
on her answering machine
that I wanted to talk to her.
What are you
going to tell her?
I'm going to tell her
to take her stupid job back.
I don't want it anymore.
Wait a minute, Sam.
Aren't you missing
something here?
What?
You desperately want to jump
this woman's bones, right?
Sure.
And you've just arranged
something for her
that she wants more than
anything else in the world.
So?
Don't you see a connection
between those two things?
Breaks your heart,
doesn't it?
You tell Rebecca
that you loved
being the manager,
but you couldn't
stand to see her
being so miserable,
so you got her
her job back.
Next thing you know,
she'll be doing
the backstroke on
your water bed.
Carla, I'm shocked.
Why, 'cause you didn't
think of it first?
Yeah. I mean,
I must be losing it.
Woody, uh,
call Melville's.
Tell them I want an 8:00
reservation for two.
Oh, and tell them
that I want
booth number five,
chill their best champagne,
yeah, and order
a chocolate soufflé for dessert.
Aw, gee, Sam, that sounds good,
but actually,
I brought my dinner.
Woody...
make the reservation.
All right, but this is a waste
of a perfectly good
meatball sandwich.
Thank you.
Sam, I can't thank you enough
for getting my job back.
I finally feel good
about myself again.
You know, the first thing I did
when I got home
was I-I put in an order
for that Mercedes.
Ah, well, I think
you'll look great
wearing one of those.
So...
you having a good time?
Yeah, I actually am.
Well, you don't have to sound
so surprised.
Oh, I'm sorry;
I didn't mean it like that.
( sighing ):
It's just that...
with all your obnoxious
come-ons, and everything,
I never expected you to be as...
as charming
as you've been tonight.
No kidding.
So, what do you find
charming about me?
Well, for one thing,
I find it charming
that you would try to impress me
by ordering an elegant soufflé,
when I know perfectly well
that your favorite dessert
is frozen Snicker bars.
Actually, they're
in the bottom
of your champagne
bucket there.
( chuckling )
Oh, I think I was
just charming again
there, wasn't I?
I don't get it.
Just when I thought
I had you pegged,
you go out and do something
like you did today.
Sam,
that really was the nicest thing
that anyone
has ever done for me.
Well, you deserve to have
nice things done for you.
You're a very nice person.
So are you.
Sam?
Yeah?
Is that your hand on my leg?
Oh, I'll be darned.
My left hand does seem to
be missing, doesn't it?
Do you want me to move it?
Yes.
That's not what I meant.
Oh, thank you, God.
Ah! Mr. Stone! Hi!
What a surprise!
Oh, good evening.
I wonder if we
could have the
table over there?
Mr. Stone,
I'm not the hostess.
I'm Rebecca Howe,
from downstairs.
Ah, yeah, of
course you are.
Miss Howe.
I guess I ought to
say welcome back.
I was a little surprised
you agreed to the
conditions, but if you
can live with
them, so can we.
Ah, here's
the maitre d'.
I wonder if I could
have that table
in the other room?
Nice to see
you again.
What was he
talking about?
What conditions?
You want some
more champagne?
Sam, what conditions?
Well, they were
so insignificant,
they really
slipped my mind.
Uh, all right, uh.
Well, uh...
You have to take
a... slight pay cut
and go back to school
for your MBA
and share the
office with me,
consult with me on
all major decisions,
and since you lack any
practical experience,
you'll have to
wait tables when
the bar is busy,
which will put you
under the immediate
supervision of Carla.
Any wonder it
slipped my mind?
Sam, uh, when were you planning
on telling me this?
After.
After what?
Afterwards.
All right, um.
I'm sorry, I should
have told you, but...
I just thought that
you'd been going through
such a tough time
that you deserved
at least one night
of feeling good
about yourself.
All right, I'll
call you a cab.
No, no, no.
It's okay.
The important thing
is that I have my job back.
You're not upset
about this?
No, how can I be upset
when I have so much
to be thankful for?
Now... where were we?
Does this look familiar?
Sam?
Yeah?
I want tonight
to be very special.
Mmm.
And I think I can figure
a way out for us to do that.
You see, I have this fantasy...
and it's something
that I've always wanted to try,
but I didn't ever think
that I'd get to do it
until tonight.
Would you like to know
what it is?
Yes, please.
Okay.
Well, you see,
I have this hot tub at home.
I love the way this begins.
And what we do
when we get there...
First?
Uh-huh.
And then...
Oh, God.
Oh, please.
A-a-a-and this is the part
that's just
a little tiny bit illegal.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, I don't think
that I should tell you.
I really think it would
be better if I showed you.
Come with me now,
so we don't spoil the mood.
Could you just give me a minute?
No.
Bye-bye, Sam.
Can I get you anything
else, Mr. Malone?
No, thank you, Paul.
Actually, Paul,
could I have another one
of your chocolate soufflés?
Are you aware
that will take 45 minutes?
Yes, Paul, I am.
Woody,
Sam's going
to be upstairs for a while.
When he comes down,
give him this message.
You tell him that it will be
a cold day in hell
before I ever share an office
with him,
or schlep drinks
in a two-bit saloon.
Oh, Miss Howe?
By the way, Midtown
Mercedes called,
and they said you can
pick up your car anytime.
Oh, and they got the one
you wanted-- the red one.
The red one?
Hi, there.
My name's Rebecca...
( voice breaking ):
and it will be my pleasure
to serve you.
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4yyc
Help other users to choose the best subtitles