Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Hey, what're you doing there, Norm?
Oh, Vera signed me up to give a speech
at her Women's Auxiliary Club.
(laughs)
I hate public speaking.
Yeah, you're not alone there, pal.
Well, it's awful, you know.
You're standing there
in front of a group
of total strangers...
palms sweating, your throat dry,
your mouth feels like
it's full of cotton.
your knees practically buckling.
It can be a miserable
experience. I tell you.
So what's the topic?
"Poise: The Key to Success."
(piano plays)
♪ Making your way in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like to get away♪ ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always glad you came ♪
♪ You want to be where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You want to go where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Thanks, Mom. Yeah, don't worry about it.
I'll find somebody to sit for the kids.
Bye.
She can't do it?
She's scared to.
Oh, yeah, I'll, uh, watch
the kids for you, Carla.
It's not fair. This always happens to me
when I have a date on a weeknight.
Oh, who's the lucky guy?
My butcher.
Oh, yeah? What happened to Eddie?
Eddie's in Vancouver.
My butcher's three blocks down.
Life is short.
I wouldn't mind, uh, looking
after your kids for you, Carla.
What am I gonna do now?
Well, I'd do it, but
I'm working on Wednesday.
Yeah.
Yeah, Vera and I would love to,
but, uh, we have this
thing Wednesday night.
Yeah, uh, Diane and I
have a thing, too. Yeah.
Maybe it's the same thing.
I don't think so. Probably not.
CLIFF: Oh, I'm, uh,
I'm not busy Wednesday.
Well, guess I'm gonna
have to cancel my date.
Well, is this a day to press
in your memory books or what?
Well, you guys sound pretty chipper.
Shall I tell them, Lilith?
Out with it, or I'm liable
to burst with anticipation.
(laughs)
Doctors Sternin and Crane
are proud to announce
that they are now officially POSSLQ's.
(Frasier chuckles)
It means "Persons of the Opposite
Sex Sharing Living Quarters."
Yes.
Oh.
You see, it's a little, uh,
lovers' in-joke we picked up
from a Census Bureau acronym.
Oh, I love those.
Well, man, hey, that's great.
Congratulations. Yes, yes.
Thank you.
But this is... quite a surprise.
You've only known each
other a few months,
and you're moving in together?
That's pretty impetuous.
Well, a week ago, we decided to
take a chance on cohabitation,
but we waited a week
before announcing the news,
so as to avoid
putting any undue pressure
on the success or
failure of the endeavor.
And now we are pleased
to announce the effort
a limited success.
Yes, pretty darn impetuous.
Well, we thought that the two of you
were responsible for Lilith and I
finding each other in
this cockeyed world,
so, we, uh, we thought
we'd like to have you
over for dinner on Wednesday
night as our very first guests.
Aw. Why, we'd be honored.
Yeah, I'll be there.
Great. We'll get away
from the hurly-burly of this place
and concentrate completely on
the lost art of conversation.
Hmm. I'll be there anyway.
All right,
Wednesday night it is
then. Oh, uh, shall we say,
oh, uh, what...
8:00-ish?
Wonderful.
You don't know how happy this makes me.
So, you and Diane have this
thing Wednesday night, huh?
Well, why don't you
just come out and say it?
You don't want to spend an
evening alone with my kids.
BOTH: We don't want to spend
an evening alone with your kids.
Neither do I.
But what choice do I have?
Well... Carla,
I think Cliff might be
interested in watching them.
Hey, hey,
what are you doing Wednesday night?
Pumping iron.
Okay, Cliff, you're up.
Be at my house Wednesday at 6:00.
But remember, you asked for it.
(chuckles)
Here, come here. Here...
obviously, she doesn't think
that I can handle the kids, huh?
Yeah, but my guess is that,
uh, they'll settle down once
they're confronted with a
strong male authority figure.
Are you bringing your mom?
I'm home, sweet potato.
Just a moment, cinnamon bear.
How was your day?
Oh, I want to take you now, by the dip.
You impulsive man.
We have guests coming.
Yes, I know.
It'll be our little joke on them.
Every time they say the word "dip,"
we'll become giddy with remembrance.
The word itself will
become a syllable filled
with our overwhelming passion.
Dear, you're using sex
to express your aggression
toward the confines of polite society.
Dip.
I love that.
What is that heavenly aroma
coming from the kitchen?
Dinner.
Oh, yes, of course, dinner.
Well, I'm sorry I'm
late, by the way. I got...
No explanation is necessary.
I know you far too well
to have expected you
to be on time tonight.
Oh, right.
Why is that?
Because I've learned that
a certain self-centered insensitivity
is a fundamental part of
your psychological makeup.
And it only endears you to me.
I'm so glad you shared that with me.
Of course you can't
know everything about me.
I mean, who would have thought
that I'd enjoy living with you,
but here we are.
You didn't expect to
enjoy living with me?
Well, you do have a...
uncompromising quality.
Mm.
A very attractive one it is, though.
Well, if you were hesitant, why do it?
That's the way you
arranged it, isn't it?
It was your idea.
Ah, yes, well,
you see, you're forgetting the, uh,
passive-aggressive trick you
have of leading someone else
into doing something
that you want to do,
thereby absolving yourself
of responsibility.
And very adorable it is,
too, my little parsnip.
Why do you insist on
displaying your magazines
in that insipid accordion design?
I'm sorry if this one little
touch of theatrical flair
is too much for your retentive nature.
We'll go into my retentive nature later.
For now, we have guests coming.
You know, I see what
you're trying to do here.
You want me to begin the
argument that you wish
you could start yourself.
Well, I will not do it.
If you want to have an
altercation, you will have to...
How could you be late
on a night like this?!
Didn't you know I'd be
nervous making my first dinner
in your house while your
stupid friends are looking at me
and judging my every move?
I'll never forgive you for this!
Never, never, never, never!
(doorbell chimes)
Just a minute!
Darling, I think that
was a real breakthrough.
So come out of the
bathroom, and after dinner,
we'll build on it.
But, our-our guests are here now.
Dear heart?
(doorbell chimes)
Darling.
Coming! Coming!
Hi! Come in, come in!
I hope we're not early.
Oh, no, no, no, your
timing is just perfect.
Oh.
Boy, am I hungry.
Sam.
Well, I am.
So, where's your lovely POSSLQ?
Oh, she's around somewhere.
Peach blossom?
Don't make yourself too beautiful.
I can hardly stand to look at you now.
(softly): Come on...
please come out, darling.
Please.
(louder): What was that?
Oh, uh...
got something stuck in her contact lens.
Oh, I hate that. Yeah.
Li-Listen, here, come sit down, relax.
Uh, pour yourself some wine, whatever.
Just, uh, make yourselves comfortable.
Oh, oh, Diane, could you hand
me that cheese knife, please?
Thank you.
Uh, enjoy. I'll be right back.
(lock rattling)
FRASIER: What do you
think you're doing?!
LILITH: Might I have a little privacy?
FRASIER: We can resolve all this later,
but for now, these people may
be my friends, but they are not
the greatest
conversationalists in the world,
and I could use your help.
Good chips.
Lilith. Ah.
Welcome to our home.
I am so happy for the both of you.
Yeah, absolutely. Congratulations.
Yeah, that's great.
(loud crunch)
Love what you've done
with this place, man.
DIANE: Oh, yes, I love
the masculine touches.
Thank you.
Say, that, uh, that dip looks good.
DIANE: Mmm.
Dip?
Yeah, the, uh, the dip.
Could you, uh, pass it, please?
(chuckling): Yes, of course.
Be my guest. Here you are.
Oh, thank you.
Oh...
Oh, yeah, that is great dip.
Mmm, here. Yeah, try it.
DIANE: Mmm, delicious, Lilith.
Frasier, have you tried
some of Lilith's dip?
Yes, I-I have, yes.
Well, then I don't have
to tell you how good it is.
DIANE: Mmm.
It's quite good.
Well, I don't mean to hog it here.
Uh, you guys look hungry.
He-Help yourself.
So, Frasier,
was it good for you, too?
What the hell's in this dip?
Well...
may I propose a toast?
Mmm!
To your house.
Our house.
Hear, hear.
Yes. (Frasier laughs)
(playing piano) ? Our house ?
Oh, I love that.
♪ Is a very, very, very fine house ♪
♪ With two cats in the yard ♪
♪ Life used to be so hard ♪
♪ Now everything is easy 'cause of you ♪
♪ And our... ♪
♪ Our house ♪
(Diane singing along): ? Is a
very, very, very fine house ?
♪ With two cats in the yard ♪
(singing alone): ? Life
used to be so hard ?
? Now... ? Et cetera, et cetera.
You know what I love
about your relationship?
No.
You never seem to have
an unexpressed thought.
I've noticed that.
How do you maintain
that level of honesty?
Well, it's simple.
Frasier and I keep no
secrets from each other.
Oh, come on.
You don't mean to tell me
you tell each other everything.
Certainly. Exactly.
We've bared our souls to each other.
Oh, now no guy's going to
tell his brand-new girlfriend
about all the women he...
You know.
Oh, but there must be
no secrets in that area.
That's where honesty counts most.
Gee, you know, I-I'm afraid
I don't think that's such a good idea.
You mean the two of
you, planning marriage,
haven't already had this discussion?
Of course we have.
Well, Diane's told
us about both of hers,
and we're just about up to the
Johnson Administration on mine.
Uh, seriously, though, um,
I-I think that we're all
entitled to our little secrets.
Why?
They only lead to embarrassment
when they're inevitably revealed.
Exactly.
I know I feel better
knowing that Frasier has told you
he and I were once engaged,
so I don't have to worry
about you discovering it
at some inopportune moment.
Like now, for instance.
Dear...
dear, I thought I told you
that Diane and I used to date.
LILITH: Date, yes.
That you had decided to marry
and spend the rest of
your life with her, no.
Semantics.
And why were you afraid
to tell me that one detail?
Because she still means
something to you, doesn't she?
She means absolutely nothing to me.
I mean, if I notice her at all,
it's merely as an annoyance,
like a bug flying around in a room.
FRASIER: Diane, Diane, be a dear.
Would you grab me the
cheese knife, please?
Frasier,
I'm sorry this happened,
but I think it would
be best for everyone
if you told her the truth.
Diane's right.
All right, all right.
Darling, I'm going to tell you
the whole truth.
(latch rattling)
Out with it.
All right, uh,
Diane and I were engaged
to be married and...
she left me at the altar.
The whole experience
was so... humiliating,
I-I-I've just been trying
to forget it ever since.
Your feelings for her were genuine?
Yes.
And it's only on account of her action
that you're not married to her
at this very moment?
Well, I-I never really
looked at it that way.
And if Sam were out of the picture,
you'd throw me over and run
back to her, wouldn't you?
I don't love her anymore.
You switch your passions
on and off very quickly, Dr. Crane.
I do not!
Then you do still love her!
Well, I never did!
You were going to marry her!
Well, maybe I just thought I loved her!
How do I know you don't
just think you love me?
Well, I don't.
I mean, I-I
didn't... I-I never...
I will not be grilled
like a common criminal!
Cheese knife?
All right, thank you very much. Bye.
Ordering another round for
the corner table, honey.
All right, Corinne.
Now listen, uh, thanks a lot
for subbin' on such short notice.
Hey, this is my life.
It shouldn't, uh, it
shouldn't be so bad.
You know, it's not really
very crowded tonight.
That's what you said the last time.
When I got home,
my can was dragging
this far off the ground.
Thanks for sharing
that with us, Corinne.
Well, that was Carla's daughter.
She said that, uh, the kids
are going to drop off Mr. Clavin.
All right. All right.
I don't think her kids
are old enough to drive.
(tires screeching)
What was that?
(pained grunting)
(tires screeching, car speeding away)
Cliff! Cliff!
Cliff, Cliff buddy, are you all right?
(Cliff mumbling)
Wait, there's a note.
(muffled shouting)
"Don't open until Christmas."
Aw, shoot.
(muffled shouting)
DIANE: Now look here,
Lilith, you needn't worry
about Frasier carrying a torch for me.
I assure you
he feels nothing but
resentment toward me.
He knows I was using him
to forget the real
love I felt, and feel,
for Sam here.
Is there any more Chex Mix?
You see, Sam is my real love.
I'm ashamed to say that Frasier
was a convenient dalliance on my part,
at a time when I needed someone,
anyone.
I'm sorry it was him.
So, essentially, Frasier was a toy
you played with briefly
and then threw away.
Well, it wasn't that bad.
A fellow human being,
whose emotions you twisted
for your own satisfaction,
with no consideration for his feelings.
Frasier had some fun.
We would speak nothing
but French on Sundays.
I heard it all.
How could I have been so blind?
Don't blame yourself.
That's right.
You can't blame anyone
in these situations.
He can blame you.
Now look here.
Our relationship was a two-way street.
Yes, and I was run
over in both directions.
Oh, Frasier, you had fun.
Diane, I never had a whit of fun,
especially on Sundays.
And the only thing more egregious
than your French
pronunciation is your syntax.
(door closes)
(bell rings)
Dinner, everyone. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, wait, wait.
Come on, this whole thing
has gone on too far here.
Hey, listen up.
This is what happens
when you open old wounds.
I mean, I don't know
what happened between Frasier and Diane,
but it seems to me
they had a little fun,
but they just weren't
right for each other.
But now that they've found somebody
that, uh, is right for them,
I-I think you both should
be happy for each other.
And leave it at that.
(door opens)
Oh.
Je regrette, mes amis.
I'm sorry, too, Diane.
I don't know what came over me.
Diane, can you forgive me?
Oh, I'm the one who's sorry.
And happy for both of you.
Thank you.
And thank you, Sam.
Yes. Mmm, well, I just
thought it went on long enough.
Besides, I-I have to
use the bathroom here.
Would anyone like some more lasagna?
DIANE: No, thank you.
I think we've had our fill.
Fine, then I'll just get the coffee.
Lasagna?
I wasn't even thinking Italian.
Well, I was closest.
I said something with meat.
LILITH: That will be all then, Jill.
You can come by and
clean up in the morning.
JILL: Thank you, Dr. Sternin.
You mean you had someone back there
helping you with this?
With the side dishes, yes.
But at the risk of sounding immodest,
I have to take credit
for the lasagna myself.
Oh, well.
DIANE: Well, bravo.
Well, shall we adjourn
to the living room
for some coffee?
DIANE: Nice.
Oh, may I propose another toast?
Why stop at seven? Hah.
Well,
we have all learned a
valuable lesson this evening.
We shouldn't be frightened of the past,
or of any affairs
our lovers have had. Indeed,
we should be grateful
for those past experiences
because they've made him or her
the person we love today.
Hear, hear.
Well said.
Oh, hey, let me, uh, fill some
of these wine glasses here.
Good night, Dr. Sternin.
LILITH: Good night.
Oh, Sam Malone!
Oh, you beautiful man!
JILL: Where have you
been keeping yourself?
Hey, Jill, how the hell you been, huh?
Great, just great.
Well, you still doing massage?
Just the way you like 'em.
Who is this, Sam?
Uh, you know, it's gettin' kinda late.
Maybe you oughta take off.
Bye-bye.
Huh!
Why is it
that we cannot go to one,
single, solitary place
in the entire city of Boston
without running into some woman
that you've had a fling with?
Oh, come on, you're exaggerating here.
Mm-hmm. At the market, at the movies,
when we got our blood
test, for heaven's sake.
Well, what're we supposed to do, move?
I mean, come on.
Excuse me.
Oh, now, don't, no, don't-don't go...
What-what're you so upset about?
I wasn't even dating you
when I went out with Jill.
That's when you were
living with Frasier.
She lived with you?
Well, only briefly. Uh...
You said you'd never
lived with anyone but me!
Yeah, open... that's right.
What are you doing?
I should have thought of this earlier.
(chuckling)
Yeah. (chuckles)
LILITH: What was that?
Frasier, what are you doing?
(door rattling)
Frasier, the door seems to be jammed.
(knocking on door) Frasier?
DIANE: Sam, open the door.
Macanudo?
Oh!
Frasier! Don't mind if I do.
Thank you. Open the door.
You know, I don't think I can stand
this caterwauling in here.
Why don't we go upstairs.
(knocking on door)
I've got all 13 episodes
of I, Claudius on tape.
Great. Man, I love gladiator flicks.
(pounding on door)
LILITH: Frasier, we are not amused!