Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Hey, Cliffy.
Oh, hey, Sam.
What are you doing
standing out in the rain?
Uh, it's good for the skin.
You know, negative ions.
Keeps it soft.
What'd you say
to Carla, Cliffy.
Called her a dwarf.
Oh.
Could you, uh, untie me, Sam?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks. Oh, whoa, whoa, wait
a second, wait a second.
How much more time
you got out here?
Uh, five minutes.
I'm sorry, buddy,
I can't do it.
She'd have me standing
right out here next to you.
I understand, Sam,
I understand.
No hard feelings.
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Attention, everybody,
I have an announcement to make.
Thanksgiving is in a few days,
and I know that some of you
will not be able to spend it
with your families.
So, anybody who doesn't have
any place to go on Thanksgiving
is welcome to come
to my apartment.
I thought that would
be a nice gesture.
How'd you like to see
another nice gesture?
Carla Tortelli
graciously accepts.
How about you, Sam?
Yeah. I think it'd be fun
to go to Thanksgiving dinner
at your place.
Oh, great.
You know, I really think I can
put together a great
Thanksgiving dinner.
This'll be the second
one that I've cooked.
And believe me, the first one
was not the disaster that
my family said it was.
Those kids had a pretty
good time in that ambulance.
It was kind of
exciting for them.
I mean, at least it wasn't
the same old same old.
Oh, wait a second.
Did you say Thanksgiving?
Aw, shoot.
See, I usually spend
Thanksgiving
with my old Army buddies.
Sam, you weren't in the Army.
No, no, but, uh,
my buddies were.
You know, I-I'd invite
you all over to my place,
but Ma's down in Florida
working on her tan.
Yeah, she's got this
standing rule that, uh,
when she's not around,
I'm not allowed to bring
any more than two friends
over at a time.
Please, she's never gonna know.
Yes, she will, Norm.
Tell you what,
why-why don't we have
Thanksgiving dinner
here at Cheers?
Pot luck, huh?
Why here? Because you don't
think I can handle
the responsibility of making
a big dinner for everybody?
Well, I was gonna beat
around the bush a little bit,
but, yeah, that's the gist.
Well, if you're gonna have it,
can we have a turkey?
I was just gonna make
grilled cheese.
All right, we'll have a turkey.
Good idea.
Okay, who's in
on the dinner here, huh?
Count me in.
All right.
Fras, what about you?
Oh, you probably have
other plans, don't you?
Oh, yes, big plans.
Frederick and I will
be spending the day
with the new friends we've
made since Lilith's departure:
Mrs. Paul,
Dinty Moore,
Uncle Ben.
Oh, and maybe the
Stouffers will stop by.
Why don't you join us, huh?
Oh, thanks, Sam.
WOODY:
Oh, Mr. Gaines.
What a nice surprise.
You remember Mr. Peterson,
Mr. Clavin?
Nick. Clyde.
Actually, it's, uh,
it's Norm, Cliff.
You're lucky I got that close.
Now, Woody, the reason
I came by here is that
now that you're my son-in-law,
I need your signature
on some papers here.
So what are they?
Oh, it's, uh, nothing important.
Just, uh, some silly forms
giving me power of attorney
over all of your affairs.
You see, the Gaines estate
is wide and varied.
And now that you're
married to Kelly,
you're part of that estate.
I'm not sure I
understand all this.
Oh, let me put it
in Hanover-ese, Woody.
You know how a turkey, when,
uh, it feeds at the trough,
will eat until it dies?
Well,
these forms give me the right...
now that you're feeding
at the Gaines trough...
to pull your head away
if I think you're gonna choke.
Well, turkeys don't
choke, Mr. Gaines,
they explode.
Well, the one clue you get
is you-you hear this hissing
sound just before they blow.
Now, you hear a turkey hissing,
head for the hills.
Turkey shrapnel can kill you.
For God's sake,
Woody, just sign
or make your mark
or whatever it is you do.
Thank you, Woody.
Oh, wait, uh,
Mr. Gaines.
I just got paid today and, uh,
if I'm now part
of the Gaines estate,
I guess I should do my part and
throw my pay-check into the pot.
(chuckling)
Good, Woody.
Always leave them laughing.
Why do you let him talk
to you like that, huh?
NORM:
Yeah,
you got to stand
up to him, Wood.
I'd never let my father-in-law
take advantage of me that way.
CLIFF:
I, uh, thought
your father-in-law
was dead, Norm.
You know, he might be.
Haven't seen him in ages.
Come to think of it,
I do remember Vera left a note
on the refrigerator one night.
Something about a funeral.
Ah, shoot, this is
gonna drive me crazy.
You know, Sam, I always
wanted to get along
with Mr. Gaines like
I do with my dad.
You and your daddy
got along well, huh?
Oh, yeah. Oh.
We'd go fish and bowl,
hang around,
pass notes to each
other in class.
Woody, you know,
it's none of my business,
but I think you ought to stand
up to Mr. Gaines right now,
or he's gonna be walking all
over you the rest of your life.
Well, I'd like to
stand up to him, Sam,
but he scares me.
Well, I know.
He's a pretty intimidating guy.
But you know the way
around that is you figure out
what you're gonna say, get it
in your head all straight,
then you go over there
and you tell him.
Well, what would you say, Sam?
Me?
Oh. Well, I don't know.
Something like, uh, you know,
"I'm disappointed in you.
"You should be ashamed
of yourself, you know.
"Things are gonna be
different from now on.
You're gonna give me
the respect that I deserve."
Yeah, I always thought
I did respect you, Sam.
Maybe I was wrong.
Tell you what,
why-why don't we, uh,
why don't we drive over there
and-and you can rehearse
what you're gonna say
on the way, all right?
Well, I suppose if I don't,
I'll have to listen
to another lecture
about how I don't respect you.
Okay, okay, I'm 95% sure
Vera's father is alive.
No, no, dead.
No, make that dead.
He's dead.
Or could he be...
Well...
suppose I'll just call
Vera and ask her, I guess.
I don't know how you ask someone
(chuckles):
A question like that.
Although Vera is always saying
we should talk more, you know.
Uh, yes, hi, honey, hi.
Uh, listen, um, do I, uh,
do I have a dark suit?
I do? Um, good.
D-Do you remember,
uh, why I bought it?
A funeral, of course.
Was, uh, was your father there?
Was he wearing makeup
by any chance?
Vera? Vera?
Shoot, this is gonna
bug me all day.
(moans):
Oh, Walter.
Oh.
Oh!
(moaning):
Oh! Oh.
Katherine, Katherine,
we can't go on like this.
Walter...
You're my brother's wife.
I mean, if anyone
ever found out,
it would ruin both our families.
You're right,
Walter, it's wrong.
Terribly wrong.
But I don't care.
That's my girl.
Mr. Gaines is in the library,
right through there.
Aren't you gonna announce us?
Very well, sir.
Mr. Gaines, there are
two gentlemen here to see you.
That make you feel
like a big man?
Ah, don't worry about that.
Okay, just like we rehearsed
it in the car, big fellow.
All right,
I'm disappointed in him,
he should be ashamed of himself,
and he should start
treating me with respect.
Attaboy.
Yeah.
Mr. Gaines?
(moaning):
Oh, God.
Woody!
What are you doing here?
Oh, I-I can see you're busy.
I'll wait outside.
My God, Walter.
Who was that?
That was my idiot
son-in-law.
Woody, just a minute!
Well, did he see us?
Of course he saw us.
I knew something like this
was gonna happen.
I've got to catch him before he
blabs it all over the mansion.
What do you mean
he's exercising?
That's what it looked like.
I-I think he was doing push-ups.
Oh, come on.
You're just trying
to back out of this.
No, I'm not, Sam.
I'm gonna tell him.
Well, then...
Excuse me.
You're the gentlemen I led
from the foyer to the library,
am I correct?
(chuckles):
Yeah, right.
Would you be a dear
and help me find my way back?
Uh, sure.
Well, actually, you know,
it's not that hard.
All you got to do is go down
the, uh, that staircase
with those naked angels
that are carved in the banister.
Then-then you, uh, go through
that long hallway
with the three naked ladies
kind of frolicking
in the field there.
And then you go take a left,
and you get in that big room
that has that, uh,
bronze statue of the b...
I'll tell you what, why don't
I take you there myself?
I'll be right back.
Now, Woody, I know you must
be terribly confused,
but there's
a simple explanation.
No, no, no,
Mr. Gaines.
You're gonna sit down,
and I'm gonna talk,
and you're
gonna listen. All right.
Now... I'm very
disappointed in you.
Ah.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
From now on, things are
gonna be different.
You're gonna start
treating me with respect.
Whatever you want, Woody.
What will it take for you
to forget everything
that's happened?
You name it.
Seriously?
Oh, yes.
Whatever you want.
Wow, that speech really took.
Well, uh, for starters,
this, uh, power of attorney
thing you made me sign.
It's gone, ripped up,
never existed.
All right, and I don't
want you to make fun of me
in front of my friends anymore.
You've got it.
Well, what I really want,
Mr. Gaines,
is just for us to get to know
each other better.
Oh, for God sakes, Woody,
I didn't commit murder.
All right, just forget
the whole thing.
Well, no, Woody,
if you want to be friends,
that's-that's fine,
that's fine.
In fact, uh,
we could, uh, oh...
Go fishing?
Yeah, uh, fishing.
Of course, fine.
In fact, why don't we go fishing
in your new boat?
(chuckles):
My new boat?!
Yes.
Really?
In-in fact, uh,
why don't we call it
the S.S. Silence?
Well, I'm sure
we can come up with
a better name than that,
but thanks.
Hooray.
(both chuckle)
You know, I get a
feeling we're gonna be
pretty close from
now on, Mr. Gaines.
Well, Walter...
did he know what we were doing?
Not only does he know,
but he's doing it to me.
REBECCA: Okay, you guys, I'm
trying to get a head count here
so I know how many people
are here for Thanksgiving
so I can have enough turkey.
Oh, easy on the turkey
for me, though, Rebecca,
'cause, uh, those tryptophanes
just put me to sleep.
Get two turkeys.
Norm, are you gonna be here?
Yeah, I might as well.
Vera's spending Thanksgiving
at her mother's.
How come?
Oh, she's still angry
about me asking
whether her father's
dead or alive.
You never know what's going
to tick some people off.
Hey, Normie, I've got
an easy way to find out
whether or not your
father-in-law's,
uh, still alive or not.
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah, you give, uh,
Vera's parents' house a call.
If a guy answers,
bingo, there's your answer.
Huh? I'll tell you what.
I'll look up the number for you
in the directory here.
So what's, uh,
what's Vera's maiden name?
It's, uh...
Damn, this is gonna
get embarrassing.
Could I be having some
severe memory lapse here?
Oh, Norm, quick.
In Herbie The Love Bug, Yeah?
Who played the bad guy?
Keenan Wynn.
Your memory's sound, my friend.
WOODY:
Hey, Sam.
Me and Mr. Gaines
just went fishing
on my new boat.
And guess what we're
doing tomorrow?
Flying to Vermont.
Vermont?
Yeah.
Well, all I did
was ask Mr. Gaines
how maple syrup was made.
And the next thing
you know, boom,
he's firing up the jet.
That's right.
Well, in spite of all
the fun we've been having,
I, I really must run along.
Oh, hey, Mr. Gaines.
What about my hug?
Oh, gee, Woody, I don't know.
Oh, yeah, I guess you're right.
I don't want to catch one
of those fish hooks in my eye.
On second thought,
come here, son!
Wow. How 'bout that?
You guys are getting
along great, aren't you?
Yep, Sam.
You know, I owe it all
to my little speech.
As soon as I delivered it,
he was putty in my hands.
Well, that's great, man,
that's great.
Yeah.
I noticed, though, you said, uh,
your speech, when, you know,
technically it was my speech.
Remember? Right over there,
I, uh, thought it up.
You may have
thought it up, Sam,
but I'm the one
who made it sing.
Well, whatever.
Congratulations.
Yeah, you know,
when, uh, Woody Boyd talks,
people listen.
Matter of fact, Sam,
I'm gonna do you
a great, big favour.
Mr. Peterson, I'm gonna talk
and you're gonna listen.
It's about your beer tab.
Wood, stay in the shallow end.
Yeah, maybe you're right,
sorry.
Get it, get it, get it,
get it, get it, get it! Oh!
Oh, man, this is great.
(TV clicks off)
Norm?
Yeah?
Th-The Barcalounger
is only here
for the day, right?
Thanksgiving just wouldn't
be the same without it, Sam.
Tomorrow it goes back, right?
I mean, you, you signed
this agreement remember?
Sam, what do you think
of all the decorations?
I bought everything
with my own money.
Yeah, you know,
I've been meaning to ask you.
What do skeletons and witches
have to do with Thanksgiving?
Well, uh...
the witches came over
with the Pilgrims.
And then the Pilgrims
burned them all at the stake.
And then, when they
were all burned up,
there was nothing left
of them but skeletons.
And that left the Pilgrims
free to make a big dinner.
They were cheap, huh?
Actually, they were
throwing them out.
Well, it looks, it looks
really nice, Rebecca.
It looks really nice.
Wh-What about the,
uh, the plates?
Oh, I'm going to borrow
those from Melville's.
No, no! Oh, don't do that.
Don't do that.
If-if John Hill finds out,
he'll blow his bald stack.
Oh, don't be silly.
Melville's is closed
and John Hill's at the Cape.
Besides, I'm already using his
oven to cook the turkey.
Well, in that case, uh, why
don't you get some silverware.
I think we've gonna run out
of these sporks.
Well, here we are, Frederick.
♪ Over the river
and through the woods ♪
♪ To the bar stool
on the right. ♪
Ah, the beginnings of a
marvellous Thanksgiving memory.
Say, Norm, uh, the last time
I was at your house,
wasn't this chair red?
Yeah, yeah, I go through
them pretty quickly.
Hi, Frasier.
Hi, Frederick. Hello.
Hey, how do you like the way
I decked the place out?
Well, uh, I must say it looks
rather... festive.
Thank you.
Oh, you're getting plates from Melville's.
You know what would look
beautiful is those, uh,
those gorgeous
candlesticks they have.
Ooh, good idea.
Why don't you go up there
and grab those?
Come here, Frederick.
Well, you guys lucked out.
You get to spend you
Thanksgiving with the Tortellis.
Hide your valuables.
Hey kids, park it over there.
Carla, why'd you only
bring three of your kids?
Well, we have this kind
of Thanksgiving
tradition at our home.
You see, at noon I set
them out on the curb.
Then the various men
they've come to know
as "Dad" drive by,
and who's ever left
comes with me.
Uh... there must
be some mistake here.
Uh... you've got me sitting
at the kiddie table.
Um, no, no,
uh, no mistake Cliff.
Uh, we all decided
that you're the only one
that we trust being
an adult supervisor.
Ah, well, that's another bowl
of stuffing, then, Sammy.
I'll be proud to watch
the little tykes.
So, kiddies...
I ever tell you about
the first Thanksgiving?
Yeah, it took place, uh,
between the ancient Egyptians
and astronauts
from a distant galaxy.
(speaking gibberish)
Oh, thank you, Frederick.
God, I wish I'd had kids.
Food's on!
Come on, everybody.
Hey.
Sit down around the table here.
Listen, here's the good news.
You can make a mess,
and don't worry about
breaking anything, 'cause none
of this stuff belongs to us.
Yay!
Yay! Yay!
Sam why don't you, uh,
make a little toast?
Oh... yeah.
All right, that's a good idea.
Uh, all right, uh...
welcome to, uh,
Thanksgiving at Cheers.
I hope everybody
enjoys the food,
and I'd like to make
a toast right now
to the man who made this all
possible: John Allen Hill.
Oh, now, now, come on.
I-I know what
you're thinking.
But you know,
I tell you the truth
uh, if John and I hadn't gotten
off on the wrong foot
I think we would have
been best of friends.
If he were here right now,
I would, uh,
I'd ask him to sit down
and break bread with us.
But because he isn't, then I say
let's raise our glasses
to that grand old gentleman,
John Allen Hill.
Cheers.
JOHN: Well, isn't this touching?
All the Who's down in Whoville
gathered 'round
their roast beast.
Good heavens, man, I thought
you were at the Cape.
I was until the police
called to tell me
the silent alarm
had gone off upstairs.
Ah, uh, yeah- that was,
that was us, John.
I-I'm sorry, we, uh,
borrowed a few things
for our simple dinner here.
John, I'll tell you what.
Why don't you join us, please?
Please come sit
at my right hand.
No, no, no, thank you.
Please, I couldn't.
But since no harm was done,
I'll be on my way.
Happy Thanksgiving.
And do sterilize everything.
Thank you, John,
and happy Thanksgiving.
So how'd you spot him?
I saw the reflection of his head
in the dessert tray.
Can I have one?
Mr. and Mrs. Woody Boyd.
How was that, sport?
Hi, Daddy.
Hello, pumpkin.
It's good to see you.
Hi, Dad.
Hello, son.
Happy Thanksgiving!
Hi, Uncle Richard,
Aunt Katherine.
Hello, darling.
GAINES: Richard.
Walter.
Woody.
Certain parties are
here this evening,
and things may
get very delicate.
Oh, don't worry
about a thing, Mr. Gaines.
Boy, she looks familiar.
Now, Woody...
Where have I seen her before?
WOODY: Help me out
here, Mr. Gaines.
I got it!
Uh, everyone
into the dining room.
I can smell that turkey,
it's all ready.
Let's just move along now.
The cranberry sauce
and stuffing,
all the trimmings.
Let's just move right along.
Come on,
move, move, move, move.
Save me a drumstick.
Woody, I thought
we had an understanding.
Now, we went fishing,
took you bowling,
we went to the arcade-
if there's a lower middle class
activity in Boston,
we've done it.
Well, I'm sorry, Mr. Gaines.
I was just trying
to figure out where I knew
Kelly's aunt from,
and it finally came to me.
Of course it came to you.
You caught me
making love to her
on the floor of my office.
I met her at the wedding.
Caught you what?
Nothing.
Let's eat.
Holy cow,
that's your brother's wife,
and you're having
an affair with her?
Yes.
You really didn't know?
No.
Then you're not
blackmailing me?
I didn't have to buy
your silence?
Well, no, I-I would never
blackmail you, Mr. Gaines.
I mean, I think what you're
doing is disgusting and wrong,
but that's between
you and Satan.
I've got something to tell you.
I think that we can't
be friends anymore.
I don't respect you.
Well, I'll just have to live
with your scorn
and contempt, Woody.
Okay, Mr. Gaines.
I just want you to know,
I'd never blackmail you.
I'd much rather do this.
Hey, everybody, I've got
something to tell you! Uh...
I want the wishbone!
Gotcha.
This is gonna be a fun night.
Dear God...
It's over.
I'm free, finally free.
Your brother's wife, eh, Wally?
Get me a drink.
We have to talk.