ANNOUNCER:
Last week on Cheers:
Oh, Frasier, I'm sorry.
I must have fallen asleep.
What time is it?
Well, it's pretty late.
Uh, I guess I...
I'll go downstairs
and, uh, sleep on the couch.
Maybe I should just go.
No, no, you don't
have to go home.
You don't have to
sleep on the couch.
Just a second.
(door opening and closing)
Frasier, what was that?
What was what?
I thought I heard a door slam.
You don't think those
guys are back, do you?
No. No, impossible.
I locked and dead-bolted it.
They'd need a key to get in.
Now, where were we?
Let's make this a night
we'll never forget.
Frasier.
Lilith?
Rebecca?!
Am I the only one
who feels awkward here?
Where is Frederick?
I didn't see him in his room.
He's with your mother.
Fine. Then I'll just go and let you
do whatever it was you were doing.
Lilith!
It was nice to see
you again, Lilith.
(theme song begins)
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
All right, exactly how
long has this been going on?!
Lilith?
What's the matter, Sam?
You look like you've
seen a ghost.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You did.
Lilith, I-I-I thought
you were in that, uh...
I've left the Eco-pod.
For a job at a gas station?
Look... everybody,
Lilith!
Well, my goodness...
uh, the-the, you know,
the time in the pod thing
has really done you
a world of...
You look so...
Your skin is, uh...
Hey, Lilith's back, huh?
Sam, please!
Tell me what's been going on!
How long has Frasier
been sleeping with Rebecca?
Beg your pardon?
Did he at least have the courtesy
to wait until I was in the ground?
Lil... Lil...
Frasier's not sleeping
with Rebecca!
Oh, well, perhaps you
should tell them that.
I just saw them in
my bed together.
Rebecca and Frasier-
you're kidding me.
How long has this
been going on?
I'm asking you!
I can't believe...
We... we were just over there!
We, we were watching
Three Stooges tapes with him.
NORM:
Well, maybe she was upstairs
the whole time and
we didn't know about it.
Well, yeah, after we left,
maybe he just toddled on
upstairs
and gave her the old
nyuk-nyuk-nyuk.
Rebecca and Frasier...
Am I to understand this is a
relatively new development?
Big news to us.
CLIFF: Who would have thought it?
Rebecca and Frasier, huh?
What's next, me and Carla?
(grunts)
Don't say it, Clavin,
don't you even think it.
See that?
It almost turned into a kiss.
You know what?
I think this is good for them.
They've been moping around
the last couple of months,
mooning about their
love life and everything.
They found each other.
This is very nice, I think.
Yeah.
Well, hear-hear!
To Rebecca and Frasier!
(all agreeing)
LILITH:
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
I'm still in the room!
Oh, I'm-I'm sorry, Lilith.
I can't believe
this has happened.
I come home to resume my life
and find that my husband
has taken up with another woman.
Well, why don't you... why
don't you take your coat off,
sit down and just
cool out for a while?
Oh, I can't, Sam-
I'm too wound up.
I've got half a mind
to go back to that bedroom
and wring Frasier's neck.
Frasier's...? Aren't you being a
little out of line here, Lilith?
I mean, the guy's
only being human.
You were the one who walked
out of here with another man.
Oh, God, you're right.
It's just that
I wanted to come back so badly
and resume my life.
As naive and selfish
as it sounds, I just assumed
he would be waiting for me.
Listen, go get some sleep.
I'll bet you in the morning
you and Frasier
can work things out.
That's a good
idea, Sam. Yeah.
Where am I gonna sleep?
I wanted to stay at home,
and now I've got
no place to go.
I've got an attic
you can hang upside down in.
(taps bar)
Sam, if you could lend me
a little money for a hotel,
I'd really appreciate it.
No problem, no problem.
Thank you.
You know, I'll be right back.
I'm going to call my mother
and check up on Frederick.
You know, I have to say that
after being
cooped up underground
for the last six months, it's
very nice to see people again.
Even you people.
That was sweet.
Can you believe this stuff?
Yeah, I'd like to see the
look on Frasier's face
when Lilith walked in.
I'm sure he was shocked.
I mean, what
would you do, Norm,
if you walked in and found
Vera with another man?
Well, I'd probably buy
a couple of his pencils
and send him on his way.
Frederick is fine.
I worry, though, sometimes
that my mother may be too
overprotective and smothering.
You got to watch that-
that'll really screw a kid up.
Here's your money.
Thank you, Sam.
So, that, uh...
pod thing didn't work out, huh?
Suffice it to say
that Dr. Pascal and I
determined that two human beings
cannot live together
underground.
You and I could, Norm.
Would you stop
saying that, Cliff?
Lilith. Here you are.
I've been looking
all over for you.
What in the world
are you doing here?
I've come home, Frasier.
Oh, my God.
I've left the pod, and I
spent the last three days
on a bus to come home to you.
I don't understand.
Frasier,
I realize that my leaving
you was very hurtful,
and I understand
your seeking comfort
in the arms of another woman.
We won't mention it.
We'll just put it behind us
and-and get on with our lives.
What I'm trying to
say, Frasier, is...
You want me back?
Oh, yes, I want you back!
You hear that, everybody?
Frasier and Lilith
are back together again!
Aw, it makes me so happy!
Here, free drinks on the house!
All right!
Just a minute, Sam-
I haven't taken her back.
Oh, sorry, Mr. Peterson.
Wait, wait, come on, now.
Now, you two kids
belong together.
Come on.
The unmitigated gall!
You think you can walk back into
my life and patch it up again
as quickly as
you destroyed it?! Frasier, I'm sorry.
All right, she's sorry-
beers for everybody!
Come on.
Frasier, please.
More than anything,
I want our life back.
What about your
boyfriend, Dr. Pascal?
I don't love him.
I love you.
(chuckling):
Oh, really?
So you've come back
to reliable old Frasier, have you?
And for how long?
Till somebody opens
a colony on Venus?!
Frasier, don't be ridiculous.
If we go to Venus, I think
we should do it as a family.
(panting):
Lilith, I have to talk to you in private.
(others hooting)
Okay, it doesn't
have to be in private.
Lilith, listen,
please let me explain.
Rebecca, you don't have to
explain anything to her.
You and I can pick up
right where we left off.
Really?
Absolutely!
Come on over here
and give me a big wet one.
Frasier, let me just
speak to you in
my office, please. Oh, okay, even better.
Heh! Sam, hold
my calls, will you?
Sofa pulls out, you know.
Sorry things aren't working out.
Is there anything
I can do for you?
It isn't over, yet, Sam.
I know my Frasier.
He doesn't take well
to sudden developments,
but he'll come around.
I'm as determined
to get him back
as I was to leave him.
Well, that's...
that's good, that's good.
Frasier, um...
listen, I know that Lilith
coming back changes everything,
and... so I'm just gonna
step out of the picture
and... and there's
no hard feelings.
That bitch!
Thinks she can waltz
back into my life
and start calling the shots?
I know that what we almost had
was very special, but...
we have a very
special friendship, too,
so I think that we should
just leave it at that.
Eco-pod my big white butt!
I was that close to popping her,
you know that?
If she weren't the mother
of my child, I'd have done it!
I-I think we should
just focus here,
because, y-you know, Frasier,
I'm trying to be very gentle,
because I want
to let you down easy.
I don't want
to break your heart.
"I spent three days on a bus,"
wah, wah, wah.
Well, cry me a river, bun-head!
For God's sake, Frasier,
will you listen to me!
I'm trying
to tell you something!
Oh. I'm sorry, Rebecca.
I've been rude; I apologize.
It's just, I can't believe
that she's come back.
Frasier...
you know, what we almost did,
I think it would
have been real special,
but...
I think maybe it's better that
we just remain good friends.
I suppose you're right.
Well, what might
have been, huh?
For what it's worth,
I'm sorry things
didn't work out.
(knocking)
Hi. Can I talk
to Rebecca alone, please?
Bar business.
Sure, Sam.
Oh, God, Sam,
why do I always screw
everything up?!
All I was doing was giving
a friend a ride home.
And then you know
how things happen.
You know, a kiss leads to a hug
and a hug leads to the bed,
and then the wife comes in
and wants to know
what you're doing there.
Why do I always make
such a mess of things?!
So who was better,
me or Frasier?
Oh!
What?
I-I don't have feelings, too?!
Frasier, I know that
I've hurt you,
and I realize now
that the only way
to get you back is to beg.
So here I go.
I'm sorry, Lilith.
Begging won't work.
I'm not gonna hang around
and be the safety net
every time you fall from one
of your flights of fancy.
That boat has sailed.
That gate has closed.
Alice doesn't live
here anymore.
Damn you, Frasier!
I know that somewhere
inside of you,
you still have deep feelings
for me,
and I'm willing to wait.
If I have to wait
a hundred years,
I'm going to get you back!
You hear that, guys?
Come on, free beer, let's go.
Aw, Lilith.
Louis!
Pascal! What are
you doing here?
Try to stop me, Crane.
I've come to take Lilith
back to our home
under the dirt,
where we're safe.
Louis, I'm not
going back there.
How can you abandon the oneness
of our subterranean life
for this world of surfies?
Surface dwellers.
Because this
is where I want to be.
Our experiment failed, Louis,
and so did our love affair.
I'm not leaving without you,
Lilith.
I demand that you accompany me
this instant.
And if I don't?
Then I'll be forced
to shoot you
a-a-and everyone else
in this bar.
What's it gonna be?
Louis, I'm not going
back with you.
So I guess you're just going
to have to shoot us.
Welcome back, Lilith.
I'm warning you,
unless Lilith agrees to go back with me,
you're all dead.
You don't scare me, Pascal.
Yeah? Why not?
Because I happen
to own every copy
of Soldier of Fortune
ever published.
I'm telling you people,
no "ifs" "ands" or "buts",
that there's no working pistol
with that configuration.
(gunshot) (shrieks)
I did miss the Christmas issue.
All right, get back, get back!
Don't push me.
The importance of the Eco-pod
is far greater
than any one human life.
Sam...
John, John,
it's not a good time.
Sam, I've put up with your rock
and roll music,
your loud parties
and your fights.
But now you've shot Ruben
the busboy in the foot.
He's an undocumented alien
without health insurance,
and that puts me
in a bit of a jam.
Oh...
A bigger jam.
Everybody but Lilith
behind the bar!
(phone rings)
All right, answer the phone,
but act natural.
Cheers.
Just a second.
Mr. Peterson,
it's Mrs. Peterson.
See, it's my wife.
Um, I'll get rid of her.
(quietly):
Woody, cover me.
Uh, Vera?
Uh, yes, yes, I know it's late.
You see, we're
being held hostage by a mad gunman, and...
What do you mean I've
used that one before?
No-no-no, you see, no-no, honey,
wait, wait, hey, hey!
(receiver clicks)
Put the gun down, Louis.
Why are you being so foolish?
Because I can't live
without you!
I miss you.
And Dr. Jaworski
misses you, too.
FRASIER:
Dr. Jaworski?!
What? There were three
scientists in the Eco-pod?
Did you sleep with him, too?!
Dr. Jaworski
isn't a scientist.
He's Loui' imaginary friend.
Did I forget to mention
that Louis is insane?
Turns out he's claustrophobic.
We discovered that
little fact about 30 seconds
after they closed
the steel doors.
(knocking)
PAUL: Hey, guys, I know you're
having a party in there.
Let me in.
Who's that at the hatch?
That's nobody,
nobody important.
We'll see about that.
So what's the big secret?
What's going on?
Paul, we're being held hostage!
Fine, then don't tell me.
Get with the others.
Actually, I don't belong
with the others.
I, I never quite fit in.
Ask anyone.
No, he doesn't.
PASCAL:
Shut up! Shut up!
Get behind the bar!
Go on.
All right, Lilith,
if you want to play
the waiting game,
I'm prepared to play along.
I give you just ten minutes
to make up your mind.
If you won't leave with me then,
I start shooting.
And this is the man
you wanted to marry?!
Who says I wanted to marry him?
Two days ago, I got a Mail-gram
saying you wanted a divorce.
Correction, I sent
that Mail-gram.
I thought that with you out
of the way,
Lilith and I would be free
to spend the rest
of our lives together.
But then Lilith escaped.
By the way, it was very clever
of you
putting that papier-mâché bust
of yourself in your cot.
I must admit,
I kissed it more than once
before I got wise.
You have nine minutes left.
(whispers):
Hey, I got a plan. Come here.
Lilith, Lilith, here's the plan.
Okay, you go back
to the Eco-pod with Pascal.
And then what?
And then the plan's done.
Don't panic.
I know Louis.
He's a little upset right now,
but he's essentially harmless.
He won't do anything that would
cause anyone any harm.
The hell I won't!
I'll shoot everyone in this bar
if I have to to get you back!
CLIFF:
Listen, okay, okay.
All right, all right, I got it.
How about I sob uncontrollably
and-and lose control
of my bodily functions?
Cliff, is that a plan?
No, actually,
it's more of a warning.
No, no, no, I,
I've got one. Come here.
I'll go up there
and I'll come on to him.
I'll flirt with him,
and I'll distract him.
Any other thoughts?
Anyone?
You're a psychiatrist.
Talk to the man.
You must be trained in
some kind of technique.
I was afraid somebody
would bring that up.
All right, all right.
I do recall taking
some sort of an oath once.
Good luck. Good luck.
Keep your distance, Crane!
Okay.
I, I just want to
talk to you, Louis.
Do you mind if
I call you "Louis"?
Listen, Louis,
I, I've been there.
I've felt the hurt.
I've felt the abandonment.
I've felt what it's like
when a woman tears
your entire life apart.
Believe me,
I've been there, my friend.
Even just looking at Lilith now
brings back all the pain
and the torment I've suffered
every second
for the last six months.
Please, put the gun down, Louis.
See, I got through it.
So will you.
Just put the gun down.
Nice speech, Crane, but get out
of my way or I swear to God
you're gonna be
the first one to go!
Oh, I can't stand this anymore.
Look, Louis, if you're going
to shoot someone, shoot me.
I won't go back with you,
and you don't want me back.
I'd only make you
more miserable.
I can't shoot you, Lilith.
Well, you're going
to have to do it, Louis.
That's the only way
to end this.
Give me the gun, Louis.
(sobbing)
I'm sorry, Lilith!
Well, Sam, thanks for another
delightful evening at Cheers.
We must do it again sometime.
I'm, uh, sorry about this, John.
Next time you come on down,
drinks are on the house.
Oh, then it's all worthwhile.
Boy, look at that
poor mule-yak, huh?
I really pity him.
It really makes you think,
though, doesn't it?
Where is that fine line
between sanity and insanity?
Look behind you, Clavin.
You stepped over it
about a year ago.
Are you all right, Lilith?
Yes, I think so.
Good.
Frasier...
do we have any chance
for reconciliation?
I'm sorry, Lilith, but no.
I just can't go
through this again.
I understand.
And I'll respect your wishes.
Frasier, you know, I hadn't
realized just how deeply
I'd wounded you
until I heard what you said to Louis.
All I can say is
please don't hate me forever.
I'll check into a hotel.
Maybe we can meet
tomorrow and sort out
the... (clears throat)...
divorce proceedings.
I think that would be best.
(high-pitched sobs)
What's that sound?
(sobs continue)
Sounds like she's got a pretzel
stuck in her throat.
As hard as it may
be to believe,
that is the sound
of my wife... sobbing.
(sobbing continues)
Hey, say something, will you?
Just make her stop.
I'll handle this.
Now, Lilith, I'm just
gonna say this once,
so hear me.
(sobbing continues)
No matter how much you sob,
no matter how much you plead,
we are not going to Venus.
Oh, Frasier!
Welcome home, Lilith.
Oh!
Boy, that's beautiful.
Start pouring, Wood.