Hey, Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Miss Chambers,
can I ask you something?
You're a girl, right?
Well, I'm a woman.
Well, that's close enough.
You see, in about five minutes
I'm going out on my first date
with a city girl,
and I'm really nervous about it.
You know, I'm afraid I might
get tongue-tied
and make a fool of myself.
I don't want that to get in the way
of me picking up the babes.
Et tu, Woody?
After only a few months
here at Cheers,
you're starting to talk
like the other reprobates.
Well, thanks, Miss Chambers,
but, you know...
...that's not enough. I wanna be
smooth with the ladies like Sam.
Well, I think I can help you out.
Have a seat.
A good conversationalist
is usually a good listener.
I've found that people love
to talk about themselves.
- Really?
- Oh, yes.
People have an endless fascination
with their own little world.
It's an observation I made
as a small child,
although I've never understood
why it holds true.
I, myself, have always found many
more interesting topics to talk about.
Of course, I've always made it a point
to broaden my horizons.
As a matter of fact,
I was reading the New York Times
at the age of 4.
And from then, on to the classics.
Of course, it caused some hardships
as a youngster,
always being far and away
the brightest in the class.
Usually, the brightest in the class
is regarded as some sort of
a pimply faced egghead.
I'm sorry, Clifford,
what was your question again?
Boy, just when you think
you can't get any older,
you go and read the paper.
- Why? What happened?
- Look at this.
There's gonna be a reunion
of The Boston Boppers.
Oh, my goodness. Look at that.
- Who are The Boston Boppers?
- It's not a who, it's a what.
Like you.
It was a local TV show,
kind of like American Bandstand.
- Carla used to dance on it.
- Oh, yeah.
I danced my way
into New England's heart.
Till they made up that stupid rule.
What rule's that?
The one that said that pregnant
16-year-olds can't Hully Gully on TV.
Those were repressive times.
Well, you must be very excited
about the reunion, Carla.
I'm not going.
Oh, how come?
I thought you loved that place.
I did love it.
But Nick was my dance partner.
That was before
we had to get married.
Boy, they sure have
tough dance laws up here.
Wipe that table off there,
will you, Woody?
We were a great team.
We really got along
when we were dancing.
And when we were dancing,
if you know what I mean.
Yes, it's frighteningly clear.
Well, why don't you just ask Nick
if he wants to go?
Forget it.
Oh, come on. You're not gonna
pass up all that fun
just for a little pride, are you?
It's not only fun.
There's a chance to win 500 bucks
and a trip to Hawaii
in that dance contest.
And we could do it.
- Then what--?
- There's no way I'd call and ask him.
And I really don't want anyone else
getting any crazy ideas, like calling him
in Atlantic City at 555-4397.
Well, here I go,
out of earshot in the poolroom
for about 1 5 minutes.
Oh, Carla.
Hey, I got an idea.
Why don't one of us call Nick?
That'd be a good idea.
- Anybody know the area code?
- 609!
Thank you.
- Afternoon, everybody.
- Norm!
How's life, Mr. Peterson?
Oh, I look at it every once in a while
when I'm in the john.
I didn't mean the magazine.
Neither did l.
- So how's that job-hunt going, Norm?
- Great.
- Hey, you got one, huh?
- Yeah, well. No, no. Vera did.
Boy, Normie, don't you feel
the least bit emasculated?
I mean, isn't it gut-wrenching
to watch your wife go off to work
every morning?
It's gut-wrenching
to watch Vera do anything.
- Who are you?
- I'm Woody Boyd.
Big deal.
Where--? Where is everybody?
Oh, there's those two bozos.
Nick, Loretta.
Hello, sweetcakes.
You been thinking about me?
Only during flea-and-tick season.
Yeah? Well, in my neighbourhood,
that's all year round.
I'm sure it is.
- Hey, Nick.
- Sam.
- Hi, Loretta.
- Hello.
- Excuse me. Glad you made it.
- Of course I made it.
Anytime Carla needs a favour,
and I can benefit financially,
and you send me the bus fare,
I'm there.
Hey, that's quite a testimonial.
So how you doing?
You still in the TV-repair business?
That's a sideline now.
I'm into bigger and better things.
What do you got there?
"Nick's Talent Emporium,
Hi-Class Talent for Less.
Nick Tortelli, Talent Manager."
Well, I'll be darned.
I only got one.
Nick's managing my career now.
Oh, yeah? You still singing
with the Grinning Americans?
Boy, I love that group.
Oh, step into the '80s.
The Grinning Americans
are so passé it's laughable.
I'm with the Lemon Sisters.
The Lemon Sisters?
Yeah, it's Loretta
and two other dames.
I thought up the name.
Well, don't people confuse you
with the Lennon Sisters?
I don't know.
Do they throw their drinks
at The Lennon Sisters?
It's pure coincidence
that the names sound alike.
Besides, I got other people
on my roster.
I also handle Wayne Newman.
Ginger ale and a Scotch.
Nick Tortelli? As I live and breathe,
what a surprise.
What do you say, Carla?
Are we gonna kill them
at that dance contest?
You came here to go
to that dance contest with me?
Sure. Yeah, I'm gonna win
that contest and go to Hawaii,
where the girls wear grass skirts.
And I'm planning on bringing
my hedge clippers.
You gotta admit, the guy's a panic.
I can't believe it. You guys
really used to rock out
on The Boston Boppers, huh?
Sure. We were the stars.
They couldn't stop us.
Hey, you remember the host,
Floyd Panjeric?
Yeah, what a dork.
Remember that time we pantsed him
during the station break?
It's gonna be great to see everybody.
I just hope I can dance as good. I...
- I'm a little rusty.
- Oh, no sweat. I'm in great shape.
I'm glad to hear that, Carla,
but it takes two to tango.
And if I'm rusty, we're nowhere.
What's that supposed to mean?
Look, I'm trying to be
a gentleman here.
Everybody knew
who was more talented.
- Yeah, me.
- Give me a break.
I carried you.
You carried me? I carried you.
In your hat. I carried you!
In your hat! I carried you!
Carla, the fact is, I can go to the dance
with a monkey and win that contest.
Oh, yeah? Who'd lead?
That's it.
If you were the last babe on earth,
I wouldn't dance with you.
I got an idea. I'm gonna show you
how good a dancer I am.
I'm gonna go with Loretta.
Oh, Nicky, I'm honoured.
We haven't danced
since our wedding.
And we've never danced
fully clothed.
There you go.
It's me and Loretta.
And you, Carla, can eat dirt.
That's what you think.
I'm gonna get myself a new partner
and beat the pants off of you.
Oh, yeah? Who are you gonna get?
Eddie Csznyk.
Eddie Csznyk, the Polish Prancer?
That's right.
He was always wanting
to dance with me,
and I always turned him down
to go with you.
Yeah, that was the last smart move
you ever made.
Come on, Loretta, we're gonna
practice until our feet bleed.
Okay.
Bye, gang at Cheers.
Hey, Carla, I saw him, I saw him.
He's dancing down the street.
Boy, he's beautiful.
Makes Fred Astaire look like a gorilla.
- You sure it's him?
- Yeah, I'm sure it's him.
I called out, "Hey, Eddie Csznyk,"
and he waved back.
This is it. My luck is finally changing.
- Eddie!
- Carla!
Check out my footwork.
Eddie, your shoelace is un...
...tied.
Good luck, Carla.
I'm really sorry about this.
- Knock them dead, kid.
- Yeah, yeah.
Listen, mac, I'd put
a cervical collar on that knee.
Give him...
Give him about
30 milligrams of cc's, huh?
Better make that 40.
- What are you gonna do now?
- I don't know.
I gotta get another partner.
Does anybody here dance?
I should've known better.
The only time I've seen
any of you dance
is when the restrooms are crowded.
Sam?
- Why don't you help her out.
- What are you talking about?
Oh, you know very well
what I'm talking about.
You're a great dancer.
You won that trophy
at our ballroom-dancing class.
Don't, don't...
The fact that you talked me into
taking that stupid class
is embarrassing enough.
- Sam, are you going to help Carla?
- No, I'm not.
- Why not?
- I am a jock.
I've got an image to protect.
I don't want people thinking I'm too
graceful, if you know what I mean.
There's nothing wrong
with being graceful.
I'm not worried
about being graceful.
I'm worried about being too graceful.
It's not like you're being asked
to perform Swan Lake in a tutu.
Why did that particular image
come to mind?
Sam, please.
Baryshnikov is graceful,
and he's one of the sexiest men alive.
Oh, come on. Barysh...
We all know why women
go for Baryshnikov.
- Oh, and why is that?
- Well, because of what he wears.
I mean, those tights
have no secrets.
Don't believe everything you see,
Sammy.
You know, I think he's padded.
Probably orders it
from that catalogue.
What catalogue?
Well, I heard some guys talking.
Well, no luck back there either.
Well, I can still take
the honourable way out.
I'm going home to burn my feet
on the radiator.
No, no, Carla.
Carla, come here. Come here.
Wait. Let's see if we can...
...do something here.
Sammy.
You're graceful.
Carla.
- Is that you?
- Yeah.
- Cheryl, is that you?
We never liked each other
very much.
Hey.
What are you doing here with Sam?
I thought you were coming
with Eddie Csznyk.
Sam happens to be
a much better dancer.
And he has the grace of a swan.
Bull swan.
Hi, kids.
That's the way he started
every show.
That's catchy.
A lot of great years,
and a lot of great music,
and a lot of grey hairs
have gone by.
But you know what?
Out of all the music,
I think our music
was the best music.
- What do you say?
- You're a lame-o!
Oh, you kids. Spunky as ever.
But we're gonna have
a lot of fun tonight.
Hey, I got an idea.
Why don't we see
how far we've all come
since the old Boston Boppers days?
Tell us the person
you most admired then
and the person
you most admire now.
I'm Cheryl Koski from Brockton.
And back then, I guess the person
I admired the most
was Frankie Avalon.
- And now?
- Now I'd have to say...
...Fabian.
All right.
Now that you're warmed up,
Iet's get down to what
you're all here for:
a chance to dance your way
to Waikiki.
The rules are simple.
If the judges tap you, you're out.
You know, Sammy,
when Nick and I used to go
to these dance contests,
we always used to spit
on each other's shoes for good luck.
Well?
You missed.
I hope you dance
better than you spit.
Here we go with "Tutti-Frutti."
Well, I'm sorry, kids. You're out.
- Oh, come on, man!
- Hey, you stupid...
Hey, they suck swamp water too.
We have our winners!
Hold it a minute, Floyd.
A great wrong is about to be done.
You know me. I'm Nick Tortelli.
High school class of '62, '63, '64.
The reason I didn't win this contest
is because my partner stunk.
And I refuse to leave
until I show you how it's done
with my ex-lovely wife, Carla.
Nicky.
- Come on, Carla.
- Forget it, Nick.
Floyd, "Unchained Melody."
Well, guess it's just you and me.
Beg your pardon?
I'd like to do something with you
that'll make him sorry.
And I don't mean dancing.
Do you have a van?
I don't really think you wanna do
something you're gonna regret later.
Oh, yes, I do.
And I wanna do it right now.
And I'm good too.
Even though I don't like it very much.
You're making too big
a deal out of this.
I mean, it's just a dance.
How good?
Introducing the winner of
The Boston Boppers dance contest,
Miss Carla Tortelli!
Oh, yay! That's wonderful.
- You two did it.
- Well, no, no.
Actually, Carla and Nick won.
I guess I just wasn't
graceful enough.
Come on, Sammy.
You were plenty graceful.
No, I wasn't.
No, really. You should've seen
Carla and Nick out there.
They were like Fred and Ethel.
Really.
Yeah, it was a magical moment.
You know, it was like
I was transported back in time.
I wasn't a tired old woman
with six kids.
I was a fresh young teenager
with two kids.
Come on, you guys.
Let me drive you home.
Oh, good.
Sammy, I think I just wanna
sit here for a little while
and bask in the glow.
Relive the moment
and have a couple of belts.
Yeah, enjoy.
Thanks.
Congratulations, Carla.
Now, aren't you glad you went?
I'll bet you looked great
out there on the dance floor.
Yeah, I did, actually.
You know, why don't you come by my
place, and I'll show you my Watusi?
And then later on,
we can dance a little bit.
On second thought,
I'm going to hitchhike.
You meet a better class of people.
My love, my darling
I hunger for your touch
- What are you doing here?
- I had to see you.
Carla...
...tonight...
...was destiny.
What are you talking about?
It was destiny that Eddie Csznyk
fell down those stairs.
And it was destiny that The Boppers
even had a reunion.
And it was destiny
that we won the contest.
When we were dancing
out on that floor tonight,
we were like the only two
people on earth.
I know we belong together,
and we always will.
Come on, Nick.
We're great when we're
on the dance floor,
but when the music stops,
we stink on ice.
No, no. We were meant
to be together.
Carla, you know me.
Look in my eyes and you'll know
I'll tell you the truth.
- You're serious.
- Yeah.
What are you saying?
I'm saying I want you to go
to Hawaii with me tonight.
Now.
Please, Carla.
Make this dream of mine come true.
- Tonight was incredible.
- Yeah.
- Wow, you and me in Hawaii.
- Palm trees.
- Sipping mai tais on the beach.
- Yeah, mai tais.
- lt'd be paradise.
- Yeah.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
- What about Loretta?
- What about her?
She's waiting for us at the airport.
Is that a no?