Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Congratulate the doctor.
I'm doing a piece on the
psychological ramifications
of Ingmar Bergman's later works
for American Film.
Oh, that's great, Fras.
I'd like to read it to you
to see if it's still accessible
to the layman.
May I have your opinion?
Sure. Buy a new suit,
get a haircut and stay home.
Thank you, Carla.
Now, I call the piece
"Ingmar Bergman:
Poet of the Subconscious."
The films of Ingmar Bergman...
Who could forget her in
Casablanca, huh?
No, no...
No, you're thinking
of Ingrid Bergman.
I'm talking
about Ingmar Bergman.
Ingmar Bergman, the boxer?
No, Woody, you're thinking
of Ingmar Johansson.
You mean the guy who
knocked out Floyd Patterson?
No, no, no-- Sonny Liston
knocked out Patterson.
Well, then who
knocked out Johansson?
Patterson.
Before Liston?
No, no, Johansson
knocked out Liston.
Who knocked out
Patterson?
Was it Ingrid Bergman?
No, Ingrid Bergman...
Shut up! Shut up!
Not one more word.
I came in here
to discuss Ingmar Bergman,
not start an Abbott
and Costello routine.
Actually, I thought
it was more like Martin
and Lewis, wasn't it?
You mean Joe Louis?
Oh, he's the one
who knocked out
Floyd Patterson.
Then who knocked out
Lou Costello?
Apparently, Ingrid Bergman.
Boy, she was tougher
than she looked.
( piano plays )
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody knows
your name
And they're always glad
you came
You want to be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You want to be where everybody
knows your name
You want to go
where people know
People are all the same
You want to go where
everybody knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
CLIFF:
Where's Rebecca?
I haven't seen her
all day.
She's down at one of her power
meetings at corporate.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, she must be really trying
to impress a biggie.
She was already puckering up
before she even hit the door.
CLIFF:
Boy, these
corporate types--
down at the post office,
I kneel for nobody.
Hmm.
Well, we'll all bear
that in mind, Cliff,
whenever we desire to
have a job where you have
to wake up at 4:00
in the morning,
walk a 15-mile route, and
make a minimal base salary.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's not that easy, pal.
You got to take a test.
Oh, my God, I've died
and gone to heaven.
We wish.
Shouldn't somebody
alert Sammy?
Ah, he knows.
He can sense these things.
I'm going to give him,
three, two, one.
Where is she?
He's slowing down,
but he's still got it.
Hey, give me a break, will ya?
There are lead pipes down there.
Interferes with the radar.
Hi.
I'm Sam Malone.
Hi, I'm Erin.
Ah.
Can I have an Evian, please?
You bet.
Thanks.
Tennis player?
Yeah, yeah, but, uh,
I'm more into biking,
running, skiing, rowing, squash.
Hey, what a coincidence!
So am I.
Maybe I could
join you sometime.
Nice try, but seriously,
I don't think you're up to it.
( hearty laugh )
Why, just because
I got a couple, five,
15 years on ya?
Sweetheart,
you're looking
at a former professional
athlete here.
Yeah, I'm sure you were.
No, I'm serious.
Listen, tell you what.
Punch me in the stomach.
If it hurts me,
then I'm out of here.
If not,
we got a date.
Nah...
Come on,
come on, come on.
Give it your best shot.
Okay, okay, here goes.
Whoa, you are
in good shape.
Yeah, I told you so.
Yeah.
All right.
Hey, this is great.
What do you say, tomorrow?
Uh, cycling?
Okay, it sounds like fun.
I'll meet you here
at 2:00.
I'll be here, flexing.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
Hey, Sam, that girl's
going out with you
just 'cause you let
her hit you?
No, she's going out with me
because I'm a lean, tight
specimen hunk.
( guffawing ):
No, really, Sam.
Woody, I'm trying
to teach you something here.
Listen, they go
for it every time.
You ought to
try it someday.
All right, for the sake
of argument, I will.
Yeah.
All right, here.
Excuse me.
Would you consider
going out with me?
I really don't think so.
Oh, yeah?
Well, what if I told you
you could punch that guy
right there
in the stomach?
( speaking quietly )
Oh, yeah, right, Sam--
my stomach.
What do you
think I am, stupid?
Well, everyone,
you are looking at a winner.
You were the best kisser-upper?
Gee, what does that
trophy look like?
I did not kiss up.
I gave an interview.
I gave one hell of an interview.
I was tough, I was insightful,
I was witty.
Meryl Streep will play me
in the movie.
You know, I gave them
a million and one ideas
to promote Cheers.
My marketing major
really paid off today.
They couldn't take their eyes
off me.
Were you writing something down
before you went in there?
Yes, I jotted down a few notes.
Were you using a fountain pen?
My lucky fountain pen.
Make that your
leaky fountain...
Oh.
I don't believe this!
And I thought they were
really impressed with me,
and they were just staring
at this big, old
stupid ink blot.
It's not that bad,
Miss Howe.
It's kind of decorative.
It looks like, uh, a bunny.
No, no, it looks
like a spider.
Or a butterfly.
It looks like my parents
having a screaming argument
on my third birthday
when I pretended
to be asleep but wasn't.
Or a butterfly.
Afternoon, everybody.
Yo-ho.
ALL:
Norm!
Beer, Norm?
Have I gotten that predictable?
Good.
Hey, weren't you supposed to
have a painting job today?
You're right,
Cliffie, I did,
but I screwed it up.
Turns out I was supposed
to show up yesterday.
So they went ahead and hired
somebody else.
Like they couldn't open the
restaurant a damn day later.
Well, you know,
you might be
the world's greatest
house painter--
although who would know
the difference?
But, you know,
as a businessman,
you really leave a lot
to be desired, you know.
You haven't had a job
in three months.
Cliff, you're
absolutely right.
I could do something about that.
Or I could sit right here
and feel sorry for myself
and nurse this beer all day.
And since I'm already here...
Wait a minute.
Here we have a man
who doesn't know how
to promote his business.
And here we have a woman
who knows everything
about promotion,
but has never really
been given a chance.
Now, if I can turn
a beer-guzzling nobody
into a successful
businessman,
then those guys down there
at corporate will see
that I can do anything.
Uh, much as I love your pitch,
Rebecca...
uh, I'm not comfortable
working with friends.
Oh, forget about friends.
In the cold light
of reason,
consider this:
Please, please, please,
for Becky?
Nah, nah, I'd rather
work by myself.
Fine, Norm, fine.
I'll just go back
to what I was doing--
going over these
delinquent bar accounts.
Whoa.
Now there's a rather huge one
in the "P" section.
Welcome to Team Peterson.
Nothing like bicycling
to clean the garbage
out of your system.
Coffee, Woody.
How do you
want it, Sam?
Uh, straight,
no cream, no sugar.
Oh, what the hell--
forget the water,
just give me
a handful of grounds.
Hey, uh, Sammy,
the old Erin machine's
really tuckering
you out, huh?
No, no, I'm fine.
I just need a little something
to pick me up here.
How about six pallbearers?
You guys are just jealous
because I'm toning
and you're not.
I am buff.
I mean I am discovering muscles
I didn't even know I had.
Oh! There's one.
That feels good,
that feels good, though.
Ah! All right,
I've got to go change.
I'm meeting Erin
to go jogging.
What's wrong
with our lives?
Yeah, we have lousy jobs
with poor pay,
we both waste all our time
sitting on our cans
in this beer hall doing
nothing but watching TV
and gossiping like
a couple of old ladies,
plus everyone thinks
we're dufuses.
Geez, you know,
I was just going
to say we could probably use
a little bit more exercise,
but, uh, I'll go along
with what you said.
Oh, Norm, there you are.
Oh, gee,
how'd you track me down?
I got some terrific
ideas for 4-A Painting.
That's what you're going to call
the company, huh?
Yeah, it's an old
marketing secret.
It puts our name first
in the phone book.
How come 4A?
Why not 3A?
Because that's
the Auto Club.
Wow, they got jumper cables
and they paint houses?
I've got to join
that club.
Woody, this is
a business meeting.
Sorry! Next time,
I'll wear a suit.
Anyway... all right.
All successful businesses
and products have logos.
Now, I have come up
with the perfect,
delightful,
charming little character
to symbolize 4-A Painting.
It's a lizard.
No, it's Carl Chameleon.
Now, like all chameleons,
Carl changes colors.
And so should your house.
When you think of color change
think of Carl and 4-A Painting.
That sure makes my old symbol
seem like nothing.
What was your
old symbol?
Nothing.
All right, Norm,
I gotta computerize
the accounts,
I've gotta get some
advertising set up,
and I gotta get a new
phone line installed.
Whoa, wait, how much
is all this gonna cost me?
Minimal.
$2,000, $3,000 to begin with.
I'm beginning to think
AAAA Painting
is gonna cost me
a-a-a-a fortune.
It's making you
stutter, too.
CLIFF:
Nah, nah,
but, uh, seems like
Rebecca is costing you
more money
than she's making you.
You thinking of giving her
the old pink slip?
I couldn't do that, Cliff.
FRASIER:
Well, you know, Norm,
I think we all agree
that letting somebody go
is the most painful,
difficult task
someone could undertake.
I'll do it.
Carla, this is Norm's problem.
He has to do it himself.
You're absolutely
right, Frasier,
and I will.
Carla, go fire
Rebecca, please.
No, no, no, nope, Norm,
you've got to do it yourself.
You've got to do it
right away.
Otherwise, it'll just
exacerbate the situation.
You can do it, man.
Be dauntless
and implacable.
You're bad!
Yeah!
Like I'm mean?
Like I'm a mean machine?
Yeah!
Cooking!
Yeah! Yeah!
That's it.
All right!
( all shouting, roaring,
growling )
How'd it go?
Great. Uh...
we found a new voice for Carl.
( growls )
( phone ringing )
Norm, that's
our phone.
That's the 4-A hotline.
This is it.
A-A-A-A.
Baby, we're in business!
Just where
did your car break down?
Well,
our tow truck
should be there within
the next, uh, 30 to 40 minutes.
Whatever you do, don't leave.
I think I'll cruise by on
the way home and yell something.
Somebody confused
A-A-A-A with A-A-A.
How could
that happen?
( phone ringing )
4-A Painting.
You saw our ad
in the phone book first.
Could you hold just a minute?
Somebody wants
to paint something.
Hello. This
is Norm Peterson.
( clears throat )
Can we help you?
Uh-huh.
Uh-huh, yes, yes, sir.
I think, uh, I think
we can handle that.
Yes, thank you very much.
And I'd like to thank you
for making 4-A Painting
your foray into painting.
REBECCA:
Well?
Well, we have a job.
Yeah!
Oh!
A development company
has a small apartment
complex, okay?
They're having
a contract problem
with their regular
crew, so we're up.
Oh!
Yeah.
It's happening.
Well, it's just
a little eight-plex.
Okay? Now don't get crazy.
Norm, Ray Kroc
started McDonald's
with one
little hamburger.
Uh-huh.
Colonel Sanders started
with one little chicken.
We are on our way
to the top, Mister.
How does that make you feel?
Makes me feel like
having a Big Mac
and a bucket
of wings, actually.
That's my boy.
Well, you poor working stiffs
gonna hang around here
and breathe this
stagnant city air.
Not me, boy. I'm...
I'm gonna go climb
a mountain with Erin.
You want to give me a hand
with this here, please, Fras?
Sure, Sam.
You know, Sam, I admire
you, actually.
Yeah?
Most of us live such
sedentary lives.
You're out there
taxing your body.
It's-it's quite
an inspiration.
I know, Frasier.
Make me stop.
I tell you, man.
I can't catch my breath anymore.
I mean, all my muscles
are beginning
to form a conspiracy to kill me
because they want
to get some rest.
Here, here, here.
Let's get you out of this.
Oh.
Sam, if all this
strenuous exercise
is taxing you that much,
you know, perhaps it's time
to face the passing of the years
and learn to deal with it.
What do you mean?
Admit that I'm 30?
I wouldn't suggest
anything that drastic,
but, uh,
maybe you ought to just,
you know, slow it down a bit.
Hey, Sam,
you ready to go?
Listen.
Erin.
I ca...
Ooh, good one.
Uh, could you
do me a favor?
Sit down here, uh...
Listen,
sweetheart.
I-I'm not gonna go,
uh, climbing
the mountain with you.
What's up?
I guess I better
be honest with you.
It's just that all
this physical activity
we've been engaging in,
it's just
too much for... you.
I mean, come on,
I'm a guy who likes
to go, go, go.
( snaps fingers )
And, uh, sweetheart,
you're just slowing me down
a little bit. I'm sorry.
Sam, I'm really kind of relieved
to hear you say that.
I guess I need
to go
and find myself a guy who
wants to just join me
in a nice, hot bubble bath
and lie in bed
with me all evening.
See ya.
Gee, that was, uh, sort of
ironic, wasn't it, Sam?
I'm gonna go home
and take a little nap.
Maybe ease into
a bubble bath,
or a wheelchair.
Life is hot and so am I.
( phone ringing )
( makes sizzling noise )
Miss Howe, phone for you.
Should I take a message?
Just do it, babe.
That's my motto.
Women on the rise
make calls,
they don't take calls.
Miss Howe, guess who's
the new director of advertising.
Oh, God, really?
That's right, Henry Weinberg.
You know him?
Henry "5'3'-too-stupid-
to-shake-the-dandruff-
off-his-glasses"
Weinberg?
They didn't mention
his middle name.
Well!
There is some crap up
with which I will not put.
Well, I guess with 4-A on the
verge of making a breakthrough,
this is just the kick
in the pants I needed.
I am going to go up
to corporate headquarters,
I'm going
to go to the top floor,
and I am going to tell
the CEO himself what
I think of him
and his stinky company.
NORM:
Whoa, no, Rebecca,
don't you think you
ought to wait
till we have
at least two jobs?
No.
I believe
in you, Norm.
I believe in me.
I'm doing it, babe.
That's still my motto.
Excuse me, Sam.
( phone ringing )
Now, what is it
about Rebecca's history
that makes me think this
is going to be bad news?
4-A Painting.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
I knew that.
Yeah, well, thanks, anyway.
Damn, damn, damn.
What's the matter, Norm?
Well, that was
the developer.
They signed with their
painters and we're out.
CLIFF:
So, uh...
you gonna chase Rebecca down
before she quits her job?
I guess I really
should, huh?
CLIFF:
But then again,
she hates her job, so, well,
well, is it gonna be
that bad if they can her?
Maybe you're right.
I mean, what's the worst
that could happen?
I don't know,
just find somebody else
to run the bar, that's all.
Right.
Oh, my God.
My bar tab could fall
into the wrong hands.
Sammy, nice socks, man.
( coughing )
My God.
Are you all right?
I just ran.
Up 40 flights of stairs?
God, no. Just from the elevator.
Is this the CEO's office?
Yes, but he's busy.
Well, I've got
to get in there.
Well, you can't.
Well, I've got to.
I'm sorry.
Security.
( chuckles ):
Right.
Lady, by the time
your 80-year-old
geezer security guard
gets up here,
I could have
busted into that office,
sang the entire score
from Barber of Seville,
and been on my merry way.
Trouble?
Not if I leave this instant, no.
You tell Japan
I can play hardball, too.
Just do it.
Do it.
( phone hangs up )
Hey, that's my motto.
Now, Miss Harris,
I hear you're looking
for a job with the company.
My name's Miss Howe and I
already work for the company.
Then everything's settled,
show yourself out.
But-But-But-
But I had something to say.
Make it quick.
Mr. Anawalt, I have worked
for this company
for six years now.
For four of those,
I didn't get a raise.
Now not less than 36 people
have passed me
on the corporate ladder.
( mechanical whirring )
Oh, my God.
What's that?
Evidently,
an out-of-work window washer.
Well, you have
to admire his initiative.
So, you've worked here six years
and you've
been treated like hell. Hmm.
But I've never
been happier in my life.
And I'd never
want anything
to change.
Thank you for letting me
get that off my chest.
Damn it.
I'm doing it.
Mr. Anawalt, I have something
else to say, and this is it.
You wouldn't know a good
marketing executive
if one came up
and bit you on the butt.
Now I am better and smarter
than 50% of the people
that work here,
and if you can't see that then
you are blind or a buffoon.
Take your pick.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have to get back to Cheers
where I am sure
all my personal belongings
will be waiting for me
in a Hefty bag on the street.
Miss Howe.
What do you want now?
You have a lot of nerve
talking to me like that.
This company was built on nerve.
Not enough young people
have the guts
to stand up and say what
they're really thinking.
I've been looking for that
brave child who wouldn't
be afraid to say,
"The emperor has no clothes."
He's nude, sir.
Buck naked.
You think you could handle
a triple-raise in salary?
Oh, yes, sir.
You think
you could handle
an executive position
with my marketing team?
Yes, sir.
Think you could
start Monday?
Yes, sir.
Welcome aboard.
Oh, yes, sir.
Sir, th-this
is a dream come true for me.
( knocking at door )
Yes?
FBI.
Mr. Anawalt,
you're under arrest.
What's the charge?
Insider trading.
Come on, let's go.
Take him downtown.
No!
Read him
his rights.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Get those files.
Anything you say
can and will...
You can't do this.
This man is innocent.
No, they have me dead to rights.
Oh... Mr. Anawalt.
Mr. Anawalt.
I'll wait for you, sir.
I'll be standing right
here, waiting for you.
( thunder crashes )
I think I am the unluckiest
person on earth.
( rain pattering )
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org