Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
A little bit more to the
left there, Woody.
Yeah, ah, perfect.
Good, good.
How's that?
Nice.
(laughing)
A little bit more to
the right, Wood!
Yeah. Ah, ah, ah.
Yeah.
Good!
There you go!
How's that?
Perfect!
Well,
about six or eight
inches more
to the right
there, Wood!
How's that?
Yeah,
perfect.
You guys ain't even close.
Uh, you know,
I think maybe we need
a-a taller building.
What about the Prudential Tower?
Perfect!
See you over there.
(both laughing)
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Good afternoon, all!
Shut the door!
Why?
To keep out the
bitter cold.
Too late.
She got in.
Oh, I sense the mood
of the bar.
You're all suffering from
the winter blues,
the shortened
daylight hours,
the cold numbing weather,
the bleak sense of isolation.
It's what we in the psychiatric
profession call,
the jackpot!
Frasier and I have
a wonderful plan
to lift our spirits.
What, are you gonna buy some
toys and canned goods
and hand 'em out
to underprivileged kids?
Well, no.
We're checking into
a luxury hotel for
a getaway weekend,
just the two of us.
Oh.
Well, that'll make
some bellboys happy.
So, aren't you gonna
bring the kid?
Well, we would, but we find
that we make better parents
if we occasionally
take a break
from our parenting
responsibilities.
Hey, you don't have
to justify it to me.
You know, my parents ran off
for a year
with the Pentecostal caravan.
Oh, sure,
they called once in a while, but
they were speaking in tongues.
Yeah.
It was just by chance that
they came back at all.
Sam!
What are you doing?!
I'm working.
What does it look like
I'm doing?
Well, excuse me,
but this is the 12th!
Yeah. Well, I work
on the 12th.
Well I ovulate on the 12th!
How was I supposed
to know that?
We all knew it.
It's in the
newsletter.
Sam, just finish up
whatever you're doing,
and let's
get pregnant.
Boy, that's what I like
about Rebecca.
She's just an old-fashioned
girl, isn't she?
Mmm.
You cannot order me
to perform!
I don't want to have sex
with you, okay? No sex.
Who said that?
I don't believe this.
If we don't do it now we have
to wait a whole month!
I'm not in the mood,
all right?
Who's saying
these things?
Sam, what is wrong
with you?
I don't know.
Boy, you two sure argue a lot
for two people who
aren't in love
but want to have
a baby.
I mean, I don't know, maybe
that's normal for two people
who aren't in love
but want to have a baby.
I wouldn't know.
I've never known anyone
who wasn't in love
but wanted to have a baby.
Woody, shut up!
Hey, don't get me caught
in your sick web.
Come here, come here, hey,
just-just relax.
Remember
what the doctor said?
You know, how stress can
keep you from conceiving.
Well, all-all we do
nowadays is fight.
Oh, shut up!
No, you shut up!
You shut up!
Shut me up!
(shouting):
Shut up!
This is what
I'm talking about.
This is stress.
Oh, yeah?
Well, you've got ten minutes
to get yourself together and
get your bad attitude in order
and get over to my place
and we're gonna make a cute
little baby!
I hate her.
Now, at 2:00,
we have a choice
between a sumptuous
high tea
and a relaxing
Swedish massage.
Ah, 2:00.
Right about then I'll be jumping
into my mail truck,
ripping off my shoes
and trying to save my toes
from frostbite.
Hey, nobody held a
gun to your head
and said, "Be
a mailman."
Frasier, we have a problem.
I've just gotten off
the phone
with Frederick's teacher,
who informs me
that your son has come down
with a case of chicken pox.
No! I'm not giving up
my nonrefundable
getaway weekend!
Frasier, your
child is ill.
(sighing)
Oh, you're right,
of course you're right.
I'm-I'm ashamed.
And deservedly so.
Shall we?
I'm on my way.
Well, friends,
I've discovered a new way
of getting over the winter
blues.
Instead of enjoying
a luxury weekend
being coddled
in a four-star hotel,
I'll be bathing
an itchy,
whiney two-year old
in oatmeal.
Say, Fras, uh,
you know,
if you have trouble getting
rid of that reservation,
I sure know a couple who've
been under a lot of stress
and fighting a
lot lately,
and, you know, they could
benefit from a,
a nice weekend
in a hotel.
Thanks for thinking
of us, Sammy.
Yeah.
Listen, uh, I just
got to run home
and get my travel
iron real quick.
I'm not talking about you guys.
I'm talking about me
and Rebecca.
Yeah, stupid.
You should have
thought of that.
You made the same
mistake, pal.
Boy, we-we
really could have used
that weekend.
Come on,
what do you say, huh?
Please?
Oh, all right.
Here, take the room.
Conceive your child.
Go make.
Well, yeah, doesn't
it at least make
you feel better
knowing somebody's
having fun?
No.
I know it sounds petty,
but frankly I,
I can't think of anything
that would make me feel worse.
Uh, Frasier, dear,
I can't remember.
Have you ever had
the chicken pox?
FRASIER:
Oh!
I can always think of something
that would make him feel worse.
Hey, everybody.
Woody, uh, set me up
with a beer, will you?
Well, aren't you gonna finish
your mail route, Mr. Clavin?
Are you kidding?
There's too much snow
and sleet out there.
Besides it's getting
a little dark.
I don't blame you,
Cliff,
I hate going out
in this weather.
Hmm. Yeah, you guys are a bunch
of whining,
complaining weenies.
What, you like
this weather?
Oh, is that the topic?
Well, are we gonna let this
weather defeat us?
Or are we gonna fight back?
Hey, I'm with you, Doc.
So what shall we do?
Hey, you guys
ever hear
of something called
the Polar Bear Club?
Uh...
PAUL:
Well, it's great.
We used to do it all the time
where I grew up.
Bunch of guys get in their cars.
They drive down to the ocean.
They strip down
to their skivvies
and they run right
into the water.
Uh, I was thinking more
of a, uh, belching contest.
Oh, I don't know, uh,
loudest or longest?
PAUL:
Fine. Fine,
but you guys don't know
what you're missing.
Now, when we were kids
we didn't care if it was January
or February, we just jumped
in that ocean and swam.
It felt great.
It was like we scored one
against winter.
Hey, if it's good enough
for Mr. Krapence.
Well, are we up to it, men?
All right.
Well, uh, well,
it's one of the earthly thrills
I haven't tried yet.
Let's do it!
GUYS (chanting):
Polar Bear! Polar Bear!
Polar Bear...
So, Paul, where were you
brought up?
Honolulu.
Whoa!
Three bucks
for a lousy pack of gum.
REBECCA:
Sam, get away from
the honor bar.
Honor bar.
Oh.
Hey, sweetheart,
what do you think?
If it's a boy, we name it Sam?
Oh, I don't know.
You know, I
always thought
that naming your child
after yourself was like
saying you want him to grow
up to be just like you,
to like the things
you like,
to act the way
you do.
Okay, Sam it is.
Yeah.
Sam.
You know something,
Dad?
I really like my name.
Thanks, Sam.
Beautiful evening, isn't it?
Oh, sure is, Dad.
Say, how's that paper route
coming?
Just fine, Dad.
Before long,
I'll have enough saved up
to buy that
baseball glove.
Ah!
Tell me again what it was like
when you were
in the major leagues, Dad.
Oh, come on, you must be getting
tired of hearing that.
How could I ever
get tired
of hearing
about you, Dad?
(knock at door)
I'm coming.
Whoa.
Hope it's not
the honor bar police.
Oh!
I'm sorry. Wrong room.
I went out to get some
stuff for the kids,
and I guess I got lost.
I'm sorry about that.
Oh, yeah, excuse me,
if you don't mind me asking,
uh, how many kids
you got?
Three boys.
Wow.
Oh, that's great.
Yeah.
How long have you
been married?
20 years.
Wow.
Hey, listen, uh,
you don't have any advice
for a guy
who's about to start
his family, do you?
Well, you know,
it's,
like it's no big secret
what you need
to start a happy
family.
Love!
You know, if a man
and woman really
love each other, they pass
that love onto the kids,
and they'll grow up
strong and healthy.
Yeah, well, I mean,
I know love's okay
and everything,
but, uh, you know,
what about, uh,
those other important things
like friendship
and a sense of humor?
A sense of humor?
Yeah.
What's that gonna
get you?
I mean, look at
Martin and Lewis.
They had a sense
of humor.
But were they happy?
No, they weren't.
No, because it
takes love.
You've got a lot
of that, huh?
Me? No, I can't
stand my missus.
It's been 20 years of
living hell for me.
BOY:
Hey look, it's Dad.
What's the matter?
Can't you even find your way
back to the room,
you stupid idiot.
Those are the kids.
BOY 2:
Come on, Dad,
move your fat ass,
and give me 50 bucks
for the arcade.
On my good days, I,
uh, pray for death.
(chuckles)
Good luck to
you, son.
You're gonna need it.
Eh.
I bet that wouldn't have
happened
if he'd named one
of his kids Sam.
Yeah, Sam.
So how's that paper
route coming?
Oh, I've been
saving up.
Why don't we pull over
here to this market,
and I'll run in
and buy us a soda.
My treat.
Great idea, son.
I'll be right back.
Okeydokey.
(door shuts)
(laughs)
He's got that Malone swagger.
(indistinct shouting)
Floor it, Dad!
Why, what happened?
I robbed the store!
(alarm ringing)
But why?
I had to do something
to make up
for the lack of love
between you and Mom.
Now move your fat ass,
you stupid idiot!
(siren wailing)
Why'd you two
even have a kid anyway?
Well, we sort of thought
it'd be fun.
Fun?
I'll show you fun.
(gunshots)
Oh, no, no!
(tires screeching)
I got one!
Boy, did you see
that guy's head explode?
Whoa, these hollow point bullets
are great!
Hey, everybody!
I'm little Sammy Malone!
And my dad
was a Major League pitcher!
And he didn't love
my mother!
(laughing maniacally)
Oh!
(device whirring)
Okay, Sam, I give in.
If it's a boy,
we can name him Sam.
Sam?
Sam? Sam?
Oh, oh!
(tapping door)
Oh!
(door opening)
Here we go, darling.
I'm sorry.
I hope I didn't
ruin the moment.
Just, I was standing
out in the hall naked.
The door slammed
shut, and I didn't
have any place
else to go.
Anyway, if you... if you
could just loan me a robe,
I... I can wait back
out in the hall.
No, no, there's a robe you
can use in the bathroom.
Larry will go look for...
what's his name--
Sam?
Sam.
Sam-- oh, you
can't miss him.
He's a big galoot
with a lantern jaw.
Have you ever been naked
in a hotel hallway?
The sailors just come
out of the woodwork.
Don't worry, miss, I'll
find him and come right back.
REBECCA:
See, I was in the
bathroom taking a bath,
and I-I was
talking to Sam,
but he wasn't really
even listening to me.
I mean, I-I
guess he decided
to go down to the store and
get some gum or something.
I don't know, and it
was... it was like he...
he didn't even know
that I was... alive.
Boy, you sure
look beautiful.
(gasps)
Oh! Look at
all these flowers.
Oh, my... boy, you must
have a huge family.
No, those are
all from my guy.
Isn't he sweet?
Wow.
Well, mine's down
right now,
getting me some, uh,
gum... I think.
How long have you and Sam
been married?
Oh, actually, we
weren't even plan...
Six months.
(phone rings)
Excuse me.
Hello?
Oh, hi, honey.
It's my husband.
He's already down in the lobby?
No, he's calling me
from the elevator phone
just to tell me he loves me.
It's supposed to be
just for emergencies.
Oh, you are so sweet.
Oh, you're the
perfect couple, aren't you?
Oh, I bet you
had a beautiful wedding.
Oh, well,
all weddings are nice.
Wasn't yours?
Oh, yeah.
We had, you know,
lots of flowe...
and we had... a lot
of people came in...
(voice breaking):
a lot of people
from out of town.
If you'll excuse
me a minute,
I'm just gonna wait
outside in the hall.
Oh, hi.
Um, there's a
bellboy waiting
outside your room
with a passkey.
Okay.
Sorry I couldn't
find your husband.
But look what
I did find!
Oh, a bunny!
You have the sweetest lips in
the whole wide world, honey!
Mmm, you've got the
sweetest lips in the
whole wide world, honey.
(door opening)
Knock-knock! The little
woman is home.
Hey!
What are you
barging in here for?
You forgot to hang
the sock on the door.
That's because I didn't
want to take it off.
It was cold.
They turned the heat off.
Oh, yeah, they turned
the heat off
'cause you forgot
to pay the bill, pal!
What was I supposed
to pay it with-- love?
Oh shut up.
No, you shut!
You shut!
Shut...
Shut... up!
Shut...!
Come on, Sam,
get her out of here.
I'm ovulating.
Oh, that's great.
You couldn't tell me
15 minutes ago?
Come on, scooch, honey.
I've got my chores to do.
Yeah, go on, go on, go
on, go on, go on.
Oh, Sam, come on, hurry up,
let's make a baby!
Let's go in the other
room and do it!
This is the other room.
Oh God! Why are we so
poor and miserable?
Well, honey, we may be poor
and miserable,
but at least we can live
on love!
You shut up!
Oh, you shut up!
No, you shut up!
Shut me up!
Shut up!
Don't you use
that word "love."
Love has nothing to do
with this relationship!
I will use any word I want
in this house!
Love!
Love, love,
love, love,
love, love, love!
You foul-mouthed barren tramp!
Half man! Half man!
(Sam grunting)
Enough foreplay for you?
Yeah. Turn off the light.
I've got a poker game on
that table in five minutes.
You'd better make it quick.
Oh, yeah, that's
gonna be tough with you.
Hey, shut up!
You shut up!
Shut!
BOTH:
Shut up!
Could you leave now?
Oh, sure.
Hey.
Why aren't you home
watching your scabby kid?
My mother's come into town
to help take care of him.
So I thought I'd steal a few
moments and come here
and relax with my husband.
He's not here.
Better yet.
Where is my husband,
anyway?
Oh, uh, some of the guys
went to do something,
and he went along.
I suppose if they all
went to jump off a cliff
he'd do that, too.
I, didn't think of that, but
it probably would have worked.
(chanting):
Polar Bear!
Polar Bear! Polar Bear!
Hey, so you guys went
for your little swim?
Yeah, well, we drove
down there, you know,
we jumped into our
bathing suits, uh...
raced each other
along the beach
our feet hit the water...
And you chickened out, right?
Yeah, well, we prefer
to think of it
as coming to our
senses just in time
to save our goodies.
So none of you guys had the guts
to go through with it, huh?
Well, uh, one of us did.
Just a few more
steps, Dr. Crane.
Darling, are you all right?
(whimpers)
What did he say?
Sounded like "oil can."
Here, this should
help warm you up.
It must have been
a terrifying experience.
Oh!
It was positively surreal.
First, the cold water hitting
me like an electric shock...
dragging me down like
a palpable force.
And then when I was crawling
back onto the beach,
it kept at me, as though,
for all the world,
someone was actually pushing me
back into the frozen water.
Told you
it wasn't funny.
Where have you been, Sam?
Just, uh,
went for a walk,
you know, to get some
fresh air and everything.
So... ready
to make the baby?
Sure I am, if you are.
Oh, you are?
Uh, well, yeah.
All right, good.
Let's... let's,
get to it here.
Okay.
Okay, let's, let's, uh,
let's make that baby.
There's something wrong
isn't there, Sam?
Uh, yeah, there's something
I want to say and I-I...
I've been walking around
trying to figure out
how to say it and I, I guess
the only thing to do
is just, say it.
Sam, I don't love you.
I'm not gonna have your baby.
It would be
a big, stupid mistake.
What?
What were you gonna say?
Well, the same thing,
but a much nicer way.
You were?
Yeah.
I mean, you know, if we
don't love each other,
how can we raise a kid?
That's right!
Because it wouldn't be
fair to the kid.
I agree.
I mean, I mean, all
we've talked about
is how much we want
a baby. We, we, we.
We never even
thought about...
about how it would be
for a baby to have us.
I agree.
I mean, I think we got
to call the whole thing off.
Oh, I agree!
I can't believe this!
This is the first thing
we've agreed about
since the whole baby
thing came up.
I agree!
Oh, Sam I love you!
Oh, I love you, too!
I mean, I don't
"love you," love you.
No, I don't "love you,"
love you, either.
And Sam, we can still have kids,
just not with each other.
Yeah.
Mm.
Mm-mm. I'm sorry.
Old habit.
That's right,
we're just friends.
Yeah. Actually friends
don't open their mouths.
Oh. Old habit.
(sighs)
See you at work
tomorrow.
Yeah.
Bye-bye.
Sam, what's happening?
See you in a couple years, Dad.
Sam?
Where are you going?
You rotten kid!
Now listen, bring
back my wallet!
KID:
You're beginning
to waddle!