Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Hi, Dr. Crane.
FRASIER:
Hello, Woody.
Set me up, will you?
Coming right up.
Boy, you know,
no matter how many times
I come in here,
I can't get over
how silly you look
in that
ridiculous outfit.
Really?
I kind of like it.
People treat me with
a little more respect.
And there's
another bonus.
Saves me that
couple extra hours
I used to spend
every morning
picking out a shirt.
Yes, that can be
very time consuming.
Whatever happened
to the good old days?
Everything
was better.
Sam still owned the bar.
He wasn't out
circumnavigating the globe.
Yonder sat Diane
with a book.
Norm and Cliff were permanent
fixtures in this place.
God, how I miss
those hail-fellows-well-met.
Where has it gone, Woody?
Oh, hey, come
on, Dr. Crane.
It'll be all right.
( sniffling ):
Will it?
( blowing nose )
"Oh, death in life,
the days that are no more."
Who said that?
Who said what?
"Oh, death in life,
the days that are no more."
You did.
No, no, you see,
I mean who said it first?
Y-You said it both times.
You know, you're right, Woody.
Some things never change.
Especially the simple ones.
And don't you forget it.
( pats counter )
( piano plays )
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always glad
you came ♪
♪ You want to be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You want to go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same
♪ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Afternoon, everybody.
WOODY:
Norm!
Well, that was it, Woody.
Last chance; I'm out of here.
You caught them
by surprise.
I'm telling you,
they'll get it.
Woody, new crowd's
a bunch of stiffs, okay?
They're never going
to get it.
Hey, Woody.
Hey, Eddie.
( chuckling ):
How you doing?
Good, how are you?
Good. You know,
I passed Norm Peterson
on the stairs.
He didn't give me
the time of day.
Oh, it's 3:15.
Thanks.
Well, would you like a drink,
or did you just
drop in for the time?
Now that you mentioned it.
Say, is, uh, Carla around?
She said
she wanted to talk to me.
Said it was real important, eh?
She just went upstairs.
She'll be back down
in a minute.
EDDIE:
Good.
Well, we haven't seen
you for a while, eh?
Yeah, you know, Carla and I
kind of drifted apart.
I don't know,
I haven't seen her in months.
The usual?
You bet, Woody.
Good memory.
Thanks.
What is your usual?
Uh, just give me a beer.
Coming right up.
Sam around?
Oh, didn't you hear?
No.
Sam sold the bar to
some big corporation.
Bought a boat.
He's sailing around
the world with it.
Hey, well, good for Sam.
Thought he was supposed
to get married.
Well, Miss Chambers
went off to write her book,
only that didn't work out,
and last we heard,
she was out in Hollywood
trying to write for TV.
I'll bet whatever
she comes up with,
it'll be pretty
darn good.
( chuckling )
I bet it will.
Oh, Eddie?
Hey, Carla.
What did you want
to talk to me about?
Okay, see ya.
Yeah, see ya, Eddie.
FRASIER:
So, Carla,
what did Eddie say
about his impending fatherhood?
He wants
to think about it.
Mmm.
Well, my guess
is he'll do
exactly what I or any
normal, red-blooded men
would do in
this situation.
On the other hand,
you might actually
hear from him again.
No, I'm joking, I'm joking.
Come on, am I the only cut-up
left in this morgue?
FRASIER:
Come on!
Remember the old days
when things were fun?
Do you remember when the bar
was brimming with scamps,
and atop every barstool
perched an irrepressible
Merry-Andrew?
You remember that, Sam?
( alarmed screech )
Oh, my God, Sam!
Sam!
Sam, you're back!
Ah, yeah, you
bet I'm back.
Oh, look at... Woody!
( chuckling ):
Hey, man, how are you?!
Good.
Whoo! Look at this.
Hey, everybody.
Who are these people?
Things just aren't the same
anymore, Sam.
Boy, yeah, I'll say.
Can't believe the number
of changes around here.
Thank God
you're still pregnant, huh?
( laughing ):
Yeah.
( chuckling )
Who's the lucky guy?
Everybody but Eddie LeBec.
Eddie.
Yeah. You thirsty?
I'll get you a seltzer.
Yeah, get me
something to drink here.
Sam, what happened
to your around-the-world sail?
Well, it kind of lost
some of its appeal, Woody,
after I sank.
ALL:
Sank? Where?
Somewhere in the Caribbean.
Well, you must
feel terrible.
Well, no, not really.
You know,
a lot of good came out of it.
I discovered a reef
that nobody
had ever heard of,
and even named it after me.
"No Brains Atoll."
( laughter )
( Woody joins in )
Maybe you two
should start calling each other
in the morning.
Sammy,
it's part of
the new regime.
They're running this joint
like a military outfit.
Well, that's too bad.
Oh, no,
look at that.
What happened
to my photograph?
Never mind;
now you're back,
you can buy
back the bar,
things can be
the way they were.
I don't have enough money
to buy back an ice cube.
But anyway, you know, hey,
I just want to work here.
If I can't
be the boss,
I can at least be the
highest-paid employee.
Yeah, well, I don't know.
We got two bartenders
already, Sam.
You're kidding. Who?
Well, hold onto
your sides.
I'm going to introduce you
to Mr. Chucklepuss.
Hey, Wayne.
Sam...
this is Wayne;
Wayne, Sam Malone.
How do you do?
Hello.
Sorry, Wayne, but Sam is going
to take over your job.
Yeah, well,
there's no reason
why you can't hang around
and be a relief bartender.
I'm hardly a
relief bartender.
Yeah, that's right.
You know, uh, Wayne
has bored the hell
out of people
in some of the finest bars
and restaurants in Boston.
And as he'd be the
first one to tell you,
he can make any
drink known to man.
Oh, is that right?
Try me.
Okay.
Um, a moonbeam.
With or without
curaçao?
Serendipity, neat.
That only comes with ice.
Saddleback.
Onion or olive?
Both. Stick 'em
in your nostrils.
( chuckles )
Well, that's all right.
What the hell, I'll
just come at this
from another angle.
Uh, who's, uh,
who's running the show now?
Oh, no, no, I-I wouldn't
approach it that way.
No, this new manager
eats live sharks for breakfast.
Ah, but don't go by me.
I've hated every boss
I've ever had.
How can you say that?
I was your boss.
Yeah, right.
Oh, I was; come on.
Anyway,
I really hate her.
"Her"? Whoa-- a woman?
Oh, is she married?
Who'd marry her?
An unmarried woman.
Might take me all of five
minutes to get my job back.
Ha-ha-ha.
Why? What?
Oh, no, what, is she
one of those pasty-faced
little business school
graduates with thick glasses
and her hair pulled back
so tight
she hears through her eyes--
one of those?
She's coming right now.
Why don't you be
the judge of that?
Watch this.
I came up
with a few new grabbers
while I was out at sea.
Mm-boo-ah.
Miss Rebecca Howe,
Sam Malone.
Sam, Rebecca Howe.
How do you do?
Ah-voo-ah.
And to you.
If you'll excuse me.
Boy, you know,
she's almost as great-looking
as I am.
CARLA:
Almost.
Gee, I wonder what
she'll make me for breakfast?
Miss Tortelli, you have
a couple of customers
in the corner
that look like they're on
the verge of a good time.
You better hurry over there
and put your usual stop to it.
Yes, ma'am.
Good afternoon,
Miss Howe.
Hello, Woody.
I mean Wayne.
Did you lose
your name tag again?
Yeah.
But I found my pants.
Keep up the good work,
Woody.
Uh, excuse me.
Um, I want to apologize
for my behavior
back there.
I was led astray.
Somebody told me that you were
kind of a schnauzer.
Uh-- Sam Malone.
Yes. Yes.
You're the gentleman
that used to
own this bar.
Well, I heard you were
sailing around the world.
Well, I was going
to do that, but, uh,
something
kept pulling me back here,
and I just couldn't figure out
what it was, till now.
Which reminds me
of the other thing
I heard about you.
( chuckling ):
Oh, no...
Wait, let me set
the record straight here.
There have been
a lot of ridiculous,
unbelievable rumors
about my sexual prowess.
I just want to tell you
that most of them
are right on the money.
You know, Mr. Malone,
we've known each other
only seconds,
and I'm already tired of you.
Uh, w-w-wait
a minute,
wait a minute.
I know
you think you've had
just about enough excitement
for one day,
but there's more.
I'm back... and I'm ready
to jump behind the bar.
We're fully staffed,
Mr. Malone.
Jump somewhere else.
Uh, well, hold on a second.
Can't we, uh,
can't we discuss this?
We just did.
No, no, no,
I meant someplace private
where we could
slip out of our things
and say howdy.
REBECCA:
I don't know
if I find
your come-ons
disgusting or
merely pathetic.
I do know you're
giving me a headache
behind the eyes.
It feels like
a little insect
boring into my brain.
Oh...!
You didn't knock.
Habit.
Oh, my God.
Boy, this place
doesn't even look
like my office anymore.
Thank you; it wasn't easy.
How could you do this?
I mean,
you-you took away all the...
all the charm,
all the warmth.
Where's Dave?
"Dave"?
My moose head.
I set him free.
If he really loves you,
he'll come back.
This is, uh,
a lot of changes to absorb
in such a short time here.
Would you just get out of here?
( chuckling ):
Oh, hey, come on.
Lighten up.
Running a bar
should be fun, you know?
No, visiting a
bar should be fun.
Running a bar
is hard work.
Mr. Malone, I have had a great
deal of training and education
to get to this point,
and it's important to me
that I succeed;
that it succeed.
Well, in that case,
you're missing a great
opportunity here.
You see, having a sports
celebrity in the bar
is great for business.
I mean, you take a look
at your, uh...
You take a look
at your, uh,
at your major places
in Atlantic City.
They got your Willie Mays,
your Mickey Mantle...
It seems
a critical difference here
is that I've heard
of those people.
Oh, now...
Wait a second here.
You know, a lot of people
may not know this,
but I happen to be
quite famous.
Well, I don't care if
you're famous or not--
I don't need a bartender.
But you're
perfectly welcome
to come here
as a patron anytime.
And I personally
guarantee
you'll be treated
with every courtesy.
Unless you're waited on
by Miss Tortelli.
Now, if you don't mind...
Wait-wait a second here.
Um...
I sold this bar
because it had a lot of, uh,
bad memories for me.
But once I got away from it,
I realized that it had
a lot of good memories, too.
Mr. Malone, I really...
Please, please listen.
I'm not enjoying this, either.
There was, uh, one memory
in particular that
I have been
trying to shake.
( clears throat )
See, I was, uh,
I was afraid
that I was gonna
walk in here
today, and, uh...
see her face
everywhere I looked,
but instead, what I saw was
all these silly changes
you made in here.
I happen to think it's...
No, no, I mean,
it was good.
It helped me.
Look, what I'm trying to say is,
uh, this place
is the closest thing
I have to a real home.
I want to come back.
Please.
I'm very sorry, Mr. Malone.
I wish that I could help.
I see.
Wait a minute.
I guess we could use
another relief bartender
a couple of nights a week.
Well, it's a start.
I appreciate that.
Don't mention it.
You've had some tough breaks.
Oh, not so bad really.
You lost the bar.
And now you tell me
that's your home.
You lost your girlfriend.
And I guess you were
some sort of an athlete
who's having
a lot of trouble
getting over it.
Anyway,
I just hope working here
can help fill a little
of the emptiness.
Yeah, well, I'm sure it will.
Thanks again.
You're not doing this
out of pity, are you?
Pity?
Well, yeah. I...
I can't take this job
if it's just pity.
It's not just pity.
There are other things.
Oh. Well, good.
Like what?
Like...
It's pity.
Just pity?
Just pity.
No respect?
No.
No personal value?
Do you like my shirt?
Actually, that's a great shirt.
Well, you know
what they say.
Uh, pity and a nice shirt,
and the world's
your oyster, huh?
Well, uh, I got the job.
All right.
Wow!
Great.
Well, it's-it's only
part time, you know.
I mean, you do
have two bartenders.
Yeah, well,
maybe not for long.
I've already launched
"Operation Wayne
Down the Dwain."
Our boys are in the air.
( phone rings )
What do you mean?
Wha...
Cheers.
Mr. Malone, will you
fill out this W-4 form
and return it to me?
You bet.
Mr. Drake for you.
Give it to me.
No, wait a minute.
I'll get it in my office.
I locked myself out.
No, I didn't.
Well, so much
for her dress shield.
( chuckles )
Why?
Who-who's this, uh...
who's this Drake guy?
He's vice president of the
corporation you sold out to,
and she's got a third-degree
case of the hots for him,
and he doesn't know she's alive.
Yeah, I have my
doubts myself.
Mm.
Hey, Carla, you
used to, uh,
listen in on my
phone conversations.
Never. I'm insulted.
Show me how to
do it, will you?
Just press that third button,
pick up the receiver.
Well, no, I have not sent
that statement over yet,
but I'll send it right away.
No, it's no problem,
I love you.
I mean, I'd love to.
I'd love to.
Oh, by the way,
I hired a new relief bartender.
Kind of a sad case, really.
Sam Malone.
Used to play for the Red...
Yes, that's him.
Well, of course I tried
to get him full time.
Wonderful drawing card.
Yes, sir.
I'll sweeten the offer.
Of course.
Thank you.
Good-bye.
Rats.
Mr. Malone?
May I speak with you a moment?
Sure, what's up, Becky?
I've just been
in there thinking.
Mm-hmm.
You know, maybe I'm cutting off
the bar's association
with sports too quickly.
Oh, I don't know, Becks,
I think you were right
in the first place.
Besides, I, uh,
I don't think I could live
on a relief bartender's salary.
Well, what if I
made you full time?
I don't think I could survive
on a full-time bartender's
paycheck, either.
Does that, uh, include
all the usual perks--
medical,
dental,
horizontal?
Mr. Malone, we can
discuss the terms later.
The important thing
is that you come
back to work here.
Oh, I don't know.
( lackluster ):
Please.
Since you're
practically begging--
Ha!-- yeah, I guess
I could take the job.
Uh, you know, I'm gonna
hate the see Wayne
hit the streets.
Yes, I agree.
Woody, may I see you
in my office, please?
You bet, Miss Howe.
SAM:
No, no, wait, uh,
no, not Woody.
Uh, what about Wayne?
I happen to think Wayne is
a very talented bartender.
I don't think he's so great.
No, Ms. Tortelli?
CARLA:
No.
I bet there are a lot of drinks
he doesn't know how to make.
Impossible.
I know every drink there is.
Oh, yeah?
I say that a customer is gonna
come into this bar tonight
and order a drink
you've never heard of.
No way, never happen.
Well, if it does,
will you take a hike?
All right.
And if I win?
Then you get Sam's sailboat.
Deal, Sam?
It's a deal.
You're on.
I love sailing.
Oh.
This looks like a nice,
friendly tavern.
Heck, I'll give it a chance.
Norm!
Not now, you idiot.
Yes, sir.
Let's see.
What do I
feel like today?
What am I in
the mood for?
I guess a, uh,
Screaming Viking'd do it.
Don't you, uh
mean a Laughing Swede?
No.
What's the matter, Wayne?
You heard the man.
That drink
does not exist.
There's been
many a morning
I wished to
God it hadn't.
I've never heard
of that drink,
and no one
else has, either.
This gentleman
made it up.
Do I have to take
my business else...
No, please, sir.
Excuse me, Miss Howe,
I can make that.
You want the cucumber bruised?
Slightly.
Shall I get your coat, Wayne?
There is no such thing
as a Screaming Viking.
I assure you, Miss Howe.
Screaming Viking
over here, please.
I don't know what's going on
here, but I've been a barten...
Bartender, make it two.
Coming right up.
WAYNE:
Wait a minute!
There is no such drink
as a Screaming...
Uh, I think I'll have
a Screaming Viking.
Although, the, uh...
the name itself
is a misnomer,
since the Vikings
were not actually
the murderous plunder...
Would you shut up!
And welcome, stranger.
You know what I'm
in the mood for?
Screaming Viking.
PATRONS:
Screaming Viking!
Yeah, Screaming Viking.
Miss Howe!
I'm sorry.
I gave it a shot.
But obviously,
I am not liked
by the customers
or the employees.
Screaming Viking!
I haven't been called that
since my honeymoon.
Mr. Malone?
May I see you in my office?
Yes, ma'am.
Whoo-hoo.
Here's to the best
Screaming Viking in town.
( chuckles )
( all grumbling )
Here you go.
What's this?
A severance check.
Please be a stranger.
Why? Wha...
What did I do?
In baseball-ese, Mr. Malone,
you showed me up.
You and the rest
of the katzenjammer kids.
Good-bye.
Now, wait a minute.
What about that conversation
you had with your, uh...
My what?
Your-your heart.
Your heart.
Y-You pity me.
You've spent your pity,
Mr. Malone.
Okay, fine.
Yeah, you know, I don't
want your pity, anyway.
You know, I can live
without this job.
I'll find another way
of supporting myself.
And my mother.
I mean, now that
the doctor's only giving me
six months to live.
Come on!
Please listen.
I swear to you, nothing like
this'll ever happen again.
Come on, a decent boss
would give me a second chance.
And I'll tell
you something, I...
Don't say, "A guy would."
I wasn't gonna say,
"A guy would."
But he would.
All right.
I'll give you another chance.
All right, thank you.
Thank you.
But I want to make
something very clear.
Okay.
You've just got
one chance left.
Mm-hmm.
And as far as
I'm concerned--
again, in baseball-ese--
it's the bottom of the ninth,
you've got two outs,
two strikes,
and no balls.
Okay, all right.
I'm still at the plate,
though, right?
Right.
All right.
Now, I think Woody
would probably appreciate
a little help out there.
Yes, ma'am.
Can...
Can I ask you
just one small favor?
What?
Can I see you smile?
Why?
You know, it'd just be
a friendly gesture,
to prove
there are no hard feelings.
Oh, come on,
I bet you're the kind of girl
that lights up a room
when she smiles.
That's stupid.
I'll give you a little help.
Watch this, watch this.
Hmm.
Gee, I was wrong.