Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
MAN ( on radio ):
And we're on the help line
with...
Oh, me.
Me, hi.
Uh, hello?
My name is Reb...
punzel.
And uh, I'm sorry if I sound
a little bit nervous,
but this is the first time
I've ever called a radio show
for help.
But I have this problem,
and it's so horrendous
that I didn't have anyplace else
to turn.
Now, I have this new boss
at work,
and he's incredibly rich
and he's incredibly powerful,
but he is also sort of a, um...
Oh, God, how could I put this
without sounding mean?
Um... a weasely little twerp.
Anyway, this guy asked me out,
and to get out
of going out with him,
I told him that I was going
with this guy named Sam...
son.
So, Samson, who can be
an incredible jerk sometimes,
told my boss, the twerp,
that we broke up.
All right, so my boss...
The twerp.
Right.
My boss asked me out, and you're
not going to believe this.
He proposed to me.
I mean, the only thing
I could think of to do,
without jeopardizing my career,
was to tell my boss
that I was still in love
with Samson.
But I cannot
keep avoiding the guy.
As an example, he is upstairs
right now having lunch at Mel...
Monico's. Melmonico's.
The thing is,
that now I'm worried.
Do you think
I did the right thing?
I think so.
Now, did you have
a gardening question?
You called
the Dr. Green Thumb Show.
Uh, just a reminder, Rapunzel.
Plant your bulbs early.
( laughing )
( piano plays )
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You want to go where everybody
knows your name. ¶
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Oh, yeah, I know, Norm,
that's a...
that's a beautiful birdie
you got there on the ninth.
Thank you.
Oh, so you guys
were playing golf today, huh?
Yeah, nothing like bashing
the old pill around, huh?
Young Woody Nicklaus here
broke 80.
All right; good man.
Hey, really?
You shot under 80
for 18 holes?
Well, no actually, it was 17.
Yeah, the 18th hole
is the windmill.
If you're stupid
enough to play that one,
it's going to eat your
little colored ball.
You were playing
miniature golf.
Oh, yeah.
Do you have any idea
how long those real
golf courses are?
TEAL:
Gentlemen,
that was a pretty poor showing
for a power lunch.
Ralph, you're going to have
to start doing something more
than just taking up space
at these meetings.
How does a guy so young
get to be
so incredibly powerful?
I just try to maintain
a cheerful attitude
and not abuse my position.
I recently read a Forbes profile
on our young Mr. Teal.
CLIFF:
Oh, yeah?
Apparently, he started
with his father's firm,
kicked the old guy out
when he was 17,
hasn't looked back since.
Big deal.
Did he ever win a purple ribbon
in the Jefferson County
Spelldown?
Anathema.
A-N-A-T-H-E-M-A.
Touché, Woody.
Touché. T-O-U-C-H-E,
and a little slanty line--
touché.
Excuse me.
Is Miss Howe in?
She's in her office;
do you want me to go get her?
No, don't bother. Dennis?
Miss Howe?
Oh, no.
Oh, yes.
The master of the universe
awaits your presence.
Dennis, I-I
sense bitterness.
I've never heard you
talk like this before.
Oh, I could tell you stories,
honey.
Here she is, sir,
per your request.
So, how's the greatest
love story ever told
working out?
Sam and I are just
as steady as ever.
As steady as yesterday
when you broke up twice?
Things are different.
Uh... It's ...
it's more serious.
I won't consider it
really serious
until I see a ring
on your finger.
Well, what I meant
by serious is, um...
is that Sam
and I are engaged.
Hey, everybody.
Congratulations,
Sammy.
Oh? What for?
She was just a stewardess.
Stop joking,
you big lug,
and come here.
Can you excuse us
just a second, Martin?
We have to discuss
our silver pattern.
Dennis, get me the papers
on the Trackwell merger.
Just keep your stupid
mouth shut and smile.
We're engaged.
Oh. Great. Well,
let's begin the honeymoon.
Sam, we're
not actually
getting married.
Well, that's even better.
I can enjoy the honeymoon.
Come on, Sam.
It's just a way
to get Martin
off my back.
Oh, dear... you mean
the problem-free relationship
suddenly
developed a glitch?
I can't very well tell
the future president
of the corporation no.
I'd never work again.
Please, Sam, just
help me out here
just until Martin
gets over me.
Come on.
Oh, I don't know.
You know, if I go
along with this,
will you go
to bed with me?
Let's put it this way.
If you don't
go along with this,
I will never go
to bed with you.
Wait. All right.
So, in other words,
if I don't...
No. Wait, wait.
That means if you...
All right,
this is me,
this is you,
this is the bed.
Sam, just do it.
No, I don't...
Yeah, I don't
personally
think we need the
salad forks, honey,
but you're
the entertainer
in the family.
Well, I suppose
congratulations are in order.
Oh, well, thank you, sir.
Yeah, I never
thought I'd get her, but...
it looks like Becky here
is going to be
my ever-loving,
everlasting little
bundle of kisses.
Little bundle
of open-mouthed kisses.
Isn't he sweet?
I'd like to propose
a toast to the happy couple,
and especially
to Rebecca Howe--
the only thing I ever
wanted and haven't gotten.
Yeah. Same here.
Um... would you excuse me
just for a minute, please?
Hey, Sammy,
quite a squeeze-a-rooni
you got there, huh?
I had no idea.
Oh, Sammy,
tell me it isn't true.
Carla, come on.
It's not true.
I knew that.
You're a lousy actor.
I'm pretty good though, huh?
Well, actually, Carla,
as a student of the theater,
I have to correct you.
What you were doing there
is not called acting.
It's called improvising.
Shut up, Woody.
Now, that would
be directing.
So when's
the big event?
Well, I was kind of
planning on tonight.
You're getting married tonight?
Married? Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were talking
about something else.
It is definitely not
going to be tonight.
Look, the important
thing is
that we are as one
forevermore.
Honeys till the end of time.
Well, Sam,
I guess
you wouldn't be interested
in spending the next month
tending bar at a seaside resort
we reopened in Cancun?
I'm there.
Whoa, hey.
Sam!
Oh, right. Yeah.
Um, that wouldn't be fair
to Rebecca here.
Who could we get
to replace me?
Oh, no problem.
I'll make an exchange
with the bartender down there.
Well, then, I'm out of here.
Hey, I'll see you in a month.
Adios, amigos!
REBECCA:
Sam?
Sam!
Martin, is this your little way
of breaking Sam and me up?
It's a bona
fide offer.
I need an
experienced
man down there.
I know what
you're thinking.
You're thinking that,
when Sam gets down there,
and he's all alone,
he's going to start roving.
Well, I can
tell you this.
You can send Sam away
for a month or a year,
and he will
only think of me.
Excuse me.
Do they have drug stores
down there,
or should I pack an extra bag?
Ramon, Ramon, Ramon,
you have been a terrific
replacement for Sammy.
I'm really going to
be sorry to see you go.
Although
I will enjoy
watching you walk
up the stairs.
( speaking Spanish )
Mi Carlita...
Adios, amigos.
Bye-bye.
CLIFF:
Take care of
yourself, Ramon.
I don't know what
that Latin lover said,
but I sure dig
the way he said it.
Well, if you ask me,
Ramon's a lot more Latin
than lover.
Yeah, you know,
study after
study show
that the old
sons of Spain
just don't have
our sexual prowess.
Cliffie, nobody
has your sexual prowess.
Thanks, Norm. You know,
it seems that
the tropical sun
dries out a man's
vital juices.
You ever
seen a raisin?
Have you ever seen a doctor?
Sam was supposed
to be in hours ago.
Has anybody heard from him yet?
No one's heard a word
from him in weeks.
Hello, Rebecca.
Heard from
Sam recently?
Have I?
Every hour on the hour.
It's almost embarrassing.
Hmm. Well, then
what's happened
seems all
the more curious.
What's happened?
According
to our reports,
Mr. Malone missed
the corporate jet home.
Uh... well, I'm sure
there's a simple explanation.
I'll just call Cancun
this afternoon
and find out
what the trouble is.
We have Cancun on the line.
You are so helpful.
I am five months
from retirement.
Hello.
Sam, hi.
This is Rebecca.
You must have
missed your plane,
you naughty boy.
So when should
I pick you up
at the airport,
my darling? Sam?
Sam?
Hello?
( loud music playing )
Sam? Sam?
Hello? Operator?
O-operator?
Yes, I was just talking
to my fiancé and I was...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Uh, me talk-o to me boy-o
amigo in Cancun,
and we were cut off-o.
It's a beautiful language,
isn't it?
What?
You no operator?
You boose boy?
Oh, bus boy.
Yeah, okay, adios.
No, no, adios.
Damn.
Thank you, Dennis.
Rebecca, you're not
losing anything in Sam.
I hear he hasn't stopped
fooling around
since he got down there.
You had him watched?
I didn't have to.
The man's escapades
have become legendary.
The Indians in the mountains
sing a folk song about him.
Rebecca, let me help you take
your mind off your problems.
I'll pick you up for dinner,
maybe a drink,
a trip to Paris, a few laughs.
Martin, not tonight.
I-I really need time
to get over this.
Well, then tomorrow night.
I won't take no for an answer.
I got him, I got him.
I caught my little
Ricardo Montalban.
Just as he was
getting into a cab.
Go get your
little apron on, honey.
Carla, how come you called Ramon
Ricardo Montalban?
Because his tight little chinos
are so packed with rich,
Corinthian leather.
Oh, yeah, I see,
now that you mention it.
NORM:
All right,
I hate to change
the subject,
but I don't know
if anyone else recognizes
we seem to have
a little problem here.
Oh, you need
another beer, Mr. Peterson?
Okay, we have two problems.
Uh, there's
a distinct possibility
that Sammy may never come back.
FRASIER:
Frankly,
I don't blame him.
Beautiful weather,
miles of beaches...
Yeah, chicks.
FRASIER:
No suits,
no rules, no tight shoes
to pinch your feet.
Yeah, that'd be good
to get out of the city
a little bit, wouldn't it?
Oh, yeah.
I got five vacation days
coming to me.
Oh, say, it may be
a crazy idea,
but why don't we
go down there, too?
Lay out in the sun
for a while,
work on that old
mañana attitude?
Should we do it?
What do you say,
guys?
Ah, maybe tomorrow.
( mariachi music playing )
Excuse me, bartender,
can we get a couple of
pina coladas over here?
Sure thing.
Let me just finish
making this margarita.
So, anyway, Margarita...
Buenos noches, amigos.
¿Que tal, Pepe?
Hola, Pepe!
Los calzones, Sammy.
Esa agua esta muy fría.
Good one, man,
good one.
Let's go, Sam.
We're leaving.
I have a cab outside.
Beckita, what
are you doing here?
I took the liberty
of stopping by your room
and packing your bags.
I can't believe you didn't pack
one pair of underpants.
Now come on, we're going home.
Home? Sweetheart, I'm...
This is home.
I love this place.
Sam, we are leaving
and we are leaving now.
I am not going to
get stuck with Martin.
Oh, right, right.
The little one.
Uh, sweetheart, yeah,
I got to tell you,
I think it's high time
you told him the truth.
I can't tell him the truth.
I'll get fired.
Well, they, uh,
they got plenty
of good job opportunities
down here.
Can you paint pictures
on turtles?
Sam, I am asking you, not
as a woman speaking to a man,
I am asking you as a friend.
Please, Sam.
When you look back
at all the countless,
selfish, petty,
vindictive things you've
done in your life,
wouldn't it be wonderful
if you could say
for one brief moment
that you did something
good and fine?
This shouldn't be turning me on,
should it?
Oh, that's it.
Cerveza, Sammy.
Be right there, Pepe.
If you won't listen
to my pleas,
maybe you'll listen
to this.
You're coming with me, Sam.
Now let's not do
anything crazy here.
I bet you wish you had
those underpants now.
Listen, I'm gonna just reach out
my hand here real slowly.
I want you to relax
and take your finger
off the trigger.
Just put the gun in my hand.
I'm sorry.
It's not loaded.
I mean, I'm sorry, period.
It's not loaded, period.
It's-it's all right, everybody.
It was just a... just a joke.
( all groaning )
I'm gonna go now.
W-w-where do you think
you're going?
You can't just walk out of here.
You pulled a gun on me
in a resort in the middle
of a foreign country.
They have laws,
you know?
Don't they?
Good-bye, Sam.
Pobrecita.
SAM:
Oh, no,
she's like that all the time.
I mean, this isn't even
a bad day for her.
¿Son todas las babes de Boston
locos como esta?
No, no-- she's kind of
the queen of loco.
I mean, she was nutty
the first day I met her.
She's... she's hyper.
You know what I mean, hyper?
All she thinks about
is her stupid career
and she keeps blowing it.
And I can't tell you
how many times
I've had to pull that
lady's fat out of the fire.
Get this, you know.
This is her latest escapade.
She wants me to pretend
to be her fiancé,
'cause she doesn't
want to marry
this pint-size executive
back home.
What do I get
for my troubles?
A gun stuck in my face.
You know what
the sorriest thing is?
Me.
I still like her.
Why is that, Pepe?
Nice buns, Sammy?
You people see things
so clearly.
Hey, uh, Ramon.
Listen, we're heading over
to Casa de Clavin
for our weekly
video film classic.
You want
to take Sammy's seat?
I'm busy.
Yeah, well,
I've got it rented
for a couple of days.
How about tomorrow night?
Uh... I am busy.
Yeah?
Sorry.
Yeah, well,
he's a nice guy, that Ramon,
but he's no Sammy,
is he, Norm?
But then again, Cliffie...
he's a lot more Sammy
than you and I will ever be.
Hey, boss, last of the riffraff
just cleared out of here.
You want to lock up?
Sure, Carla, can you
show me how a key
works again?
Oh, brother, you been
in there drinking all night?
Carla, I am celebrating.
I think that I am the luckiest
woman in the world.
I'm going to marry
the geek tycoon.
And you know, he's going
to give me money and jewels
and all sorts
of rich stuff.
I am going to be so rich,
I can stink
and no one
will even tell me.
I'm sure you two
will be very happy together.
I'm sure I will, too.
I'm gonna spend
the rest of my life
living in big,
old mansions,
wearing fabulous clothes
and being real nasty
to the help.
You feeling sorry
for yourself
because you have
to marry a rich guy?
Boo-hoo, boo-hoo.
Come on, Carla.
You wouldn't trade
Eddie for him.
I'd trade Eddie
for a ride in his car.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have a Spam casserole
lurking in the oven.
Hey, we're the same size.
Hi, honey, you're home.
See?
Aren't I gonna make you
a wonderful wife?
You've been drinking,
haven't you?
Just a sippy or two
to celebrate.
Well, now that Sam's
out of the picture,
I assume that leaves
the path clear for me.
Shall we proceed?
Rebecca...
will you do me the honor
of becoming my wife?
I guess.
Outstanding.
Shall we set a date?
Whenever. I don't care.
You're about to see
my impulsive side.
This is Justice
of the Peace Wilson,
these are four dozen
long-stemmed red roses.
I'm the perspective
bridegroom.
Guess what you are?
Dead meat
on a hook?
Um...
Martin, you can't do this.
My parents aren't here.
Your parents aren't here.
My mother passed away,
and, uh,
you know my father.
Dennis?
Welcome to the family.
MARTIN:
Rebecca,
you should know by now
that I haven't gotten
where I am
by waiting for things
to come to me.
As far as I'm concerned,
this is a done deal.
So let's make it legal.
Hey, baby, I'm back!
Call off the Federales.
Sam!
I couldn't stay away from you
for another second, my darling.
Kiss me.
Oop...
Hey, did I interrupt
something here?
No, Martin and I
were just going
to get married,
but now that
you're back...
Oh... Martin.
I'm so sorry.
This is really
tearing me apart.
But I need
to follow my heart.
Well, if that's what you feel,
Rebecca, you've got it.
I hope you two
will be very happy together.
But remember: you blew it
in a big, big way.
I hope this won't affect
our business relationship.
Why should it?
Gee, when I sober up,
I'm probably going
to worry about this.
Better not let that happen.
I don't believe this.
You came all the way back here
just for me?
I just feel so terrible
for everything I ever said
or did to you.
Well, gee, now, there must be
some way you can thank me.
You're right, Sam.
I think the time
has finally come.
Yeah.
You've waited long enough.
Oh...
Oh, no.
That's funny.
Usually they pass out
afterwards.
No, no, no.
I am a gentleman.
But I may never
have this chance again.
( humming )
( laughing )
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/64sr
Help other users to choose the best subtitles