WOMAN ( on TV ):
You're up pretty late,
aren't you?
Nothing better to do
than watch TV?
Feeling a little lonely
in the big city?
Come and join the party.
Call 5, double five, P-R-T-Y,
for the best party line
in Boston, that's right.
There are lots of fun people
on the line right now
waiting for you to join
in their fun talk.
Only $2.00 plus toll if any,
for three minutes
of party line madness.
Why don't you try it?
There's only one way to find out
what sort of wild people
call the party line.
Dial 5, double five, P-R-T-Y.
( TV shuts off )
Hi, my name's Woody
and I'm from Indiana and I...
Oh, hi, Mr. Clavin.
Hey!
( piano plays )
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You want to go where everybody
knows your name ¶
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
How about over here
by the bar, Miss Howe?
Do we really have to do this?
What's going on?
I'll be right with you.
The Globe's doing an article
on women who run pubs.
Now he wants
to take my picture.
I really dread this, Sam.
Why?
Because I get
so tensed up
in front of a camera.
All of a sudden
I start looking like something
the cat coughed up.
Ooh, can I have
an eight-by-ten
for my mantelpiece?
How about a two-by-four
for your bridgework?
Listen, let me give you
a few hints here.
I had a lot of pictures taken
of me when I was playing ball.
Just relax, take
the tip of your tongue
and wet your lips.
Good.
Now, wet my lips.
Oh, Malone!
Uh-oh, you're tensing
up now, just relax.
( camera shutter clicks )
Thank you.
No, wait a minute!
You can't use that picture!
I had my tongue
sticking out.
Can I have three
copies of that?
Now, please, take
another picture and
warn me this time.
I want this to look
natural and spontaneous.
Come on, come on.
You gotta relax.
Think of something
ridiculous.
Like what?
Like him.
( giggles )
Hey, you're better than
the Snoopy puppets
I use with the kids.
Thanks, Miss Howe.
Boy, oh, boy.
How many times have I walked
through that door, huh?
Yep, good-bye old bar.
Take care, old stool.
Where you
going, Cliff?
I'm going in
for surgery tomorrow.
Who knows if I'll ever
walk into God's blue sky again.
It's all up
to the man upstairs.
Vic, the maître d'
at Melville's?
No, Woody.
No, never mind.
What, what are you, what
are you talking about?
Well, it took
a lot of expensive
and complicated
tests, Sammy,
but they finally
found out
what that pain was
in my abdomen.
The experts call it
appendicitis.
( all chuckling )
Woo, Cliffie,
come on.
Now, that's a simple...
you know, I had it
when I was a kid.
There's nothing
to it.
I actually liked
having my appendix out.
My parents told me I could
have all the ice cream I wanted.
No, Woody,
I think you're
talking about tonsils.
Well, it was a long time ago,
Sam, but I'm pretty sure
it was ice cream.
So when are you going in?
It's tomorrow.
Now, look, I want you guys
to promise me, you know,
if I don't pull through
this thing, you know,
there'll be no big,
emotional scenes,
no eulogies,
just a small
memorial service
where you guys sit around
and tell the funniest
stories about me.
Okay, I got dibs
on this one.
Great news, everybody!
Lilith and I have just gotten
back from the auto club.
LILITH:
We have the complete
itinerary for our
motoring trip
through the U.S.A.
in our Chevrolet.
It's a Mercedes, dear.
That was a joke, Frasier.
Oh, I forgot I
married a madcap.
Hey, listen, folks,
nobody's really interested
about your little
motor trip.
We're talking about
my upcoming surgery.
So, now,
where was I?
So you gonna see
the Grand Canyon?
Yeah, don't miss Yosemite.
WOODY:
Listen, if you've go
to the alligator farm
outside Tallahassee,
tell Ivar Woody
says hey, hey.
FRASIER:
Of course. Okay,
gather around everybody.
I'll show you the interstates
we're gonna take.
Sam, can I talk to you
for a minute?
Sure, have a seat.
Frasier and I
will be covering over
4,500 miles round trip,
and I think it's only fair
that I share
some of the driving.
However, I am handicapped
by one tiny thing.
I've never operated
a motorized vehicle before.
You don't know
how to drive?
I always meant to learn,
but when I was a teenager,
I was too busy having fun.
Would you teach me, Sam?
Uh, well, what
about Frasier?
We're too close.
I need someone
to whom I have
no emotional
attachment whatsoever.
So as a friend,
would you do me this favor?
Yeah, why not?
When do we start?
The sooner the better.
All right.
Um, how do you
think I'll do?
I've never had a woman in
a car that didn't do great.
Wonderful.
You teach me to drive,
I'll help you
with your sense of humor.
Here's where you've
got to be real careful.
You see, I-75 runs
right down here into I-30.
Now, if you don't stay in that
far left lane,
it's hello, Tulsa!
Well, I've got to be
moseying on, you guys.
I'll, you know,
see you later.
I'm going under the knife
in about 12 hours or so.
Yeah, look, don't feel
that you have to go
out of your way to stop by,
you know, and visit,
New England Presbyterian,
Room one niner four,
visiting hours between
11:00 and 9:00.
Cliffie, I'm sure everything
is going to be just okay.
Oh, yeah, well, no,
sure, there's no...
You know, I'm in the hands
of skilled professionals.
It's not like the old days,
is it, you know, where
they give you a shot of whiskey,
lick the scalpel and they
go a-carving, huh?
You know, the same is true
in my profession.
Time was when a person's
behavior deviated in any way
from what society
considered normal,
the town barber
would take a rusty drill,
bore a hole in your head,
and let the evil spirits out.
Well, it's a good thing we
didn't live back then, huh?
Yeah, you'd be looking
pretty much like a whiffle ball
by now, wouldn't ya?
I don't believe you guys.
That's it.
I'm leaving.
Come on.
Fine! Fine!
Who needs your kind
around here anyway?
Gentlemen!
Now I think that this bar
is big enough for people
who like The Addams Family
and The Munsters.
Okay, all right, fine.
I'll take back what
I said about Cousin It.
That's okay, it was in
the heat of the moment.
All right.
Hey, hey, hey,
here's that article
they interviewed
Rebecca for.
Look at that.
Oh, hey, how's
her picture?
There isn't
one.
Oh, God, it was so crummy
they didn't even print it.
Oh, wait a minute.
there it is, right
there on the back.
How is it?
ALL:
Eww!
Is it that bad?
No, Norm got cheese whiz
all over the paper.
Actually,
the picture's not bad.
Not bad?
It's great.
Let me see that.
This is a decent
picture of me.
Look at that!
I'm gorgeous and sexy.
And dead as a doornail.
What?
You're in the obituaries.
Oh, God!
No, don't feel bad, it says
you died in bed.
I didn't know you helped
build the Panama Canal.
Woody, that is someone
else's obituary.
I am not dead.
I am a living,
breathing human being.
I know that.
So where'd they put
all the dirt, anyway?
Excuse me, can I get
someone to sign for these?
Yo, right over here.
Let me see these.
Oh, they're from
corporate headquarters.
Did we do well last month?
"Dear friends at Cheers,
we mourn the loss
"of Rebecca Howe.
At last her pain is over."
I'm going to call them up,
straighten this out
before they start making
funeral arrangements.
If I were you,
I'd have a closed casket.
Yeah, well, why Grandpa Munster
never won an Emmy,
I'll never know.
Come on, maybe it's because
he stole his whole character
from Uncle Fester.
Oh, Lord, is this
still going on?!
This has got to be one of
the stupidest arguments
I've ever heard
since I started
coming to this bar.
Hey, we resent that.
Yeah, why wasn't
it the stupidest?
Well, frankly, it lacks
meaningless statistics
and inane historical trivia.
Say, where is Cliff anyway?
Yeah, is he still
in the hospital?
Uh, I don't know,
how's he doing?
I thought you were
going to go see him.
Well, I tried, I mean, I got
as far as the hospital lobby,
but you know, the smell of
alcohol makes me really queasy.
Well, I, you know, I was gonna
go see him, but I got to wait
until I have a night off here.
Woody? How about you?
Oh, that's what this string
on my finger is for.
What the heck is this one for?
Surely somebody gave him a call
or sent flowers, a card?
Carla?
Yeah, right.
( muttering excuses )
Look, this is terrible!
Don't you realize
that since Cliff's
mother moved to Florida,
we are his sole support group?
This desertion
in his hour of crisis
could cause him deep
emotional scars.
So why didn't
you go see him?
Well, what,
I don't have a life?
I think we ought to go
down there right now
and tell Mr. Clavin
how we feel about him.
Don't you think that
would be a little cruel?
I mean, the guy
just had an operation.
Actually, visiting
hours are over.
We're going to have
to wait until tomorrow.
Yeah.
Hey, wait a minute.
Cliff's at New England
Presbyterian.
That's on my rounds--
I have to go by there tonight.
I can get in to see him.
Well, great, why don't
you go buy a card
and date it yesterday,
sign all our
names to it, okay?
Slam dunk.
Is that going to be enough?
Come on, it's just
an appendectomy.
They're taking out
a useless organ.
He's chock-full of those.
Ah, excuse me,
I'm Dr. Crane.
Uh, where is Mr. Clavin?
He was just discharged.
Oh, great, just my luck.
I'm the one who gets to run all
over town to find a stupid card
for the idiot, Clavin,
and he isn't even here.
Just a token of
how much we care.
Don't you want
to read the card?
I, uh, just
forgot my jacket.
Well, you're going to hear it
anyway, Cliff.
"Glad you're feeling better.
"So sorry you were ill.
"If you thought things
were bad before,
wait till you get the bill."
Oh, that zesty greeting card
humor, huh?
( chuckling )
Well, gee, Cliff,
I was just trying to help.
You want to help?
Well, uh, maybe you
can help with this.
I, uh,
I been doing some
soul searching here.
A man gets a lot of
time to think with a
tube up his nose, and...
What I... what I
realized is that, uh...
I'm alone in this world.
I mean, uh, nobody
came to visit me.
Not one of my so-called
friends out there
even bothered to
walk through that door.
Look, and they all feel terrible
about it, Cliff.
They lead busy lives.
They just couldn't find
the time.
Come on, Doc, cut the
malarkey, will you?
They found the time
to visit Sammy
when he was
in the hospital.
And Carla when she
had the twin.
Normie, when he went in
for the butt tuck...
I know why they
didn't visit.
It's because it was me.
No, Cliff.
Oh, yeah, come on, Doc.
They don't like me,
they don't really care.
Come on, you can
tell me the truth.
Go ahead, right between
the eyes, give it to me.
Well, I suppose you're not
the most popular person
in the bar.
Oh, and you are, huh?
Doc, you suppose
comments like that
are part of the problem?
Could be.
God, I don't believe it.
I mean, all these years,
and I never realized it.
( chuckling softly )
Could I really be
that insensitive?
( man groaning )
Cliff.
Oh, God, I am insensitive.
Hey, sorry there, old timer.
What can I do about it?
A little therapy
might not be amiss.
Oh, no, Doc, isn't there
something better than therapy?
I mean, you know,
something
a little quicker;
you know, a little easier.
We're talking about a major
personality change, Cliff.
It's not like you're
trying to quit smoking.
We can't give you
an electric shock
every time
you reach for a cigarette.
Hey, hey, hey, yeah,
that's not a bad idea.
Now, now, now,
just calm down.
Look, maybe
I'm overstating the problem.
Maybe all you need to get people
to like you a little better
is just some good,
old-fashioned politeness.
Maybe you don't need to take
any desperate measures.
Oh, yes, he does.
So, you get ahold of him?
No, no, no, just get
the darned answering machine
all the time.
I hate that message.
It's not so much
the content of the message
as the fact that Cliff sings it
to the tune of "Volare."
Well, he's got to come back
sooner or later.
Look, I suggest
that when he does,
we all give him
a very warm welcome.
Well, all I'm promising
is not to treat him like a bug.
Well, you see, Carla's willing
to go that extra mile.
Hello, Frasier.
Ah.
Hello, blossom bottom,
how was your lesson?
I like driving.
It's a wonderful feeling.
Total control of
woman over machine.
The speed, the power, the
ecstasy-- I was jazzed.
You know,
you're insane.
You're a maniac.
You're certifiable.
I'm glad to see you're
talking to me again.
Has your nose
stopped bleeding?
Geez, Sam,
are you all right?
No thanks to your wife.
I cannot believe you made
that gesture to that guy.
I see people make
that gesture to
Frasier all the time.
Yeah, but Frasier's not driving
an 18-wheeler
with a little bumper sticker
that says
"Insured by Smith & Wesson."
Well, he cut me off.
That happens all the time.
It doesn't mean
that you gun it up to 80
and run the guy off the road.
I blew his doors
off, didn't I?
The last thing you want to do
is stop the car, get out,
and start poking your finger
in the folds of his neck.
I wasn't afraid; I thought
you could handle him.
Yeah, well, I tried, didn't I?
Oh, yes, that vicious
head butt to his fist
sent him reeling.
Hey, come on.
Come on, honey,
let's hurry
and have lunch.
I'm anxious to
take you for a spin.
Certainly, my dear.
Yeah, lots
of luck, Doc.
You know,
she's a menace.
You know, you are a hazard
to every driver and pedestrian
on the road.
I'll tell you
something else.
You know,
you shouldn't be allowed
to get anywhere near
anything with wheels,
because you are, by far,
the worst, the most dangerous,
the most maniacal driver
I've ever seen.
I was fine.
Now, Cliff,
let me remind you again,
that it's
extremely unorthodox
to use shock aversion treatment
outside the clinic.
I make no guarantees.
Hey, look, we
covered all that.
It's time to go for
broke, all right?
Whatever you say;
are your contacts in place?
Yeah, here, better test
it just to make sure.
Good idea.
Say something obnoxious.
What do you
mean, obnoxious?
I don't know
what's obnoxious.
You're the
so-called expert.
( grunting )
Perfect.
Guys, look, it's Cliff;
he's back.
Okay, remember, this is
his first time back
since the operation, so just
make a big welcome for him
and act like you're interested
in everything he has to say.
CLIFF:
Hey, guys.
Hey, Cliffie!
Hey!
( all shout greetings )
All right!
Hey, I hardly recognize you
out of uniform, big guy.
SAM:
Yeah, listen,
we're so sorry
we didn't come down
to the hospital.
Oh, no problem.
Yeah, so how was the operation?
Yeah, yeah, how much
did they shave?
Ah, I don't want to bore you
with stories about me.
I'm more interested in, uh,
what you guys have been up to.
I don't
know, uh...
usual stuff, I guess.
No, no, don't be shy;
come on, share with me.
Sam's giving Dr. Sternin
driving lessons.
( snide chuckling )
Should be giving her
personality lessons.
( chuckles, yelps )
But, uh, who among
us is perfect?
SAM:
So, uh...
when are you getting back
to the route?
Well, the doc said
an ordinary guy
would be out
for three weeks,
but with my incredible
physical stamina...
( yelps softly ):
Three weeks.
NORM:
Cliffie, uh...
are you okay?
You know, the...
Oh, yeah, uh, it's a little
pain from the stitches.
SAM:
Oh, wow, man.
You know, it's lucky
you dropped by.
We were having
this argument.
Maybe you can settle it
for us.
We were wondering
who came up
with that great post office
phrase, you know,
rain, sleet, dark of night--
that kind of thing.
( everybody agreeing )
Excuse me.
( clearing throat )
He did ask.
Okay, but
keep it short.
Well, uh, you know,
interestingly enough, uh...
it harks back to, uh, the early
Persian empire, about 500 B.C.
Oh, is that right?
Great.
Really?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
As a matter of fact,
a lot of our ancient
wonders are postal related.
Get out.
Oh, yeah; no, really.
The pyramids for example--
they were post offices.
And the Sphinx, that was
a late-night drop off.
( groaning )
But, uh, I digress.
Cliff?
CLIFF:
Eh?
When you were
in the hospital,
did they give
you a lobotomy?
I mean, it suits you.
( chuckling ):
Boy, did I miss
this good-natured ribbing.
( groaning )
Ah, excuse me.
Getting a little trigger happy
with that thing, aren't you?
Well, you sounded
a little sarcastic.
I wasn't being
sarcastic.
Judgment call.
Fair enough.
Welcome back, Cliff.
( groaning )
What the hell
was that for?
Oh, sorry, thumb spasm.
Well, it's good to be back.
So who's gonna buy me a beer?
( groaning )
Come on,
it was a joke, you bozo!
( groaning )
Stop that!
( groaning ):
I said stop that!
All right,
the experiment's off!
( groans three times )
You're a quack!
( rapid series of groans )
( groaning continues )
Okay!
Let's see how
you like it, pal.
( rapid series of groans )
( groaning continues )
Remember, we still have
your deposit on that unit!
So, uh, what were
we talking about?
Cliff...
what's going on here?
Where?
Come on, Cliff.
Well, it's some harebrained
scheme I came up with. I...
When you guys didn't
visit me in the hospital,
I... knew it was
because I wasn't popular,
so I, uh, went down to
this aversion therapy place
and bribed the guy
to give me a shock
every time I acted
like a jerk.
I thought it would make
me a different person.
I guess
it didn't work, huh?
I better be going.
Uh... I'll see
you guys later.
You know, as a matter of fact,
I, uh...
guess I won't, huh?
He'll be back.
Yeah, sure he will.
I don't know.
Yeah, kind of sounded
different this time.
Somebody ought
to go get him.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
But who?
I want Norm.
Looks like you're up,
big fella.
Yeah, I'll have to see
if I can go catch him, huh?
Cliffie?
Cliff, come back in
here, you big lug.
You know we love you, huh?
This place wouldn't be
the same without you.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
No, no, and we owe
you a big apology
for not going to visit
you in the hospital.
( murmuring apologies )
And?
I'm sorry
we made you feel
like you had to do all
that dumb shock therapy stuff.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
And?
And it wasn't
really necessary
because we're
the jerks
and you're not.
Yeah.
And?
Don't push it, Clavin.
Now, now, Carla,
stop your blubbering.
Well, I guess I'm a big enough
man to accept your apologies
and I guess there are one
or two things I could change
about my personality, and, uh,
well, let's start with this.
Innkeeper,
champagne on me
for all my friends.
All right!
What a guy!
Uh-huh.
Sammy?
Yeah?
Let's make it
the cheap stuff, okay?
( groaning )
All right, who's got the button?
Nobody here.
Not here.
( groaning )
Dance, mailman!
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/64sf
Help other users to choose the best subtitles