Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Woody, I have a lot
of work to do here,
so please make sure
I'm not disturbed.
WOODY:
Yes, ma'am.
( knocking )
Yes?
Miss Howe?
You want me
to hold business
and personal calls?
Yes.
You got it.
( knocking )
Yes?
Miss Howe?
Uh, what if it's an emergency,
or something
only you can handle?
Woody, I'm turning the bar
over to you.
I have complete confidence.
( knocking )
Yes?!
Miss Howe?
I want you to know
how much I appreciate
your confidence in me.
I won't let you down.
( sighs )
( knocking )
Woody, I am trying
to get some work done here,
and you are driving me crazy!
Now, get out of here,
and leave me alone!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
( sobbing ):
I'm sorry, Miss Howe.
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ¶
Hey, Fras,
new briefcase?
No. It's my new
portable cellular telephone,
the answer to every busy
therapist's prayers.
You see, with this,
I can instantly
get in touch
with patients
in crisis.
Who knows how many
lives it may save?
Looks cool, too?
Doesn't it?
Yeah.
( phone rings )
Oh, excuse me.
Oh, geez.
I seem to have forgotten
the combination.
( phone rings )
I was certain I programmed
Lilith's birthday
so I'd remember it.
Oh, no?
My birthday.
( ringing continues )
Frasier, that's getting
a little annoying.
Yeah, yeah.
Of course.
Freud's birthday.
Hello. Cheers.
( phone rings )
Two drafts, Sam.
Coming right up.
Shouldn't you be on your way
to the airport?
No. Eddie called
from Louisville.
He said the
performer's plane
was gonna be
a little late
so he'd meet
me here.
Oh, you must be getting
pretty excited, huh?
Yeah. I thought
that ice show
would never get
back to Boston.
Yeah, it has been tough.
He misses me.
Yeah.
You know? Kids miss him.
Not to mention
that I have moved
into my sexual peak.
You've been there
since you were 12.
When you find a place you like,
why leave it?
( phone rings )
MAN:
Answer the
damn phone!
Sorry, sorry.
Oh, wait.
Jung's address.
Finally.
Hello.
No, there is no Itzhak here.
Woody, here are your tickets.
Tickets?
Woody gets tickets?
Company season tickets.
Patriots-Dolphins tonight.
Two on the 40-yard line.
Ooh-ooh-oh-wee!
Oh. You know,
thanks, Miss Howe.
You know, you are
the greatest boss I ever had.
( clears throat )
I mean...
you're the prettiest boss
I ever had.
( clears throat )
I mean, thanks.
So, uh,
Woodster, what time
we leaving, bud?
Well, Mr. Peterson,
you'd be interested
in going to something like this?
Yeah.
Dit-dit-dit-dit...
Fair is fair.
What?
Now, Woody...
didn't I, uh,
invite you
to a very special occasion
just last week?
That's right, Mr. Clavin.
I sure did enjoy
that garage sale.
Excuse me, but why do I seem
to have been
automatically excluded?
You have to go
home to your wife.
What about your wife?
You can't be this dense
with your patients.
Hey, Carla, I'm back.
Hey.
Hey, everybody.
N-n-not-not here.
Everybody's watching.
Excuse me.
I-I'll be right back.
I just got
to show Eddie something.
( clears throat )
Oh, Eddie.
( moaning )
( door rattling )
Ah, gee, it's
good to be home.
Give me a beer,
Sam... here.
Thanks, Sam.
Yeah.
( gasps )
A charm bracelet
from Cincinnati!
Yeah. There's
a little beer stein,
little bowl
of sauerkraut,
and Pete Rose's head.
Ooh, Carla, can I borrow it?
Fat chance.
This better not
turn my wrist green.
No.
Hey.
Hey, buddy.
How's the show doing?
Oh, terrific.
We signed a new headliner--
Franzi Schrempf.
Oh, you mean,
the East German gold medalist?
That's her.
She's joining the show
here in Boston.
Sure would like
to meet her
without having to go
to that stupid ice show.
Mm.
You may be in luck, Norm,
because I invited her
and some of the cast
to drop by here later.
Oh, boy.
Hey, hey...
Oh, God, she is amazing.
She actually grabs the blade
and touches the back
of her head with it.
Can you do this?
Hey, are the kids home?
I haven't talked to them
since I got back.
I want to give
them a call.
Oh, yeah, go ahead.
All right.
Just make sure
you identify yourself by name.
Just saying, "It's Dad"
leaves too much room
for confusion.
CLIFF:
You know, Carla,
according to the,
uh, Weekly Gabber,
this Franzi Schrempf
has affairs
with every man
she's worked with.
I'm telling you,
she's a man eater.
Look, Clavin,
I'm not worried,
so just shut up.
There's a lot of things wrong
with Eddie,
but I know I can trust him.
We've been married
for over a year now,
and not once
in that entire time
has his eye wandered.
Well, his good eye.
I'm talking completely
over her head.
I mean, she must be,
like, triple-jointed
or something.
Hey, Eddie,
Eddie, come here.
You know, I was just laughing
at something stupid Cliff said.
He says that this Franzi
has a thing
for the men she works with.
Says she changes lovers
more times
than most people change socks.
I don't have anything
to worry about
with you
in that area, do I?
No, honey, not at all.
I put a fresh pair
on this morning.
Hey, here she is.
Everybody...
I want you to meet
Franzi Schrempf.
( hooting and chattering )
( clapping )
SAM:
Welcome
to the bar, Franzi.
We're all, uh...
Well, we're big fans of yours.
Thank you.
But we were
just wondering,
now that you're here
in Boston, um,
well, what are your plans?
Well, while I'm here,
I would like to wear blue jeans,
see a Tom Cruise movie,
and eat a Big Mac.
Whoa. Sexy, dumb,
and a cheap date.
( laughing )
Well, uh, in the
spirit of detente,
I wouldn't mind
having some arms talks
with Franzi.
( laughing )
I'd like to see her try
to control my arms.
( laughing )
I wouldn't object
to a little mutual
on-site inspection.
See what kind of payload
she can deliver.
( laughing )
Reduce missiles
in Western Europe.
( Woody laughs )
EDDIE:
Hey, Sam,
she is something, eh?
SAM:
Yeah.
You know, if I was younger,
taller, handsomer,
and had a brain
in my head,
I never would have
started this sentence.
You think she's pretty,
don't you?
Well, yeah, if
you're into looks,
which I'm not.
Just don't get any ideas.
Ideas?
Franzi doesn't
even know I exist.
Eddie, do you have a light?
You know, I'm sort of
the host here tonight.
I-I better take
care of this.
Sure.
( indistinct chatter )
CLIFF:
Uh!
Paper covers rock,
and the mailman goes
to the Patriots game.
Oh, that is absurd.
You're telling me
that if I took my rock
and hurled it,
it wouldn't smash
right through
that puny piece
of paper?
Oh, will you come on?!
You're just crying baby shoes
'cause you're not going
to the game.
Oh...
Baby shoes...
Children,
children,
there's a much
more fair way
to decide this. Now,
foot race to the corner
and back.
The winner goes to the game.
False start. False start!
I'm running this race
under protest.
Carla, I don't think
you have anything
to worry about
with Eddie.
But I don't know.
I get this sense of doom.
Maybe it's intuition,
and maybe it's the fact
that every time
Eddie gets excited,
he starts sweating
like a ditch digger.
Mom, you'll never believe this.
I'm calling you
from a briefcase.
Yeah?
Say, Franzi, uh,
you know, I was
just thinking,
seeing how you're
new in town,
how about I show you
our fair city?
I do not think so.
We have just met.
That's not proper
in my country.
I drive a 'Vette.
I drive a Porsche.
Oh, well, maybe we could
race sometime.
Oh...
( panting )
Hey, congratulations,
Mr. Peterson.
You're the winner.
Put it on my headstone.
( panting )
Well, congratulations, Norm.
You won the first leg
of our triathlon.
Now, onto the....
Now, onto the, uh, biking
and swimming portions.
Anybody know
this guy?
We found him face down
at the top of the steps.
Never saw him before.
Oh, hey,
Mr. Peterson,
we better hurry,
or we're gonna
miss the kickoff.
What? Get out of here.
What are you...?
Come on, come on.
Got to run.
Oh, no...
Woody!
No, man! Wait.
Excuse me.
I think the guy on the steps
would like something to drink.
We don't do takeout.
Hey, uh, Franzi,
what's the matter?
Sammy doesn't spin
your propeller?
He's rude, crude
and very stupid.
I guess all the sweet,
simple guys are taken.
Don't you forget it.
( sighs )
Say, I'll bet
with all that skating
you get pretty sore muscles.
Have you ever experienced
Sammy's all-American,
deep muscle massage?
Have you ever experienced
knowing when to quit?
( laughs )
Are you sure you're
not from around here?
Eddie?
Yes.
Would you be so kind
to give me a lift back
to the hotel?
Oh, sure, Franzi.
Anything.
You're so sweet.
( laughs )
CLIFF:
Well,
there he goes, Carla.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
You got to give her credit.
She didn't say it.
Say, uh, Rebecca,
was it a big hassle
getting those company tickets
for Woody?
No.
Can you get some for me?
I get it.
Employees only, huh?
No.
Gotcha. Can't go
to the well too often.
No.
Then you just don't want
to get 'em for me?
Yes.
Well, no harm in asking.
Man, what is with
these East German babes?
All week long
I have been trying:
phone calls, flowers,
the whole thing.
What am I doing wrong?
Well, Sam, I see
no alternative.
You're just going
to have to become a communist.
What do you do?
Do you apply for membership
or something?
I cannot believe my ears.
What?
We're not talking
about the Moose Lodge here.
We're talking communists,
the most reprehensible
perpetrators
of social and economic
oppression ever known
to mankind.
I mean,
they brainwash you,
they put you to work
in some tractor factory,
and as for your creature
comforts, forget it.
Yeah, but the stuff you had
before you joined is still
your stuff, am I right?
Ordering.
What are you ordering, Carla?
I forget.
You know where to reach me.
Carla, are you preoccupied
or something?
You don't still think
Eddie's messing around
with Franzi, do you?
I have my suspicions.
Well, what evidence
do you have?
I'll tell you what I have.
I have nothing!
That was the one good thing
about Nick.
With Nick,
I always knew for sure.
How?
He told me.
I mean,
Nick used to stick Polaroids
in the family album.
Carla, you don't have
anything to worry about.
I am telling you
Franzi would never date anyone
from that crummy ice show.
I can't believe that dame!
She said she can't see me
because she's fallen
for some guy in the ice show.
( gasps )
Carla, she's probably
just saying that
because she wants
to get Sam to quit bugging her.
I'll have to remember
that one.
She's dating somebody,
all right.
Get a load of this
little tidbit of gossip.
"One international skating star
was seen spooning spaghetti
with a short, dark,
melon-faced companion."
Eddie!
SAM:
Oh, come on, Carla.
"Short, dark, melon-faced"?
I mean, that could be anybody
in the show.
Yeah, guess that explains why
it's not one of the more
popular ice shows.
That no-good, two-timing
scum-sucking, son of a...
Hey, honey bear, come give
your lover man a hug.
( screams )
Hey, Eddie, Eddie.
Hey, do you mind if I borrow
Carla here for a minute?
No problem.
It'll give me time
to look for my tooth.
Hey, Frasier, help him
out there, will ya?
Tell him one of your funny
psychiatry stories, will ya?
Will you sit down?
Now, what the hell
do you think you're doing?
I'm killing
the horny little frog!
Just come on.
Come here, will you?
Look, murder is not the answer
to every one
of life's little problems,
you know that?
First of all,
you don't even know
if he did anything wrong,
and second, if he was
a little tempted,
maybe you pushed
him into it.
Oh, what are you
talking about?
Did you ever think
that maybe you aren't
exactly nice to the guy?
Sammy, you know me.
This is as nice
as it gets.
But this is the way
you handle everything
in your life,
and it never works.
Okay, O God
of Good Relationships,
what do you suggest I do?
Carla, Carla,
you got to let Eddie know
how you feel inside.
You must embrace him
not, not just
with your heart,
but with your very soul.
Give unto him and
he will give unto you.
Okay, no more for this clown.
Listen,
I'm talking
about the occasional back rub,
the general all-around
pampering.
You know, maybe buy one of
those low-cut, frilly dresses.
Oh, you mean
that "total woman" BS?
I find that
completely repulsive.
Well, that explains
all the men beating down
your door, doesn't it?
Listen, you got to become
the ideal woman, you know?
Treat him like a god,
cater to his every whim.
Oh, yuck! I can't do that.
I can't do frilly.
You know what they say.
"You can catch more flies
with honey than with vinegar."
Maybe I shouldn't
be butting in here,
but you can catch the most
with dead squirrels.
Come on.
Guys, guys,
I am not going
to do this, okay?
I'm going to get to the
bottom of it my own way.
So, I say to this patient,
"Look, you're never going
to get well
until you get over
this paranoia."
And he says to me,
"I was afraid you'd say that."
Well, you had to be there.
Your phone is ringing.
Ooh.
Why did you attack me
like that?
I'm sorry, Eddie.
Look, I've been very tense
lately.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Are you happy with me?
Boy, am I.
No complaints?
Not one complaint.
You're lying.
Everybody has one complaint.
I want one complaint
or I'm not going
to believe you're happy.
Well, okay.
What?
Remember the other night
when I asked you
if I could have
a few buddies over
for poker,
and you shoved my face
into the refrigerator?
Well, I guess
I didn't like that.
Listen, Eddie, I want you
to promise me something.
I want you
to promise me
that if you ever find someone
who makes you happier than I do
that you'll tell me.
Oh, yeah, right.
What do you mean by that?
You'd kill me.
No, I won't.
Now tell me the truth.
Are you having an affair?
No!
Did you believe me
when I said
I wouldn't kill you?
No!
Then if you were having
an affair,
you would still be saying no!
Yes! And if I weren't
having a affair,
I'd still say no!
Honey, look, I got
to tell you something.
I have a real bad headache
from this conversation.
I need to lie down
in a dark room.
Where do I go for frilly?
All right,
I will see your nickel
and I'll raise you
a nickel.
Too rich for my blood.
Hey, honey,
more chips and dip.
Right away,
sweetheart.
Hey, Ed, what's
with the old lady?
Why is she
acting so nice?
I got no idea.
She's been doing it all week.
But I got no idea
how a car works either,
but I don't mind riding in one,
eh?
Shades of the Algonquin
Roundtable.
Here you are, sweetheart.
Just the way you like it.
Oh, thanks. I thought
you forgot us.
Oh, no! I was just carrying
another keg in from the garage.
( doorbell rings )
Oh, let me get that, baby face.
And when you're through with
that, could you grab me a beer?
Anything you want.
Me, too, please.
What do I look like,
a waitress?
Oh, Sam, thank God
it's you.
I think I'm hemorrhaging.
Don't worry about it.
I got some great news,
for you at least.
I went down to Franzi's
dressing room,
give her one last chance.
Guess who was there.
Her boyfriend.
Her boyfriend was there?
Yeah, yeah.
And Eddie's here?
Hey, Carla, beer me!
You think
Eddie looks like a melon.
Boy, I tell you,
you put a cantaloupe
up next to that guy's face,
I defy you
to tell the difference.
Hey, Carla,
Carla, what are you
doing out there,
growing the hops?
Right away, dear.
You know, maybe I'll join them
for a couple of hands of cards.
Don't bother.
The game's just
about to break up.
Thanks for the warning.
Hey, honey, we're running
a little low on dip.
You want some dip?
Mm-hmm.
Here's your dip
and your chips and your drinks
and your cards.
You want 'em?
Help yourselves.
I don't know about you guys.
I'm a little bushed.
You know, we really must get
together like this more often.
Oh, for God's sake, Norm.
Let the dog have the dip.
Now what the hell
was that all about?!
You never laid a hand
on that Franzi, did you?
Did you kiss her even?
Did you pinch her?
Did you do anything?
No, I swear it!
How could you
humiliate me like that?!
Franzi?
Carla, is that
what you're all upset about?
You think there's something
going on
between me and Franzi?
Listen, if that woman
threw herself at me,
I would have nothing
to do with her.
In fact, today at rehearsal
I saw how inhuman she could be.
She humiliated
one of the guys
just because he made
a little mistake.
Chewed him out
in front of everyone.
Actually spit on him.
If it upset you so much,
why didn't you
defend the guy?
I was the guy!
So nothing was going on
and you let me walk around
like Debbie Reynolds.
Why didn't you stop me?!
I thought maybe you were
pregnant again
and this was your way
of telling me.
Well, you didn't have
to like it so much.
Like it?
It gave me the creeps.
Well, you certainly seemed
to like it
when you were making
all those stupid cracks
in front of your friends.
Well, you know
the competition
to be witty
in front of those guys.
Besides, honey, I mean,
isn't the important thing
I've been faithful to ya?
You have been, haven't you?
Yeah.
Guess I kinda lost
sight of that.
I was never married to anyone
who was faithful before.
( scoffs )
You're really
a good guy, Eddie.
I don't deserve you,
but I'm going
to try to from now on.
I'm going to be
the perfect wife.
I don't want you
to be the perfect wife.
I want the girl
I married:
feisty, strong-willed,
and, well, downright nasty.
In a beautiful way.
You really mean that, Eddie?
Oh, you bet I do.
Then get your sorry butt
into the kitchen.
There's a sink full of dishes.
The garbage disposal
is clogged,
and there's a cat box
with your name on it.
What are you doing?
Oh, my sweetie is back.
Beat it.
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org