Cheers if filmed before
a live studio audience.
Hey, Dr. Crane.
Look what I got.
That's quite a trophy, Woody.
I didn't know
you played golf.
I don't.
There's a...
trophy shop down the street.
You just... bought this trophy?
You don't even golf?
Why should I?
Well, because the idea
of a trophy is to show
some sort of
accomplishment.
You should
learn to golf.
Go out, take a couple
of lessons.
Spend some hours mastering
the finer points of the game.
And then?
Well, then you get better
and you can join a country club.
And then?
Well, and then
you can compete.
Maybe enter
some tournaments.
And then?
And maybe some day, you'll be
the best and you'll win,
and then you'll get a...
A trophy, Dr. Crane?
Congratulations,
Woody.
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
There's something different
about Dr. Sternin-Crane.
I can't put
my finger on it.
Is it her hair?
No, no. I'll-I'll get it.
Her dress?
Oh, I've got it,
her husband's growing a beard.
Did I hear someone
mention my beard?
That's right,
Woody-- a beard,
the ultimate manifestation
of masculinity.
Testosterone surging
through my face!
Every red-blooded man's
birthright-- hair on his chin.
I don't know why I didn't do
this before.
Because I wouldn't let you.
Oh, yes. That's right.
It all comes back to me now.
Hi. I-I'm looking
for Woody Boyd.
Oh! Russell!
Hey!
Russell! Russell! Russell!
All the way
from Florida!
Hey!
How're you doing, cuz?
I'm great, man! Great.
Hey, Sam,
guess who this is.
Uh-h, your cousin Russell
from Florida?
Wow! What are
you, a witch?
Hi, Russell.
I'm Sam...
Sam Malone.
I know. Woody's told me
all about this place.
Oh, Miss Howe, just as beautiful
as Woody said you were.
Well, thank you, Woody.
Hey, uh, there's Mr. Peterson,
and look, Mr. Clavin.
Hey, there's the Cranes.
You were right, Woody,
like she's seen a ghost.
And there, and there's
Carla, right?
And Tecumseh
and the, and the jukebox,
and the wooden lady,
and the little porthole...
Hey, Russell, I-I guess
you know who I am.
I'm Paul Krapence.
Who?
I-I was going on and on.
I had to draw the line
somewhere.
Hey, uh, Russell, let me
get you something to drink.
Well, well, one of
Woody's relatives.
Hello, Russell.
Hi.
Say, Russell, uh, have
you ever been to Hanover?
I spent every summer
of my life there.
Yes, well, Woody's told us
a lot about it,
and I'm sure we'd
all be interested
in a different
perspective.
Well, you know, it's just like
any other small,
rural town in the Midwest.
There's acres and acres
of farmland,
and hard-working people.
You know, it's also the U.F.O.
capital of the world.
Enjoy your stay
in Boston, Russell.
Thank you.
Hey, Russell,
you can stay with me.
I got a real
nice apartment.
The couch almost opens out
into a bed.
Most days you've got heat
and hot water.
And it's usually quiet,
except the couple next door
is off the wagon this week.
Wow, Woody, that's
a great offer, man,
but I already made
a reservation
in this cheap
little motel.
Can I stay with you?
Well, Russell, why don't you
put your suitcase in the office.
That's real kind, sir,
but like I just told Woody,
I already got a room reserved.
Oh, well, then
just while you're here.
Hey, Sam... be
real nice to him.
He's... he's heartbroken.
His girl he's been going
out with for a long time
just dumped him.
So he's come to Boston
to make a new start.
I think he's hoping to hit
the big time, like me.
Big time?
Woody, you're a bartender.
You-you're living
hand-to-mouth.
Yep. Back in Hanover,
people think I made
a pact with the Devil.
What's Russell going to do while
he's here in Boston, Woody?
Well, I don't
know, Miss Howe.
(playing simple melody on piano)
I was hoping
he could work at Cheers.
What does he know how to do?
Uh, that's the question.
Yeah, he was always off writing
and sculpting and painting,
while the rest of us
were bettering ourselves
by learning air-conditioning
repair and riding dirt bikes.
Yeah, to tell
you the truth,
I don't know if he can
do much of anything.
(plays boogie-woogie melody
virtuosically)
Of course!
Why didn't I think of it before?
He can be a busboy.
Hey, Russ...
Sam, why don't we hire him
to be the piano player here?
Well... maybe,
as long
as he works for tips.
Well, you-you
won't regret it.
I know about
these things.
I have a golden gut.
It must be worth a fortune.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought you said
"golden butt."
Well, here's your mail, Rebecca.
Thank you.
CLIFF:
Hey, uh, Twitchell.
Hey, Clavin.
How come every other mailman
in this town is out there
busting his hump
and you're in here
sitting on your over-sized
irregular?
Return it to sender,
Twitchell.
You left this in your box,
Clavin.
What's that?
That's the official memo
regarding the new uniforms.
Starting tomorrow,
they are regulation wear,
and that's by order
of the Postmaster
General.
Huh.
Wait a second.
I can't believe you opened
my mail there, Twitch.
Hey...
Ah!
(chuckles)
That's a good
one, Clavin.
Yeah.
But, uh, you can't
escape the fact
that starting tomorrow,
we all have to wear
the new uniforms.
No exceptions.
Oh, yeah?
Well, this is what I think
of the new uniforms.
Oh, come on, now.
It's not as bad as that.
You haven't even
seen them yet.
That's right,
and I don't want to.
As far as I'm concerned,
it doesn't exist.
This is the uniform that made me
want to become a postal worker.
And this is the uniform
I'm sticking to.
You wouldn't have that problem
if you washed it
once in a while.
Uh...
You know, this is
insubordination, Clavin.
I got no choice but to report
you to the supervisor.
I don't care if you do.
There comes a time
in every man's life
when he's got to show
his manhood,
put his cards
on the table.
Can we just see
the cards?
You know, you guys,
if we're going to have
a piano player
that's this great,
we shouldn't hide him up
there in the corner.
I think we should move the piano
down here
and put it against this wall.
If you help
me move it,
I'll give
each of you a free beer.
Oh, great.
I mean, I suppose
you think we're...
we're like a couple
of trained dogs.
Every time you want us
to do something,
you'll waggle a free beer
under our face.
Uh-uh. We have
some self-respect.
We have a little dignity.
Am I right, Paul?
Mm-hmm.
If I do it by myself,
can I have both beers?
Sure.
Way to go, fathead.
I was working her
for a pitcher.
(both grunting)
There.
That wasn't so hard.
Yeah. Get a couple guys
who know what they're doing,
no problem, huh?
Just hope Rebecca doesn't
need us to move it back.
That could get
a little hairy.
(playing boogie-woogie
melody)
That's great, Russell.
All right.
Whoo.
Thanks...
Thanks a lot, Miss Howe.
Say, what would you call
that color of hair?
What? This hair?
Mm-hmm.
Well, it's
nothing unusual.
It's just,
uh, what a...
medium chestnut
with auburn highlights.
Is that what it said
on the bottle?
Why do you ask, Russell?
Well I was hoping to use it
in a song.
Do you mind if I just say...
The color of romance,
(playing gentle melody)
the color of longing,
the color of the feeling
I get...
when I see you smile?
Okay.
I think we have a May-December
thing happening here.
Yeah. December
of the following year.
I'd say he's got a major case
of puppy love going here.
He's following you around,
asking to do errands for you,
wanting rides
back to the motel.
Oh, so what if he has
a little crush on me.
I think it's sweet.
Rebecca, you know I've seen
this type of behavior before.
When Frasier first had
a crush on me,
he had difficulty
expressing his feelings.
He was very shy.
So he expressed them
in other ways.
Uh, calling me at all hours,
and then when I answered,
hanging up.
Just sitting quietly
in his car,
in front of my house,
hour after hour.
Going through my mail,
and then carefully replacing
the letters in my mailbox.
In other words, stalking me.
It got what I wanted,
didn't I?
You know, you guys, there's
no need to worry about this.
I mean, if it gets out of hand,
I know just what to do.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I would like to dedicate a song
to a very, very lovely lady,
Miss Rebecca Howe.
(piano playing)
♪ I spent last night ♪
♪ Dreaming of your eyes ♪
♪ But your hair kept
getting in the way ♪
♪ Your lips dropped in ♪
♪ To tell me how you'd been ♪
♪ And when I tried
to kiss them ♪
♪ My pillow told me
I missed them ♪
♪ Your voice dropped by ♪
♪ And sang a lullaby ♪
♪ And it was then
I knew just what to do ♪
♪ I'd fall asleep and then ♪
♪ I'd dream of you ♪
♪ Again. ♪
Oh, sure,
but ask him to fix
an air conditioner.
My muse.
My inspiration.
Oh, Sam, he's so sweet.
I don't want to hurt
his feelings.
What do you say
when you break up
with a woman?
I usually say,
"I'll call you tomorrow."
Well, Russell
and Miss Howe.
Yeah.
Never thought of it,
but it could work.
I mean, they
could go out.
They could hit it off.
Maybe even get married.
Hey, who knows?
Maybe he could give her
the baby you couldn't.
That was a choice, Woody.
Hey, thanks a lot for the ride,
Rebecca.
You feel like coming in
for a cup of coffee?
Uh, no, thanks,
Russell.
Um...
Russell, I-I had
something
that I wanted
to say to you
and I, and I-I didn't get
a chance to in the car, um,
I don't know exactly
how to put it.
I wanted to
talk to you
about the crush
you have on me.
I don't have a crush
on you, Rebecca.
You what?
I don't have a crush on you.
(quietly):
You don't?
No.
Oh, my God.
(laughs)
I'm so embarrassed.
Oh, dear.
Oh, well.
All right, Russell,
I will come in
and have that cup
of coffee.
Yeah, come on in.
Oh.
After you.
(gasps)
Rebecca,
I don't have a
crush on you.
I just love you with all
of my heart and soul.
(piano playing)
Thank you.
Thanks.
Say, folks, I'm gonna be
taking a short break.
Woody, have you seen
my snifter?
Oh, it's over there.
Sammy, you want to put
a head on this, please?
That's yours.
Thanks.
Say, uh, say,
Sammy, is, uh,
is Rebecca coming in today?
Well, she's scheduled
to work
so I'm not really sure.
Well, maybe I should
swing by her place
and see if she's all right.
Say, does anybody know
where she lives?
Never mind, I'll find it.
Thank God he's gone!
Hey, where the hell have
you been all afternoon?
Hiding up at Melville's
waiting for Russell to leave.
You know, I sat up there
for three hours pushing
my glass around
making moronic
small talk.
Boy, if I ever get like that,
put a gun to my head.
I thought he had a
little crush on me.
Mm-hmm.
It's a full-blown
obsession.
The man worships me.
It's like he's
a little bit
off balance,
if you know what I mean.
He worships you
and you think he's a
little off balance?
Woody, was Russell
different
in any way when he
was growing up?
Well, he does have
one little quirk.
You know, when he likes
something,
he really gets
carried away.
I mean, uh, you know,
one time he liked trains.
I mean, really
liked them.
Collected them,
wrote songs about them,
pasted pictures
all over his walls.
You know, in fact
he-he even thought
he was a train
for a while.
Every morning
at 7:53, you could hear him
coming through town.
What do I do?
The advisable
course of action is
to not take any chances.
A woman living alone
who feels threatened
in any fashion,
is entitled
to police protection.
I thought I'd just be
a little bit more direct
and tell him
I wasn't interested.
Yeah, right.
Be direct.
Lay people.
Uh, can I
help you?
Do you have a Clavin
here?
Yeah, but it hasn't been
flushing right lately.
Wait, wait,
there he is.
There's
the renegade.
Oh, hey,
Twitchell.
What'd you do, tell
your dad on me?
Henderson.
Postal inspector,
South Branch.
There have been reports
of your refusal
to wear the new postal uniform.
Oh, gee,
I wonder who reported me.
It was me, stupid.
That's the only reason I'd
come in here on my day off
to see you
knuckle under.
Yeah, so, uh, what if I don't
wear this new uniform?
Then I will have no choice
but to put you under
immediate suspension.
Eh, you wouldn't do that.
When I'm through with you,
you'll be lucky to get
a job sticking flyers
under windshield wipers.
Now what's it gonna be?
Oh, all right.
You win this time.
Hey, Paul,
guard the men's room door
for me, will you?
I'm gonna be naked in there.
Again?
(both laughing)
Hook, line and sinker.
Hey, fellas, what's up?
Oh, Sam, I want you to meet
my brother-in-law, Frank.
Hi, Sam.
Frank.
Hey, what are you guys
trying to pull?
Ah, I'm sick of Clavin
shooting off his mouth
about the new
uniforms.
He's never
even seen them,
so we came up with
our own Clavin version.
The old fake uniform gag.
Yeah.
Why didn't we think
of that?
You know, I'm a little
disappointed in all of us.
I just think
we're gonna have to work
a little harder around here.
There you are, Rebecca.
Hello, Russell.
Where you been?
Hiding...
I mean,
doing my taxes.
Russell, come here.
I-I think you
and I need to have
a little talk.
Sure. I could talk
to you all night.
In fact I have,
in my own way.
Uh, Russell, have a seat.
Oh, you know,
Rebecca,
I hope I didn't frighten
you last night
with my little tribute
to you on the walls.
Russell,
you have to stop this.
I'm not worthy
of all this attention.
I'm Rebecca.
I'm nobody. I'm nothing.
I know it, that's-that's
what Carla told me.
And-and Cliff
and-and Norm
and Paul and
Cousin Woody,
Well, anyway...
Mr. Hill upstairs and
Ruben, the busboy...
The point...
Russell, you're young,
attractive and sensitive
and-and, you know,
there's just so many women
out there for you.
I'm just not the one.
Boy, I've-I've heard
this speech before.
Just...
just pipe down and...
put some clothes on
or we'll call Amtrak
security, right?
Is that it?
Is that the one?
Yes, Russell, you pretty
much said it for me.
All right, I-I won't
bother you anymore.
I-I guess my little songs
and doodles
could never have-have won
the heart of a woman
as-as beautiful
and wonderful as you.
Shoot,
I'm a richer person
for having known you,
Rebecca.
You'll always be special.
Phew.
Glad I don't have to deal
with that anymore.
"I love you, Rebecca.
I love you, Rebecca."
Who needs it?
(whimpering):
I feel better.
Any year now, Clavin!
I'm coming.
I'm coming, for
crying out loud.
Hold your horses.
Well, I was wrong.
This thing is great.
Well, uh,
you haven't
seen the hat.
Wow, all right.
Now this is a uniform
that demands respect.
Yes, sir.
There's gonna
be one less reason
to make fun of Cliff Clavin
tonight.
No, no, Mrs. Clavin,
it wasn't us.
No, it was a couple of guys
from the Post Office.
Yeah, I know.
I wish we could have
thought of it, too.
It was, it...
You're kicking
yourself. Yeah.
(laughs)
Okay.
Well, we'll talk
to you later.
Bye-bye.
She's not exactly
Donna Reed, is she?
No.
No, no.
Sam,
I've been in there thinking
about Russell.
I mean, what's wrong with
somebody paying attention to me?
I mean, so he loves me,
is that a crime?
I'm gonna go talk to him.
Somebody cover for me.
Cover for what?
You don't do anything
around here.
Ha-ha.
Seriously, what does she do
around here anyway?
(loud music playing)
Russell!
Russell, it's me, Rebecca!
Russell, I know you can hear me.
R-Russell, I was wrong
to turn you away.
Russell!
I'm coming in!
I want you to give me
another chance!
Oh, hi, Rebecca.
Isn't Carla dreamy?