Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Oh, Robin, I just get
so lonely and confused
when I'm not with you.
Well, now, I've missed
you, too, sweetheart.
Did you like the little
surprise I sent?
Surprise?
The Polaroids.
What? I-I don't remember.
The pictures of me
wearing that teddy
you like.
The picture of me holding
that teddy you like.
Now, Rebecca, don't tease.
Not so early in my sentence.
Oh, Robin, you really mean
you didn't get the pictures?
I think I would remember.
Well, I know I mailed them.
I went to pick up
my final paycheck at Cheers
and then I mailed them.
Oh,  well, they'll get here.
Yeah.
Okay, for this one
without the teddy,
we will start
the bidding...
start the bidding at ten bucks.
Don't crowd.
$100.
(theme song begins)
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Takin' a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always
glad you came
You wanna be
where you can see
The troubles
are all the same
You wanna be where everybody
knows your name
You wanna go
where people know
People are all the same
You wanna go where everybody
knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I guess I don't have
to show you where anything is
behind the bar,
right, Mr. Peterson.
No, no, no, we got
the, uh, beer taps,
you got your
uh, cherries,
olives, pretzel
bag... Hey!
You guys got a cash
register back here.
Oh, my God!
I'm in one of Norm's dreams.
No, no, no.
I'm just doing my hour
behind the bar to qualify
for the employees'
basketball game.
Although my dreams are
very similar to this.
Except for, uh, in my dreams
the, uh, kegs
are a lot taller
and, uh...
well, I can fly.
Oh.
I've got a good feeling
this year, guys.
I think we're gonna
beat those guys
from Gary's Old Towne Tavern.
Yeah!
Al right!
Oh, this again.
I mean, every year they beat
you, humiliate you,
outsmart you
and take your money.
I mean, where's
the virtue in that?
Tradition.
Well, forgive me if I don't
share your enthusiasm.
I've just been feeling
a bit edgy these days.
Why's that, Dr. Crane?
Well, Lilith, in her own
dear, compulsive, little way
made the mistake
of asking me
if I thought
she looked fat.
And what did you say?
Well, I told her
she looked just fine.
Ooh, rookie mistake.
Yeah.
So, uh, what kind of
punishment are you getting?
Oh, I'm not getting any.
Oh, you got off easy.
No. I'm not getting any.
No, you're getting off easy.
Ho, Woody, think fast!
(laughs)
(patrons cheering)
Way to pass her
off there, Sam.
Wait till you guys hear
what I did this weekend.
You know, ever since
I bought this bar,
I've been trying to remind
people it's still a sports bar,
so I've been going around
renewing some of my old
sports contacts.
And for those of you
who've never seen Sam
renewing his old
sports contacts,
it goes something like this.
"Oh, come on!
"You've got to remember me!
You've got to!"
This shows what you know.
I happened to spend
the weekend
going head-to-head
with Kevin McHale.
Whoo.
Whoa.
Hey.
That's my
favorite Celtic.
Yeah?
You know, uh,
basketball was invented
by the ancient Celtics.
You know, interestingly enough,
so was the parquet floor.
You've been working
without your hat,
haven't you, Cliff?
So, Sammy...
shot hoops
with Kevin McHale, huh?
Actually, no, I, uh,
I played golf with him.
Beat him, too, you know.
Hurt him bad.
All right!
WOODY:
Yeah, you know,
big a star as he is, you, uh,
shank a tee shot into his shin,
and he'll cry
just like anybody else.
Hey, Sammy, I've got
a great idea.
Yeah, what?
Ask Kevin to play on our team.
No.
Then we'll really cream Gary's.
Yeah!
No, no, that'd be cheating.
But that'd be
good cheating.
You know, at what point
does cheating become
a moral dilemma?
I mean, can the severity
of snitching that
last piece of cake
be compared to, oh,
cheating on one's wife with
the beautiful, young woman
that works in the
office next to yours?
I should footnote this
by adding that I'm
not getting any.
Hello, sports fans!
(patrons booing)
What are you doing here, Gary?
I just came by to introduce you
to some of my new employees.
Come on down, boys.
FRAISER:
Oh, hey, hey...
CARLA: Oh, hey!
Come on.
Yeah, what...?
Those guys are ringers.
They're just
a couple of kids
working their way
through college.
GARY:
Oh, by the way,
I just wanted to let
you know that we're open
to any wagers.
Oh, oh, that's right.
You guys are too
chicken to bet.
Hey, we're not chicken to bet.
We bet you stomp all over us.
If I were you Sam,
I'd get a piece of this action.
He means do we want to bet
on ourselves here, Woody.
(laughs):
Are you kidding?
With those two skyscrapers?
Man, I thought
I was the bumpkin here.
Have it your way.
Oh, oh, Sam, give me
the ball for a second.
Watch this.
(laughs)
See you at the gym.
Boy, that Gary's a rat.
Yeah, can you
believe that?
Bringing in a couple
of professional ringers
like that?
No, I meant
stealing our ball.
Oh, man, that's
my favorite ball!
I hate that!
Give me the phone.
I'm calling,
I'm calling Kevin right now.
All right!
Yeah!
He'll be able to get
that ball back for us.
He's way big.
Yeah, all right.
If he wants to play that way,
I'm just gonna
get Kevin McHale
to come down
and play with us.
There you go!
Yeah.
If he doesn't want to do it,
then I'll get Larry Bird.
No, no, no, no,
not Bird.
If he's in, I'm out.
CLIFF:
Woody.
Woody, Woody, you telling me
you know Larry Bird?
I don't have to know him.
He's from French Lick, Indiana.
He's a doofus.
So what?
You're from Indiana
and you're a doofus.
Yeah, but I would rather
be a doofus from Hanover
than a doofus from French Lick,
'cause everyone from Hanover
knows that French Lick is
the doofus capitol of Indiana.
Of course everyone from
French Lick thinks it's Hanover.
It's a fuel
of a raging controversy.
Yo, Kevin.
Hi. Sam Malone here.
Hey, listen, you remember how
I told you about that game
my bar is playing against,
uh, Gary's Old Towne Tavern?
Yeah, how'd you like
to get in on that?
No, I... I know, I know
you've got a busy schedule
and all...
Sammy...
tell him it's for charity.
No, no listen,
I understand, I understand.
I'm not gonna bust
your chops here.
You know...
these needy orphans
have been through it all.
They're used to people
letting them down.
Oh, I'm sorry, didn't I tell
you it was for charity?
Oh, I'm sorry man.
Yeah, charity.
Well, no, don't worry about it.
I can get one
of the Lakers to do it.
I mean, they're good guys.
I mean, they'll give up
an hour of their time
to change some poor kids' lives.
Sam, leave the man alone.
You know, if somebody doesn't
want to do something,
no amount of manipulation,
cajoling, pleading
or lying can get them
to change their mind.
That's fantastic, man!
All right.
I'll see you down here.
Could you call
Lilith for me? I'll...
Boy, look at the curves
on that glass.
Oh, feel that.
Boy, he's really not
getting any, is he?
Pathetic.
Woody, uh, pour me
another beer, will you?
Put it in one of those
girlie glasses.
Hey, everybody!
I want you to meet,
uh, your bartender, here,
Mr. Kevin McHale!
(cheers, whistles and applause)
Kevin...
watch your head,
watch your head.
Low bridge.
Welcome aboard, Kevin.
I hope your years at Cheers
are as happy
as mine were.
Sam, I'll get my stuff together
and get out of your way.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Come back here, man.
He's not replacing you.
He just filling in here
for a little while
so he can qualify to play
the game against Gary's.
Oh!
Oh, in that case,
here's an apron.
All right.
Well, so what's it like
working with Larry Bird?
Hey, Larry's great.
Larry's funny as can be.
Boy, he's got some
great jokes.
And most of his jokes
are about these doofuses
from Hanover, Indiana.
Did you ever hear this one?
How many guys from Hanover
does it take
to change a lightbulb?
It doesn't even matter
'cause they gotta drive
all the way over to French Lick
just to get the lightbulb.
I heard it
a little different.
NORM:
Hey, Kevin!
Want to slam-dunk me
a beer over here, buddy?
Nah, I can't do that.
That's against NBA policy.
Oh, right, yeah, yeah,
they don't, uh,
like their athletes
promoting drugs or alcohol,
so tonight, uh, Kevin's
just going to be serving water.
To whom?
Do you believe this, huh?
I'm about to play ball
with Kevin McHale tonight?
You know, I didn't realize
we were playing at night.
Are you sure the orphans
can stay up that late?
The orphans?
Yeah, the orphans.
The orphans, yeah,
you know, well...
Oh, oh, right, right.
See, uh, one of the, uh,
one of the great things
about orphans is, they have
no parents to tell
them when to go to bed.
Listen, Kevin, about the, uh,
these orphans, uh...
well, they're not coming.
Uh, seems there was
some kind of mix-up.
You know, they had
tickets to the, uh,
circus or something
like that.
You know these orphans,
they're always getting freebies.
Oh.
I don't know, Sam,
there's no circus in town.
Well, uh, may-- oh, right.
It was the, uh,
monster truck rally.
That was it.
No, no, no-no,
not tonight.
All right, guys, where do
you think the orphans are?
Come on, Sam.
There are no orphans, are there?
W.. in the world?
God, Kevin, I wish
that were true, man!
Oh, Sam, this is all a big scam.
There are no orphans.
I'm out of here.
Aww, Kevin, Kevin,
wait a minute.
Let me talk to you
here for a second.
Listen, man,
wait, wait, wait.
We've got a $5,000
bet with Gary.
$5,000, huh?
Yeah. I-I can't afford
to lose that kind of money.
Well, I do have
a friend of mine
who's on the board of directors
at the Sunny Grove Orphanage.
I'll bet he knows
where the orphans are tonight.
Anyway, I-I know that
they're desperate for money.
And let's say the winnings
for our game were
to go to the kids...
Oh, hell, yes!
We don't mind
if those tykes get their cut.
No, no, Sam,
not their cut.
They get every penny.
Every... Uh, guys,
what do you say here?
I mean, we're in it
to beat Gary, right?
I mean, that's what
it's all about, isn't it?
I want my money back.
SAM:
Listen, listen.
If Kevin plays,
then we're definitely gonna win,
so it'll be Gary's $5,000
that we give to the orphans.
But if he...
if he doesn't play,
then we're definitely
gonna lose,
and it'll be our five grand
that we're giving to Gary.
All right, I'm behind you.
I agree.
I want my
money back.
Okay, then,
we're all agreed.
Here they are,
God bless them.
They're at
the boat show.
MEN (chanting):
Gary! Gary! Gary!
Gary! Gary!
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Gary's not here.
Find Gary!
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, man.
We're just early, that's all.
We'll have to wait.
Wait for Gary!
Wait... What, am I
the only one here?
Okay, guys, let's
huddle up here.
All right,
all right.
Have a seat.
Have a seat, fellows.
All right.
Settle down.
Come on.
Okay, now,
the way I see it,
anyone gets within ten feet
of the ball,
they pass it to Kevin.
Yeah.
Sounds good
to me.
What if
he's not open?
(laughs)
Yeah, yeah.
MEN:
Old Towne Tavern!
Well, the cheerleaders
are here.
Well, Sam,
you really want to
go through with
this formality,
or you just want to call
the whole thing off?
Oh, let's go through
the formalities, Gar.
Say, have you met
our, uh, new bartender?
Right over here.
This is our
ringer, Gar.
You're getting a little bald
on top, fellow.
Let's go.
(shouts)
Wait-wait-wait...
SAM:
All right!
All right, way to go,
way to go!
Kevin.
SAM:
Good stuff, man.
Good stuff.
SAM:
Keep going.
Get it!
Nice one, Kevin!
Go, Kevin.
NORM:
Yes, Kevin!
Go!
Yes!
Hey, hey!
Yeah, right, yeah!
Take that.
In your face!
Come on, Woody!
Come on!
Woody!
Kevin can't do
everything here.
How's it going?
Kevin's doing
everything here.
Yeah?
Well, say,
what's the score?
Uh, 70... two.
To what?
We have 70,
they have two.
All right.
Sammy, I need a break.
I cannot... move.
Oh, yeah,
take a break.
Why don't you get yourself
a beer?
Okay, fellows, I'm
playing for Norm now.
Go!
Sammy!
Oh, there
you go.
Fast break,
Kevin.
Whoo!
Yeah. Don't you
love teamwork?
(laughing):
Well, say,
don't you think
maybe somebody ought to
go in for McHale?
I mean, he's the only one
been playing the whole game.
What, are
you nuts?
What, we're ahead
by, what, 70 points?
I don't want to
just beat this guy.
I want to humiliate him.
I want to hear that clown, Gary,
scream for mercy.
(screaming)
That wasn't
Gary, was it?
Sorry, Mr. McHale.
You know, sometimes
you can just pop these babies
right back
into place.
(screaming)
Maybe not.
Gary, it's Carla.
Yeah, the guys just wanted me
to give you a call,
tell you that you left something
at the gym.
Your money!
Your pride!
Did you lose a blue gym bag?
Cheers rules!
(cheering and whooping)
Oh, man, victory
is so sweet.
This is even better than the
time we didn't lose so badly.
You remember that?
Yeah, but the best part
was Kevin getting up
and walking off the court,
knowing his foot was okay.
No, no, The best part
was Gary's total defeat
and humiliation.
Yeah...
Yeah, that was
the best part.
Yeah, did you see his face
when we told him
we were going to give
his money to charity?
Yeah, you know,
uh, those moppets
will be glad
to get the money.
Yeah, a lot they did for it.
Yeah.
SAM:
Anyway, uh...
that orphanage guy is coming
over here in a little while
to take the money back.
You know, Sam, I, uh, don't know
if I've told you,
but tragically I lost
both my parents when I was...
oh, in my early 30s.
I could sure use that money.
Say, Lilith,
how about that?
Would $5,000
buy anything?
What?
Nothing, dear.
I'm getting nothing here.
Mr. Malone?
Yeah, over here.
I'm Dr, Walter Froenmeyer
with the Celtics'
medical staff.
Uh, yeah?
I wanted to get
your version
of Mr. McHale's
accident last night.
Oh, well, uh... no big deal.
He fell down,
we put him back up.
Nothing serious.
Does this look like
nothing serious to you?
God! The skin's
all gone.
This hairline fracture
runs the entire length
of the metatarsal,
which would indicate
there was some sort
of a jarring after
the initial impact.
It was me!
I fell on him and then I tried
to pop it back into place.
I'm sorry!
Woody, Woody...
Excuse me just for a second.
Woody, Woody, no,
now come on.
Don't blame yourself.
You were just at the wrong place
at the wrong time, that's all.
If anything led to this,
it was Sam's pigheaded refusal
to take McHale out
of the game earlier.
What are you talking about?
Woody's the clod
who broke his foot.
Oh, God!
FROENMEYER:
If you'll excuse me,
I've got a whole gang
of reporters back at the Garden
waiting to find out why
McHale's out for the season.
Wait a minute--
out for the season?
Oh, my God. People
are gonna hate us.
Hate us? Man they'll kill us
first, then they'll hate us.
SAM:
Excuse me, Doctor,
listen, there's no need
for you to mention
the bar's name, now, is there?
Why shouldn't I?
Professional courtesy.
I'm a doctor.
You're a bartender.
We're both professionals.
Sam, wait a minute,
let me do this. all right?
Doc, how much would it take
to put a hook in your mouth?
$10,000.
Five.
Deal.
Now, she's a professional.
Hey, great work there, Carla.
Right. Dodged
that bullet.
Way to go, Carla.
I want my
money back.
Oh, for goodness
sakes, Frasier,
we've been intimate several
times this last month.
Look at my day planner.
We were together every
night this weekend.
Oh, good heavens!
That wasn't you.
What do you mean
it wasn't me?
I'm kidding.
See? Look how tense you are.
You wouldn't enjoy it anyway.
Well, fine.
I don't want it anyway.
You do, too.
I do not.
You do so.
All right, I do.
Well, you're not getting any.
Oh, Frasier, isn't it enough
that I'm doing it to your mind?
Hey, Sammy.
You're walking!
Kevin, when did you get
out of the hospital?
What are you talking about?
Talking about your foot.
Aw, it's fine.
I iced it down for about
a half hour after the game.
Feels great.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
wait a second.
Who-Whose X-ray is this,
then, huh?
Is that not yours?
I don't know. Let me
take a look at it.
It says "adult male gorilla."
That's not me.
Could be Laimbeer, huh?
Oh man, I can't believe this.
Gary sends in a fake doctor
to steal our money.
Do you believe that?
SAM:
God! Even when we
beat him, he wins.
Hey, Sam, I'd like you
to meet Father Conrad here,
from the Sunny Grove
Orphanage.
Yeah, hi.
I hope you don't mind
that we brought
a photographer along.
Listen, Sam, why don't you
come on around there and get
a picture with Father and I
and the $5,000
you're giving us.
Come on.
You want to do this,
uh... right now?
Yeah. Come on over.
Let's go.
Okay. I'll be right there.
What are we gonna do?
All right, short people
in front.
Look what you did!
You made me smack you
in front of a priest!
Boys, boys,
we can work this out.
Yeah, how? We don't
have any money.
No, no, no, but we've got a lot
of people in here, right?
How about we collect
as much money as we can,
That's good.
we give it to him,
and then we make sure everybody
knows that Gary's the one
that stole the 5,000 bucks
from those kids.
NORM:
There you go.
Uh, give me some money.
It's for a good cause.
What cause?
'Cause I said.
Hey, Sammy, Father and I
were just talking about it.
Those kids are really going
to enjoy that money.
Gonna get some shoes,
some eyeglasses...
You know, Kevin, we don't
quite have $5,000,
but we're pretty
darned close here.
Sammy, Sammy, where is
the orphans' money?
He has it.
(booing)
Thank you, Sam.
Thank you all for coming.
Father, on behalf of Gary's
Old Towne Tavern,
I'd like to present you
with a souvenir jacket,
and we have one
for you, too, Kevin,
with extra-long sleeves.
Oh, nice!
Uh-huh.
Here's a little check
for those wonderful kids.
$5,000, Kevin.
$5,000! That's great.
Hey Gar, let's get
a picture with it.
That's a great idea.
Sam, would you get
out of the way here.
You're blocking
the check.
We've got a
donation, too.
Hold on a second.
How much
have you got?
$11 and, uh, 75 cents.
That's so cute.
Uh, gentlemen,
I have a bus outside.
We can swing by,
pick up the orphans,
and we can drive them
over to Gary's
for some milk and cookies.
What do you think,
Father?
I think that's fine.
It's a great idea.
Come on!
You don't
understand, man.
That $5,000,
that's our money.
Shame on you, Sam.
You know it's
the orphans' money.
Hey, Gar, thanks a lot
for the five grand.
Get out of here. I don't want
to see you again. You're a bum.
Go on. Get out
of my place.
Go on, scoot.
Fine. Fine.
Eight years of humiliating
you weenies is enough.
I'm gonna find a tougher
gang to humiliate.
Hey, you can look
all over Boston.
You won't find any weenies
tougher than us!
Yeah, that's
telling him, Woody.
Huh?
Sam, we've got to
get back at Gary.
Worse than we ever
got them before.
Come on,
let's get Gary.
Let's get Gary!
Let's get Gary! Let's get Gary!
SAM:
Come on...
Let's get Gary! Let's get Gary!
Aw, don't worry
about it.
Let's get Gary!
Come on.
What are we doing?
Man, we're pathetic!
We've been trying
to get Gary for eight years!
We never win!
We're pathetic.
There's nobody more pathetic
than us in the whole world.
Oh, please, Lilith.
Anything.
A back rub. A handshake.
Blow me a kiss.
We're not Frasier.
(chanting):
We're not Frasier!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/5ywu
Help other users to choose the best subtitles