Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Boy, did I have a
crazy dream last night.
What was it?
I was at this party with
a bunch of strangers.
The food was great. The music was loud.
All of a sudden,
everybody in the place
stopped and was lookin' at me,
and I realized that I
wasn't wearing any pants.
Oh, yes, yes.
I've had that dream a million times.
Yeah, me, too, and boy, is
it ever embarrassing, huh?
Why is that?
Uh... uh, Norm?
Never embarrassed me.
Tell you the one I hate.
You know, you're back in college, right?
And you haven't been to
class the entire semester,
and the teacher's about
to give the final exam.
Oh, yeah, that one's the worst.
What're you talkin' about, Carla?
You never went to college.
It's a dream, stupid.
Well, how about the one where
you go to this fancy restaurant,
and before they let you in,
they make you leave
your legs at the door?
Then the girl gives you
claim check number six.
So you go in,
but instead of food,
everyone's eatin' their silverware.
Only you can't really enjoy your fork
because you're so worried
that whoever got claim check
number nine might finish first
and pick up your legs by mistake.
Yeah, oh, yeah.
(piano plays)
♪ Making your way in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like to get away♪
♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always glad you came ♪
♪ You want to be where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You want to go where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Two vodka martinis and a Wallbanger.
Wallbanger!
Sam, I need to ask a big favor.
All right, as long as
it doesn't interfere
with your job.
Okay, then, I need to ask a huge favor.
Would it be possible
two weeks from this coming Wednesday
for me to leave work
early about ten minutes?
Sure, why not?
Oh, thank you, Sam.
Thank you very much.
And thank you for not prying further
into the matter.
Especially since, well,
I've no valid excuse
for my early departure.
Sam, I must be frank.
Sounds good.
I'll be Bob.
I mean, it's not as if I had
a dental appointment
or had to pick up some
relative at the airport.
Okay, Diane,
why do you have to leave early
two weeks from this Wednesday?
Well, if you must know...
I have a date.
Oh, yeah, I've heard of those.
Have fun.
Oh, sweet transparent bravado.
Could there be a soul dearer
than the little boy lost,
trembling on the edge of despair,
yet struggling manfully to
maintain his stiff upper lip?
Thank you for noticing.
Oh, wait, Sam, wait. One more thing.
What?
After our five-star-dinner-
and-season-premiere-
of-the-ballet
date,
Chad-- Dr. Stark,
may desire a kiss.
Would you mind--
should he ask--
if I let his lips touch mine?
Touch your what?
Oh, Mr. Peterson, I forgot.
Some guy dropped by earlier
and asked me to give this to you.
Oh, thank you, Woody.
And thank you, God!
Oh, well, what's that, Normie?
A research grant from the
National Beer Foundation?
No, Cliffie, just a measly
little pair of sky-view seats
for the Sox-Yankee
doubleheader tomorrow.
Whoa, you're kidding me!
I pulled every string I had
and I could only score standing room.
Come on. How'd you get that?
Sammy, it's not who you know,
it's who I know, all right?
Yeah.
A client friend of mine, Jerry Donahue,
sent those babies over to thank me
for being such a fantastic
financial counselor.
No, seriously, how'd you get 'em?
I'm tellin' you,
I saved the guy a bundle
on his taxes last year.
He asked me to invest
his windfall, you know?
And in the space of six short months,
I kinda doubled his money.
We got lucky on a little
convenience mart in Worcester.
What'd you do? Hold it up?
(laughs)
You guys are hilarious.
But Jerry's laughing
all the way to the bank, all right?
I diversified the guy.
We went into, uh, mutuals,
and a very pretty little biotech company
that just went public.
Boy, sounds like you got
the Midas touch there.
You should hear some
of the other great ideas
we have cooked up.
Yeah? Like what?
Mm... no, no, sorry, guys.
My lips are sealed.
Buy you a beer.
It's called "Tan 'N Wash".
Tan and wash, guys.
The ultimate marriage of
luxury and convenience.
A combination tanning salon
and coin-operated laundry.
Get real.
Come on.
The timing's right on this.
Summer tans are fading.
Winter's coming.
It's always dirty clothes season.
It's gonna be the hottest place in town.
I'm glad you're already
thinking about arson.
(laughs): Yeah, arson.
Don't listen to them, Norman.
And never be deterred
by the mindless jibes
of the ignorant masses.
Those ignorant masses are
gonna be our customers.
Hey, I'll be there will bells on.
Everyone'll be there, buddy,
fluffing, folding, relaxing happily
beneath the healthful rays
of a federally approved
UVA bronzing unit.
Well, Normie,
I gotta say it's the silliest,
most harebrained scheme
I've ever heard of.
Yeah.
Well, I gotta go.
(quietly): Normie, walk me out.
I'm not leaving yet, Cliff.
Neither am I.
Ma and I want in.
In where?
Don't be naive, Normie.
Put me up for five shares.
No, no, no.
Investments are risky, Cliff.
Look, I never do business
with friends, all right?
Besides, it's 200 bucks a share.
Put me down for five, too, will ya?
Oh, great, Norm, now
the cat's outta the bag!
CARLA: I think you're all crazy.
But if Clavin makes
big bucks and I don't,
I won't be able to live with the shame.
Give me a share.
Oh, me, too! Me, too!
You, Diane?
Laying bets on a laundry?
Well, in my case, it's not a gamble,
but rather a show of faith
in our great free enterprise system.
Yes, even Diane Chambers is not immune
to the renaissance
of American patriotism
in the 1980s.
Although I hasten to remind you
this does not imply any
shifting of my support
toward the current administration.
I hope nobody was looking
for a silent partner.
CARLA: You know, Diane,
you shouldn't be investin'
in a tanning salon.
You oughta be usin' one.
You got skin the color of Elmer's glue.
I happen to have
what Restoration poets
refer to as "alabaster skin."
Well, at least your hair looks nice.
Besides, with my rendezvous
with Chad coming up,
I dare not risk freckling.
Why not? If it got boring,
you could always
play connect-the-dots.
God, how this must torment you.
No, no, no, come on, Norm.
You gonna let us in or not?
Let's just change the
subject, all right?
Hey, he's tryin' to sidetrack us.
This thing must be a gold mine.
Yeah, yeah, hey, Normie,
uh, correct me if I'm wrong,
but yesterday you had a letter
you needed mailed.
I did it, and you can at
least return the favor.
Cliffie, that's your job.
Well, all right.
Then, as one
professional to another--
come on, Norm!
(all pleading)
I know what's gonna happen!
I know what's gonna happen.
Somethin's gonna go wrong
and you're all gonna blame me.
(all protesting)
All right, well, well.
All right, yes! Whoo! Whoo!
Hey, Wood, do you want in?
I don't think so.
You know, when I left home,
my father gave me
some very sound advice.
"Never trust a man who
can't look ya in the eye.
"Never talk when you can listen.
"And never spend venture
capital on a limited partnership
without a detailed, analytical
fiduciary prospectus."
Afternoon, everybody.
ALL: Norm!
Hey, Norm, how's the
world been treatin' ya?
Like a baby treats a diaper.
So...
what's the deal with
the, uh, "Tan 'N Wash"?
For a new business, I'd say Tan 'N Wash
is doing as well as could be expected.
Oh, yeah?
I dropped by this morning
and the only customer in the place
was a lonely woman kicking the hell
out of a jammed change machine.
Oh, come on. By the way,
you owe me a quarter
and a new pair of shoes.
Patience, Carla, all right? Patience.
There are gray skies on the horizon.
Yeah, it's gonna get cold
and damp and miserable.
We'll be wading in customers.
Yeah, I think we're wading
in something right now.
I've worked out a great
new promotional campaign.
Promotional campaign? Yeah.
Whew! Hey, hey!
Check out Mr. Tan there, huh?
Say, Sammy,
did you just fly to the
tropics and spend a week
and thousands of dollars under
the blazing, unhealthy sun?
(dismissive laugh)
No, no, Norm. No, I
just spent my lunch hour
under some healthful,
federally approved UVA rays
at the Tan 'N Wash.
Say, those clothes are really
lookin' clean there, pal.
Well, thank you, Norm.
Yeah. Now is it true
that with these coupons
anyone can get 25% off on
their first five visits?
Well, that's what I hear.
Great.
Well!
Hey... I tell ya,
is that Cliff Clavin
or is that Don Ho, huh?
Uh...
Where ya been, buddy,
some, uh, faraway island resort?
Oh, easy mistake, Norm,
but, no, I got this tan
right here in Beantown.
Is that at the new Tan 'N Wash
I've been hearing so danged much about?
That's right, Normie.
And, by the way, did you realize
that the tan first gained popularity
in what is now known as the Bronze Age?
Great, great. Well, I'm sold.
Oh, and, by the way, look
how white I used to be.
You wore your socks
in the tanning booth?
Well, I, I gotta be careful, Sammy.
The Clavin men have, uh,
feet like a baby's bottom.
With faces to match.
Will you back off, Carla?
I don't see you pitchin'
in for the cause here.
Yeah, yeah?
Well, all I know
is I wouldn't stick a fork in a toaster,
never mind my valuables.
Come on, guys.
Uh, whatta you say we
snap up these flyers?
They can't last forever.
Wouldn't be so sure, Norm.
You know, Peterson,
you've got the guts of a burglar.
In here peddling a tanning salon
on the sunniest day of the year.
Outside of someone
with a financial interest in the place,
who'd be stupid enough
to spend a minute in
your rip-off joint?
You try to help out a few
newly enterprising friends
and what do you get for your trouble?
45 minutes in hell.
Sit. Keep it down, will ya?
Keep it down here.
Keep it down?
I've got the worst sunburn of my life,
thanks to a faulty thermo-regulator
on tanning machine number three,
the Bahama Mama.
Frasier,
you're supposed to start
off slowly, all right?
But I must say, you do have
one heck of a fantastic
base coat there, Fras.
Yeah. Yeah, and your, uh,
your shirt sure smells fresher.
Really?
It's not too lemony?
Not for you.
(humming "Isn't It Romantic")
(humming)
Sorry.
Well, it's just that
it's such a lovely, sunny day out...
as your tanned faces will attest.
Well, I guess I'm feeling
especially girlish.
How come, Miss Chambers?
Nah, nah, nah, don't, don't.
You know, Woody--
the usual thing
that puts a bounce in a girl's step.
Ah! Support hose.
You're adorable.
No, I'm referring to
a very special evening.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Didn't you have a date
or something last night?
You know perfectly
well I saw Chad, but--
it was no big deal.
(humming "Isn't It Romantic")
Yeah.
I refuse to ask her about last night.
You ask her, Woody.
Gotcha.
Well, looky here.
The paper predicts the same
high for Boston as Honolulu.
That is Honolulu, Hawaii,
the state where you can get
a free tan all year round.
Carla, if you're
trying to say something,
why don't you just
spit it out, all right?
Tan 'N' Wash bites it.
Okay, I'll admit Indian
summer's killing us temporarily,
but this is Boston.
It's gonna get cold.
(humming "Isn't It Romantic")
Hey, Sam.
I found out all about
Miss Chambers' date.
I mean, uh...
beautiful night of magic.
Just spill it, will ya, Woody?
Well, the ballet was exquisite,
but it paled by comparison
to the enchanting coach
ride under the stars.
Chad held her porcelain
- like hand lightly,
tracing tiny circles on her alamander...
Alabaster.
...alabaster skin,
and then, fearing that
the spell might be broken,
she invited him up
to her pied-de-teer
for some quiet conversation
and warm brandy, and then...
What?
Miss Chambers said if you want to hear
the rest, you gotta ask her yourself.
(laughing) Oh...
Forget it! Forget it, man!
Oh, ask her, Sam.
Sounds like you won't be disappointed.
Forget it.
Frasier, a sunburn?
No, I'm doing my impression
of a blood blister.
CARLA: Hey, Frasier.
You know, there's something I've
always been meaning to ask you.
What was your reaction
the first time you saw Diane naked?
(screams in pain)
Normie, I can't hold out any longer.
Ma's getting antsy.
The last time she
spent a thousand dollars
was on a house.
Cliff, I'm sorry.
I-I really am, but you guys
begged me to let ya in.
It's not like I didn't warn you.
CARLA: Oh, sure.
"Don't do this. I pray
to God you don't do this."
You call that a warning?
You know, I predicted this. You guys are
nervous Nellies and you're
trying to blame it all on me.
I want out, Norm.
Yeah, me, too.
Who wants a tan in the winter anyway?
Wait, wait. This is not the smart move.
You gotta hang in there.
You gotta roll with
the punches, all right?
You're gonna roll with the punches
if you don't get us outta this.
Nah, I just don't think
that we're cut out for it.
No. Apparently not, all right?
Yeah, geez, have it
your way, guys, okay?
Look, all right, I tell ya what. Okay?
I'll personally buy out
your shares, all right?
I'll have your checks in
the mail within a week.
Stupid mistake. Stupid.
Stupid.
Ooh, ooh, boy.
It's still snowing out there.
Yeah, and every flake means
another buck in Norm's pocket.
You, you guys still moaning
because Norm hit the
jackpot and you didn't?
Hey, come on, Paul, give us some credit
for being adults, huh?
Hey, what do you say we
toilet paper his house?
Nah, it'd only make it look better.
Sam, excuse me.
May I have your ear for a moment?
Sure. Just don't leave any bite marks.
Sam, I've decided
to break off my relationship with Chad.
Who?
What an actor you are.
You know, if you hadn't
chosen bartending,
you could well have had
a career in the theater.
Or as a model.
Anyway, you needn't continue
this charade of nonchalance.
I'm ending my affaire de coeur
because I can sense how it's
secretly gnawing away at you.
Okay. all right.
I'm glad.
All I've been able to
think about is you and Chad.
In your apartment.
In his car, on the stairs.
Doing things even we never did.
I mean, I can't eat,
I can't sleep.
Oh, Sam. Really?
Gee, maybe I could have been an actor.
Oh!
Afternoon, everybody.
Norm!
Norman.
How're you feeling today, Norm?
Rich and thirsty.
Pour me a beer.
Yes, sir, Mr. Peterson.
Boy, you sure have
gotten successful, huh?
Well, Woody, you know what
they say about success.
It's one percent inspiration
and 99 percent perspiration.
So is your shirt.
Yeah, and you know what else they
say about success
there, Mr. Rockeflounder?
It's lonely at the top.
Yeah, but the food's better, Cliff.
Hey, you don't have to rub
our noses in it, man.
I mean, we're your friends, after all.
Friends?
You call yourselves friends?
The last four or five
times I've walked in here,
you treat me as if I've
done something wrong.
You know, not one of
you guys has bothered
to congratulate me for my success.
Which, I might add, you all had
a chance to share in.
Maybe I should just take my
refreshment business elsewhere.
When I think of all the
hours I wasted in here
when I could have been
wasting them somewhere else.
DIANE: Norman, Norman.
Please don't leave.
We're taking it out on you,
but we're really mad at ourselves.
The hostility you're feeling
is for our own stupidity
at bailing out of this project.
Right, everyone?
You guys are beautiful.
Oh, well, come on, wait a second.
Come on back here.
Yeah, we've been actin'
like creeps, Normie.
CARLA: I'll fluff up
your favorite stool.
Yeah, I'll open a fresh bag of pretzels.
And I'll pour you a beer
just the way you like
it-- within reach.
What we're trying to say here is,
we're sorry.
CLIFF: Yeah.
You had the guts to stick it out,
and we didn't, and you deserve
all the success now.
Thank you, Sam. Guys.
I'm really glad to
hear that because, uh,
I have a little surprise for you guys.
I never took you out
of Tan 'N' Wash at all.
And here are your first dividend checks
right here, huh?
Oh, Norman!
You're kidding me.
(all talking excitedly)
ALL: ? For he's a jolly good fellow ?
♪ For he's a jolly good fellow, ♪
? For he's a jolly good
fellow, ? (phone rings)
WOODY: Cheers.
It's for you.
Put 'em on hold.
♪ Which nobody can deny. ♪
Hey. All right.
This is great.
Hey, look at that! It's snowing
even harder out now.
Oh, it's a harbinger
of good fortune!
You said it, bone butt!
Snow today means dough tomorrow.
Hey, let's carry Mr. Peterson
around the bar on our shoulders
and then go play in the snow.
Let's go play in the snow.
Hold it! Hold it!
Last one out's a Clavin.
No, you're not. You're
not gonna get me this time.
Oh, I'm always the Clavin.
Ah, Woody. Woody, Woody, Woody.
Look at them, huh?
Isn't that great?
They're singin' and dancin'.
It gives me a great feeling all over
to do something good for those people.
Oh, speaking of people,
you got one on hold here.
Hello. Yeah, hi.
Oh, no. No.
No, get out. No!
What're you...?
No, man, no!
No...
Well, at least we...
No?!
We, no, but wait a, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Bad news, Mr. Peterson?
Wrong number, Woody.
Aren't those annoying?
(all yelling, laughing)
Uh... Huh! Guys! Good friends!
Listen, people, uh, excuse me!
Listen, I know things have
been going just beautifully,
but, uh, hey, would you stop jumping
up and down for a second?!
Thank you.
Now let's just take a
hypothetical situation.
Just for fun, let's just
say that the roof collapsed
over at Tan 'N' Wash from
the weight of all this snow
and by some little quirk we
didn't have any insurance.
How would you guys feel about that, huh?
Just checking.