Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Woody.
I hear that you and Kelly
are having a hard time
getting a wedding ring.
That's right, Carla.
They're pretty expensive,
you know.
Yeah. That's
what I thought.
And you know, I'm not
gonna be able to afford
to get you kids the kind
of present you really deserve,
so, on the way
over here
I stopped by my bank,
and, uh,
I took this out
of my safety deposit box.
Oh, Carla, that's a beaut!
Yeah, I know.
It's solid silver.
It's been in my family
for years.
My great uncle Amerigo
gave it to my
great aunt Sophia,
and then I was gonna give it
to my youngest girl,
but she inherited
the Tortelli knuckles.
Oh, Carla, I could
never take it.
Oh, Woody,
I-I want you to have it.
Well, at least let me
give you something for it.
I have $500 in my budget.
Well, if it makes you
feel better.
Well, you know,
the thing is,
uh, Kelly really
prefers gold.
Oh.
Well, I got it
in gold, too.
Perfect.
Hey, does she need
any earrings?
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Afternoon, everybody.
ALL:
Norm!
Oh, hey, Mr. Peterson,
that's quite a haircut.
Yeah, well, they're only
halfway done, Woody.
I got a little thirsty.
You know what I mean?
Give me a beer.
Hi, Woody.
Oh, hey, Kelly.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to
spend the afternoon
with Mr. Peterson
and Mr. Clavin.
Boy, you've been spending
a lot of time
with them lately. What's up?
I thought it would
be a good idea
for me to get to
know your friends.
Why?
Because when
we get married,
and you turn to me
and say, "Kelly,
I'm gonna spend a
night on the town,"
and I burst into
tears and ask you
to spend just one
night at home, and
you say, "I'm gonna
be with my friends,"
well, I want to know
who those friends are.
Boy, could I sing
a couple bars of that.
So, what do you guys
talk about?
Oh, the usual.
How the Celtics
need a point guard,
the Sox need pitching,
the fact that there's an
exact replica of the earth
on the other side of the
sun that we can never see.
Wow. Really?
The Sox need pitchers?
Well, on this earth.
Anyway, Woody, if
you'll excuse me now,
one of your friends is gonna
teach me how to play pool.
Oh, which one?
I don't remember
his name, but
he's the man from the CIA
who trains the Green Berets.
Let's go, tootsie. We're up.
Do you realize
it's been 18 years
since we've seen each other?
Me, too. I can't wait.
Okay. Bye-bye.
You'll never guess
who that was.
Your dental hygienist?
Come on. Be
serious. Guess.
Okay, I'll be serious.
I don't really care.
(scoffs)
Well, I'm gonna tell you anyway.
It was Mark Newberger.
We have not seen each other
since graduation night.
Oh, Mark Newberger.
We met doing The Bad Seed
in our sophomore production.
He was my first boyfriend.
I really loved him.
Maybe he was the only guy
I've ever really loved.
I don't know
why I gave him up.
Oh, I guess I wanted to go off
to college and be free,
that whole deal.
I don't know.
What an idiot.
Why would I ever
give him up?
Nobody's listening
to you.
I am trying to pretend
like I have a friend, okay?
Wait. What am I saying?
I do have a friend. I
don't need to pretend.
Mark Newberger is back,
and he's better than
any friend you have!
I'm sorry.
I wasn't listening.
Anybody in here
know this guy?
Sam! My God, what's the matter?
We found him out
in the middle of the street
staring at an empty
parking space,
muttering to himself,
shouting at people.
SAM:
My corvette!
They stole my 'Vette!
Frasier, have you seen
my 'Vette?
Oh, Sam, I'm
afraid not.
Well, Sam, stop by
the station house sometime
and fill out
a report.
Then you'll give me
my 'Vette back!
Whatever you say.
Oh, God.
I left it outside!
What was I thinking?
I should have
stayed with it!
Boy, oh, boy,
oh, boy, Normie,
I'm gonna miss that car.
Here, take a look at that.
Wow. That's you next
to Sammy's 'Vette.
Yeah.
Truth be told, I, uh...
I tell the ladies it's mine.
Yeah.
Wait. That's not
even your body.
It's Sammy's body with
your head superimposed.
Yeah, you'd be surprised
what Ma can do in a darkroom.
Yeah. Yeah, we got one of, uh,
me at the Yalta conference.
Yeah.
You-You should see the look
that Churchill's giving me.
Oh. Oh. Oh!
I suppose one of us ought to
go over and cheer Sammy up.
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Well, I'll do it.
I, uh...
I got a flair
for this kind of thing.
You just, uh, stay there
and drink your beer.
Okay. We all have to play
to our strengths, I guess.
Oh, Sammy.
Sammy, Sam, Sammy.
Gee, you know, I, uh,
heard about the bad news.
I'm really sorry, pal.
It's, uh, terrible
what these guys do.
You know, they, uh,
just pluck your car
right up off the
street and take it
to what's, uh, commonly
known as a chop shop.
Yeah, where they
unceremoniously dismantle it,
and after that,
the felons take
an acetylene torch, and, uh,
just methodically
cut the frame
into little,
tiny pieces.
Cliff, do you really think
any of this helps?
Well, it sure as heck keeps
the car from being traced, Sam.
(raspy voice):
Uh, hi.
I'm looking
for Rebecca Howe.
She's over there.
Rebecca?
My God, Rebecca,
you're beautiful!
Who'd have ever thought
that you would've developed
into this gorgeous creature?!
No, Mark!
Over here!
Rebecca, you haven't
changed a bit!
My God, look
at that hair!
If you had any more,
I could get you listed
as an endangered species!
Well, come on, turn
around, turn around.
Let me see.
Oh, I like it.
More to love.
Me? What about you?!
Hey, I'm bulking up
for the Olympics.
(laughs)
You'll never
guess what.
I finally gave up smoking.
Oh, I can tell. Your voice
sounds so much better.
Sam?
Sam, I want you
to meet somebody.
Sam, this is Mark Newberger.
Mark Newberger,
this is Sam Malone.
Sam owns the bar.
Let me go get some of
my other friends.
Okay.
Hey, guys, guys, I want to
introduce you to somebody!
Somebody stole my car.
Oh, I've been there.
Yeah? Really?
Yeah, my ex-lover.
First he stole my heart,
then he stole my car.
He?
Aren't you supposed
to be Rebecca's old flame?
Well, I'm
not that old.
Thank God he didn't
steal the water bed,
the lying little tramp.
Meow!
Like you were there.
REBECCA:
Mark,
I want you
to meet all my friends.
All right,
this is Dr. Sternin-Crane,
our resident
researcher.
This is Cliff Clavin,
our resident
trivia expert.
This is Norm
Peterson,
our... resident.
Uh, this is Woody,
the bartender
and Carla,
the waitress.
And what do you
do, Rebecca?
(whispering):
Shut up!
Thought I could trick
her into telling us.
Oh, Lilith,
I feel so victimized.
I feel so angry.
I don't know what to do.
Well, actually, Sam,
this is precisely how
victim support
groups got started.
People who were suffering
and unable to cope found
they felt better
if they were able to
share those feelings.
Well, maybe I should try
to get in one of those groups.
I wonder if they have
a group for people
who have had high-performance
automobiles stolen.
You had a
car stolen?
Yeah.
What kind was it?
'64 Corvette.
'57 Tee-Bird
two weeks ago today.
Oh, man.
Does it still
really hurt inside?
Sometimes more
than others.
Like, when I'm
late for work,
and I run out of the house
and try and jump in it.
Just end up in the
gutter weeping.
Oh, man, I hear you,
I hear you.
It just
isn't fair.
Oh, no kidding.
You know, when bad things happen
to good-looking people.
Oh, here's you
in glee club.
Captain of the
debate team.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, Mark, you...
Oh, look, Water
Polo Champion.
Oh.
Head of the
prom committee.
Most likely to succeed.
Are you in there,
Miss Howe?
Well, sure I am. Here.
I... I know I am.
Wait. There.
Oh, yes.
Yes, there's my elbow
on protest day.
Oh.
What were you
protesting?
Oh, I-I don't know.
The war, cafeteria food,
the bomb.
Uh, it's just a real neat way
to meet kids.
Look at this.
18 years old--
ready to graduate
and take on the world.
Wait a minute.
You graduated from high
school when you were 18?
What, did Daddy
pull some strings?
(gasps)
Look at this! Look,
look, look, look, look!
Here's our production
of South Pacific.
Oh, Mark, you were the most
powerful Emile de Becque.
Oh, and you were a great...
one of the nurses that washed
Nellie Forbush's hair.
Hey, Kelly,
how's it going back there?
Oh, fine. I just came out
to get myself a soda
and some suds
for the Philster.
Kelly, why are you
doing this?
I want Woody's
friends to like me.
Did you buy them
a round?
Yes.
You'll never
get rid of them.
You know, Carla,
you're the only one
of Woody's friends
that I haven't
spent time with yet.
Let's you and I
have a chat, hmm?
I'd better put on
my thinking cap.
Oh, doll,
I have got to run.
Kiss, kiss.
Oh, Mark,
so soon?
Yeah. Well, I found
this great apartment,
but the rent is sky-high,
so I'm interviewing roommates.
This could be exhausting.
Later.
So that was
the old boyfriend, huh?
(sighing):
Yeah. Can you believe it?
How could I have been
so stupid?
I should have seen it
way back in high school.
Well, we all have
our blind spots.
Yeah. This one was just
staring me right in the face.
He is the perfect man for me.
I think this is the man
that I'm gonna marry!
(clapping)
Mr. Peterson.
Yeah?
It's your barber
on the phone,
and he says it's been two days.
He wants to know
when you're coming back.
What should I tell him?
Tell him what
I tell Vera.
Uh, he'll be home
after one more.
Yeah, I'll tell you,
Cliffie, uh,
when it comes
to photography,
your ma's quite
a hotshot.
Yeah, yeah,
she's pretty good.
Uh, you like
this one, huh?
Yeah.
That's me planting Old Glory
on the lunar surface.
Here's my favorite.
It's you getting
hitched to Princess Di.
Yeah, what a day
that was.
Excuse me,
is this where
the victim support group
is meeting?
Yeah, right over
by the office there.
I'll be right with you.
There you go.
Sam, uh, am I
to understand
that you took it upon yourself
to form a
victim support group?
I think that's
an excellent idea.
Well, actually,
it was Lilith's idea.
It'll never work,
I hope you know.
You Tom's friend?
Oh, yeah, I'm,
uh, Kirby,
1967 vinyl
covered hardtop,
sun fire yellow, 427
high performance engine.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Hi, hi, I'm Sam, I spoke
to you on the phone.
'64 ragtop, black interior,
rally red
with, uh,
knock-off hubs.
Good to know you, man.
Yeah.
This is '70
Cutlass Supreme
convertible,
uh, white interior
with overdrive.
I'm sorry, I'm not very good
with names-- what's your name?
Sam.
Sam, right.
Shall we?
Honey, come on, sweetheart.
We... we got the office here,
thank you.
Sorry.
I'm almost ready
for my big date.
Hey, guys.
Don't wait up for me.
Nudge, nudge, wink, wink.
(laughs)
If she was only a...
horse with a broken
leg or something,
we could shoot her.
Well, hey,
Norm, Norm, Normie,
we... we've got
to tell her.
Come on.
One of us has got
to tell her-- let's go.
One, two, three.
All right!
My rock smashes
your scissors.
Oh, no, not these
scissors, pal.
What?
This is a, uh, special
titanium steel alloy...
Oh, give me a break!
Developed by NASA
for the space program.
These scissors would smash
your rock to smithereens, pal.
No, no, no, not this
rock-- this rock happens
to be Kryptonite, from
the planet Krypton.
Oh, for
crying out...
Maybe you've
heard of it, huh?
Sounds to me
like you guys
are trying to get out
of telling her.
Oh, well, gee, Woody,
if you're so brave,
why don't you, uh,
go back there and tell her?
All right, I will.
'Cause you know what?
That's what friends do.
They look out for each other.
If one friend knows something
that another friend needs
to know, then he lets them know,
even if it's difficult.
That's what friendship
is all about.
What am I supposed to tell her?
Tell her that her friend,
Mark, is gay.
(laughing):
Oh, I could never tell her that.
Okay.
Hey, girls,
here's a little trick
I learned
in high school.
You put on your lipstick...
then you powder them.
That way,
when you're making out,
you don't get the lipstick
all over the boy.
(giggles)
Aha.
Rebecca,
I believe you're laboring
under a misconception...
Oh, no, Lilith.
Rebecca, you see,
what Lilith
is trying to say
is that...
the powder isn't gonna keep
the lipstick off the boy,
but if he really cares,
he's not gonna mind.
Yeah.
So just go on out
and have a great time.
Oh, thank you, guys!
Bye!
Why didn't you
let me tell her?
'Cause it would be wrong.
It-It's not
our place
to interfere with
their personal lives.
That's why they're
called "personal lives."
It's not our place
to play God.
Well, actually,
I pulled down 60 big ones
last year playing God,
but I see your point.
And I owe you an apology.
I actually thought you didn't
want to tell her
so that she would be humiliated,
at which point you
would make fun of her.
See how wrong you were?
(door closes)
How was your date
last night, Rebecca?
Get lucky?
(laughing)
Okay, let's talk some
more about how we feel
about having our
cars stolen.
Alice, you want
to start off?
I feel empty.
Okay.
Empty, how?
Like...
a Crock-Pot?
Let me... let me
just respond
to what Alice
just said,
you know, that...
that Crock-Pot thing.
Yeah, yeah, that's me.
Sometimes when I'm walking
down the street,
I think I see my car
out of the corner of my eye.
Let me, let me just
say something here, you...
That... that
"corner of the eye" thing...
yeah, that's me.
Guys, you... I just thought
of something, you know.
I mean, maybe our cars
weren't actually stolen.
Maybe... maybe they
were just towed by the city
and it's... and it's
taking them time to...
to process the paperwork
and, you know...
and, uh...
(sobbing)
I think what Kirby's going
through here
is what they call denial.
(crying):
I feel so silly!
Oh, no, man, come on,
don't say that, don't be...
This is not silly;
this is beautiful.
This is what
it's all about.
You know,
I think it's true.
Suffering does bring
people together.
I tell you, I feel very close
to you all right now.
I-I just want to say I...
I treasure our friendship.
(knock at door)
Hey, Sam.
Police called--
they just found your car.
Okay,
meeting's over.
That was a great
dinner tonight.
I haven't had osso buco
that good in years.
What the hell is
osso buco anyway?
You don't want
to know.
Mark, I-I had the
greatest evening tonight.
Well, we're gonna have a lot
of great nights.
I want to pick up
right where we left off.
Do you want to
start right now?
Sure.
Okay.
You just make
yourself comfortable,
and I'll be right back.
I feel like we're
in high school
again, don't you,
Marcus Aurelius?
Yes, I do, Beckus Aurelius.
You remembered
my Latin name.
Well, how could I forget?
You're the one
who got me
through Mr. Vincent's
Latin class.
(Rebecca gasps)
Oh, Mr. Vincent-- I
forgot all about him.
Oh, God, I had
such a crush
on that man.
(softly):
Who didn't?
Here I am.
Be still, my heart.
Do you like what you see, Mark?
It's gorgeous.
Get over here.
Give us a feel.
Okay.
Fabulous.
Give it--
is it silk?
Rayon?
I don't believe it!
So what do you do, you put it
in a delicate cycle,
let it spin?
We have to talk.
Mark, stop joking.
You know perfectly
well that the point
of this nightie is not
laundry instructions.
The point of this
nightie is to...
To what?
You know... a
man and a woman...
Where?
Oh, Mark.
Rebecca, you know I'm gay,
don't you?
Why, of course, I do!
Why do you think I
feel so comfortable
wearing this in front of you?
I mean, this is my housecoat!
I know it's sexy,
but I paint in it.
You're gay?
Don't tell me you didn't know.
I mean, usually I assume
that somebody is straight
until I find out they're not.
That's funny,
I usually assume people are gay
until I find out they're not.
Sometimes we find out together.
Oh.
I'm the one, aren't I?
Yeah, I'm the one
that put you off girls.
No, Rebecca.
No, no, really,
go ahead, you can say it.
I've heard it before.
Rebecca, if anything,
you confused me.
You're the only woman
I've ever been attracted to.
Thank you.
Oh, look at you--
you're getting goose bumps.
Come on, let's cuddle up
on the couch
with a blanket, huh?
(sighs)
So we both
like men?
Yep.
Are we stupid
or what?
They're so insincere
and they're
inconsiderate, rude.
They lie,
they cheat on you.
Men.
You know, things really
would have been
a lot easier
if I was attracted to women.
Me, too.
You want to
watch some TV?
Yeah, sure.
Maybe there's
an old movie on, huh?
Rebecca.
Hmm?
What are you doing?
Looking for the
remote control.
It's on the
coffee table.
You can't blame
me for trying.