CARLA: Hey, Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
FRASIER: Hi, Wood.
Let me get a beer, will you?
Oh, say, what'd you
do to your thumb there?
Oh, well, it's a long story, but, uh,
I was playing this guy
some pool last night,
and I had this one-
four-seven combination.
Yeah.
So, I was trying to show off
and sink all of them in one shot,
but the balls were positioned
in such a way that I had to lean
way over the edge of the table
and get in a kind of twisted-up...
Yeah, so, what, you fell
and you broke your thumb?
No. I still couldn't get the shot,
so I went and got the bridge
and I got up on a chair
and I put all my weight on the bridge.
And it snapped and you
fell and broke your thumb?
No.
I made the shot and I beat the guy.
Oh, so he got angry and
he broke your thumb, right?
No, I beat him fair and square
and he paid me the ten bucks he owed me.
So, how did you break your thumb?
I slipped on the ice on the way home.
Woody, why did you go into
all that long-winded
detail about the game?
Well, now, it wouldn't
have been much of a story
without the pool stuff.
Hello, Woody.
What happened to your thumb?
Oh, I slipped on the ice.
Woody, why didn't you tell him
the long, drawn-out version?
That's the guy I was playing pool with.
(piano plays)
♪ Making your way in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like to get away♪ ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always glad you came ♪
♪ You want to be where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You want to go where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
What the hell is keeping Diane?
I'm gonna be late for school.
School, Carla?
Well, I must say I'm
delightfully astonished.
You know, I've always
held that adult education
is one of the finest gifts
that one can give oneself.
Kudos on joining the
ever-burgeoning ranks
of enlightened, wondering minds
seeking betterment through knowledge.
It's traffic school, you nimrod.
You got pinched, huh, Carla?
Yeah, speeding.
But it wasn't my fault.
There was a leaf stuck on my windshield,
and I had to gun her
up to 80 to blow it off.
What, and the cop didn't believe you?
No. Couldn't be bribed, either.
Carla, what, you offered
a policeman money?
Money? With a body like this? Huh.
Hello, everyone.
We're back.
Sammy, where you been, man?
Picking china patterns.
This may have been the
stupidest morning of my life.
Oh, Sam, don't forget.
Tomorrow we register for flatware.
The second stupidest.
Well, did you select something nice?
We've committed to
Royal Doulton's Carlisle
for the fine china,
but Sam still hasn't made up his mind
about the everyday ware.
Yes, I have.
I, I like the dishes with
the different colored flowers.
Oh, ish!
Come on, I love those.
They're just like I
had when I was a kid.
They're real pretty,
and-and if you don't like
the food on your plate,
you can hide it in the pattern.
Okay, fine.
Well, uh, why don't you think about it,
and if you still insist
that they're not the
most garish, bourgeois,
stomach-turningly ugly
pattern in the book,
then that's what we'll get.
She's making me nuts
with this wedding stuff.
So, ditch her.
You know, if I had my way,
I would find the nearest
justice of the peace
and, and tie the knot.
You know, that's not such a bad idea.
Right. Or you could ditch her.
Don't you have traffic
school, or something?
Nuts! Now I'm gonna be late!
Well, I guess I can make
it if I run all the yellows.
Sam... Yo.
I've got Penelope from the
bridal registry on the line,
and we're going back
over the linen choices.
Now, for the fingertip towels
in the guest bath, do
we want monogrammed,
or is that too ootsie?
The second thing you said.
I agree.
Of course... a simple
initial can be elegant.
Oh, I think you'd better
look at the picture.
I need a man's opinion.
Frasier, help Diane, will you please?
Sam, these will be our fingertip towels
for the rest of our lives.
We'd better get married
quick, or I'm gonna kill her.
All right, all right, that's it.
Bachelor party here tonight.
What are you talking about?
Well, didn't you hear the man?
Uh, they might be eloping.
And I'm not gonna be, uh, done out
of my right as best man
to, uh, throw him the best
wingding of the century.
All right now, so
what're we gonna have...?
Just a second here, Cliff.
Uh, Sam asked you to be his best man?
Well, not in so many words,
but, uh, you know, who's closest?
So, uh... (everybody talking)
Hold on now, I don't know.
I may not have known Sam
as long as some of you guys,
but we're pretty darned close.
I think I'm kind of like
the brother he never had.
Wait, Woody, Sam has a brother.
Guess we're not as close as I thought.
Well, look, I think we better throw
the greatest bachelor party
for the greatest
bachelor who ever lived.
Tell you what.
I'll pick up some deli
platters and some champagne,
and you guys can just reimburse me,
you know, at your leisure, all right?
CLIFF: Why didn't you
say so in the first place?
Okay, we got the food and
the drink taken care of.
Now we need a little
bit of entertainment.
Who's gonna...?
Well, I-I think
tradition calls for, uh,
what about a stag film, huh?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, I think there's
a place on my route
that might sell them.
Uh, the, uh, Hot and
Nasty Video Boutique.
Yeah, I think there might be
one or two laying around there.
Okay, we got the food,
drink, entertainment.
Now all we need is a, uh,
a girl jumping out of the cake.
(general agreement)
Oh, yeah, I've seen them do that
in the movies all the time.
That seems like a waste
of good cake to me.
You see, Woody, the cake
is really immaterial.
It's the girl who's the actual dessert.
Right.
Well, then I think it
should be Miss Chambers.
FRASIER: Ooh. Aw, come on.
you know,
no guy wants his fiancée
jumping out of a cake.
It's, I mean, it's like
taking your mother to the prom.
(chuckling)
Or so I'm told.
PAUL: Okay, okay, okay,
so where can we get Sammy someone hot?
Dare we look in his book?
Nah, Sammy's had all those girls.
Oh, Sam, stop being
such a grumble-bunny.
Just grit your teeth and
pick out a dust ruffle.
Guys, I still say
we're missing a bet
right under our noses.
Look, pal, trust me...
Oh, it's... that's okay.
Listen, I... it wouldn't hurt to ask.
CLIFF: No, no, no, no, don't, don't...
Excuse me, Miss Chambers?
Yes, Woody? Uh...
Uh, would you like to jump out
of Sam's bachelor party cake?
Woody, I abhor such
juvenile, sexist male rituals.
Yeah, but would you do it?
Just checking.
All right, guys, you're right.
We're going to have to find
some other beautiful
girl to be Sam's dessert.
Wait a minute.
(laughing)
I, I just realized
why you want me,
the bride-to-be,
to jump from the cake.
It's a wonderful irony.
(laughs)
Oh...
Of course I'll do it.
Of course.
Oh, great.
Imagine me, of all people,
missing the point of a joke.
(laughing)
Hey, don't worry about
it, Miss Chambers.
It even happens to me.
NORM: Sammy, uh, what
time you got there, man?
11:15.
11:15. How did it get so late so early?
I'd better be getting home to, uh, Vera.
(yawning): Oh, yeah.
(everybody talking and yawning)
Yeah, you know what they say:
"An early bird catches
the obsessive-compulsive."
(laughing)
'Night, Sam.
MAN: Oh, boy!
They sure took off in
a hurry, didn't they?
Yeah, but that doesn't seem
suspicious to you, does it?
No, I... I guess not.
Oh, hey, I have an idea.
You go in the back
and total these receipts,
and we'll get out of here.
Okay.
All right.
Say, Woody, when I come back out here,
there's not going to be a
surprise for me, is there?
A surprise party, maybe?
No.
You're not lying, are you?
Sam, you'd know if I was lying.
I'd... I'd tell you.
Right. I'll, uh, I'll be in my office.
WOODY: All right.
Come on in, guys.
He doesn't suspect a thing.
Come on down, fellas.
(half-whispers)
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Okay? In the words of the
immortal bard, "Party!"
(silent cheering)
Uh, Sam, you can go home now.
EVERYONE: Surprise!
(whooping and cheering)
(laughter and applause)
Wow!
Sam, you should have seen
the look on your face!
(music playing on video)
SAM: Ooh!
FRASIER: Hey!
All right!
(guys whooping)
Boy! Thanks, guys.
Yeah, man.
That last scene gave me new
respect for rowing machines.
I hear you, bud. Ooh!
Hey, you guys, oh! Thank you.
This has been fantastic.
I have to admit
that I used to think
that bachelor parties
were kind of embarrassing.
Get the lights!
SAM: Oh, God, not again...
(guys cheering)
Girl in there, right?
Well...
Just your type.
So make the obligatory
speech and have at her!
GUYS: Yeah!
Oh, no, I can't do it.
I... you know... (scoffs)
No, I-I know you went
to a lot of trouble.
I'm sorry, but it
just wouldn't be right.
CLIFF: What? Come on,
Sammy. What is this?
Malone, King of the Road!
(everyone whooping)
Better make hay, buddy.
After this, it is one woman
for the rest of your life. Oh, boy.
EVERYONE: Yeah...
I-I never really thought
about it in those terms before.
One woman for the rest of my life.
(everyone chuckles) I
mean, don't get me wrong.
I mean, she's... she's a...
she's a great woman, but, uh...
there's only one of her...
...for the rest of my life.
But, you know, it'll go quickly.
Just go-go ahead, cut the cake.
Boy, it really makes you think.
You know, I've been a
bachelor a good long time.
I mean, a good lot of women.
Now there won't be any more women.
Just woman.
One woman.
Yeah, but what a woman!
I mean, you know what? I've got an idea.
Why don't we have some cake?
(everyone agreeing)
One perfume.
One set of earlobes.
Not, not even sensitive earlobes.
One pair of lips flapping in my ears...
day after day until I die.
Oh, my God!
Sammy, Sammy, that's great.
Look, we got a big,
wonderful cake here, you know,
with a... with a very
special surprise inside...
which just might spoil
if you don't shut up!
Uh... I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
What am I doing?
I mean, if I'm going to tie myself
to the old ball and
chain, I might as well get
one last night of freedom in here.
(everyone agreeing)
Okay, bring her out here.
Strap her on.
Come on.
EVERYONE: Yeah!
Strap this on!
Sam, you should see
the look on your face!
Hi, guys.
Hey, Carla, how was traffic school?
Eh, it was all right.
NORM: Yeah?
Well, don't all those
gory movies they show
kind of turn your stomach a bit?
Hey, Norm, you're forgetting...
I've seen Diane without makeup.
Hello, everyone.
Hi.
Hello, you.
Let me help you with that.
Well, all right.
Boy, you look fantastic, dear.
That is a great outfit on you.
Sam... Hmm?
You make a lousy sycophant.
Yes, but I make a great margarita.
May I speak to you in
your office, please?
Sure, anything you want. You bet cha.
SAM: Oh, come on, smile.
DIANE: For some reason,
I don't feel like smiling.
Did I ever tell you how cute you are
when you're mad?
Come on, listen, snap
out of this, will you?
I mean, I-I didn't say
all that stuff last night
to hurt your feelings.
My feelings aren't hurt.
I just feel bad for you.
Sentenced to a life with one perfume...
...one set of insensitive earlobes,
one set of lips flapping in your ear...
...till you die.
Come on! I was with a bunch of guys.
I mean, they forced me to make a speech.
How the hell did I know
my fiancée was hiding
in the cake, taking dictation?
Did you mean it, Sam?
No.
See, it's just this...
this whole marriage thing's
kind of snuck up on me, that's all.
I mean, I'm happy that
you're the only woman
I'll make love to again... ever.
(fingers snapping)
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, but-but, you see...
I mean, if I had known
that the last one was
going to be the last one,
I-I-I would've
prepared myself for it.
Sweetheart, it's kind of like popcorn.
Now, you-you can munch away
as long as you know there's a bowlful,
but, you know, if all of a sudden,
it's all gone, there's nothing
left but the salt and the duds,
well, you feel bad,
because if you'd known
the last kernel was the last
one, you would've savored it.
Am I making myself clear on this?
Oh, yes, yes...
Oh. I'm salt and duds.
Well, I-I-I
don't know. I...
I don't know what to say to
make this right, except...
I'm sorry.
Would 24 hours of wild, uninhibited,
hedonistic sexual carousing with
anything in a tube top suffice?
In-in a-addition
to saying I'm sorry?
Sam, you can apologize
till the cows come home,
but it won't alleviate the problem.
After much consideration,
I propose that you go on a flesh binge.
Sow your wild oats.
Get it out of your system.
Savor your last kernel of popcorn.
Are you serious?
Absolutely.
It's the only way we can
establish a clean slate.
No guilt, no remorse, no regrets.
So...
dive into that little black
book of yours and enjoy.
Oh, you know,
I threw that dumb thing
away when we got engaged.
I'm sure you have one
or two numbers etched
in your memory.
You listen to me.
I'm only going to agree to do
this because I love you, Diane.
Well, don't do it for me, Sam.
Do it for the health
of our future marriage.
Right, right, right.
Uh, excuse me, uh...
when do my, uh, 24 hours begin?
Right now.
All right. The same as mine.
Okay. Wait, wait, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Yours?
Of course, Sam.
This is the only way we can be sure
that I have all other
men out of my system.
No... no...
Sammy back yet?
Uh, well, uh,
"T" minus 30 minutes and counting.
I figure right about now,
Sammy's probably leaning
back in bed and smoking.
Oh, wait, I don't, uh, remember
ever seeing Sammy smoke a cigarette.
Who said anything about cigarettes?
Ho, the man!
All right!
Hey, what's the score, Sammy?
Oh, Norm, you know he's not the
kind of guy to kiss and tell...
not that he wastes much time
kissing, anyway, eh, compadre?
Yeah, you guys know me, all right.
So, has anyone, uh...
anyone heard from Diane?
No, not a word. It's been heaven. Ah.
Why? You worried about her?
No, I'm not worried.
Wha-What makes you think I'm worried?
Uh, what time is it, anyway?
It's time for you to stop worrying.
I mean, for God's sakes, Sammy,
who'd be stupid enough to touch Diane?
Besides you.
Good point.
You know, uh, yeah, what
am I worried about here?
Oh, Rick, you really came through.
Sam, Sam, Sam, Sam!
Rick was kind enough to drive me to work
when my car broke down.
I knew that.
I, uh...
I just wanted to give
him a thank-you shake.
Thank you, thank you.
Uh, maybe I'll, uh, take
a rain check on that drink.
Uh, good luck with your marriage.
Yes. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Thank you, Rick.
Well...
I guess I'll just, uh...
begin my shift.
Uh, yeah, like hell you will!
Sam? Now, Sam! Sam!
All right.
Where were you last night, hmm?
I was taking full
advantage of my 24 hours.
I looked into the recesses of my heart,
and I realized that I still had...
one oat that needed to be sown.
One fantastic oat.
Is that all you
think about-- sex?
You know, it's disgusting!
Wh-Wh-Whatever happened
to romance, to commitment?
I mean, look at you!
Look at you-- you haven't
even changed your dress!
I am wearing this dress
again because I like it.
It sets off my eyes.
Yeah, I'll set off your eyes.
You know...
You want know something?
I had the exact same 24 hours you did,
and I didn't do anything.
You know why?
Because I happen to be a one-woman guy.
I mean, I mean,
I think we got something
special going here,
and I didn't want to cheapen
it, like somebody else
I could mention.
You-you know, people could
refer to you as a tart.
How can you say that?
Easy. Tart!
Tart, tart, tart, tart!
I mean, what-what else
do you call somebody who didn't go home?
How do you know that?
Because I was idiot enough
to spend the entire night
watching your apartment from my car,
and you did not go home.
Well, you must be exhausted.
Yeah, yeah, that's right! I'm exhausted.
You're damned right, I'm exhausted.
Oh, come on, Sam.
Now, you had a little
catnap around 6:00 a.m.
Did not.
How'd you know that?
Because I was down the street
in my car watching you watch me.
Oh, my God, you spied on me!
I mean, that stinks!
What... what hap...
what happened to faith?
What-what-what happened...
what happened to trust?
My God!
Sam!
I took a lover's leap of faith
in granting you sexual carte blanche
for the past 24 hours!
And just as my heart suspected,
instead of gallivanting about,
you spent the whole time spying on me.
(wry chuckle)
I had one last night to go
out and have a great time,
and I blow it.
God, I'm a poor excuse for a stud.
I don't know about that.
We still have five minutes left...
in our deal.
Five minutes?
Mm-hmm.
Well, hell, somebody
should've told me that.
Damn it!
How long did you say we have here?
Five minutes.
Not enough time. Now, come on, Sam.
We'd better skip to the good part.
No... come on.
We have to go to work! Sam! Whoo!