Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
CLIFF:
Oh-- here's Sam.
CARLA: Oh, come on, Sammy.
Hey, Sammy.
Sammy, open up.
It's freezing!
SAM:
Hey, what are you guys standing
around for?
How come somebody
didn't let you in?
CARLA:
I left my keys home.
SAM:
Oh, no, I was
counting on yours.
REBECCA:
I left mine
in the office.
Hurry up! It's cold!
Well, how are
we gonna get in here?
NORM:
'Morning, everybody.
OTHERS: Norm!
(keys jangling)
NORM:
Sorry I'm late.
(theme song begins)
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Takin' a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always
glad you came
You wanna be
where you can see
The troubles
are all the same
You wanna be where everybody
knows your name
You wanna go
where people know
People are all the same
You wanna go where everybody
knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(grunts)
Sorry I took so long
getting here this morning.
Sam, you know, this is
the fourth time this week
that you've been late.
As a responsible businessman
and the owner of this bar,
you owe it to yourself
to stick
to a more responsible schedule,
you know.
Absolutely.
If the post office ran
its business the way
you run yours...
Never mind.
I have a good excuse this time.
I'm being treated
by a dermatologist.
Is it anything serious?
No, no, no...
I just told her
that I had a patch of dry skin,
and we stayed up all night
looking for it.
Found it, too--
four times, by golly.
Sammy, uh, can we stick
to the topic at hand, please?
Yeah, Sam. I don't mean to make
any threats here,
but Gary's Old Towne Tavern
already opens
a half-hour before you do.
And how do we know that, Norm?
Hey, who's on
trial here, huh?
Hey, everybody.
Hey, Woody...
You won't believe this.
I just found out
that on cable TV,
they have this channel
where they show you stuff
and you can buy it any hour
of the day, any day of the week.
How did we live before?
Yeah, yeah.
Home Shopping Channel--
Ma loves it,
she's always watching it.
She's always saying, "If I had
a rich son, he'd buy me this,
If I had a rich son,
he'd buy me that."
Who do you think bought her
the TV in the first place?
You, Cliffie?
No, but if I find the guy,
I'm gonna shove that clicker
down his throat.
Look at this--
I already got my first package.
Yeah?
Huh?
It's a toy car...
and also rewinds videotapes.
Now, uh, wouldn't a VCR
rewind tapes?
Uh, not the one I bought
last night.
REBECCA:
Excuse me,
Carla.
Did you read my last memo?
No.
Well, if you had read it,
you would know
that we are no longer accepting
time cards made out in pencil.
From now on,
all paperwork must be done
in ink.
Okay.
Did you hear me?
Are you acknowledging my memo?
I heard you!
I acknowledge
the damn memo!
Now would you get out of my face
so I can finish this time card?
I mean, this isn't easy,
you know.
My pencil's
almost down to the nub.
Well, as long as you're aware
of the problem.
Oy... that's something,
eh, Norm?
Remember the good old days?
When you used to be able to take
an argument like that
between two gals and turn them
into the Jets and the Sharks?
Tell you what, Cliffie,
for you, I'm gonna
tee it up one more time.
All right.
Watch this.
Rebecca, uh,
I noticed your
little exchange with
Carla over there,
and I have to say, I admire
your management technique.
Thank you very
much, Norm.
It takes a lot of courage,
you know, to humiliate yourself
just for the well-being
of one employee.
If you were a Japanese
businessman,
I mean, to lose face like that,
you'd probably have to
commit some sort
of ritual suicide, you know?
But here in America...
Carla!
Come in my office,
bring that time card
and a pen.
I'd better be
getting a raise.
(door closing)
CLIFF:
Oh,
the master returns
from his triumphal march
to the valley of evil.
I got a raise.
Frasier, darling,
today is
our monthly luncheon
with the Psychoanalytic
and Social Therapeutic
Practitioners Society.
Have you forgotten?
Well, let me finish this
double, and I might.
Now, Doctor...
Yeah, well, Lilith,
I really can't stand
another dry,
endless luncheon
in some stuffy
old restaurant.
Pretty boring,
huh, Fras?
Well, let me put
it this way, Sam.
Lilith is the
Dorothy Parker
of this particular
roundtable.
Come on, Frasier,
let's go.
All right, but I
won't enjoy it.
Hey, Norm, go ahead,
make them fight.
Oh, you do
it, come on.
Me?
Yeah.
CLIFF:
Hey, Fras, you
think Carla should be
filling out the time card
with a pen or a pencil?
I can see
why you can't tear yourself
away from this place.
All right, all right,
all right.
So I'm not you.
Cliffie, come on now.
Buck up, buddy.
You're, you're just
warming up here.
You got to start out with
an easy one first, huh?
Yeah.
Look, there's...
there's Paul!
There's Paul.
Hey, Hey, Paul!
Shut up, fathead!
Hey, guys.
Hey, Wood.
Look what I just got
on the shopping channel.
Now, there's
only about 2,000
of these little
babies left, so...
a word to the wise.
Well?
Well, that's, uh...
It's beautiful, Woody.
It's a beautiful cow.
Yeah.
I'll say, and that's not
the best part of it.
It's also a great clock.
(click)
MALE VOICE:
It's...
(imitating cow bellow):
...noon.
What, um...
What happens if
it's 7:00 o'clock?
Well,
a cow's power of speech are
kind of limited, you know.
Everything kind of
sounds like...
(imitates cow
bellowing):
...noon.
How do you ever know
what time it is?
Well, it helps if
you wear a watch.
I think it's, um...
I think it's nice, Woody.
Really?
Yeah.
It's yours.
Oh, no, Woody.
I-I-I... I real...
I couldn't.
Miss Howe,
I've been to
your apartment.
Take the cow.
I know you fellows favor
a more formal atmosphere,
but allow me
to charm you
with the quaint
hospitality of
my friendly
neighborhood tavern.
Excuse me, Frasier.
I have to go check
my messages.
You got one
from Madame Tussauds.
"Get back
to the museum."
Champagne for everyone, Sam.
Oh!
I'm trying to convince
my esteemed colleagues
to move their monthly meetings
to your fine establishment.
Oh, hey, thanks.
That's great.
Uh, my, uh, gold card
should keep the, uh...
the bubbly flowing.
(laughs)
NORM:
Cliffie, the master
has a thought.
CLIFF:
Yes?
One might wonder what
would happen if, uh,
we called a certain
credit card company
and reported that
number as stolen.
Then when a certain
bartender tried
to put it through for
a certain customer,
and it wasn't honored,
what do you suppose
would happen?
I don't know.
Major fireworks.
Oh!
You're a genius!
Why do you put up with me?
I don't know.
Frasier, I have to leave.
There's been an emergency.
Is it Frederick?
No, no.
Otto, my lab assistant,
has gotten into the
synthetic hormones again.
I have to
bail him out.
Or her. I won't know
until I get there.
Oh, no!
Miss Howe,
look what I found in the trash!
It's your cow!
Oh, dear, how could that
have gotten in there?
Sam?
You told me to
throw it away....
So, the
paranoid says...
(laughing)
"Help! Help!
They're all out to get me!"
(laughing)
I guess you had to be
in the session.
Dr. Crane, can I speak
to you for a minute?
Oh, of course, Sam.
SAM:
Got a little
problem here-- I, uh,
called to get approval
on your credit card here, and
they told me it was stolen.
Well that's utterly
ludicrous, Sam.
Well, yeah, that's
what I told them,
but they-they insisted
that it is stolen.
Yes, I-I knocked myself
over the head
and stole my own credit card.
That's brilliant, Sam.
Who would ever suspect me?
SAM:
I'm not kidding here.
You know, they're very
serious about their rules.
They told me that I
have to cut this up.
You wouldn't, Sam!
I don't want to, no!
Tell you what. Um,
why don't I, uh,
run a tab, huh?
Well, I don't need a tab.
It's a perfectly good card!
Well, why don't
I just, uh...?
This is on the
house, all right?
Oh, fine! Now you're adding
insult to injury!
Well, I don't take charity!
Just give me back
my card!
I can't give you back
the card, Frasier.
I've got to cut it up
and send the pieces
back to the company.
(scoffs)
You do not have to do that.
Yes, I do!
They spent a
half an hour
on just that fact at the
seminar at the Sheraton.
Sam, I am telling you,
you do not have to do that!
You weren't at
the seminar.
If I don't do this,
they're gonna take
my little card
thingy away.
Sam, I am not asking you.
I'm telling you!
Give me back my card!
Don't take that tone
of voice with me!
Frasier, can I help?
I have a card that works.
Oh shut up, you
Skinnerian baboon!
Sam, do not touch
those scissors to that card!
I got to do it, Frasier.
You do not!
Yes, I...
(choking grunt)
I'm sorry.
I t-tell you what.
Here, take-take
my credit cards.
Oh, fine!
With your $90 credit limit,
I can go hog-wild
at Monkey Ward's!
You have made me look the fool.
Yeah, I think you've
taken care of that all
by yourself, Frasier!
Oh. So it's come
to this, has it?
After years of friendship,
you proudly pour a tall cup
of humiliation.
Well, I've had enough,
thank you.
This is good-bye.
You have seen and heard
the last of Frasier Crane.
From this moment forward,
I am never stepping foot
in this bar again!
I close the iron door upon you!
What do we do now,
oh master?
Shut up and stop
calling me master.
Anyone hear from Frasier
since yesterday?
He'll be back,
don't worry about it.
I don't know,
he left here pretty angry.
I mean,
I keep calling the house,
and the machine
keeps picking up.
Oh, Lilith answers?
He's blowing off steam.
He'll be back.
Oh, I hope so.
Well... (clears throat)
I guess we really
messed up, huh?
We learned our
lesson, Cliff.
We've got to stop messing
with people's minds.
Yeah, I agree.
By the way, your
fly's open, buddy.
Yeah, so's yours.
(both laughing)
You can't expect a guy to
go cold turkey, you know.
(laughing)
You checked,
didn't you, Cliff?
Oh, yeah, like
you weren't looking
through the bottom
of that beer mug.
Miss Howe?
Last night the shopping channel
was a consumer bonanza,
and I took advantage of it.
Their loss is your gain.
First, I got you a genuine
gold-look bracelet
with 200 real sapphires.
Oh, Woody.
First of all, you have
to stop buying me gifts.
And second of all,
you have to learn
that sapphires are blue.
Okay, but you can't say
"no" to a new and improved
snackmaster and a portable
solar-powered telephone.
Woody, I cannot accept these.
People are going to get
the wrong idea.
What, that I have
a crush on you?
No, that I like crap.
You're calling
this stuff "crap"?
I'm sorry, Woody.
No, no, I was looking
for the right word.
Well, if you don't
like it either,
why do you keep
buying this stuff?
Not "stuff,"
Miss Howe-- "crap."
I buy it because
it looks good on TV.
The second they flash
that 800 number, I'm dialing.
Woody, this-this
has got to stop.
Well, it-it has
stopped, Miss Howe.
I went over my credit
limit with this... crap.
Unless, of course,
you'd care to advance me
six months on my paycheck.
Could be another
necklace in it for you.
An-And if you decide
not to give me the advance,
just keep the necklace
as your free gift.
Woody, you are hooked.
Listen to me,
you need help.
I don't need help, I
just need more credit.
You're right, Miss Howe,
I do need help.
I'm scared.
Help me.
Hurry.
Act now.
Well, I just got in
touch with Frasier.
NORM:
Oh, yeah, what'd he say?
Well, he said that he considers
these phone calls a harassment.
If I don't cease and desist,
he's gonna get a court order
restraining me from coming
within 50 feet of him.
Restraining order--
the last resort of shrinks
and housewives in nightgowns.
Come on, Cliffie.
We've gotta stop this
before it gets any further.
We've got to go to Frasier,
tell him exactly what happened.
Accept all blame,
and the sooner the better.
Yeah, you're right.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
What?
I just thought
of something.
What's that?
If we wait like a couple of
hours, it'll be dinnertime.
Might be able to snag
a free meal.
You are the master,
oh salam.
Now, this is lovely.
The baby's with my mother,
and there's nothing to
disturb our peaceful Eden.
You're right,
darling, nothing.
Except for the burned-in image
of Sam
cutting my gold card into pieces
before my very eyes.
You know, Frasier,
after listening to you complain
about that
for the umpteenth time,
it's becoming impossible for me
to sympathize.
(quietly):
Of course not.
Sympathy is a human emotion.
What?
Oh, I'm sorry, darling,
I'm just lashing out.
(quietly):
Got off a good one, though.
Frasier, you've got to stop
this cycle of negativity.
Come, let's try some
positive imagery.
You're back in Maui.
Feel the trade winds
caressing your cheeks,
ruffling your hair.
Smell the plumeria.
Taste the mai tai.
Feel the gentle swaying...
swaying of the
ancient palms.
The rhythm...
the rhythm...
Are you there?
Yes, I'm there.
I'm in paradise.
And I'm paying
for the whole shebang
with my gold card.
Which was gladly accepted,
and returned in one piece,
by a man in a flowered sarong!
Frasier, get a grip.
Oh, you're right,
you're right.
You know,
Sam's done me a favor actually.
Instead of spending the night
there in his sleazy saloon,
I'm... I'm at home
here with my love.
I'm going to serenade you.
Why, Frasier, you haven't
done that since...
Have you ever done that?
Well, I'm doing it now.
Remember this one, darling?
(plays gentle melody)
How could I forget?
Autumn in New York...
Moonlight in Vermont...
You sing it.
All right.
Autumn in New York
What makes it seem
so exciting?
Autumn in New York
It spells the thrill
of first nighting...
(music stops)
It was a lovely
honeymoon, wasn't it?
(voice breaks):
I bought this piano
with my gold card.
I mean, yes, dear.
(doorbell rings)
I'll get it.
Hi, Lilith.
Cliff, Norm.
Frasier, it's Cliff and Norm.
Well, good night,
gentlemen.
I've suddenly developed
a splitting migraine.
Norm. Cliff.
What a pleasure to see
my boon companions
here in my home.
Come in. Come in.
Yeah, well, Fras, look,
we don't want to interrupt
your dinner or
anything like that.
Oh, no, we finished hours ago.
Yeah, nice shortcut, Cliff.
I see that you
left the butcher
of all things plastic
back in the bar
to come visit
old Frasier.
Yeah, yeah.
Fras, uh...
just out of curiosity, what
did you have for dinner?
Uh, uh, let me guess.
Wait. (inhales sharply)
Ah, porterhouse steaks,
smothered with mushrooms,
green beans with sliced almonds,
some, uh, apple brown Betty,
and, uh....
decaf cappuccino.
(laughs)
Ain't he something?
Actually, we had
Chinese brought in.
Guess it must be in my coat.
Here, come... come and sit down.
You know, I can't tell you
how special this is.
We never seem to get together
outside of that infernal bar.
Never get together
just as pals.
Yeah, whatever.
Fras, you don't have any Chinese
left, do you?
No, sorry.
Norm, Norm...
we come here
to talk about a topic
a lot more important than food.
Found an almond cookie.
If you're here to try
to patch up my relationship
with Mr. Malone, just forget it.
Give me half, will you, Cliff?
I tell you,
I have seen
the last of that ex-jock
in a pompadour.
Frasier, you've got to let us
explain what happened here.
Fras, uh, you see,
sometimes guys...
do things, you know,
which they...
they think seem like...
a good idea at the time.
But they're really
not such a good idea.
I guess what
I'm trying to say is...
That... that Sam wants me
to come back to Cheers
so that he can get down on his
knees and apologize to me
in public and in person.
Yeah, that's even better.
Great, come on,
let's go.
Sammy,
don't drop down on your knees
to beg for forgiveness
till he's all the way
through the door...
but look who's here.
Hey! You brought Frasier back.
See, now, if we can just
get them to erase
everything from their memories
from the last 36 hours,
we're home free.
I'm waiting, Sam.
Waiting for what?
Sammy, don't torture
your friend.
Frasier just swallowed his
pride to come back in here,
so get down on your knees
and beg him to forgive you
and then we can
start celebrating.
I'm sorry.
Thanks, Sam.
NORM:
That's what we
like to see.
Yeah, I bet you
nobody even remembers
what started the silly argument
in the first place.
I do--
Sam cut up his gold card.
That was funny.
Woody, come on,
we're, uh...
you know, I
apologized for that.
We're beyond
that right now.
Is that it?
That is the sum total
of your contrition?
I mean, I know you're not
Walt Whitman, Sam,
but I mean, really a couple more
"uhs" and "you knows"
would at least lend it
a little creditability.
Well, you didn't let
me finish, Frasier.
I was going to say
that I'm sorry
that you were such a
big jerk yesterday
and that you're such
a big baby today.
Well, that tears it.
When I walk out this time,
believe me when I tell you
that I will never brighten
this door again.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Frasier, Frasier,
wait a minute.
Before this thing
gets any further,
come on now, sit down, relax.
I think it's time
that both you guys
understand the truth.
Cliffie?
Well, Fras,
see, yesterday, uh,
Normie and I, we were
feeling a little frisky
and as sort of a gag,
we, uh, made a phone call
and reported
your credit card stolen.
My God, Cliff,
that is fraud!
You think you
know a guy, Sam.
Damn it, Norm.
Come on.
All right, all right,
all right.
I may have, uh,
been in the vicinity
during that phone call.
I might have actually
dialed the number.
So it's your fault?
Sam, I owe you an apology.
No, no.
I had no idea.
Boy.
You guys are really
stirring it up, aren't you?
Okay, fellas,
give me your credit
cards right now.
What?
Aw...
Give me your credit cards.
You-you can't cut them up.
I'm not gonna cut them up.
NORM:
Don't cut them up, Sam.
Woody, you're back in business.
Shop away.
NORM:
Oh, no.
All right.
Get the scissors
and cut them right now.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/64kf
Help other users to choose the best subtitles