Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Hey, how about
a couple of beers?
I'm afraid I'm going to have
to see some ID.
All righty. Thank you.
And If I can see yours, please.
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
Why don't we just
forget about it.
Let's just
get out of here.
Guys, guys,
wait a minute.
Before you run
screaming from here,
let me ask you
something.
This friend of mine
is having twins.
All right, it's me.
Now, I don't care
if they call each other
cute little names like
"Chipper and Skipper,"
or if they pretend
to be each other,
make their teachers' lives
a living hell.
See, what worries me
is that they'll have ESP,
you know,
and they'll communicate
silent, evil thoughts
and I won't know
what they're saying about me.
You think that's weird?
Well?
We're discussing it.
( piano plays )
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always glad
you came
You want to be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You want to be where everybody
knows your name
You want to go
where people know
People are all the same
You want to go where
everybody knows your name.
Listen up, everybody.
Clifford Clavin has decided
to make
a major life change.
Don't bother--
you'd be a dorky woman, too.
That's a good one,
Carla.
A good one.
NORM:
All right, Cliffie.
What's up, bud?
There's a new condo complex
going up on my route.
You know, one of those places
filled with beautiful people
having the time of their lives.
I said
to myself,
Clifford C.,
you'd take to that place
like a fish takes to water.
All slimy
with your eyes bulging out?
Shouldn't you be squatting
in a field somewhere, Carla?
Well, make a long story short,
I am, uh,
Boston's newest homeowner.
Bought a condo.
NORM:
Hey. Wait, wait.
That means
you're moving out on me?
Normie, I can't
live with you forever.
Well, you can't do that.
Who's gonna mix
Vera's cocoa?
Who's gonna rub her feet?
Who's gonna talk to her?
Normie, I'm afraid
you're just gonna, uh,
have to pick up the slack.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
Not me.
Maybe I can hire
some high school kid.
Did everybody see that?
Yes, I've started
smoking again.
I've been under
a lot of pressure,
and I needed something
to calm my nerves, all right?
And I don't want to hear
any stupid remarks
about yellow fingernails
or kissing ashtrays,
and if you use
the phrase "coffin nails,"
you better be a mortician.
Any questions,
comments, snide remarks?
No? Good.
Well, it certainly
has calmed her down.
Uh, excuse me.
You know, I have to apologize.
I feel like this
is my fault.
What are you
talking about?
Well, obviously you
started smoking again
because you got some sort
of pent up sexual
frustration going on.
And I don't think
we have to tell each other
who's responsible
for that, now do we?
Oh. Hey.
Come on, I'm just trying
to help here, you know?
You know what you ought to do,
you ought to come on over
to Dr. Sammy's
Stop Smoking Center.
Today's special
is a free chest exam.
Sam, is this one
of those two-week programs
with a simple two-day follow-up?
( doorbell chimes )
( chuckling ):
Those guys.
Come on in.
( music playing outside )
Hey.
( chuckles )
What a surprise, you guys.
Welcome to Chez Cliff.
Sounds like party central
out there.
Well, I just hope
that they can, uh,
keep up with the
Chairman of the Broads.
( laughing )
Cliffie, I
brought you
the traditional
housewarming gift.
Whoa, six-pack.
Yeah.
Well, a five-pack.
Well, uh, so,
you guys ready
for the grand tour?
Okay. Yup.
Right here we have
the living room.
Mm-hmm.
Right over here
is the bedroom.
Whoa.
Hey, slow down, let me
catch my breath here.
Whoa, almost forgot
the kitchen.
Yeah, I think the
builder did, too.
Let me, huh, put these
beers on ice here.
Yeah, good idea.
It's not too cold
in here, buddy.
Oh, yeah, yeah,
I noticed that, Normie.
I think it's the,
uh, amalgamator valve.
I've been meaning
to strip it down,
check out the
engine, you know.
I think I better
put, uh,
some more Freon in
the regulator, too.
Or else you could just
turn this little dial to cold.
Well, yeah, if
you're... you know,
you want to take
a stopgap approach.
Oh, hey, did you notice
the pool on your way in?
Yeah.
So when, uh,
summer rolls around,
and all those girls
are out there
in their French cut bikinis,
I don't have to
tell where I'll be.
Standing right here with
a pair of binoculars?
That's right.
Boy, oh, boy.
Hey, thanks for
coming by, you guys,
but, you know, I don't
mean to be rude, but, uh,
I got to ask you
to skedaddle.
I got somebody soft
and sweet with a voice
like a nightingale
coming over.
Who, the busboy from
Melville's is coming over here?
No, no, Woody.
Ruben's not
coming over here.
It's a... it's
one of the women
in the building.
Wait a minute, Cliffie.
Are we actually
talking a female here?
Oh...
I mean, a real, live,
breathing woman,
three-dimensional,
no posters, no polyurethane?
Well...
you know, Normie,
Sally is the real McCoy,
and she is one
gorgeous babe, to boot.
All right, well,
this I got to see, Cliffie.
Yeah, maybe we
could stick around
and meet your
lady friend, huh?
Uh, no, you know, I, uh,
guys, I really don't think
that's a very good idea.
Well, why don't you bring her
by the bar or something?
Well, you know,
I've been trying
to get the woman
to go out, Normie,
but, uh, she just
wants to stay, uh,
held up here in our
little hideaway.
I guess I'm her...
love hostage.
Well, that's something
I definitely don't care to see.
Okay.
Good to see you.
( music playing outside )
Hey, if I'm not
down at the bar,
send out a missing
swinger's report.
Oh.
( doorbell rings )
( clears throat )
Hi.
Hi, Sally.
Guess what?
I have great news.
What?
I was named employee
of the month
at the Yarn Barn.
Well, I tied.
That's-that's
really great news, Sally.
I'm really happy for you.
So I was thinking
maybe to celebrate,
we could go out.
( chuckles )
I got a-a better idea.
Why don't, uh...
we just stay in?
Oh, Cliff, we've
done that every
night this week.
I was thinking
maybe we could
go to that bar
you're always
talking about.
You're kidding.
That dive?
Uh, you know,
uh, Sally, I, uh...
spend all day, you know,
walking around,
uh, uh, outside,
and, you know,
at the end of the day,
I just like to come
back to my own
little apartment here
and just sort of relax
and take it easy and, uh...
get my tensions relieved,
if you know what I mean.
Yes, I know
what you mean.
I'll get the lights, huh?
Fine, I'll-I'll
just get comfortable.
And I'll,
uh, meet you
on the sofa in
about five seconds.
All right.
Have you got the, uh, you know?
Oh, yeah.
ANNOUNCER:
And now, here's the host
of Jeopardy, Alex Trebek.
TREBEK:
Thank you.
Welcome once again to our show.
We are delighted, of course,
to welcome back
our returning champion,
the lady from Boca Raton...
Uh-oh.
Here comes Madame Nicotine.
I just had the most disgusting
morning of my life.
Ooh, can't wait
to hear about it.
I just spent the last hour
at a no-smoking clinic
looking at pictures
of ugly ashtrays,
rooms filled with smoke,
people coughing.
And the worst one
was a cigarette snuffed out
in the yolk of a fried egg.
Mm. Bet that stopped you
from wanting a cigarette, eh?
No, but I think
it's put me off eggs for good.
I'll be in the office,
chewing on my hair.
This is going
to be fun.
Carla,
what are you doing?
I am going to
torment her
with this fresh pack
of cigarettes.
No, Carla, you mustn't!
Carla, now, granted,
she's been in rather
a foul mood lately,
but Rebecca has made
a serious life decision,
and what she needs now
more than anything else
is encouragement
and support,
and I for one
am not going to fail her.
Oh, Rebecca?
REBECCA:
What do you want,
Bone Dome?!
Here, try these.
They're menthols.
Next case.
Dr. Crane,
I-I'm really sorry.
I think I'm just
a little on edge.
Look, I apologize, too.
I behaved
very unprofessionally.
It's just that I'm
really frustrated
because I can't seem
to kick this habit.
Well, listen,
may I suggest something
that seems to have worked
for many of my patients?
Changing doctors?
Thank you, Carla, no.
You're engaged right now
in a psychological battle
with your will.
Now, you've got
to bring
to the foreground
every weapon available.
Promise yourself
that if you smoke
one more cigarette,
you'll do
the most disgusting,
repulsive thing
you can imagine.
Dr. Crane, I can't
even imagine...
( whistling )
Sam Malone...
if I smoke another
cigarette,
I'll go to
bed with you.
( glass breaking )
Darn thing's on the blink again.
Excuse me,
( clearing throat )
Rebecca?
What?
Uh, there's a problem
I'd like to talk over with you.
I am really trying
to quit, all right?
Oh, no, no, no,
it's not about that.
It's, uh...
I met this girl.
And?
Oh. People usually
stop me at that point.
Anyway, uh...
night after night
I keep begging her
to come down to the bar
and meet the guys, but
she just won't come.
Just wants to stay at
home and watch Jeopardy.
Uh, I think that maybe she's
a little-little bit ashamed
about the way she looks,
and she's afraid she
might embarrass me.
So, uh, you got
any suggestions,
or what can I do?
Let me see here. Um...
Oh. Have you ever seen
those beauty magazine makeovers?
Oh, yeah, yeah,
yeah. Sure, sure.
Well, then what are you
bugging me for?
Oh, wait a minute.
If you ever see me
with a cigarette
hanging out of my mouth,
would you do me a favor?
What's that?
Kill Sam.
Did you, uh, dab lip gloss
on your eyelashes
so they sparkle
like the North Star?
SALLY:
Yes, Cliff.
I'm coming out now.
Okay.
Listen, don't stand
too close, okay?
Try me from a distance first.
Okay.
All right,
I'm backing up.
All clear!
Wow.
Gee, thanks, Cliff.
Oh, isn't it about time
for Jeopardy?
Huh?
Jeopardy.
Uh...
All right. Uh...
Why don't we go out?
Really, Cliff?
Sure.
Great.
Okay. I'll-I'll just, um,
go do a little more blending,
and then we'll go.
I'll just, uh, be out here
on the front porch and catch
a little breath of fresh air.
I got a fox!
Carla, Carla, Carla, Carla.
Ladies room,
ladies room. Please.
No, I'm not following her
in there again, Sam.
I'm one puff away from paradise.
Come on. Please.
There's only so much
polite conversation
you can make
yelling over a stall.
Cliff, this isn't a dive.
Well, no, by a dive,
I meant that, uh...
it was below
street level.
Oh, right.
( nervous chuckle )
Yeah, let me introduce
you to my cronies.
but I gotta
warn you first,
they can be a little
bit crude, all right?
Hey, guys.
Va-va-va-voom, huh?
Hello.
I, uh, thought we'd met
all of Cliff's cousins.
Oh, I'm not
his cousin.
No, she's my date.
Would you like a
little seat here?
I'll get you
something to drink.
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
WOODY:
Well, I'll tell you.
She's what guys back down
on the farm where I come from
would call ethereal.
Woody,
where exactly
was this farm?
A couple of beers,
there, Wood man.
You got something
on her, don't you?
You found something
incriminating in her mail.
For God's sake, Cliff,
just ask her for money.
Don't be vicious.
Look, look, look,
is it so hard for you people,
and whatever you are, Carla,
to believe that,
uh, this, uh,
beautiful woman would go out
with me on her own accord?
No, of course not,
Cliff.
I can think
of any number of reasons
why a woman
might behave that way.
You can?
Well, of course,
but remember...
I'm a psychiatrist.
So, hey, w-where's Sammy?
I wanna show him
one gorgeous Bostonian
that slipped
through his net.
He's over there
hauling her in.
Ho! Ahem!
Sammy!
Oh, Sammy.
Oh, young fellow.
Oh-ho, boy.
Oh, Cliff,
do you know each other?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Can I have a word
with you, Sammy?
Yeah, see, she's with me.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Excuse us, Sally.
Hey, she is one
very pretty lady.
Yeah, thank you, Sam.
Another one of
your, uh, cousins?
She's my date.
Really?
Well, is she, um...?
Well, we think so.
Well,
congratulations, man.
Yeah, yeah.
Great. Listen, Sam,
about that over there...
No, I'm sorry. I
want to apologize
if I was out
of line there,
but, well,
the truth is,
you're gonna have
to expect that kind
of thing happening
from now on.
What do you mean?
Well, she's definitely
a major-league
looker, there, Cliff.
I mean, guys are
gonna be hitting
on her all the time.
Ah, you don't have
to worry about that, Sammy.
Sally is a one-man woman.
Better check your
arithmetic there.
Hmm?
Ho!
( clears throat )
Hey, Sally.
Cliff, look who's here.
It's Jeff.
From 325.
Hey, I-I know you.
You're the guy with
the binoculars.
Uh, Sally, I think
it's, uh, about time
we, uh, vamoose out of here.
You know, Jeopardy's going to be
starting in a little while.
Let's go, Sally.
Listen, uh, Jeff just got
a new Porsche Turbo
and he wants to take me
for a ride.
You don't mind, do you?
Well, uh...
We'll just be gone
a few minutes.
You don't mind, do you.
Oh, no.
No, I-I don't mind.
( chuckles ):
That's fine.
I don't care.
I don't mind at all.
( clears throat )
Beer here, Woody.
Excuse me,
excuse me.
What was that lady
doing in there?
Oh, oh, no, no, no.
You know... no, you
don't understand.
See, we...
W-Wait a minute.
We have... we have this
little bet between us.
Let me... let
me explain here.
See, I get to go to bed with her
if she smo... Ow!
All right, fine.
ALEX TREBEK:
Jamie Kelt
is a correct response,
but you forgot to phrase that
in the form of a question.
That's why they call it
Jeopardy.
Beer, Sam, please.
Are you okay, Cliff?
However, you get to make
the next selection.
Jeopardy used to be
our show, Normie.
It's just
not the same
watching it
by myself.
I just don't know
if I can go on without her.
She's only been gone
for ten minutes.
Yeah, I had to make her
beautiful, Normie.
I've created
a beautiful monster.
What am I going to do?
What is Paraguay?
WOMAN:
TREBEK:
Right.
Yeah! All right!
Well, thanks a lot, Normie.
What is Notre Dame?!
WOMAN:
What is Notre Dame?
TREBEK:
That's right.
Ooh, yeah!
Hey, hey, hey, Carla.
Do you smell smoke?
Come here.
Of course I smell smoke,
you dink.
It's a bar.
I can also smell beer,
sweat and lousy tips.
No, no, no, no.
No, she's smoking in there.
I knew she couldn't
last this long.
Oh...
A-ha!
Oh, uh... hey, uh,
where's the pool table?
Ah, wrong room.
( laughing )
I knew it! I knew it!
I knew it!
I'm not going to say I knew it,
but I knew it.
I knew it.
Now, this was your idea, too.
I did not come up with this.
This is your idea.
What a great idea! Oh!
( laughing )
Well, what do you say?
Uh, shall we, uh, strip down
to our smiles here
and show the, uh...
show the couch here a good time?
No.
We'll go to my place.
Excuse me?
Ooh! You're really going to go
through with this, aren't you?
Yes, I am, but I want to
get one thing straight.
Ooh, yeah, yeah.
My smoking has
nothing to do
with sexual frustration
over you or anyone else.
It's just a
stupid habit.
But I made a pact,
so now I'm going to
suffer the consequences
no matter how vile
or disgusting
they may be.
Let's go.
Well...
You don't really want
to do this, do you?
No, it's all right.
I'll just close my eyes
and imagine someone appealing.
Besides, I have a feeling
it won't take long.
You know, gee whiz, you know,
if-if you're not going
to get in the spirit of this,
then I-I just don't want
to do it.
No, come on, come on,
a deal's a deal.
No.
Look, I made a pact.
I just want to get it over with.
No, I don't want to do it.
You know, I have some pride.
I have some dignity.
I'll tell you what.
You find someone else
to do your dirty work.
Thinks she can mess
with Sam Malone.
What happened?
She asked me to go to bed
with her, and I said no.
Oh!
Oh, Cliff,
I have never driven
so fast in my whole life.
I had the best time.
Eh, great, great.
So did I.
Cliff, is something
the matter?
No, uh, nothing's the matter.
What could be the matter?
I'll tell you what's the matter,
Little Miss Porsche.
Try to do a girl a favor,
help her become
a little bit more attractive,
and next thing you know,
she's out there...
attracting people.
Is that what's
bothering you?
This makeup?
Is that what all
this is about?
Well, yeah, you got to admit,
before you put it on,
you were a...
a sweet thing
who, uh...
was content to sit
by a dear friend's
side on an evening
and watch a rousing,
wholesome game
of Jeopardy.
So...
all I have to do to make
things right between us is...
take off all this silly makeup
and go back to being
the way I was?
Wow, you... you'd
do that for me?
No way.
I like the way I look in makeup.
Wait till they get a load of me
at the Yarn Barn.
It makes you look
like a... cover girl.
( laughs )
I'm sorry, Cliff.
That's what you're stuck with.
You're just going to have
to learn to live with it.
Well, I guess I'm...
big enough of a person
not to let your appearance
get in the way
of our relationship.
I'm glad.
Besides, appearances
don't matter at all.
Of course they don't.
Like, it doesn't
bother me
that you wear
those funny white socks.
Of course it doesn't.
Or that it looks
as if you trim
your mustache
with a butter knife.
Eh, another
fine example.
Cliff, have you ever considered
joining a gym?
Oh, you ever considered
wearing flats?
I can help you
with that smoking
problem, you know.
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.OpenSubtitles.org