Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Well, Rebecca, how are you
on this magnificent day?
None of your business.
(imitating John Wayne):
Well, who stuck a burr
under your saddle, missy?
Sorry, Frasier, I've just been
in a bad mood lately.
Would you like
to talk about it?
It might help
to alleviate your depression.
No, I really wouldn't feel
comfortable talking to you.
Why is that?
Because you know me too well
to think of me as a therapist?
No, because I saw you
dance around this bar
in your underwear, with
swizzle sticks in your ears,
when they brought back
Classic Coke.
Well, granted,
that wasn't my finest hour,
but you can taste
the difference.
Now, Rebecca,
counseling people is what I do.
Please let me help you.
(sighing):
All right, Frasier.
It's just that I can't seem
to make anything work.
Robin is in prison.
I manage this crummy bar.
My career is
at a standstill.
I'm miserable.
I'm lonely.
And now,
I have to sell my Mercedes.
I see.
Well, I'll, uh...
I'll give you $5,000 cash
and take over
your payments.
Six thousand firm.
Deal.
Thank you.
Damn!
It's good to heal.
(theme song begins)
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always
glad you came
You wanna be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You wanna be where everybody
knows your name
You wanna go
where people know
People are all the same
You wanna go where everybody
knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
You know, Sam,
this is a treat.
I've got this side
of the bar to myself.
I can drink my beer
and enjoy my newspaper
without being pummeled on
every side by inane chatter.
Yep.
Say, look...
well, look at this.
There is barometric pressure
on Venus.
Now, how did
they measure that?
Beats me.
A man was reunited with his
twin brother after 30 years.
They worked in the same
auto plant in Columbus, Ohio!
That's nice.
Say, would anybody like me to
read their, uh, their horoscope?
I'll, uh, start with Aries.
Somebody want to play
with Frasier, please?
Hi, Sammy.
Sorry I'm late.
There's a prison work crew
in the park across the street.
Man, you should have heard
some of those raunchy,
sleazy, come-ons.
Pretty bad, huh?
Oh, yeah.
I really outdid myself.
I should write a book.
Hey, Becks, you know, you might
be interested to know
that one of those cons
out there
is your pasty-faced,
billionaire boyfriend.
Robin?
Yeah.
He was out there
picking up trash.
I wonder if he was using
the same line he used on you.
My poor, sweet baby.
I better go see him.
Oh, wait--
no, I better not.
If the other guys get jealous,
they might give him a hard time.
But then,
if I don't go see him,
then he'll probably think
that I'm ashamed of him.
But if I see him, it might be
all too painful for him.
What should I do?
I don't know.
What do you think
I should do?
Twins in the same
auto plant?
Come on, you guys.
You just don't care.
Honey, I'm trying
like hell to care.
Look, if it means
that much to you,
why don't you run outside
there and blow him a kiss.
Yeah, right.
Get him in trouble so he has
to spend the night in the box.
(sarcastically):
Blow him a kiss.
You heartless bastard.
Boy, it must be pretty rough
on ol' Robin Colcord, huh?
One day he's living
in a penthouse,
the next day he's picking up
trash with a stick.
You're loving this,
aren't you, Sammy?
Every minute.
Sam, you missed
a great lunch.
Mr. Clavin and Mr. Peterson
treated me at the Hungry Heifer.
SAM:
How was it?
Wednesday Ribscapade, Sammy.
End of story.
Well, where's
the third member
of your gastronomic
suicide squad?
Mr. Peterson's
still at the Heifer.
Uh, you know,
we got some bad news.
They're gonna
tear the place down.
Oh, dear!
Well, I can see why Norm would
want to spend some final moments
of contemplation in the place
that meant so much to him.
No, no, he was just
sopping up some gravy
with a Parker House roll.
Well, each man mourns
in his own way.
I hope it doesn't
hit him too hard.
What's the big deal?
So they're leveling
another beef joint.
Another beef joint?
You obviously
have never been there
for "You Keep
the Hoof" night.
Well, you know, this is
not atypical behavior.
I mean, many people
can form emotional bonds
to significant places
in their lives.
I think we should all
be very sensitive
to what Norm
is going through.
Yeah, you know,
that's a good idea, Fras.
Maybe we shouldn't say anything
to remind him
of the Hungry Heifer
when he comes back here.
You know, maybe not say
any words like, uh,
"beef" or "meat."
Sam, what about "meet"
as in, "Let's meet
for dinner tonight?"
Yeah.
That'd be fine, Woody.
Great.
W-Where do you want to go?
You feel like Chinese?
You know, on second thought,
maybe that's not a good idea.
That's why I asked.
Afternoon, everybody.
GROUP:
Norm!
Hey, how's life treatin' you,
there, Norm?
Beats me...
then it kicks me and
leaves me for dead.
Well, here's a... here's a
cold one for you there, buddy.
Hey, uh, Norm,
how about some of these
extra-salty pretzels
you so heartily
enjoy, huh?
You're welcome to share some
of my beer nuts, if you like.
Meat!
(all clamoring)
Aw, everybody was
thinking it!
I was the only one who
had the guts to say it!
We're sorry, man.
We-We-We feel bad
'cause we know how much
the Hungry Heifer means to you.
You don't know
the half of it, Sammy.
I love the Heifer.
SAM:
Aww...
Don't know what I'm gonna do
without that place.
It was like my home
away from Cheers.
If you'll excuse me, guys, I...
just want to be alone.
Hey, whoa! Ho.
Not that alone.
Well, they're carting
the cons away.
Robin's leaving?
Yeah, just loaded him
and his sunburned pals
into the van.
Mm, he was red as a lobster.
Bet he blisters.
Carla, honey,
I don't think Rebecca
wants to talk about
this right now.
I mean, after all,
her guy's in jail.
I mean, she's lonely,
she's hurting.
She's a woman in need.
She misses her man.
(sighing):
I do, Sam. I do.
Say, hon...
I just want to say that...
I know what you're going through
right now,
and if there's anything
I can do for you,
or to you...
I'm here for you.
Or there for you or on
the floor for you, it's...
Gee, Sam.
When you put it like that,
you make me sick.
Well, you think about it,
though--
I mean, 'cause you're thinking
about it right now.
I bet if I took an X-ray
of your brain,
I'd be lying, right
stretched out all naked.
Don't leave out the
tag on your toe.
Would that tag
happen to say:
"For a good time,
follow this leg?"
(laughing):
Whee!
I sure know how
to make my own fun, don't I?
Guys, look, uh, sorry
I was getting all emotional
about the Hungry
Heifer, I mean...
Aw...
It's just that
I'm losing someplace
that's so close
to my heart.
Don't you mean
clogging your heart?
Well, Norm, there are
other restaurants.
NORM:
It's not just
the restaurant,
it's the owner, okay?
Sid Nelson.
He's a funny kind of guy,
you know?
He's all tough on the outside,
but really soft and mushy
on the inside.
Hmm. Not unlike his entire menu.
Anyway, Sid was always
there for me.
Not unlike his entire menu.
I remember one
time, in college,
I had to stay up all night
to finish a term paper.
Sid stayed up with me
till we finished it.
We also finished
a two-pound onion loaf.
Well, Norm, I don't blame you
for being depressed.
No... depressed?
Come on.
You know, life's only
temporary anyway, right?
When you're born,
blah-blah-blah, you die.
Geez, Norm, I-I look at you and
I see a man at a crossroads.
This may be your very first
brush with mortality,
with the temporal
nature of things.
You may feel
futile now,
but there are ways
to combat that.
Yeah? How?
Well, by guaranteeing
your own immortality.
By leaving your mark
on the world.
He always leaves two
dents on the stool.
Carla, please.
Well, he does!
Big ones, too!
When he goes
home at night,
this stool looks
like it has a Mohawk!
Look, I was hoping
for something
a little more
life-affirming, thank you!
Now, Norm, there are... there
are many roads open to you.
Geez, you... well,
you could do something
to help save the
Hungry Heifer.
Or, well, better yet, you
could help do something
to save yourself!
Turn over a new leaf.
You could diet, exercise,
work for a charitable cause.
Or, if you want
the ultimate way
of guaranteeing
your immortality,
go home to Vera and start
a family right this minute.
Frasier... you are right.
When you're right,
you are right!
I am gonna do it!
(friends shouting
encouragement)
I'm gonna save
the Hungry Heifer!
Well, what about, uh,
dieting, exercise,
making a baby with Vera?
Pfft!
You do it.
Hey, Sammy.
Hey.
Here you go.
SAM:
Enjoy yourself?
Ho-ho, yeah!
I tell you, you haven't lived
until you've washed a car
in front of
a bunch of drooling cons.
(laughs)
Ooh!
Just like in Cool Hand Luke!
Whoo!
Here you go, Fras.
Thank you.
What do we got here now?
Uh, Joe... Marty...
Who had the
powder-blue Caddy?
Carla, how's it
going out there?
How does Robin look?
Okay.
He was being pushed around by
this big old hunk of a guard.
His name is Vince
and he has got some muscles,
I'm telling you.
He could snap Robin's neck
like a number-two pencil.
But he didn't hurt
Robin, did he?
I mean, Robin's okay,
isn't he?
Yeah, sure, whatever.
Anyway, then this, uh, Vince,
he gets a load of me
and my bucket of suds
and he starts flexing.
But Robin-- Robin-- he
gets dehydrated easily.
Robin, Robin, Robin.
So your boyfriend's in prison!
Boo-hoo!
Can't you be happy
for someone else for a change?!
Hey, don't listen to her.
She's trying to get
under your skin.
I can see how much this
must be hurting you.
Watching the man you
love out there in the
sun all day long
picking up garbage
while a whole city looks
at him, and laughs at him.
Thanks for
understanding, Sam.
Yeah.
You really do relish
this, don't you, Sam?
Every single minute.
Come on, stop
moping around.
Look, why don't you do what
any woman would do for her man--
strip to your skivvies,
grab a chamois and wash
a couple of cars.
Get your front wet.
I don't think Robin
would respond
to something cheap
like that.
Oh, yeah? You should
have seen how fast
he stabbed that
trash when I did it.
FRASIER:
Hey, uh, Norm,
how's it going with the petition
to save the Heifer, huh?
Great. Got a hundred more
signatures back there.
Hey, all right.
Although I am getting a little
bit of writer's cramp.
Well, I wish you
luck, Mr. P.
Yeah?
I know how hard it is to get
people to sign a petition.
Yeah, I remember
back in Hanover...
I tried to gather signatures
to rebuild the town band shell
after the Fourth
of July explosion.
I had a heck of a time.
I couldn't even get
my Uncle Elwood to sign.
Oh. Couldn't even
convince your uncle, huh?
Oh, he was convinced.
He just couldn't
grip the pen.
See, he was,
he was in charge
of lighting
the fireworks.
They had extra small
fuses that year. No-no...
Time to pound
the pavement.
If I get like
a hundred more signatures,
I can bring this petition
over to City Hall.
Good for you.
Frasier, you were
absolutely right.
This feels right.
This feels great.
It's been a long time since
I pounded the bricks
for a cause.
Oh I can't stand thinking
of Robin out there
in the blazing sun.
Aw, honey, well,
I'll tell you what,
let me, uh, let me put on
a song here for you,
take your mind off of things.
No, Sam, that's
not gonna work.
All right, go ahead.
It doesn't...
...situation thought
I could take them...
Dang it, Sam, turn it off.
For a while, baby...
Is that your idea of a song
that's gonna cheer me up?
Well, hey, it's got
a great beat.
It's easy to pick
up trash to.
You just can go on
with your stupid little idiotic
nasty jokes
because you know what?
I love Robin and I'm going
to remain loyal to him,
like it says right there,
B-14, "Stand By Your Man."
I'm just sitting here in...
For a while, baby, I never
thought I could wait...
I'm just sitting here
in...
For a while, baby, I never
thought I could wait...
Cliff, you want to go
shoot some stick?
Let's shoot some
stick, Doctor.
Oh, hey, before you go
back there, Dr. Crane,
I should tell you that
Carla's keeping a guard
on the pool table.
Why is she doing that?
I guess she likes him.
Afternoon, everybody.
ALL:
Norm!
Hey, how would a beer
feel, Mr. Peterson?
Pretty nervous if
I was in the room.
In fact, let me buy
a beer for everybody, okay?
All right!
Thank you, Norm!
Guys, I have saved
the Hungry Heifer.
(all cheering)
That's great.
How'd you do it?
Well, I went over to
City Hall to drop off
the petition right?
Stopped in to do
a little research.
It turns out that
the Hungry Heifer
is the only building on the
entire Eastern Seaboard
that has a giant red-eyed
steam-snorting bull on the roof.
What about Hub's Steak Hut?
It's gone.
Well, Lucky Chucky's
Chuck House?
Struck by lightning.
Bill's Place for Steak?
Stolen.
Wow. That really is
the end of an era.
Yeah.
Wonder who's next.
Are they gonna take down
those big buckets of chicken?
There's a message in
this for the Big Boy:
get rid of those overalls
and get a real job.
Yeah. You know who doesn't
have to worry?
Denny.
Nobody knows
what he looks like.
Oh, sorry, was that out loud?
NORM:
Anyway, the city
planner's
office issued
a temporary injunction
against any demolition
until it can be determined
whether the Hungry Heifer
can be declared
a roadside landmark.
Oh, congratulations, Norm.
Gentlemen, start
your enzymes.
(chanting):
Norm. Norm. Norm.
Norm. Norm...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna invite you guys all
to the Hungry Heifer tonight.
Well, what was supposed to be
a sad little farewell dinner
is gonna turn into the happiest
meal of Mr. Sid Nelson's life.
Everyone's gonna be there, guys.
Even the Big Eaters Circle.
You in that, Mr. P?
Oh, no, no, Woody, please.
This is a closed table.
I mean, someone has to die
before you can get a seat there.
Wow, too bad.
Oh, no. These guys
drop dead
like once a week.
I've got a real shot
at it, I think.
Say, honey, I hate
to bother you, you know,
with Robin on your mind
and everything,
but I just bought
some new clothes.
I'd like a woman's
point of view.
Fine. Let's see them.
Hit it, Fras.
Our model, Sam, is sporting
the latest in "big house" chic.
This ensemble
is equally
appropriate
for playing the harmonica
or just crushing rocks.
It comes complete with anklet
and matching
trash ka-bob,
made popular by
billionaire swindler,
Robin Colcord.
You think you're hilarious,
don't you, Sam?
Well, I bring the party
with me, don't I, babe?
Optional with this outfit
is a matching set of,
uh, tattoos reading:
"Born to Raise Hell"
and, uh, "It's
Society's Fault."
You guys, don't encourage him.
Guys, guys, guys,
look at this.
Quick impression
of Robin Colcord.
(British accent):
Blimey.
There's a lot of trash
on the ground, isn't there?
Well, I'll just have to impale
it and flush it down the loo.
Cor.
Look, it's all over the place.
Look at that. Look at that.
Look at that.
All right, that's
it. Let's go.
You're spending the
night in the box.
(laughing)
What're you
talking about, man?
Hey, what're you doing?
I'm not one of
your prisoners.
I know, but you
stabbed my foot.
And I got a gun.
So you're spending
the night in the box.
It was an accident.
I didn't mean... Guys, do
something, will you, Rebecca?
Okay, Sam.
I'm just sitting here...
Oh, great.
She's got a problem.
Okay, all right.
Attention please.
(banging)
Okay, before we get
to the ceremony,
I'd like to make
a little announcement.
Because of tonight's
very special occasion,
the fudge volcano will keep
erupting for one more hour.
(cheering and applause)
All right, there we go, yeah.
Okay.
The Big Eaters Circle.
All right.
Now, I'd like to introduce
to you folks,
the owner and operator
of the Hungry Heifer,
our very special guest,
Mr. Sid Nelson.
(cheering)
(chanting):
Sid. Sid. Sid. Sid.
Sid. Sid. Sid.
Sid. Sid...
Let me get right
to the point, Sid.
I knew you were expecting
a tearful farewell
dinner here tonight,
but, uh, that is
not going to happen.
What are you talking about?
Well, the Hungry Heifer is
not going to be torn down.
What are you talking about?
NORM:
Perhaps this
piece of paper
will help explain
things, Sid.
This is an injunction,
making the Hungry Heifer
immune to any wrecking ball.
It will be here for our children
and our children's children.
Sid obviously wasn't prepared
for this happy news.
Uh, tell you what, uh...
have the band strike up
another tune, okay?
Oh, the band felt
bloated and left.
You've got to pace yourself.
Sid.
Sid, what are you doing?.
You could start
a grease fire in here.
I mean, I know you
have them every day,
but this one could
get out of hand.
You jerk. You
ruined everything.
But I thought
you'd be happy.
Happy? Why should
I be happy?
The developers were going
to give me three times
what this joint is worth.
I didn't know you wanted
out of this place, Sid.
Why?
How would you like to
spend seven days a week
up to your elbows
in cow flesh?
Sid, I never knew
you felt this way.
Well, I didn't always.
But, I don't know,
this is the '90s, Norm.
We've learned a lot
about the kind of poisons
we've been putting
into our bodies.
Now, you look at that.
You see some T-bones
and a rump roast.
I see a loaded gun.
I've been carrying it around
with me for a long time, Norm,
the guilt for what I've been
doing to bodies like yours.
I thought I had a way out.
I could sell the place to the,
to the lube syndicate.
But... I guess the only
way out for me now
is just to torch the place.
Hey, no, no, you can't...
Sid, you cannot burn down
the Hungry Heifer.
Yeah. I guess
you're right.
Yeah.
I'd be the first one
they'd suspect.
But who am I gonna get
to do it for me, Norm?
I've got no family.
Who's gonna light
the match for me.
I've got no son.
You're the one who came
closest to that for me.
Thank you, Sid.
Light the match.
No, no. There's no way
I'm gonna let you go
through with this. No.
I'm an old man, Norm.
I've got nothing
to look forward to.
Light the match.
Look, there's no way
I'm gonna let you go
through with this.
Hey, you mean too much
to me, all right?
I mean... look, I
never said this...
to my own father,
but I... I love you, Sid.
Hey, I didn't know
you felt like that, Norm.
Yeah.
Gee, I love you, too.
Thank you, Sid.
Light the match.
Would you stop with
the matches, Sid?
Just stop with it.
So, Sid finally
came around, huh?
Yeah. You bet he did. Yeah.
WOODY:
How'd you convince him?
Well, I told him he could serve
a healthier menu,
uh, smaller portions,
leaner cuts of beef.
He's actually gonna put some
greens in the salad bar.
Oh.
You know we could
change the name
to the Healthy Heifer.
Yeah.
I think I really turned
his life around today.
What the hell...?
Sid... Sid!
What's going on?
This is Gus, the busboy.
Now he's the son I never had.
Fire!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org