Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Barkeep, pour me a beer.
Uh-oh, Normie.
Flimflam alert.
Uh-uh.
Hey, guys, how you doing?
Pretty good, Harry.
Yeah.
Good to see you.
It's been a long time.
How long's it been?
Well, two to ten,
with time off for good behavior.
( cash register rings )
Oh, boy,
I need change for this 50.
You need change.
Maybe I can help you, huh?
Great.
Hold it, hold it.
Oh, come on, guys.
Give me a break.
I'm a reformed man.
Oh, yeah?
Well, maybe you
wouldn't mind
if we monitored this
little transaction.
Yeah.
HARRY:
Wouldn't mind at all.
Okay,
you got 50 bucks.
Here's one, two, three,
four, five.
Norm, what time is it?
11:00.
11, hmm?
12, 13, 14.
Gee, my watch must be fast.
I got, uh, 11:25.
26, 27,
28. Cliff,
you have not aged a day.
How old are you?
Oh... 39.
39. 40, 41, forty...
Wait.
You can't be that old.
When were you born?
'47.
48, 49, 50.
There you go, barkeep.
Thank you.
Good to see you, guys.
Yeah.
Hey, Sam, long time no see.
What was Harry the Hat
doing here?
WOODY:
He just came
in for a beer.
Oh.
And some change.
Oh...
( shouts indistinctly )
( piano plays )
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always glad
you came
You want to be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You want to be where everybody
knows your name
You want to go
where people know
People are all the same
You want to go where
everybody knows your name.
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
Afternoon, everybody.
ALL:
Norm.
How's life treating you?
It's not, Sammy,
but that doesn't mean you can't.
Uh, boy, I'd love to, man,
but I don't have a dime
to my name.
And my boat sank
and everything...
Yeah, I know--
the bottom of the Caribbean.
What is that,
the 17th or 18th time
we heard that speech?
Oh, hey, Normie?
Listen, that was
great meat loaf last night, huh?
It was, wasn't it?
You know, uh,
Cliff, I've been meaning
to talk to you.
Hmm?
I don't mind
you staying with us
for a little while
till you get your new place,
but, uh, it's beginning
to be a little bit
of a problem for Vera.
The dishes,
the bed,
the way you leave the bathroom
in the morning.
( laughs ):
You got to start leaving
something for her to do, pal.
I mean,
she wants to spend time with me.
Booze, Woody, and quickly.
What's the
matter, Dr. Crane?
Oh, I'm devastated.
I need something
expeditious and brutal
to numb my sensibilities
and blast me
into sweet oblivion.
How about a boilermaker?
Make it a mimosa.
What's got you so upset?
Some college professor
has just published an article
that refutes everything I said
in my last paper.
Sounds like a shoot-out
at the cuckoo corral.
What could motivate an honored
and distinguished colleague
to launch a personal attack
like this?
Well, now, maybe it's just a,
you know,
honest difference of opinion
between scholars.
Oh, goose poop, Sam,
the man's a yahoo.
Hey, Sammy?
Mm-hmm.
You want to see
what makes Rebecca's
loins ache?
Sure.
Well, he just
walked in.
It's the great and
powerful Evan Drake.
See to my table upstairs.
Uh, yes, sir.
She's skipping the thrill ride
that's Sammy Land for that?
While I think of it,
take care of that
telex to Paris.
First thing tomorrow.
Now.
Uh, yes, sir.
What's she see in him?
Money, power,
prestige.
Yeah, but I'm several inches
taller than him.
Sam Malone.
Evan Drake.
How do you do?
I've been looking forward
to meeting you.
I was a big fan of yours.
Oh. Any fan of mine
is certainly welcome here,
especially one
who could fire me like a shot.
What can I get you?
You got some 20-year-old Scotch?
Uh, no, but we got some pretzels
that have been around
for a while here.
( laughs )
How about a Dewar's, huh?
That'll do it.
So, Mr. Drake,
things are going pretty
good at the old bar.
Well, I'm glad
to hear that.
We sank a lot
of bucks into it.
Oh, boy, don't talk to me
about sinking, man.
I lost my boat and...
Yeah, I heard.
Oh.
I remember
watching you pitch, Sam.
I'll bet you got a lot
of great stories, huh?
Well, yeah.
I got a million of 'em.
Hold still, I'll
be right there.
Mr. Drake, they're ready
for you upstairs now.
I'll tell them to wait.
You know how people are
always catching you naked
when you don't
want them to?
Well, this time...
Can you settle
an argument here?
How much you figure
a guy like that pays
for his socks?
...I don't want
to talk to anybody...
I've seen those
at Barney's.
They're about
75 a pair.
( chuckles )
Even I pay a dollar for mine.
SAM:
The next thing I know,
there's a guys
standing next to me...
So there I am in
the locker room
signing the game ball
for this guy, buck naked.
I tell you, I'll never
forget his name,
because it was
so unusual.
Ueberroth.
Peter Ueberroth--
the Baseball Commissioner?
Uh, that's where the story
kind of falls apart.
I'll be right back.
Where you been?
I had to change
a flat.
Mr. Drake's here.
Carla, don't even think
of joking about that.
Hello, Mr. Drake.
( squeals )
Oh, my God.
I didn't know you'd be here.
I look messy.
Close your eyes.
Not you, Woody.
An attractive woman.
A little jumpy, though.
Yeah, but she makes
it work somehow, doesn't she?
You know, some of the guys
down at corporate
have asked her out,
but she always shot them down.
You tried your luck
with her yet?
Oh, no. I have a rule
about not dating
people I work with.
Struck out, huh?
Every time.
Yeah, you know,
some of the guys
there in the office
think she's a...
What?
...a lady's lady.
Rebec...? Oh, no.
Oh, I can't believe it.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Drake.
I would have been
here sooner,
but I was working
on my car.
Uh...
well, I got
a lunch partner.
Well, you know
it was really nice
to see you again.
Even if it was just
for a short while.
Oh, by the way,
I'm hosting a little
party Friday night
for some of
the key people.
I would love it
if you could come.
Oh, Mr. Drake,
I'd-I'd-I'd-I'd...
...really love that.
That's great.
8:00, my club,
black tie.
Yeah, here's the address.
And bring a date.
Uh, or a companion,
or whatever.
Sam.
I wonder what he meant
by "a companion
or a whatever."
Who knows?
( chuckles )
What's so funny?
Uh, well, it seems that
the love of your life there
thinks that because
he's never seen you date anybody
that maybe you...
well, prefer ladies.
You-you set him straight,
didn't you?
Based on what?
God, I...
I can't believe this.
He's all I ever
think about,
and now he thinks
that I'm...
Yeah, yeah,
it's a nutty world, isn't it?
You know something,
though--
I'm bet you could change
his mind real quick
if you were to show up
at his party
just crawling all over
this incredibly good-looking,
hot, macho stud.
You for instance?
You recognized
the description.
Look, Sam,
just because I put my work
before my social life,
does not mean
I don't have boyfriends.
I have boyfriends.
I could pick up that phone
and have a dozen dates
for Friday night.
Yeah, but could you get one
as great looking as I am?
Blindfolded, gagged
and with both hands
tied behind my back.
We were just talking
about a party Friday night.
Sammy, where is it,
and what time
should I be there?
Good evening, Sam.
Hey.
Can I, uh, get a glass of water.
( hiccups )
Got the hiccups, huh?
Yes. It's merely psychosomatic.
( hiccups )
I guess I'm still
upset about
that journalistic
stab in the back.
( hiccups )
You ought to put
a bag over your head.
No, no.
I'd look ridiculous.
I'm just going to do what
my mother always taught me.
( Sam chuckles )
Oh, yeah, you're right,
the bag would look silly.
There.
Hey.
( hiccups ) Oh, damn.
Wow, Miss Howe.
You look pretty enough
to take to a barn dance.
REBECCA:
Thank you.
Sam, when I'm gone tonight,
I want...
Why are you wearing
a tuxedo?
Why does Superman
wear a cape?
To rescue people.
This is your big
party night, isn't it?
Yes.
He did tell you to invite
somebody, didn't he?
Yes, and I did--
an old boyfriend Ryan.
Oh, really?
Yes, and it wasn't
an easy decision.
Yeah, I'll bet not.
I thought about
asking Steve,
but he had a modeling gig
in New York.
And then Jean Pierre
is such a bore.
Keep humming, though.
Keep humming.
( humming )
Keep it up. Keep
humming. come on.
I think it worked.
( hiccups )
CARLA:
Frasier, I'm
telling you,
you should put a
bag on your head.
Carla, I'm not putting
any... ( hiccups )
...bag on my head.
( hiccups )
Oh, give me the damn bag.
CLIFF:
You know what else
I found works,
is putting a lemon
in your mouth.
Wait a minute,
you can actually
get a whole lemon
in your mouth?
Well, young man,
let's take a trip
over to Mr. Wizard's
laboratory.
Yeah?
Woody...
What's this message,
"Urgent. See Woody"?
Oh, right.
Uh, Ryan from
the escort service called,
said there a mistake
in the booking.
He couldn't make
it tonight.
Said to be discrete about it.
That's why I wrote
the note that way.
Sweetheart, can you help me
with my cufflinks?
Sam, you are not
going with me.
No way.
An escort service?
You couldn't get a date
from an escort service?
I am not going
with you.
There are a lot of people
that hang out here
that I'd rather
be seen with.
Dr. Crane would probably
enjoy a stylish evening
with refined company.
I'm cured.
I think I'm cured.
I think I'm cured!
SAM:
Just remember now,
I don't go all the way
on the first date.
( indistinct conversations )
Do you think that's her?
This is ridiculous.
Listen, uh, why
don't you let me
freshen your
drink up there,
and I'll find out
if that's his wife.
I'm not even thirsty.
Don't be obvious.
Uh, do that again there,
will you, partner?
Nice party.
Ah, glad you like it.
Yeah, yeah.
I guess
I was way off base
about Rebecca,
wasn't I?
Oh, yeah, way
off, way off.
On the way over
in the car,
she was all over me
like a cat in heat.
Interesting.
Say, uh, I haven't
met your wife here.
Oh, no, that's not her.
Uh, she's in Bora Bora.
Oh, uh, visiting family?
( chuckling )
Actually, we're, uh,
we're separated, Sam.
Oh, oh, well,
that's too bad,
'cause she's missing a
heck of a party here.
Well, thanks a lot.
Well?
She's in Bora Bora.
They're separated.
I knew it.
I knew it, I knew it.
You know,
I gotta tell you,
I'm a little bit
confused here.
The red sauce is
for the shrimp,
and the mustard's
for the egg roll.
That's not what I meant.
But thanks.
No, I was just wondering...
why haven't you made
a play for this guy?
I mean, how long have
you been carrying a torch?
It's not a torch.
What a silly expression.
I am not
carrying a torch.
All right.
Two years.
Two years?
You haven't dated?
You haven't done
anything with anybody
for two years?
My God, what happens
to a person's body?
You haven't given
him a clue?
You didn't how you
feel or anything?
Oh, sweetheart.
You got
to tell him tonight
before you explode
or something.
I can't.
I wouldn't know
what to say.
Well, hell, I'll
tell you what.
Let's rehearse it
right here,
just the two of us.
You really think
that'll work?
Absolutely--
just pretend
that I'm Mr. Drake here,
and you've finally
gotten me alone
and you're going to tell me.
Okay. Okay.
Mr. Drake...
No... Evan.
Evan...
No, no. With feeling.
Evan.
Yeah, that's good,
that's good.
Now, uh, run your hand
up my thigh, here.
Wait a minute...
No, no, trust me.
Guys think that's charming.
I just want to leave.
No. Hey, listen.
You're never gonna find
a better time than this.
I mean, he just
separated with his wife,
he's here alone,
we're at a party,
you look terrific.
Now, call me crazy,
but this could be
the perfect moment.
You're right.
Yeah.
I have to seize
the moment.
There you go.
Good girl.
Mr. Drake?
Yes, Rebecca?
Take me.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm sorry. Oh,
I'm so sorry.
Sam, I think
she needs to go home.
No, I don't
need to go home.
Good night.
I'm humiliated.
I know. Come on.
And disgraced.
I'm going to
kill myself.
I still think
that thigh thing
would have been charming.
( phone rings )
Cheers.
Oh, hi, Mrs. Peterson.
Yeah, just a minute.
Hello. Hi, Vera.
Whoa. That's great news.
Great.
Cliffie. Here,
she wants to talk to you.
Me? Huh.
So, uh, what's the good news?
That she wants
to talk to you.
Yeah, Vera.
Oh?
Well, uh, uh, you following
the recipe exactly?
Oh, gee,
no, Vera, look.
It's supposed to be
two cups of water,
not vinegar.
No, uh, get ahold
of yourself, now, Vera.
Y-y-you're making a cake,
not building a bomb.
He obviously hasn't had
her tuna casserole.
( weepy muttering )
( jukebox begins playing )
Hello, young lovers
Wherever you are
I hope your troubles
are few...
( record scratches,
music stops )
( muttering )
Stupid.
Hey, Woody.
Where is Rebecca?
Uh, she was just
playing the jukebox
then she went into the office.
Thank you.
Yeah. I'll be right over.
Oh, I gotta
get over there, Normie.
She's-she's up to her armpits
in batter.
You don't mind if I stay, Cliff.
I've already seen that.
Yeah.
Don't blame me.
I told you
to talk to the guy,
not inhale his gum.
I couldn't
help myself.
Yeah, well, at least you know
how he feels now--
he's not interested.
Who wanted to know that?
You did. You were
miserable not knowing.
I was happy being miserable.
Now you've ruined it.
Oh, listen.
Now, just...
Come on, sit down
here, will you?
Relax, please.
Just, you know, just...
Could I have this?
I'm probably gonna lose my job.
Oh, right. Sure.
He's gonna come over here
and fire you
because of one lousy kiss.
Talk about paranoid.
( knocking )
Miss Howe.
Mr. Drake's here to see you.
Talk about coincidence.
I'm dead.
No, you're not.
Now, I'll take care of this.
Uh...
Woody, can you stall
for a minute there?
Sure.
You know, in high school,
I entered
the 4-H Club...
Not us, Woody-- him, him.
Not us, him.
Out there, boy.
Come on.
Okay?
Sure, Sam.
Would it have killed you
to be a little more specific?
What am I going to do?
Well, just wait. Uh...
Well, all right,
I'll-I'll go out there
and I'll tell him, uh,
that you were bombed
and that
it didn't mean anything.
Terrific. Wonderful image.
A girl goes to a party
and gets hammered,
then turns promiscuous.
Well, all right,
all right, uh...
I'll-I'll tell him
that, uh,
that you were trying
to make me jealous
'cause you're crazy
in love with me.
That's...
Let me see.
My choices are
I'm a boozy slut...
or a complete idiot.
I'd go with the idiot.
I already did.
So, that's how we
knew, beyond a doubt,
that we were putting
way, way too much bran
in the pig's fodder.
Hi, Evan.
Oh, Sam...
What are you
doing here, huh?
Well, I was on my
way to the airport,
and I thought
I'd come by here
and clear this matter
up before I left.
Oh, yeah, listen,
I gotta tell you,
that whole thing
at the party was my fault.
I mean,
we had had a little tiff,
and she was trying
to make me jealous.
Yeah,
I figured it was
something like that.
Yeah.
Well, I better
go back there
and apologize to her.
Wait, wa...
You're going to apologize?
Well, yeah,
I overreacted.
I was a little
rough on her.
Oh.
Yeah.
Uh, actually, uh,
give me a second here,
will you? Um...
She probably
needs to freshen up.
She's pretty upset
by this whole thing.
Her mascara's probably
down in her shoes by now.
How much do I owe you
for that, bartender?
Oh, no charge, Mr. Drake.
I mean, after all,
you kind of own the place.
Oh, no, no, no, no,
I'll pay for it.
Credit card okay?
Sure.
All right.
I'll need to see
a driver's license.
Listen, I did my best.
I mean, I gave him
the jealousy story,
but he just didn't buy it.
I tell you, man,
he is really steamed.
Damn.
You know, he said
that if, uh,
if you were really
in love with me,
that he might understand.
You know, that it would
explain everything,
but he just...
didn't buy that.
Oh, God, what am
I going to do?
I don't know.
Unless...
Unless what? What?
Ah... No, no, yeah,
yeah, that wouldn't work.
No, no, what?
Tell me, please.
Well, all right, well,
maybe, you know, if...
well, if he were
to walk in here
and find you kissing me
more passionately
than you kissed him...
Forget it,
forget it,
forget it.
All right
all right.
You know, you
never give up.
You are always
on the make.
Let me tell you
something, buster.
All right.
I still have a
little self-respect.
I have a little pride.
( knocking )
Have it your way.
Hello.
( clearing throat )
Oh. Ha.
Sorry, Evan, there.
I didn't, uh, didn't
hear you come in there.
You know how it is
with young lovers, here.
We just can't keep
our hands off each other.
Yeah.
You're a lucky man, Sam.
Oh, yeah,
you're telling me.
Well, this little
honey of mine
gives me a lot
of good loving, don't you?
Sure do, punkin.
Well, I just
came by to apologize
for how I reacted earlier.
Apologize?
To me?
Well, yeah, I told Sam outside.
You told Sam?
Gotcha.
So why don't we just
not say anything more about it?
I think
that's a great idea.
Uh, let me walk you
to the car here.
Yeah.
Malone.
No, no.
I think we should say
nothing more about this.
Sam, get back here.
Ha. Some women
just can't get enough.
You haven't met
my wife, Sam.
SAM:
Oh... Oh...
Good night.
Hey, listen. Come on.
I'm just having
a little fun with you.
You know,
I know why you're upset.
You found out something
in that room
you hadn't counted on.
Your true feelings
were revealed.
What?
No woman
can kiss like that
and not mean it.
Are you nuts?
No, no, no.
No, it can't be done.
You can't fake passion
like that.
Oh, is that right?
Hey, Fras.
Nice try.
Frasier?
( Frasier hiccups )
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.OpenSubtitles.org