Yes, I'll tell him.
Sam, I just had a conversation
with your date tonight.
Bambi.
She said she can't make it.
She's had an accident.
You're kidding. What happened?
She fell off her shoes.
Gee, that's tough.
That leaves me only two hours
to find another date.
- Those are the breaks.
- Not to worry.
The book!
Cliff, I swear,
it just gave off a beam of light.
- A little black book?
- Yeah.
Didn't those go out with getting
a girl drunk and seducing her?
That's out now?
Let me see.
Christie Leveroni.
Christie Leveroni, come on down!
Come on, Sam, let me dial this one.
It's been a long time since I've run
my fingers over a girl's digits.
Norman.
You know, I haven't seen Christie
since Woodstock.
- You were at Woodstock?
- A friend told me to go there.
Said it was a great place
to pick up chicks.
I should have known
you weren't there for the music.
There was music at Woodstock?
Sammy, it's ringing.
Hello. Is Christie there?
She entered a convent?
Boys, it looks like
your idol has fallen.
So what's the number over there?
- Hi, Coach.
- Hi, Diane.
Hey, Coach.
Sam. Look at me.
- Do I look OK to you?
- Yeah, why?
I just went
to renew my driver's licence.
They asked me
to donate my kidneys.
No, don't take that personal, Coach.
They ask everybody.
Those highway robbers.
It used to be a lousy two bucks.
- Carla's late again.
- Yeah, I know. I wonder why.
Sam, you know why.
Why aren't any of us saying anything
about Carla's problem?
I don't think we should be
the ones to bring this up.
You know Carla, she's proud.
Maybe she just wants to keep
this one under her hat, that's all.
Maybe it's not even
what we think it is.
- Coach, what else could it be?
- Gas?
- Hi, everyone.
- Hi, Carla.
- I got to go change.
- OK.
What are we all so afraid of?
We've known for well over a month
that Carla's...
Let me be the first to say it aloud.
Carla is pregnant.
That's it, Sam, it's out.
Sam, she is all alone in the world.
She needs some support.
She's probably waiting
for us to reach out.
- You people call yourselves friends.
- Why don't you talk to her?
Well, I would, but Carla's
never actually called me a friend,
unless "doofus"
is a term of endearment.
No, don't look at me.
Vera and I don't have any kids.
I don't know anything
about the subject.
How come you and Vera
never had any kids?
- I can't, Coach.
- Gee, I'm sorry, Norm.
I look at Vera... I just can't.
- So how's it going, guys?
- Hi, Carla.
This is...
Look, Carla,
we just want you to know that...
Well, if there's anything
you ever need, just ask us, OK?
Well, since you
brought it up, Sam.
Yeah, what?
I'm going to need a couple
of hours off at the end of April.
If you don't want to talk about it...
No, it's OK. I told the father
about it yesterday.
He's been out of town.
I just wanted to tell him first.
Tell the rest of them.
I mean, they're dying to hear.
- I'll go talk to them.
- Alright.
What was I saying?
The weather is really...
It's always just...
sort of beautiful.
Everyone?
- I'm pregnant.
- What?
No! You're pregnant? Carla.
Well, why didn't you say anything?
I've got a lot on my mind.
I can't remember everything.
Sure. Busy girl.
Congratulations.
Unless you don't want another kid.
- Of course she wanted the kid.
- Sure I do.
What penniless, unmarried
mother of four wouldn't?
See what I mean?
Don't worry about that. I'll give you
a little bump-up in pay.
- Thanks, Sam.
- That's great.
Carla gets a raise
for getting pregnant.
I wonder what I have to do
to get a raise out of the boss.
You could get a raise
out of the boss.
So who's the father?
We want to know.
You're about to see for yourselves.
He's coming in.
I really got lucky this time, boy.
He's a nice, responsible guy,
and he is going to support this kid.
That's great.
You going to get married?
Well, you know, actually
we probably would, Sam,
except it goes against
my most cherished belief.
Men are toe jam.
Who is this guy?
Marshall.
- Marshall?
- Carla made love to a PhD from MlT?
Look, guys, if you can't say it
in front of me, don't say it at all.
No, Coach.
Coach, Marshall is the father
of Carla's child.
Marshall? I don't believe it,
and I believe everything.
- How are you feeling, little mommy?
- I'll make a deal with you.
You don't call me "little mommy",
and I don't put your tongue
in the blender.
- Come down and sit down here.
- Come on, Marshall.
- Way to go.
- I'm so happy for you both.
- Congratulations, Marshall.
- Congratulations, Dad.
Why don't you have a seat,
little... Carla?
Thank you.
We have something to celebrate.
A little champagne.
- A toast!
- Serve it up, boys.
I'll get the glasses.
By the way,
I recommend the Lamaze method.
I've read about that
and it sounds wonderful.
No, forget it.
I got my own method.
Knock me out and wake me
when it's potty-trained.
Let's make a toast.
Somebody make a toast.
- Diane, make the toast.
- Alright.
To the baby.
With Marshall as the father,
it's sure to have brains.
With Carla as the mother,
it's sure to have need for them.
I'm kidding. What I mean is,
to the baby and its luck
at having such wonderful parents.
Hear, hear.
What, what?
I think I'd better just lie down
for a minute, alright?
Would you all excuse me?
I'll be right back.
I didn't even know
you and Carla were dating.
Actually, Coach,
we just dated the one time.
One time?
Just once?
It's a funny thing, too,
because Carla wouldn't
give me a second look before that.
Or since.
But she sure was ready, willing
and able that night.
She was a woman possessed.
So the whole thing was her idea?
Yes, I think you could say that.
Not that I didn't enjoy myself,
but I had no idea
this would be the result.
I was so surprised
when she told me about it yesterday.
Would you excuse me, Marshall?
I think I need to talk to Carla.
- You clever girl, you.
- What?
I know what you're up to,
you sly boots.
Got to hand it to you, pretty smart.
- I don't know what you mean.
- Yes, you do.
Marshall's not the father
of that child.
Maybe he is and maybe he isn't.
Come on, Carla. You can tell me.
I'm proud of you.
This shows real initiative.
Well, since you already guessed,
you're right, he's not the father.
I lied so he'd support it.
What a great, great plan.
Yeah, well, I hate
to sing my own praises.
Well, don't sing your own praises.
Why don't you hum
a few bars of this tune?
Carla, how could you?
Why don't you sit down
and let me talk for a change?
Fine.
I'd had a really rotten day.
I got stiffed twice.
Sam bawled me out for something.
You were here.
I got soaked on the way home.
By the time I got the kids
locked in their rooms,
I had really had it.
So I sat down at the kitchen table,
a bottle of Chianti.
I just started thinking
about how rotten my whole life was...
...when I saw his face
through the fog in the door window.
- Who?
- Nick, my ex-husband.
Besides everything else,
it was our anniversary.
I see.
But I was so down, I figured we could
just talk for a while, you know?
So we were drinking
and remembering
the couple of good times we had.
It was the first laugh
I had all day.
He was wearing
his black fishnet T-shirt.
I could see his panther tattoo
through the little holes.
No woman could resist.
With the rain and everything
and the wine,
I just got carried away.
Carla, this is the man
you once referred to as "seepage".
Sure, Nick's disgusting,
but he knows this spot
on your earlobe.
One nibble and you are
a heaving mound of flesh.
I find that very hard to believe.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Well, let me just show you.
- Carla, don't be ridiculous.
Carla.
Cliff, no, this isn't
what you think it is.
No, it's OK.
I'm an '80s kind of a guy.
- Seen all the right movies.
- Yes. Well, no.
Cliff, you see, Carla and I
were testing a fascinating
scientific hypothesis.
Scientific.
I like science.
Step right this way.
Carla, show him.
- Unbelievable.
- I didn't feel anything.
Well, sometimes
there's a delayed reaction.
- Maybe if both of you jumped on...
- Take a walk.
Listen, if you need a trois
for that ménage, I'll be in the bar.
Alright, let me see if
I have the decadence straight.
When you discovered
you were pregnant,
you purposely seduced Marshall
because you assumed
that your husband
would not assume responsibility
for the child.
- Exactly.
- Depraved.
Now, look here, Whitey.
You know, you can talk,
but I got four kids,
and I've been raising them alone
and it's been damned hard.
I can't take it any more.
Somebody is going to help me
ease my load a little bit this time,
and I don't care
what I have to do to get it.
Carla, it's wrong.
I don't care.
And I don't care what you think.
- What did you guys do to Cliff?
- What's the matter?
We just had to pull him
off the wooden lndian.
- Cliff.
- Yes?
Yeah, Cliff. Sip. Beer. Sip, Cliff.
Carla, do you know the story
of The Tell-Tale Heart?
- Take a leap, Whitey.
- I'm going to tell it to you.
A young man killed an old man.
While carrying out the crime,
he could hear his victim's
heart beating in fright. Ba-boom.
He was very glad
when the man was dead
and the awful sound stopped.
Then he dismembered his victim
and buried him under the floorboards.
Soon, he could hear a sound
coming up from the floor.
Till he couldn't stand it any more.
Surely everyone heard it.
Eventually,
guilt drove him totally insane.
You can never escape
your conscience.
OK! Tom, I've been cheating on you.
You are a wonderful man
and I don't deserve you.
- I'm sorry.
- Wait, darling.
- ls this having any effect on you?
- None at all.
Maybe you need bigger ba-booms.
Diane, would you just
leave me alone?
Carla, don't get upset.
Sit down with me.
Thanks. So, how's it going, Dad?
Great, I think I'm approaching
a state of euphoria.
- Coach, could I have that beer?
- Absolutely, Marshall.
Carla, what do you think
we should name the child?
We got time for names, Marshall.
The biggest argument
I ever had with my wife
was over naming our daughter.
She kept insisting on Lisa.
I wanted to stick
with the original name.
- What was that, Coach?
- Baby Girl Pantusso.
You know, Carla,
I've been thinking.
Tomorrow, I'm going
to go to my lawyer,
and have a new will drawn up
and all of your children will
be named as my beneficiaries.
Gee, Marshall,
I never expected that.
That's about the sweetest thing
anybody's ever done...
Diane, would you just cut it out
with the stupid "ba-booms"?
Carla, Diane's in the back room.
Come on, we got to talk.
You win. I'm going
to tell him the truth.
Will somebody please tell me
what's going on here?
- She's going to tell him the truth.
- The truth about what?
Sam, it's terrible. She lied.
The real father is her ex-husband.
I don't believe this.
I mean, I know the guy.
Her ex-husband is an insensitive,
macho pig with one thing on his mind.
- Some women are attracted to that.
- Name one.
Arlene Abrams.
Angela Adams.
- I'm going home.
- No, listen. Wait a minute.
I'm going to talk to you first.
Sit down. Now, look.
Diane told me what's going on
and I just have to say something.
Marshall, you and Carla have a chance
for some great happiness here.
I don't think
you should throw it away.
- Sam, you don't...
- Come on, let me say this.
- Look at me, Marshall.
- Look at you?
Yeah. Now, a lot of people
think that I've got a great life.
But you have a... You can have
something that I don't have.
You can have the love
and the warmth of a family.
You know, if you don't marry Carla,
some lucky guy's going to.
As a matter of fact, if you
don't marry Carla, I'm going to.
I'm not going to marry her.
- I got the veil in my locker.
- You understand that what...
Get out of here. You're all toe jam.
You know,
I just feel terrible about this.
I guess she really did
want some help with this child.
Yeah, she's barely getting by
just the way it is.
Carla's probably never felt lonelier
than she does at this moment.
Got any more of those
little yellow goldfish crackers?
We don't have any crackers
that look like goldfish.
What did I just eat?
I wish I had the money so I could
take care of the kid myself.
Me, too, Sam.
Wait, I've got a wonderful idea.
We are always taking up collections
for little league teams
and to give gifts to orphans.
We are now going to take up
a collection to help Carla.
I think Cheers
should adopt this child.
You know,
that's not such a stupid idea.
We could all take turns
doing things with the kid.
- Right.
- I could teach him how to pitch.
I could teach him how to hit
your pitches out of the ballpark.
I'll do the kid's taxes.
Coach, come here.
Listen, everybody.
This is for Carla's kid.
It's going to be our kid.
I can teach it
how to slide into second base.
You can't. Remember your back.
- I can teach him how to swim.
- You're afraid of the water.
Well, I can teach him
how to tie a Windsor knot.
Why do you think you wear clip-ons?
Well, I can just sit there.
I'm going home.
Carla, before you do,
we want you to take this from us.
It's to help out with the kid.
We'd kind of like it
to be our kid, too.
When you walk through a storm
Hold your head up high
And don't be afraid of the dark
Everybody, come on.
At the end of a storm
is a golden light
And the sweet silver song of a lark
Walk on through the wind
Walk on through the rain
Though your dreams
be tossed and blown
Walk on, walk on
With hope in your heart
And you'll never walk alone
You'll never walk alone