Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Guinness stout and a gin and tonic.
Something the matter, Carla?
Yeah, something's the matter.
My life is the pits.
Seems like good things happen
to everybody except me, you know?
Norm has a new job.
Frasier actually seems happy
since he met his creepy girlfriend.
And Sam has given up women
and decided to marry Diane.
And what have I got? Zip.
Woody, I mean, how do you keep
such a sunny disposition
in this rotten, stink-infested world?
You mean, what do I do
when I see Mr. Blues
peeking around the corner?
Oh, God,
he even has a cute name for depression.
Well, I just close my eyes,
and I think a happy thought.
Here, I-I'll show you.
What was your thought?
I'm glad I'm not you.
(piano plays)
♪ Making your way in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like to get away♪ ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always glad you came ♪
♪ You want to be where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You want to go where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Hey, Mr. Peterson. Yeah.
I'm working on this month's
issue of the Cheers newsletter,
and I wondered
what's new with you?
Nothing, really, Woody.
Well, you sure?
Uh, I don't know. Check last month.
What was I up to then?
Let's see. Norm Peterson.
Nothing.
Oh.
Well, I guess it's not new then, eh?
How about you, Dr. Crane?
What's new in my life?
Well, it's not easily
put into words, Wood.
Perhaps it has something to do
with my relationship with Lilith.
And perhaps it's just a maturity
that comes with age.
All I know is that I feel
I finally know who I am,
and I'm happy with that person.
Does that answer your question?
Sure does.
Dr. Crane: Nothing.
Sam!
Great news!
I found a house.
Hey!
Turn it in. Maybe you'll get a reward.
No, you goose.
I found our house.
I was driving to work today
and, as luck would have it,
there was an eight-car smash-up.
Yeah, that didn't come out right.
What I meant was I was forced to take
an alternate route,
and it sent me right
past the perfect house.
Oh, Sam, you should see it.
Three bedrooms, two and a half baths,
a formal dining room,
a huge fireplace in the living room.
Excuse me for interrupting,
but we're not looking for a house.
I know. I already found it.
No, I mean that we agreed
to live in my apartment
for a year first.
Well, yes,
that was the original plan. Yeah.
But that was before
I saw hardwood floors,
bay windows, crown moldings.
Yeah, well,
so what's wrong with my apartment?
Well, granted this house
doesn't have your view of
the Exotic Dancing Academy.
But I think you could learn to live
in the shade of a stately elm.
Oh, uh, I, uh, hate
to be a buttinsky here,
but, uh,
this is the absolute
worst time to buy a house.
Why is that?
Ah, seller's market.
Unless you run into
that, uh, rare breed,
you know, the motivated seller.
Now, you know, for a price,
I could put you in a sweet little, uh,
three-bed,
two-bath number.
Uh, it's got, uh,
fishnetting over the patio
and a handmade, uh, uh, lava
rock fire pit in the back.
Cliffie, uh, that sounds a
little bit like your house.
It is my house, Norm.
NORM: Wait, wait, wait now.
You said your mother
was going to live there
till the day she died.
Well, uh, she's clean,
and she doesn't eat much.
Sam, please.
Just come with me and take a look at it.
I'm not-I'm not ready to own a home.
It's a... you-you got
to work up to that.
Sammy's right.
It's a big responsibility.
You got uh, lawns to mow.
You got plumbing to fix.
You got gutters to clean.
Then, you know, every couple of years,
you got to paint the entire
thing from top to bottom.
Honestly, I don't know where
Vera gets the energy sometimes.
Norm, you should be ashamed of yourself.
Yeah, I guess I should, shouldn't I?
You know, thank God I'm not, huh?
Well, Sam and I will split
the chores at our house.
Would you just slow down?
We're not buyin' a house. I mean it.
Now, Sam, don't be so hasty.
This could be the house for you.
Does it have a basement?
Yes, it does. A large one.
Great.
You can convert it into a
dungeon to keep Diane in.
Then, when you're done torturing her,
you could bury the body
under the cement floor,
cover it with a Ping-Pong table.
Well, maybe. I don't know.
Sam.
No, no, maybe you, not her.
Will you stop stalling
and come with me, please?
Just give me one good
reason why I should.
Because we own it.
That's a pretty good reason, Sam.
You bought a house without asking me?
Well, I-I didn't exactly buy it.
Uh-huh. I put down the teeniest
of refundable deposits.
You know, I don't believe this.
Oh, now, Sam, there was
another couple there,
and they were all ready
to make a bid on it.
I had to move quickly.
Yeah, talking about moving quickly,
you get into my office right now
and you call them tell them
that I want my deposit back.
Okay, Sam, whatever you say.
But first I want to call the decorator
about ordering drapes.
Yeah, well, make it quick.
Well, I guess it's
time we started thinking
about a housewarming gift.
Ah, it's pathetic.
Yeah, you'd never catch a woman of mine
leading me around by the nose.
No, but you might catch her
sunning herself on a rock.
It's ours.
It's finally ours. I can't believe it.
Neither can I.
Wow, you know, every time I come here
I like this place more and more.
Oh. (chuckles)
Thank God you talked
me into this. Oh, yeah.
Oh.
You don't think we spent
too much money on it?
Oh, absolutely.
What the hell?
It's a great house.
Yeah. And it's ours.
Well, not quite yet.
You know, I never feel at home
until I hang this little baby up.
Oh, God, Sam.
What?
Oh, not where people can see it.
You know, I have never understood
your attitude about this painting.
I mean, it's a classic.
"Dogs Playing
Blackjack."
(laughing)
I never look at this
without cracking up.
Ah.
Well, that's the purpose of great art.
You know something? I think you,
you're missing the subtle humor here.
I mean, see this guy
right here? He's cheating.
(laughs)
Oh. Oh, Sam,
I can hardly wait till
I'm in the kitchen,
pot holders in hand,
cooking a nice big roast,
calling out to you,
"Dinner's ready, honey."
"I'll be right there.
I'm in the workshop."
The workshop?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
My dad always had one.
I used to go down there all the time.
I just loved the smell of sawdust.
Wonder where I can buy some of that.
(laughs)
Oh, Sam,
I have wonderful plans
for every room in the entire house.
That's funny, so do I.
(laughs)
Why don't we start right
here in the living room?
Yeah, these floors
look like they could use
a little polishing. Oh, Sam. Sam.
MAN: We really have
to leave now, my dear.
WOMAN: Yes, I guess you're right.
Uh, hello? Hello?
Oh. You must be the new owner.
Yeah, yeah, I'm, uh,
I'm Sam Malone. How do you do?
How are you?
This is my, uh, fiancée, Diane Chambers.
Hi. Bert and Lillian Miller.
Oh. Hi, how are you?
Pleased to meet you.
Oh, it's a pleasure.
The house is beautiful. Mmm.
Oh, yes, yes.
Well, of course, we know
we're supposed to be out of here by now,
but, well, we forgot a few
odds and ends, you know?
And, uh,
well, we just wanted
to take a last look.
Well, you know,
when you've lived in
a house for 40 years,
taking that last step out the door,
well, it-it-it's
pretty hard.
Of course.
I confess, I... touched
liquor this morning.
Oh, tha... that's all right, my girl.
But you look like a fine couple.
I'm glad the house is
going to you. Thank you.
Oh, yeah, yeah, we plan
to do great things in it--
with it, with it.
So many memories.
Like when Mikey climbed
up the bookshelves
and hit his head on the mantle.
You remember?
Oh, we were all so worried.
And that's where little Janey
rehearsed her dance for the school play.
Oh.
You know, I studied ballet as a child.
So I became quite experien...
Berty Junior
took his first steps
on this very spot right here.
And... that's where we
always put our Christmas tree.
LILLIAN: Every year.
40 Christmases.
Thirty-nine.
Hmm?
Well, we didn't quite make it
to Christmas this year.
Oh, sure.
BERT: You know,
I think we'll
miss the Christmases most of all.
I know, Bert.
The children
and the grandchildren.
BERT: Ah, never mind.
There, there now.
Out with the old.
And in with the new.
Now, we're just going
to get out of your way,
so that you two can
share your lives.
Well, good luck to you. Thank you.
Can I help you with those boxes there?
Oh no, they'll be fine. No.
We're just going as far as the bus stop.
Okay, okay.
Have a nice day.
SAM: Yeah. Glad to meet you. Thank you.
Good-bye.
(weepy): Good-bye, house.
SAM: Bye-bye.
BERT: Bye-bye now.
Gee, what a sweet couple, huh?
Let's see, where were we?
Oh, yes, yes, yes, I think we were, uh,
talking about polishing the floor.
Do want to wax or shall we buff?
I cannot live a single
day in this house.
Oh, God.
SAM: Come on, come on.
It's all right.
I mean it, Sam.
I could never live here.
No, don't say that. Don't say that.
Listen, hey, I got a surprise for you.
Look, I took the picture down.
Sam, it has nothing
to do with the picture.
I-I... Although I do appreciate that.
This place belongs
to Bert and Lillian.
It's alive with their memories.
Oh, poor Mikey. Now,
that must have smarted.
Come on, come on, we love this house.
Now, I know how you
feel right now, but...
but wait till we make some changes here.
Look, we can... we can...
we can knock out this wall right here
and make the whole room different.
I mean, yeah, what
the hell? Look at that.
They got writing all over this wall.
Oh, look.
"Mikey at one year, 30 inches."
"Bert Jr. at two years, 36 inches."
How can you possibly
think of tearing this down?
Can't you see
this is a record of their lives?
Well, all I can see
is that little Janey here was a moose.
How'd you like to have that
coming at you in a tutu, huh?
You have the sensitivity
of a dung beetle.
I'm just trying to
lighten the mood up here.
Well, I'm not in the
mood for fun and games.
Well... ALL: Happy housewarming!
Hey, hey...
No, don't.
This isn't our house.
We don't belong in it.
I'll never live here.
Not one day, not one minute.
Please, leave, please.
You know, Sammy, a couple of years ago,
this might've taken me by surprise,
but now I just kind of roll with it.
This is great!
I got the one where
they're on the train.
Yeah. Not now, Woody.
(laughs)
Look at that.
I never noticed that.
The bloodhound's doubling down.
Look at that.
(horn honks)
Uh, I'm sorry about this, you guys.
It's a... it's a bad time.
CARLA: Wait till the honeymoon!
We're trespassers here, Sam.
The love and warmth
that fill these walls
didn't come from us.
We can change the wallpaper,
we can paint,
we can put up new curtains,
but the soul of this house
will still be those
two sweet, old people.
I'd be afraid to wash the dishes
for fear I'd turn the faucet on,
and instead of water coming
out, it would be Lillian's tears.
Oh, brother.
I-I-I'll put
a purifier in.
All houses have ghosts.
You know, memories of people
who lived there before.
Now, the only way you
can get rid of them
is to-to start making
your own memories,
and the only way we can do that
is if we move in here
and start living here.
Mm...
maybe you're right.
Yeah.
I guess I've been overreacting.
Oh, that's okay.
(sighs)
What do you say we carry
on this conversation naked?
Do you think I could ever
make love in this house?
Afternoon, everybody.
EVERYONE: Norm!
Hey, Mr. Peterson, how's life?
Oh, the plot's okay, Woody,
but it kind of falls apart at the end.
Where's Sammy and Diane?
They're in the office trying to unload
The Nightmare on Diane Street.
Well...
they'll just have to miss my big news.
Woody, I want you
to stop the presses on
that, uh, newsletter.
You'll never guess who I saw
in front of my office today.
Robert Urich.
(gasps) Okay?
I want to tell you
he's just as nice a guy
driving past at 50 miles an hour
as he looks on that TV screen.
Hey, Woody, Woody, Woody.
Another round. Quick, too.
Hey, how's it going in there? Oh, great.
The couple in there are crazier
about the house than we were.
You know, I have to admit,
I was a little ticked off
when Diane said she
wanted to sell the house,
but as it turns out, I
think we're going to make a--
that's
good, Woody--
make a nice little profit here.
Are you sure I can't change your mind?
I'm sorry.
That's my final decision.
You know, I-I-I'm
getting on in years,
and my hearing may not
be what it used to be,
but did you just queer this whole deal?
I had to turn them down.
Why?
Sam, those people
were bereft of soul.
They had no intention
of embracing that house.
Their only desire was to live there.
They wanted to live in
the house they just bought?
My God, they must've
been raised by wolves.
They weren't the right kind of people
to live in Bert and Lillian's house.
Oh, you know...
That's it, that's it.
You know, I... we have
always done things your way.
I have bent over backwards
to make you happy.
I bought the ring you wanted,
the china you wanted,
the-the crystal you wanted.
I even agreed to have
a duvet cover on my bed,
and I don't know what a duvet is
or what it's supposed to cover.
When are we going to do something
that I want to do?
May I remind you that we're going
to Disney World for our honeymoon?
Big deal. Who isn't?
Sam, every time I look at that place,
I can't help but think
about that poor, old couple,
shambling away from their house,
wishing they could spend
one last Christmas
there with their family.
Well, then why not just give them
one last Christmas there,
if that's what they want?
But rid yourself
of the guilt you feel by robbing them
of the last few happy
memories left them.
Oh, you know, that-that's
the screwiest idea
I've ever heard. No, Sam, he's right.
We-we'll-we'll call the
Millers and all their children,
and we'll plan a Christmas party.
Oh, Sam, it'll make
the transition easier
for them and for me.
Well, what are we supposed
to do until December?
Bunk out with Ma Clavin?
No, I mean, we'll do it now.
This year, Christmas comes next week.
Oh... Huh? Oh, it'll be fun.
Oh, gee, I hate it when
they change holidays around
just to make a three-day weekend.
Who's ready for some
delicious hot apple cider?
Can I have mine with ice?
It's 80 degrees outside.
Where's your Christmas spirit, Naomi?
It melted.
There's another present
for you there, Naomi.
Isn't that right, Santa?
I'm looking, I'm looking, I'm looking.
All right, here it is, here it is.
There you go, kid.
There you are.
Oh, boy!
What do you say, Naomi?
Thank you, Santa.
SAM: Ah... And what do you say, Santa?
Yeah, Mrs. Claus is
going to pay for this.
Come here.
Look, look, how much longer
do we have to do this?
Oh, the children are loving it.
Yeah, well, can I at
least take this beard off?
No, no, no, no.
Now, we don't want to
spoil their illusions.
Don't you think the fact
that Santa's here in mid-May
sweating bullets is making 'em
a little suspicious already?
Uh, yes, Santa, what a great idea.
Why don't you lead us all
in some Christmas carols?
Uh, m-m-maybe somebody
else ought to do that.
Uh, Santa's got a little
summer cold going here.
Oh, well, David is the
musician of the family.
Well...
"Let it Snow" in "E" flat.
(plays note)
♪ Oh, the weather outside is frightful ♪
♪ But the fire is so delightful ♪
♪ And since there's no place to go ♪
♪ Let it snow, let it
snow, let it snow... ♪
All right, all right, look,
we-we did it, we did it.
They're singing their carols.
We passed out the presents.
Now can we put out the stupid fire
and-and get the Millers
out of here, please?
Oh, but, Sam, we haven't
roasted the chestnuts yet.
Oh, guess again, sweetheart.
Well, you know,
that was great, kids, but I think
perhaps we-we ought to thank
the kind and generous friends...
...who've let us make
this Yuletide possible.
Oh, no. No, no.
You really don't have to.
No, no, not at all.
Now, Sam and Diane
have opened their home--
it is their
home now--
so that we can enjoy
one last Christmas here together.
Well, of course, we've
known a lot of Christmases
around this hearth, but for you kids,
this will be the last one.
And all they'll have
is pictures, home movies
and memories to fill the gap
through their lives.
Oh, I hope the memories survive.
Say you'll remember, children.
CHILDREN: We'll all remember, Grandma.
BERT: Yes, and-and what about Easter?
Will you remember the Easters, too?
I don't remember, Grandpa.
Oh, honey...
Please don't make Grandma
and Grandpa leave, lady.
No, go... Oh, oh,
th-th-they
don't have to.
Listen, why don't you
come over next week,
and we'll have a big Easter egg hunt
right here.
And I will make it an annual occasion.
CHILDREN: Yay!
No, no, no, no!
No, no, I am not putting
on a bunny suit for anybody!
Now, now, listen,
we've done everything--
more than everything--
anybody could possibly expect.
We got to draw the line somewhere here.
I mean, we can't arrange our
lives just for you people.
I mean, this is our house now.
Y-Y-You can't
have it anymore.
Please, I mean,
w-we-we need a chance
to start our own lives here.
I mean, for God's sake, we
haven't even had a chance
to be intimate in our own home yet.
What does Santa mean, Mommy?
Mommy will explain it later, dear.
Yeah, and somewhere else, Mommy.
Uh, c-come on, everybody, please, out.
(children whining)
LILLIAN: Oh, no, no, no.
Now, don't grumble. Santa is right.
He may have been a
little rude about it...
...but it is true.
We have been imposing.
So let's all go over to
Grandma and Grandpa's new condo
and have Christmas there.
CHILDREN: Yay!
♪ Frosty the Snowman
was a jolly, happy soul ♪
Bye-bye, happy holidays.
? With a corncob pipe and button
nose ? Yeah, bye-bye, bye-bye.
? And two eyes made out of
coal... ? There we go. Bye-bye.
Thank you. There we go.
What about our presents?
Uh, we'll ship 'em to you.
I can't believe what you just did, Sam.
I am not going to apologize, Diane.
Suddenly, the house is ours.
You mean that?
You claimed it for me.
Oh. Just stood up
and claimed it for me like
some animal out of the wild.
Oh, Sam...
you're so sexy when you're territorial.
So, uh...
anything special you want
from Santa this year, little girl?
Oh, Santa...
Well, I think that can be arranged.
There you go...
Where is that?
It's in there someplace.
You know, Santa? Hmm?
I think it's time to take you up
on that offer to polish the floor.
Oh, well, uh...
what room would you
like to start in here?
Hmm... how about the dining room?
Oh, good, good, good, good, good.
(Sam laughing)