Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Hey, guys,
guess what followed me home.
A slime trail?
This cute little
fellow right here.
Huh?
Isn't he sweet?
The cutest little dog
you've ever seen, huh?
What you gonna do
with him, Cliff?
Oh, I, I thought we'd just keep
him in the bar here, Sam,
you know, kind of like
a bar mascot.
Guys, I kind of thought
I was the bar mascot.
I don't think so, Cliffy.
All right, Sammy.
Come on, Spotty.
Bye-bye, Spotty.
Oh, how cute.
Hi, little fellow.
Ah.
What's his name?
Well, this is,
this is Spotty, huh?
Isn't he cute?
Yeah, he's kind of like
the-the bar mascot.
Hey, you know,
he and I are about
to take a bath.
Would you like to join us?
(theme song begins)
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always
glad you came
You wanna be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You wanna be where
everybody knows your name
You wanna go
where people know
People are all the same
You wanna go where
everybody knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Hey, Mr. Clavin,
if you're looking for
a home for the dog there,
I'd be happy
to take him.
Ah, no, Woody.
You see, Spotty here is
a thoroughbred puppy.
Needs a lot of attention, a lot
of care, needs a lot of space.
I'll give you five bucks
for him.
Here you go.
Hello. Any messages?
Oh, yeah.
One of your old baseball
buddies called, Dutch Kincaid.
I'll be damned.
Wonder what he wants?
Probably another home run.
I think you served him up
something like 27 in his career.
What did that
work out to, Sam?
Oh, yeah, uh, one
for every time he faced you.
That was a long time ago.
Yeah.
Poor guy's probably
down and out--
wants to borrow a few bucks
from me.
No. He wants you to show up
for Dutch Kincaid Day
at Yankee Stadium.
They're having a Dutch Kincaid
Day at Yankee Stadium?
Yeah. They're bringing him back
for one more time at bat
before the game.
He wants you to pitch to him.
Smart guy, that Dutch.
He's gotta be kidding.
Why the hell should
I want to help him?
I, I'm gonna get on a plane
and fly down to New York
just to give him
some free publicity?
What are you worried about?
You afraid he's
gonna pop one out
and you're going to have to see
the old Dutch Windmill again?
What is the Dutch Windmill?
Oh, every time
Dutch hit a homer,
he used to do this little dance
while he ran around the bases.
It's kind of his trademark.
Yeah, if memory serves,
it was something like this.
He'd have that
left arm pumping,
and the right arm
like a windmill,
and wiggle his fanny
back and forth.
NORM:
No, no, no,
more like this.
No, Norm, less jiggle.
I haven't started
dancing yet.
Hey, this is fun.
Did you have
a trademark, Sam?
Shut up and
leave me alone.
Actually, Sam, that's
more of a motto.
No, come on, man, don't
let him lick your... Ew!
Don't let him lick
your lips like that.
Oh, it's okay.
You know, it's an
interesting fact
that that dog's mouth
is probably cleaner
than anybody's in this bar.
There's a shock.
Fras, how about you?
You want to play
with the puppy?
I don't know.
Uh, my mother never allowed me
to have a puppy
when I was a boy.
Consequently, she instilled
in me a slight fear of animals.
I'd say it's about time
you got over that.
Come on, now, Spotty.
I want you to say hello
to your Uncle Frasier.
Well, hello, Spotty.
Norm, I, I think Spotty
wants to go away now.
No. He feels pretty
comfortable there, doesn't he?
Well, did I mention to
you that, uh, Spotty
wants to buy you a beer?
Good boy, Scotty.
Can I help you?
Yeah. I'm looking for
a yellow-bellied,
runny-nosed has-been.
Hmm, can't make
one of those.
I'm out of cassis.
Hello, Dutch.
Mayday.
What are you doing here?
I hear you're too chicken
to pitch to me, Fluffy.
What's the matter,
afraid I'll make you
look bad again?
I'm not afraid
of anything, Dutch.
And I don't have anything
to prove, either.
Hey, you know, Malone,
if word gets out
that you're pitching
to me again,
it might give the guy
the kind of publicity
that would put him back
in the public eye.
Maybe even in the Hall of Fame.
Oh, get out.
I could never get
into the Hall of Fame.
Not you, you pantywaist.
It's Dutch Kincaid Day,
not Sam Malone Day.
Man, what an ego.
Find yourself another
sucker, will you?
Okay.
Have you got a men's room
in here?
Oh, what am I asking you for?
It's in the back.
Yeah, thanks.
Oh, uh, I gave my neighbor's kid
a Sam Malone baseball card
to stick in his spokes
of his bike.
Now, when he rides it, it goes
"wimp, wimp, wimp, wimp, wimp."
Come on, Sammy,
let's go.
It would be great to
see you pitch again.
No way. I told him "no"
and I meant it.
Come on, the guy is a jerk.
You've got to nail him.
No.
Knock him down a few pegs.
No. No-no-no.
Oh, no.
You're afraid he's still
gonna be able to hit you.
Oh, are you kidding me?
The guy's a washed-up
old has-been.
I mean, he hasn't
played for years.
I can strike him out with one
hand tied behind my back.
Worth a try, Sammy.
The other way never worked.
That was then, you know.
Now I've got the edge on him.
I'm young. You know,
I'm in good shape.
Aw, shoot.
I've got to remember
to warm up before I do that.
So why don't you
just go out there
and humiliate him
for a change?
Yeah.
Come on, Sammy.
Yeah, Sammy.
Listen to yourselves, will ya?
Have some class.
The guy's an old man.
FRASIER:
Good for you, Sam.
I'm impressed by your stand.
It shows real maturity.
Yeah, well, it's gonna take a
lot more than a stupid insult
to get me to go all the way
to New York.
I'll see you later, Underpants.
That does it!
All right, I'll
see you Saturday.
Yankee Stadium.
That's the spirit.
Listen, and don't worry about
getting into the stadium.
Saturday is Ladies Day.
That'll teach you to pinch a
lady's butt in a locker room.
Guys giving
you trouble?
No.
I was teaching them how to pinch
a lady's butt in a locker room.
Ah, look at this.
I'm focused, I'm
psyched, I'm sober.
Hey, Dutch doesn't stand
a chance today?
Yeah.
Only one thing
missing, huh?
I know, Sam.
Yeah, I wish
Coach were here.
He is.
ANNOUNCER:
Attention, ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to...
Call me sentimental, but doesn't
this bring back the old days?
Yeah.
I want you to get
out there, Sammy,
grind him into a raw,
meaty pulp,
spread him on home plate
and slide into his guts.
(sobbing):
I've got to get a Kleenex.
Hey, Sam Malone.
Yeah.
Cap Richards.
I'm Dutch's
personal manager.
I cooked up this
whole thing.
Glad I got a chance
to talk to you.
Uh, here's how
it's gonna work.
Throw the first two pitches
however you want.
The third one, though,
just float it across home
plate, nice and easy.
Oh, what?
Yeah, I thought the home run
would be more dramatic
on the third pitch.
But if you want to do it
on the first pitch,
like you used to, go ahead.
You've gotta be kidding.
Sam Malone does not take a dive.
Yeah, I came down here
to strike this guy out
and that's what I'm gonna do.
You know, if he wants to get a
hit, he's gonna have to earn it.
Whoa, this is not good.
We have a special ceremony
in honor of...
You ready, Sammy?
Yeah.
...Dutch Kincaid.
I can strike this
guy out, can't I?
Of course you can.
Listen,
this is your chance
to make up for the old days.
It's the last thing
anyone's ever gonna remember
about Sammy Mayday Malone-- that
he struck out Dutch Kincaid.
Now go on out there
and smoke three fast ones
past that lousy
flat-headed bastard.
(sobbing):
I need to get another Kleenex.
Yeah? Huh?
Oh.
Excuse me,
are you Sam Malone?
Yeah.
Yeah. Wh-wh-what's your name?
Billy Kincaid.
How do you do, Billy?
Oh, now you wouldn't,
you wouldn't be a relation
to Dutch Kincaid would you?
He's my grandpa.
I've heard all his
neat stories about
how you used to help him
hit those long home runs.
I never got
to see one, though.
I sure hope I can see one today.
I may have to
disappoint you there.
This is the last time
Grandpa's ever going to play.
It's today or never.
Go away, will you?
Go on.
My two brothers and my baby
sister are all watching at home.
None of us ever saw him
hit a home run.
Give me a break, will you?
Grandpa told us he wants
to hit a ball so hard,
it'll go up to heaven,
so Grandma can say hello.
ANNOUNCER (over PA):
Now pitching, Sam Malone.
Yeah, all right.
Hey, how'd it go?
Great.
Need me to scalp
any tickets?
No, no, you've done
enough for today.
Thanks, Vinnie.
Hey, you guys aren't
supposed to be in here.
That's all right,
we're with Sam Malone.
Mm-hmm.
We're his personal trainers.
So you're okay down here?
(chuckles)
We know our way
around a dugout, pally.
Look out, Cliffy.
Incoming.
Boy, that ball girl's
really got an arm, huh?
Here you go, Toots.
Aw, Norm.
What?
Barbecue sauce got
all over the nachos.
Hey...
Hey, guys, did I
miss anything?
Sam hasn't started yet.
Oh.
Where you been?
Oh, I've been visiting
the other team.
I ran into somebody I used
to get hot and sweaty with.
Who's that?
The other team.
And now, stepping to the plate
to face Sam Malone,
the man we all turned out today
to honor...
Dutch Kincaid.
(applause)
Boo-o-o-o!
Hey, you guys, come on.
The first pitch.
Okay, Sammy go!
Go-go!
Come on, Sammy.
(ball thuds in mitt)
Oh, yeah!
Strike one!
Go, Sammy!
All right, Sammy.
Look at him out there.
Doesn't he look
cool on the mound?
Oh, I've got
goose bumps.
Yeah, all right,
here comes the stretch.
Hey, ram it down his throat,
Sammy!
Sammy, oh!
Come on, Sammy!
(ball thuds in mitt)
Oh, yeah!
Strike two!
(wild cheering)
Oh, yeah!
Bring on the
heat, Sammy!
He can't hit
what he can't see!
(loud crack)
Apparently,
he saw that one.
ANNOUNCER:
Look at that ball go.
It may clear
the center field fence.
It's going, going,
it's out of here!
(crowd cheering)
Poor Sammy.
Wow, he must feel lousy, huh?
Yeah, he's really gonna
need our support.
Well, we'll just have
to be really nice to him.
We can sneak out of here.
I know a shortcut
through the showers.
Better yet.
Too late.
He's seen us.
Okay.
I know what you're thinking.
But I can explain it.
I know it looked
like a home run.
Yeah, our first clue
was when the ball
actually left the stadium.
Yeah, but it doesn't count
'cause I did it on purpose.
All right.
Oh, sure, Sam.
You let him get a home run
off you on purpose.
No, no.
I did it for Kincaid's grandkid.
He wanted to see his grandfather
hit a home run, so...
Well, hell, he can
explain it to you.
Billy.
Yo, hey, Billy!
Oh, right, Sam.
Whatever you say.
We believe you.
Why are you
using that voice?
That's your "I don't
believe you" voice.
No it's not, Sam.
I do believe you.
Then why are you
still talking...
Oh, come on, listen,
Billy'll tell you everything.
Hey, Billy!
Come on, Billy!
Sam, Sam.
Come on.
Let's go home.
We get to go on
an airplane ride.
And maybe when we're up there,
we'll get to see that pitch
you served Dutch.
I'm telling you,
I did it on purpose.
I swear to God.
There was this kid...
Come on, Billy!
This isn't funny!
...78, 79...
If you keep moving
around, Spotty,
I'm not gonna be able
to get an accurate count.
One, two, three, four...
Woody.
five...
I guess you've given up
on finding his owner, huh?
Well, why don't you want me
to have this dog, Ms. Howe?
It's not that I don't want you
to have the dog, Woody,
it's just that
I have this... this thing
about being completely honest
when it comes to lost pets.
Okay, when I was
ten years old,
I had this beautiful
Persian cat named Princess.
She only loved me.
She didn't like anybody
else in my family.
One day I woke up,
Princess was gone.
My mom and dad said
that she got out
through the bedroom window.
The weird thing is,
I could have sworn
that bedroom window
was painted shut.
It bothered me for years.
Then as you matured,
you came to accept the fact
that it was your parents who,
in fact, got rid of the cat.
What?!
My Princess?!
They took my Princess?!
Oh, boy, me and my big mouth.
Why don't I just go down
to the park
and tell the little kids
about Santa Claus?
What about Santa?
But we do
believe you, Sam.
I'm getting tired
of that voice.
You know, I don't care
what you guys think.
In my heart,
I know I did this...
ALL:
...for a little boy
and his dead grandmother.
Oh, guys, look.
Spotty fell asleep
on my shoe.
He's so sweet.
I just wish
I was wearing sandals
so I could feel
his little puppy breath.
Hi, gentlemen.
What can I get you?
Just coffee.
We're on duty.
What's the matter?
Well, two weeks ago
our dog ran away.
Cutest little puppy
you ever saw.
He's just about so big.
Today, Chief made us
give up our search.
Oh.
Woody, I think they're
talking about Spotty.
Do you want
to say something?
No.
Make them go away.
Come on, Woody.
It is obvious that
it is their dog.
And give me a break,
a Dalmatian,
the fire department.
It's a different
dog, ratfink.
Just 'cause you lost
your stupid cat.
Remember when
he was born?
Oh-h-h-h.
We each took hour-long shifts
feeding him warm milk
through an eyedropper.
Remember how he used to
fall asleep on my shoe?
Yeah.
I can still feel his
warm little puppy breath.
(cries)
What is it?
Nothing.
Go away.
Isn't there a fire somewhere?
Oh, the heck with it.
I didn't want him anyway.
He's all covered with spots.
Hey-hey-hey...
Take him, I didn't know
he was yours, honest.
Thanks, kid.
Looks like you took
real good care of him.
Yeah.
You know, we had
a reward posted--
a hundred bucks.
Oh, I don't care
about the money.
I just want what's
best for Spotty.
Gee, I'm, sorry, kid.
Now, a ride on a real
fire engine might help.
We can't let you do that.
(cries):
I miss him so much!
All right, come on.
But don't tell anybody.
Yeah!
Hey, can I, can I
run the siren?
No, that would be illegal.
(cries):
Oh, geez, Spotty meant
everything to me!
All right, you can
turn on the siren.
Well, can I wear your hat?
It's part of the uniform.
Well, can I drive,
please, please?!
Here, take the dog.
Take the dog.
(crying)
We snowed 'em, dude.
Where's little Miss Malone?
In the office?
Haven't you humiliated him
enough?
Hey, not as much
as he humiliated me.
Hey, Malone...!
Pull on your pantyhose
and get out here.
We've got a score to settle.
Come on, Dutch.
You had your home run.
Why don't we just
leave it at that?
I'm not gonna leave it at that.
You deliberately
threw me a cream puff.
I don't need your
charity pitches.
I didn't do it for you.
I did it for your grandkid.
I don't have any grandkid.
What do you mean, you
don't have any grandkid?
Naw, my personal
manager and his kid
are always pulling
that scam.
That's how I got
Dutch Kincaid Day.
This was a setup?
I had a chance finally
to strike you out in front
of a stadium full of people
and I had to let it go
for a stupid, lousy setup?
You never had
a chance, Malone.
I can hit anything
you can serve up.
Oh, come on.
Give me a break.
My first two pitches
went right by you.
Well, I let them go by
for the drama.
Drama?
You let them go by
for the drama?
You want drama?
I'll give you drama.
Come with me, you, you,
come on, right now.
All right.
There's still plenty
of daylight out there.
Let's do it.
Yeah, well, I'll be back
in about three pitches, fellas.
Two grown men
settling a rivalry
by throwing a little white ball
at a wooden stick.
How pathetic.
Now, boxing...
that's a man's sport.
Punch a guy in the face
and scramble his brains.
That proves something.
Fras, you're coming
around, buddy.
Thank you.
Hey, shut up, you guys,
Sammy's pitching.
(crack)
Oh, my God,
there's two moons in the sky.
SAM:
All right, lucky hit.
Let's go again.
(crack)
Gee, he almost hit
a helicopter.
(crack)
SAM:
Okay, 226 lucky hits.
CARLA:
Hang in there, Sammy.
He's old.
He can't live forever.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/5yzq
Help other users to choose the best subtitles