Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
I got something to add
to the conversation.
If a 100-megaton warhead
detonated over the city
of Boston,
the results
would be so horrific
that the survivors
would envy the dead.
We weren't having
a conversation, Cliff.
Well! Then food for thought.
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Hi, guys.
Hey, there he is!
All right,
a star is born!
The man of the hour.
Oh, Woody!
Woody, you opened last night
in Arsenic and Old Lace.
Why didn't you tell me
so I could go?
I did tell you, Miss Howe.
I told you dozens
of times and I
sent you an invitation
with a cute,
little cartoon
of me drawn on it.
You said you were
going to be there
and I reserved a seat
for you in the front row.
Oh!
Then I was sick.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you feeling better?
Hmm, so-so.
Well, it's probably best
you didn't come last night.
I've still got
to iron out a few bugs.
CLIFF:
Well, all I can
tell you, Woody,
is that Ma loved the play.
Yeah, I mean, there's
something about the idea
of sweet old ladies being
cold-blooded murderesses.
Just seemed to tickle her
funny bone.
(laughs)
All the way home
she just laughed and laughed.
Matter of fact,
I woke up at 3:00 a.m.,
and there she was sitting in my
room in a rocking chair
rocking back and forth,
staring at me
and making this low,
guttural chuckle.
Boy, does she love the theater.
Hi, guys.
Carla, your
psychic called.
Madame Lazora called me?
Yeah, she's coming by today.
Madame Lazora is coming by?
Maybe she just wants
to say hello.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
You don't understand.
Madame Lazora does not
just say hello.
She must have had a horrible
premonition of me getting
hurt or killed or...
or pregnant.
Hmm.
Look, Carla, if you're
really concerned what this
charlatan has to say,
why don't you just call her?
Yeah, you're right, Doc.
I might as well just
get it over with.
Wait a minute.
What if she was calling me
to warn me to keep away
from telephones?
What if she's seen
a vision of me
horribly disfigured
in a telephone accident?
Carla, don't
be ridiculous.
Woody, you okay?
Oh, I don't know,
Mr. Peterson.
Uh, this is bad.
I can't breathe.
I can't move.
Hey, Woody, your review is out.
It is?!
Oh, boy! Oh, boy!
I can't wait to read it!
I'm gonna make copies
and send them to my mom!
Oh, here, here.
Here you read it, Mr. Peterson.
I'm too nervous.
Well, he likes it!
Hey!
"A charming romp."
"A charming
romp"!
He likes the cast.
"A deft ensemble."
Ooh, good!
"Deft ensemble."
Uh, what does
he say about me?
And he sort
of goes on and on.
No, no, go ahead, read it.
I can take it.
"Woody Boyd is weak."
"Weak"? Is that all?
Not handsome and weak?
Well, Woody, you know
what they say,
"There's no such thing
as bad press
as long as they spell
your name right."
Actually, it says
"Woody Doyb is weak."
Oh, Madame Lazora.
I sense the tortured anguish
of many lost souls
screaming for release.
Uh, that's probably me.
I had kielbasa
for breakfast.
Madame Lazora,
let me go
get Carla; she's gonna want to
see you right away.
She's been kind of worried.
I sensed she would be worried.
How did she know?
Amazing.
(burps)
Oh, Carla.
Darling, I must talk to you.
Please sit down.
Sam, just stay with me.
I'm really scared.
All right. Okay.
All right, here we go.
Just tell me it's going
to be quick and painless.
I don't understand.
You don't foresee a hideous
disaster in my future?
Of course I do, but
that's not why I'm here.
Oh, then why?
I have decided to retire
and move to Florida
at the end of the year.
I see myself
on Miami Beach
with those muscular
cabana boys.
See? I told you there's
nothing to worry about.
"Nothing to worry about"?
Madame Lazora has been
my spiritual advisor
since I was 17 years old.
Without her my life would've
been a complete disaster.
Honey, I thought your...
Well, it could
have been worse.
Sam, you're
smothering me here.
Get the lady a drink.
You...
I'd like a beer, please.
Oh, wow, she read my mind.
Madame Lazora,
if you retire,
what am I supposed to do?
Who am I going to turn to?
Who are all your clients
going to turn to?
You.
And why me?
Because Princess Katya
said it would be so.
Princess Katya said that?
(gasps)
Sam, did you hear that?
Princess Katya has
chosen me to take over
for Madame Lazora.
Ah.
Well, who's Princess Katya?
She's Madame Lazora's
spirit guide.
Her contact
from the other side.
Katya, she was a 17th-century
Romanian princess,
very much misunderstood
in her day.
The villagers hammered a mask
lined with spikes
onto her face and burned her
at the stake.
And to this day, that woman
still keeps her sense of humor.
Well, you, you've got
to admire that,
don't you?
Princess Katya thinks
I have spiritual gifts?
She knows.
And tonight,
when I return,
all the secrets
of the spirit world
will be revealed to you.
Well, why can't
we start right now?
I have to get
my teeth cleaned.
We all have many lives,
but only one set of teeth.
Whoa! I'm gonna be a psychic!
Who could have predicted that?
(Carla sighs)
I guess I better start
practicing.
Sam, I'm going
to read your mind.
Okay? Think of something.
Right now?
Yeah.
Okay.
CARLA:
You're thinking
about your car.
Nope.
You're thinking
about some babe.
Nope.
Oh, wait a minute.
Give me a minute.
I can do this.
Just give me a chance.
(sighs)
You're thinking
about your hair.
Nope.
Come on, Sam,
that's everything
you ever think about!
That's not true.
I think about other things.
Yeah? Like what?
Well, I was thinking
about what happened
at the end
of Planet of the Apes.
I fell asleep.
Uh, uh, Sammie,
Chuck Heston
found the decayed ruins
of the Statue of Liberty.
What are you saying?
You're saying he was
on Planet Earth the whole time?
Whoa!
Man, I wasn't even close.
I guess I'm just
fooling myself.
What a prize dork,
thinking I had the power.
Oh, come on,
just 'cause you
didn't get it
the first time?
Come on, let's do it again.
What's the use?
Come on, I wasn't
concentrating.
We both weren't concentrating.
Now, let's-- come on,
let's do it.
Okay. I'm going
to do it one more time.
Just... you've got
to just relax though,
Sam, okay?
All right, mmm.
I see something.
It's you.
And you're young.
And, uh, it's summer.
And there's an animal, a pet.
You had a pet,
didn't you, Sam?
Yeah, yeah, I did.
And you loved him very much.
Yeah, I did love him.
Suddenly this is
all so clear!
Frasier, I see you,
as a young boy,
reading all those books
and not having any friends.
Norm, I see you,
having lots of friends
and not reading any books.
And, Cliff, I see you.
(shudders)
Sam. Sam, there's more.
Yeah?
That pet...
It's a Labrador
named Sparkey!
And he's running to a woman.
It's your mother!
Her black hair is waving
in the wind!
Oh, my God!
This is so incredible!
Huh?!
Madame Lazora was right!
I am gifted!
I am a seer!
Marry that girl.
Quit that job!
I have the power!
How do you explain
that, Dr. Crane?
Why ask me, Woody? I mean...
Do I know something
that no one else knows?
I mean, we all saw
what we saw.
I mean, do you enjoy
having me explain
every little thing
that happens?
You know, I mean,
"Let's ask the
esteemed Dr. Crane.
Yeah, see, he'll know."
Well, I'm sorry, Woody.
I have no answer for you!
Frankly, I'm,
I'm downright scared.
To tell the truth, I got,
I got a little creeped out
when she got that dog's name.
Frasier, Frasier...
Calm down, man,
I, I lied.
I just didn't want
to hurt her feelings.
I knew that.
Sam, can I have
a, a scotch?
Oh, excuse me.
I'm-I'm looking
for Woody Boyd.
Oh, no!
What is it?
It's my director,
Lee Bradken.
Uh, is Woody Boyd here?
WOODY (quietly):
Tell him I'm not here.
I'm sorry, Mr.
Bradken, he's not here.
How did you know
my name was Bradken?
WOODY:
Tell him it was a lucky guess.
Lucky guess.
Who's that person
crouching by the side
of your leg?
WOODY:
Okay, give me a minute
on this one.
Woody, what do you mean
by saying you're not going
to do the show tonight?
Okay, I'm sorry,
Mr. Bradken.
You're too smart for me.
Not that my partner
gave me a lot of help.
It's just, I read that
scathing review, and I...
I just don't think I
can face an audience.
I'm not saying your performance
was weak, Woody,
but if it was-- and it was--
then maybe,
that's because, as an actor,
you're afraid to examine
your-your own feelings.
Here, I want you
to do an exercise.
Write down
your true feelings
as they come
to you, okay?
Now, how do you feel
right now?
I feel weak.
Not what other people
tell you to feel.
Do you really feel weak?
I feel strong.
Darned right you do.
And how do you feel
about that critic?
Am angry.
So? How are you gonna get even?
TP his house.
No.
By giving the best performance
you can give.
Look, I talked the critic
into coming back tonight, Woody.
If you can change his mind,
he'll say so
in tomorrow's column.
Now, Woody, how do you feel
about going on tonight?
Feel great!
And how do you feel
about your fellow actors?
Am better than
other actors.
Well, Woody...
Can direct better
than Bradken.
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey!
You've still got
a long way to go.
I'll see you tonight.
"Is jealous of my youth
and good looks."
Guys, it's gonna be so cool
being a spiritualist.
REBECCA:
Oh.
Poor Carla.
It's gonna break her heart
when she sees
that she can't read the future.
Well, she must be
able to, Miss Howe.
She filled out her time
card for the whole week.
She's gonna work 80 hours
between now and Friday!
That is eerie!
Are you ready to receive
the spirit of Princess Katya?
You bet I am.
I can't wait to quit
this penny-ante job
and start doing something
I'm more suited for.
Excellent. Now,
all we need
is a nice, quiet, dark place
where we won't be disturbed.
No problem. I'll clear
out the poolroom.
Good.
Hey, isn't that Michelle
Pfeiffer out front?!
(overlapping chatter)
And who's she with,
Kevin Costner?!
Where?!
Hey, Sammy?
Catch you later.
When you see
me again,
I'm gonna be
on a higher astral plane.
Yeah, wait.
Come... Wait.
Hold on a second here.
You're not... You're not serious
about quitting Cheers, are you?
Because if you are...
No, you don't
have to tell me.
I can read
your mind.
You're afraid that
we're gonna grow apart,
and we're not gonna
be friends anymore,
because I'll
be a psychic,
and you'll be a
lowly bartender.
Honey, you remember when
you-you were reading my mind?
Well you-you didn't get
as much right as you thought.
Oh, yeah? What
did I get wrong?
Everything.
But everything
was so clear!
Well, okay, maybe I
didn't read your mind,
but I was definitely
reading somebody's mind,
because those images
were as clear as day.
Come on, Carla.
Okay. All right.
Who here had a mother
with black hair
and a Labrador retriever?
Come on!
I can't be the only one!
Oh!
(sing-songy):
Carla!
Princess Katya
and I are waiting.
Madame Lazora,
I-I can't do this.
I'm sorry, but I am just not
cut out for this kind of stuff.
Are you telling me
that Princess Katya
and I are wrong?!
I'm telling you that
I don't have any
psychic powers.
I mean, I tried!
Problem is, you have no faith,
and without faith,
you are not worthy
to house the spirit
of Princess Katya.
I had such high hopes
for you,
but now you're nothing
but an empty disappointment.
Farewell forever, Carla!
(in deep voice):
Lazora, halt!
I am Princess
Katya.
I am inside Carla.
(normal voice):
Oh!
What happened?
Carla, you had faith,
and it happened!
It did?!
I did it!
Yes! Yes!
You're a natural!
And more and more, you will
be able to see the spirits
of the dead are
all around you!
And very soon, you will see them
lingering in the shadows
of this very bar,
just as I do.
Oh. That's just Lilith.
Everyone makes that mistake.
Oh.
All the tools you will need
are here in this carved box.
Precious crystals--
windows to the unseen future.
The tarot cards--
ancient diviners of fortune.
The I Ching coins--
symbols of Oriental wisdom.
The moist towelettes.
You get a lot of trade
off the street in this business.
(door bells tinkling)
MAN:
Hello? Hello?
(door closes)
What's that, a spirit?
No, no, no. That's Bob,
your first client.
I'll never forget
my first client.
Who was it?
Bob.
Madame Lazora, I-I'm
really not ready for Bob.
Oh, don't worry.
I'll be here with you.
There's just one more piece
of information
you need to fully understand
your mission here.
Look, Madame Lazora,
you don't understand.
I have a terrible
confession to make.
Back in the bar,
Princess Katya didn't
really enter my body.
I was just faking it so that
I wouldn't disappoint you.
I don't have any
psychic powers.
I am just an awful person.
I hope you don't hate me.
Oh, Carla, I'm
so proud of you
for having the courage
to be honest with me.
Oddly enough,
this relates
to the information I
was about to give you.
What's that?
I'm a complete fraud.
Now, we just have time to
work on your spooky voice.
What?
Your spooky voice.
You have to learn
to speak lower--
talk more
from the diaphragm.
You're a fraud?
All these years you've
been leading me on?
Hi.
Oh, hello, Bob.
I want you to meet
your new spiritual advisor--
Madame Carla.
Hello, Madame Carla.
Hello, Bob.
Madame Carla...
study Bob's aura.
Tell me,
what do you see?
Can you see
something?
Yeah, I can see something.
I can see that you're a sucker,
a big dope.
For 20 years you've
been forking over
your hard-earned cash
to a sleazy con artist.
You have been taken in
by the cheapest,
most obvious scam in the world
just because you wanted
to believe it.
I see that you
should wise up, chump.
(door closes)
That will be $50, please.
Yow, I wonder what's wrong
with Carla.
(chuckling):
We all know what's wrong
with Carla,
but I'm the only one
with enough courage to say it.
Not enough bran.
(Cliff yelps)
Hey, everybody.
Hey, Woody, how'd it go?
Oh, it was
a great performance, Sam,
and I actually got a chance
to talk to that
critic afterward,
and he said that
I was much improved.
Well.
There you go.
SAM:
Well, I can't wait
to go see you next week.
Oh, well, no, actually
I'm not in it anymore, Sam.
What happened?
Well, the other actors read
my notebook and got upset.
Well, Woody,
people can be very sensitive.
Well, I think they're being
a little oversensitive.
I mean, come on, Dr. Crane,
I mean, if you read
in my notebook
that you were a snobby,
know-it-all windbag,
would you be upset?
Yes, I probably would.
Oh.
(page tears)
(playing "Greensleeves")
I guess someone ought
to go talk to Carla, huh?
Allow me.
Carla, would you like
to talk about it?
No.
Well, then,
would you like me
to show you the correct
fingering for "Greensleeves"?
She's a fake.
Madame Lazora
is a fraud.
All these years she's
been nothing but a fake.
I am sorry, Carla.
I don't suppose this
is an appropriate moment
to say "I told you so."
No, this is the perfect
moment to say it.
I told you so.
I can't believe it.
I know I can, but then
again, I did tell you so.
All right, just give
me a minute to wallow.
I'm sorry.
I mean, if
she's a fake,
then everything's a fake
and everything
I ever believed in is wrong.
I guess that's it.
I've got nothing left.
Game over.
Carla, Madame Lazora
is just one individual.
Don't give her
the power
to destroy
your entire belief system.
You know,
the mystic world
that's given you so much
comfort may very well exist.
You don't really believe that.
Of course I do.
Although if, if it doesn't
I-I'm logging in right now
to say "I told you so."
The truth is,
no one knows.
What's your point?
That you should profit
from this experience.
You've graduated
from Madame Lazora.
You've become
a stronger Carla--
a smarter Carla--
one who's learned.
You want to know
what I've learned?
I've learned
that a woman
with a funny voice and some
fancy scarves can charge
any stupid idiot 50 bucks
just to tell him
what he wants to know.
Hey.
What is it, Carla?
I got a scarf.
(in deep voice):
I can do a spooky voice.
Now, now, Carla.
Gather around,
everybody,
and I will tell you of
the future for 50 bucks.
Carla, no.
You're right.
60 bucks.
Gather around,
gather around.
Thanks, Fras.
Well...
I guess my work here is done.