Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Hey, everybody!
I have a great new way
to promote the bar.
( others groaning )
REBECCA:
No, no, no, no,
you're gonna like this one;
it's different.
It not only demonstrates
social concern,
but it is also
contemporary and hip.
Now, Cheers is the bar
that cares.
Therefore,
if you are not in condition
to drive yourself home,
we will appoint
a designated driver,
free of charge.
Oh, that's nice,
that's really nice.
So is anybody a little tipsy?
Come on,
don't be ashamed.
Does anybody feel
that they might have
the slightest difficulty
driving themselves home?
I might.
Well, hi. I'm Rebecca Howe.
And I would be happy to
drive you home myself.
That's very nice of you.
Where do you live?
Philadelphia.
Well, what's
your address?
Eh, it's a blue house;
I'll know it when I see it.
( inaudible )
( piano plays )
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody knows
your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ¶
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Frasier?
It's time to take mother
to her hair appointment.
Oh, well,
then we'd better hurry up
before they run out
of her special shade of blue.
Frasier, how many times
have mother and I asked you
to cease and desist
with the snide, cliché,
battle-axe,
mother-in-law jokes?
You know mother's
not like that.
You're right,
dear, I'm sorry.
Uh, I was just trying
to amuse my friends.
Geez, it wasn't
very funny.
CLIFF ( chuckles ):
Well, you-you know
what was funny,
when you said you could hear
her perfume coming a mile away.
NORM:
Yeah, yeah, or the one where
you said, uh, she's
had so many facelifts,
if she wants to smile,
she has to cross her legs.
Lilith, you understand,
it was all in-in good
humor, you know.
Of course.
You know I have
a sense of humor
about mother.
Now, say good-bye
to your friends.
You're grounded for six weeks.
Shoot!
Hey, Sam.
Hey, Woody, what's new?
Well, nothing much.
Oh, your car alarm's
going off.
What? Someone's
breaking in my car
and you don't run in here
to tell me?
We're not talking
about any car here, man,
we're talking about my 'Vette!
It's a classic,
it's irreplaceable!
Hey, why don't you come
in and sit down here.
Sam, what about your alarm?
Well, you're taking care of
that, Woody, aren't you?
I was?
Oh, I must be off
in another world.
Sammy's done it again.
How come he always spots
the gorgeous ones first?
'Cause he doesn't spend
all his time peeling
dead skin off his elbows?
What, are you gonna
do it for me?
So, how can I help you?
I'm looking for Becky Howe.
Wow, well, Becky'll
be here in a minute.
In the meantime, can
I interest you in a...
Sam Malone?
No, thanks.
But I will have
a Perrier with lime.
Ah.
Sworn off the hard stuff, huh?
Coming right up.
Sam.
Yeah?
It was nothing.
Oh, thanks.
Hey, listen, you know that girl
you were talking to?
Yep.
I swear I've seen her
someplace before.
Well, she asked for Rebecca.
Called her Becky.
Must be old friends.
Yeah, that could explain a lot.
What's that supposed to mean?
CLIFF:
Well, figure it out.
Rebecca, who doesn't date,
suddenly has this
good-looking friend show up.
A slender, boyish,
female friend,
with whom she probably, uh,
sunbathed nude somewhere,
perhaps on the Isle of Lesbos.
They ever get the tests back
on that dog that bit you?
So, uh, where do you
know Becky from?
She's my sister.
I'm Susan Howe.
You're sisters?!
Well, of course!
God, I love sisters!
I love the whole idea
of sisters.
Well, any sister
of Rebecca is a...
Are there any
more of you?
Uh, afraid not.
Well, no, that's...
You're more than enough.
( laughs ):
Oh, wow!
( whispers ):
Sam, come here.
Let me tell
you something.
Excuse me. What?
I just remembered who she is.
That's Susan Howe.
I know, she's
Rebecca's sister.
No, the actress-- I saw her
in Night of the Mutants.
What, is that a movie,
or your family reunion?
A movie, Carla.
I don't remember, uh,
Rebecca saying anything
about having a sister who
was in a horror movie.
Are you sure about that?
Let me check.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
You know, if she had
another, smaller head
growing out of her neck,
I'd be positive.
I got to check this out.
Hey, ask her if
they let her keep
the little head.
Sorry about that.
Uh, bar business.
So, what brings you to Boston?
I'm shooting a bank commercial.
Oh, I was right!
You are Susan Howe,
the actress.
I loved you in that
two-headed movie.
Oh, which one?
I did two of them.
Was it the one where the head
was coming out of my neck?
Uh, yeah, that's the one.
Oh, thank goodness,
because the other one
I am not proud of.
Oh.
Well, so, you're, uh,
you're here to see Becky, huh?
How long has it been
since the two of you
saw each other?
Ooh, it must be three years.
We had a little... falling out.
I only hope we're grown up
enough now to kiss and make up.
Grown-up sisters,
kissing and making up.
That warms my cockles.
( chuckles )
Let's get you two gals
back together, shall we?
Will you excuse me
just a minute here?
CLIFF:
So, uh, what's the bone, Jerome?
Any late-breaking
bulletins here?
Yeah, oh, yeah.
I think I'm on to something
here, fellas.
Carla, you hate your
sister, don't you?
Sure, why?
Well, what would I have to do
to get the two of you
back together again?
Simple, Sam, ask me to come down
and identify her body.
She's missing the point.
Can you imagine what
the reward might be
for anybody who would act as
a peacemaker between these two
tragically estranged
but perky-bottomed sisters?
Ah...
To Sammy, the man who
keeps the dream alive.
CARLA:
Wait a minute.
What makes you think you
can get the both of them?
It's taken you two years
to get a polite kick in
the teeth from number one.
( chuckling ):
Carla, Carla, Carla.
Am I gonna have to teach you
about women?
Yeah, Cliff, why don't you?
Nah, you better take
this one, Sammy.
I don't want to hog
the spotlight.
Carla...
I know you don't have a lot
of experience with this,
but sometimes women
get... really happy.
And when that happens,
they get all emotional
and vulnerable.
And that's when it's time
for a fella like me,
who's very sensitive
and caring, to move in
and give new meaning to the
words, "triple-decker Sam-ich."
NORM:
Hey, hey!
CLIFF:
Hey!
All right!
So, Cliff...
Huh?
tell me more about women.
Well, all right here, uh...
They're warm and soft, and...
( sighs )
...when they wash their cars,
they're dressed
in nothing but suds,
a suntan and a cowboy hat.
Sorry, I must have drifted away
there for a second.
( sighs ):
So...
Oh, whoa, wait,
wait, wait.
I've got a
surprise for you.
Sam, move your hand; your
cologne is stinging my eyes.
Come here, come here,
there's someone waiting
to see you, and
you're never gonna
guess who it is.
Careful, careful.
You are gonna love this.
Ta-da!
Susan.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see you.
Well, now
you've seen me.
Yep, yep, there you are.
Boy, oh, boy,
is this a moment.
Yeah, I was here on a job,
and I thought I'd drop in
and say hello.
Hello.
Good-bye.
Fine, I tried.
You are obviously
not interested.
Obviously.
No, no!
Wait, wait, wait a minute.
Come back here.
Listen, listen.
You know what's happening here,
you're both so excited
to see each other that you're
getting all tensed up here.
I think what we need to do
is put ourselves
into a little bit
of a more relaxed situation.
I know this hot tub club
where we can get
group rates.
I'm kidding,
I'm kidding about that.
What we should do is,
we should go upstairs,
and we should have lunch
at Melville's.
Just the three of us.
What do you say? My treat.
Well, I did come here
to make up.
Huh?
I did skip breakfast.
All right!
That's the spirit!
Family! That's what made
this country great.
Come on.
Sam...
Yes?
why are you so
desperate to see my
sister and I make up?
I mean, what
is it to you?
Is this another stupid
ploy to get me into bed?
Oh, come on, Rebecca,
don't be ridiculous!
I'm thinking of both of you.
This is nice.
Rebecca, I can't finish
my filet.
Do you want the rest?
Why, do you want me to get fat?
Oh, come on,
you have not been fat
since you were 12 years old.
Of course, you were
the Goodyear blimp then.
At least when I gave
my "I am an American" speech
at the Flag Day assembly,
I did not wet myself.
Rebecca, I was six.
But she did, Sam, she did.
Shut up.
You shut up.
No, you shut up.
No, you shut up!
Shut up...!
This is nice.
You know, I really don't think
this was such a good idea, Sam.
And I hope you'll
excuse me, Susan,
if I don't clean
your table scraps.
Oh, wait a minute, sit down,
will you, pl...?
Girls, girls, girls,
what is the big problem
between you two anyway?
Sam, it is one of those
complicated issues
that you can't just pin down
into one certain thing.
Well, try.
( sighs ):
All right.
Dan Buddinger.
Mike Dietz, Jeff Carnahan,
Ron Allen, Steve
Melman, Terry Toban,
Clay Fisher...
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Does this have anything to do
with boy trouble?
Yes. The trouble is, she can't
keep her hands off my boys.
If it bothered you that much why
didn't you just take them back?
Because I didn't want to stoop
to your level!
Besides, I tried
and it didn't work.
Look, the point is,
that was back when we were kids.
A million things have changed.
No, no, no,
the fact still remains
that every time
I am attracted to a guy,
you are on him
like white on rice.
So excuse me if I
don't leap over there
and say forgive me,
please, please, please,
for breaking
my heart over
and over and over and over.
Excuse me,
I have to get out of here.
I have work to do.
Sam, I'm sorry
you had to see that.
Well, that's okay.
I don't think it was
fair for Rebecca to say
that you tried to
steal every guy she
ever got interested in.
But I'm warning you
right now, missy,
you better not
try that with me.
Oh, Rebecca's interested in you?
Are you kidding me?
She's got a big old
crush on me.
Well, I am glad to see
she hasn't lost her good taste.
Well, that's very sweet
of you to say that.
More wine?
This is nice.
This is very nice.
I snuck out of the house.
So don't tell Lilith.
Gee, where's Sam?
Oh, he'll be
here any minute.
He's still up having lunch with
Miss Howe's sister, Miss Howe.
Oh, you mean Rebecca's sister's
in town.
Susan Howe,
the, uh, movie star.
You mean, the Susan Howe,
the star of
Night of the Mutants?
Wow.
You saw it?
Well, yes. Lilith and I
rented it last week.
Oh, really?
You two don't seem
the slasher-movie type.
Oh, well, purely for scientific
purposes of course.
But, you know,
this may surprise you--
I rather enjoyed it.
See, I think films with scenes
of graphic disembowelment
and mutilation
can, in some cases,
help people to,
well, release some of the fears
and aggressions
of modern society.
Also, it's the first time
Lilith's mother
went home before 9:00...
screaming.
Hey, everybody.
Oh, Miss Howe, I'm
Dr. Frasier Crane.
My wife and I
rented your film
Night of the Mutants
last week, and, uh,
well, I was wondering, um...
could I have your autograph?
Ah...
Sure.
Thank you.
Uh, I tell you what,
just make it out to
"Mother Sternin."
And say, if you would,
"I know where you live
and I'm going to get you."
Hey, Sammy, Sammy, Sammy,
what's the skinny, huh?
Yeah, what's the score?
Two to one?
Guys, guys,
I know I've accomplished
some truly legendary
feats in my day,
but this...
this is my masterpiece.
This is my Moaning Lisa.
( chuckling )
Okay, tell me:
what's the plan
and how are we involved?
Well, here it is
and you're not.
Turns out that these two sisters
are very competitive--
especially when it come to guys.
So all I had to do was
let the little one know
that the big one
had the hots for me
and bingo, she was eating
out of my hand.
Was she wearing
a cowboy hat?
It's a figure of speech,
Cliffie.
Well, she could have been.
What I need to do now
is make sure
that the big one knows that
the little one is interested
and I will be ping-ponging
between the two of them
until they bury me
with a smile on my face.
( chuckling )
No, please stop.
I'm too young to die.
( screams )
Breathtaking!
Thanks. You guys
are a great audience.
What'd I miss?
Have you had her scream for you,
Sam?
Later, Woody. Later.
Okay, uh, let's
see, the plan is
that I meet you back here
at closing time, right?
Yeah, can't wait.
Yeah.
See you then.
Oh, boy.
Yeah, it's not fair.
All the chicks
in that family
are loaded
with great faces,
hair, bods.
What'd my family get?
Look at the bright
side, Carla.
Probably takes them hours
to get ready every morning,
whereas you look
the same with or
without makeup,
and your hair
practically combs itself.
Thanks, Woody.
Never hurts to spread
a little sunshine.
( knocking on door )
Hi.
So, what is it?
Well, um, I don't...
I don't want
to get in the middle
of a family squabble, but...
your sister
just asked me out.
She what?!
Yeah, is that the craziest
thing, or what?
She obviously thinks
that I'm attracted to you.
Oh, come on,
why would she think that?
I don't know;
did you say something?
Me? Come o...
What would I have to gain
by saying something like that?
Man, this makes
me so furious!
She comes out here
and she says that she's sorry
and she wants to make up for it,
and then the second
my back is turned,
she comes onto the guy
she thinks is my boyfriend.
If there's just something
you could do
to get back at her.
What could we do,
what could we do,
what could we do?
Did you say that you'd
go out with her?
Yeah, but I could kick myself
for that.
That was perfect.
Sit down here a second.
You know how you've always
wanted to go out with me?
Yeah.
Well, now your wish is
going to come true.
You break that date
with my sister,
and I will go
out with you.
Oh. Oh, boy.
That is vicious,
but she asked for it.
And, Sam?
Yeah?
Thank you.
Oh, you kidding me?
Come on,
what are friends for?
( register rings )
Well, fellas...
at this very moment,
Rebecca Howe is in her house
spending two hours
getting into an outfit
she's going to spend two minutes
getting out of.
Hey, what are you going to
do about that sister, huh?
Oh, I already made a phone call
to postpone our date.
Oh, you going to take her out
tomorrow night?
No, I'm going to take her out
in a couple of hours.
No, don't worry.
We'll be back here
in the morning
for our usual debriefing.
By that time, I'll be able
to compare and contrast them.
And that's when this stuff
gets really interesting.
Yeah.
Sammy?
Yeah?
Sorry I was a little hard
on you before, but you know,
I was just trying
to make you reach.
Push out the edges
of the envelope.
CLIFF:
We're all proud
of you, Sammy.
God bless you on this night,
Sam Malone.
Oh. At la...
Susan.
Oh, Sam,
I know
you put off our date,
but I just couldn't wait
to see you.
You're all I've been
thinking about today.
Is there someplace private
we can go
for a few minutes where I can...
touch you and hold you?
Um, usually I go
for this stuff in a big way,
but at the moment...
I'm in a little bit
of a time jam here.
Oh, I'm so in the mood.
And I am so good
when I am in the mood.
Would you excuse me
for a second?
I got to make a
quick phone call.
I'll be right back.
Oh, come on, Rebecca, pick up,
pick up, pick up, please.
Pick up, pick
up, pick up.
As long as you're not going
to be talking with those lips...
( groaning )
( provocative chuckle )
( both moaning and chuckling )
Oh...
( both continue moaning )
Sam, I'm ready
for our date.
Susan!
Uh, Rebecca, I
can explain this.
Wait, just... Ow.
My finger's caught
in your bra.
Listen...
You don't owe me
an explanation.
It's Susan.
It's always been Susan.
My entire life,
it has been Susan.
I'm glad you saw us.
You deserve to be hurt.
Oh, no, sister.
Come on.
I don't hurt anymore;
I am way beyond hurt.
Don't be silly, now, girls,
please, please.
And now it is Susan Howe's turn
to hurt.
( gasping )
Hey, that's a gun.
It ain't licorice.
No, come on, let...
Let's talk about this.
Now, this is silly.
No, please,
I'm too young to die.
Rebecca.
( Susan screaming )
( gunshot )
Oh...!
Holy cow!
That was for Dan Buddinger.
And this is for Jeff Carnahan.
( gunshot )
Oh...!
And Mike Dietz.
( gunshot )
And Sam Malone.
( three gunshots )
Oh, boy, oh, boy!
What did...?
What is it, Sam?
Oh!
What, because I killed
my sister?
Uh-huh!
I didn't mean to do that anyway.
Oh, well, it's done.
All right...
we got to get this
body out of here.
Wha...? Wha...?
You got to help me, Sam;
come on.
Come on, take a hold of her.
Come on.
Oh...!
Everybody does at least one
bad thing in their life.
Sam, take her hands.
There.
All right, now, make
sure nobody sees us.
( whimpering )
Stop being a baby!
Oh!
Oh, boy, oh, boy...
Move.
ALL:
Sammy!
She did it.
Boy, Sammy, when you said
you were going to knock 'em off
one at a time,
you were serious.
Oh, no, no,
no, you don't understand.
I mean, she... she's real...
I'm dead.
( gasps )
( laughter )
( laughter continues )
That wasn't funny.
I mean, that's the kind of thing
that could, you know,
give somebody
serious mental damage.
Am I right, Lilith?
No, it was funny, Sam.
( laughter continues )
Susan, Susan, you
were so good.
Wasn't Susan good?
SUSAN:
You were pretty good
yourself.
Sam, are you all right?
I'm hurt.
I'm hurt and I'm...
I'm offended.
And quite frankly,
I can't believe
that you two think that
this is some sort of silly joke.
Am I right, Norm?
( laughing ):
Yeah.
I'm never going to
speak to either
one of you again.
Oh, Sam, that's really too bad,
because you know, in a way,
fending off your stupid advances
brought Susan and I
back together.
We haven't been
this close since
we were kids.
We're grateful.
How grateful?
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org