Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Whoa, Cliffie,
new Weekly Gabber
I see, huh?
Yeah, you betcha.
Look at this headline here.
"Suicidal Twin Kills
Brother by Mistake."
Oh, Cliff,
you don't actually believe
that pack of lies, do you?
Well, Dr. Crane, it just
shows you how much you know
about free press
here in America.
I mean, uh, they can't print it
unless it's the truth.
Well, granted, you know,
some of these stories
might be a bit exaggerated,
but, uh, I guarantee you
at the core of each
is the kernel of truth.
Allow me to demonstrate.
Hey, hey.
Come here, fella.
Listen, I just won
five bucks in the lottery.
Pass it on, will ya?
Thanks a lot.
The truth
has begun its journey
now around the bar.
When it returns, it
may be a little bit
distorted, you know.
People will be saying
I won $500,
maybe $5,000,
maybe five million dollars,
but I guarantee you
the essence of the message
will be the truth.
Hey, Norm, get this.
Some geek brain's
all jazzed
because he just won
five bucks.
Touché.
( piano plays )
¶ Making your way
in the world today ¶
¶ Takes everything you've got
¶ Taking a break
from all your worries ¶
¶ Sure would help a lot
¶ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ¶
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You want to be where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ You want to go
where people know ¶
¶ People are all the same
¶ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ¶
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
Listen up, everyone.
One of the most influential
reviewers in the city
has been going around
to different bars in the area
reviewing them.
Need I say more?
Yes.
Woody, in case
he comes in here,
I want everybody
on his best behavior.
Aw, gee, does this mean
we're going to have to cancel
the midget tossing contest?
Sam, please don't
joke about this.
This really means
a lot to me.
Oh, don't worry
about it.
I'm sure
we'll do great.
As long as the reviewer
doesn't happen to be
that SOB Murray Treadwell.
You remember him?
Well, I'm not saying it is,
but what if it were?
Well, then you better
kiss your butt good-bye.
Actually, that sounds
more like a job for me,
doesn't it?
What's the matter
with him?
He's a hater.
The guy hates everybody.
I hate people like that.
Yeah.
He gave Cheers
a really bad review
a couple years ago.
Really bad.
I almost stopped
coming here.
What did he say?
A bar full of bores.
Yeah, oafish clientele.
Dumb lug of a bartender.
Well, we're under
new management here.
A lot of things have changed.
Like what?
We have ferns.
Didn't he say
anything nice?
Yes, as a matter of fact,
he said
the one saving grace was
the refreshing lack of ferns.
You guys are just
trying to rattle me.
With the changes I've instituted
and with Carla locked
in the storage closet,
everything's going to be fine.
86 the ferns, Woody.
Hi, guys.
Oh, Carla, Eddie called
and said he got a job
as a penguin.
Great!
Hey, did you hear that,
everybody?
My husband just hooked on
with the Pittsburgh Penguins.
Hey, that's great.
Pittsburgh-- they're an
up-and-coming club, huh?
I'd say Eddie LeBec is
on his way to becoming a legend.
Gee, Cliff, what a great thing
to say, thanks.
I meant every word of it, Carla.
( clears throat ):
Can Eddie get us tickets?
You know, what I like
best about that team...
What?
is their uniforms.
I mean, the Penguin uniforms
are far and away
the coolest in the league.
Hey,
everybody!
Eddie?
Who else could it be?
Wow, Carla, are their home
uniforms that neat-looking too?
Hey, Carla, listen.
It's been breaking me up,
you know, not being able
to find work,
not being able to
support you and the kids.
It's like I was
losing myself as a man.
Well, now, you know,
I got a job.
Aren't you proud of me?
Eddie, take off
your beak.
This is a joke, right?
You're with Pittsburgh.
Pittsburgh?
No, I'm with
the Wonderful World of Ice.
You know,
that big ice show.
They're hiring lots
of hockey players like me.
Hey, at least you
won't have to worry
about renting
a tux, Eddie.
( chuckling )
Yeah, what are they
paying you, Ed?
Seven, eight fish a day?
Hey, you guys, knock it off.
He's got himself an honest job.
He gets paid.
He, um...
come on, help me
out here, man.
All right, all right.
Can it, you clowns.
You know, a lot of people
criticize hockey players.
They say they're
wasting their time.
After their careers
are over
they're not prepared
for anything.
Well, my Eddie just
proved them wrong.
Thank you, Carla.
You walked around in
public in that thing?
I thought you'd get
a kick out of it.
Listen, uh, Carla,
I got to fly
to Seattle tomorrow.
You can't fly in
that thing, can you?
No, Woody, I'm going
on an airplane.
I know, I mean you're not going
to fly in that thing, are you?
Seattle?
I just...
I can't believe
you're going to be
that far away.
It won't be that long.
Look, I'll call you
every day.
Hey, maybe you want
to come out and see me, huh?
Yeah. Yeah, well...
you know, it's really
a long way, Eddie.
We'll talk about it
tonight, okay?
What do you want
for dinner?
I don't know.
I kind of got the urge
for mackerel.
Gee, I'm sure going
to miss you, Carla.
Well, who wouldn't?
You know, not to be
overly sentimental,
but you're the best
husband I ever had.
I'll see you, Carla.
Yeah, see ya...
Penguin.
I wonder where couples get
those cute little names
they call each other.
Well, soon.
Eddie, look, I just can't
fly out of here.
Are you forgetting
I got seven kids?
Oh, right, eight.
Look, look, I'd love to
talk to you some more,
but Sam's calling me.
What?
( stamps )
Ow!
Be right there, Sam.
Okay, I'll talk to you
tomorrow then, bye.
Hey, uh, Carla,
I couldn't help but notice
that Eddie calls you
every single day
asking you to go out there,
and you just keep
giving him the brush-off.
I mean, hey, what gives here,
little lady?
Drop it.
Or I'll set
your face on fire
and beat out the flames
with your butt.
Well, does that satisfy
your curiosity, Cliff?
Totally.
But it does raise
a series of other questions.
Hey, hey, hey.
That restaurant
critic guy's here.
Where?
Right over
there, see?
Oh, my God.
How do I look, Sam?
You've got a little drool
on the corner of
your mouth there.
No, no, no, leave it.
I think I better
go see what he wants.
No, relax.
Carla's got it.
Oh, my God!
Carla, you don't mind, do you?
Not at all.
When you're through,
there's a table
of six in the corner.
Hello.
You're Murray Treadwell,
aren't you?
Yes, and you must be one
of the Flying Wallendas.
No, I'm Rebecca Howe.
I'm the new manager here.
I hope you enjoy
your visit here.
Oh, I'm sure I will.
Would you like a drink?
That seems vaguely appropriate.
I'll get it.
You probably want
something specific.
How about a vodka martini?
Excellent choice.
Anything special?
Stirred, shaken, two olives?
A little sword?
I'd like it today.
Coming right up.
Vodka martini for Mr. Treadwell
and make it snappy.
Oh, no, that's the one drink
I don't know how to make.
Things seem to be
going very well.
Yeah, just make sure
he gets a napkin.
We only lost about
a thousand points
on that last time.
As if it would have
really killed him
to use
the paper towels.
Thank you, Sam.
Here you go, Mr. Treadwell.
Notice the cocktail napkin.
There's plenty more
where that one came from.
Mm, very nice.
Yes, we make
a good martini here.
Oh, that, too.
Very sweet of you.
Do you have any questions
about Cheers?
Actually, I do.
But, unfortunately,
I'm running a little bit late.
Would you, by any chance
be free for dinner tonight?
Dinner?
Yes, it's the third meal
of the day.
We could find somewhere
nice and quiet
where we wouldn't be disturbed.
Uh... I don't know.
You know,
the more time
you and I spend together,
the happier I think
you'll be with the review.
Will you excuse me a minute?
I just want
to check my schedule.
He wants me to have
dinner with him.
That means he
expects something
for a good review.
I'll get the petty cash.
Sam.
He wants me to
compromise myself.
Honey, we all do.
Why do I even
talk to you?
I'm not going to make
a big deal of this.
It's just going to be
another business dinner.
That's all.
Everything will be fine.
Listen to me.
Listen.
If, uh, one thing should
lead to another tonight
and you wake up
in the morning
and find out
you done something
you wish you hadn't,
I just want you to know,
I'd love to take you
out tomorrow night.
So I stand by
my original review,
"the Hungry Heifer
is a trough."
Okay, fine.
But listen, if you can find
a better 25-ounce steak
for $1.99, pal,
you just let me know,
all right?
I'd be happy to have
dinner with you tonight.
Great, I'll pick you up
at 7:00.
Terrific.
I'll see you then,
Mr. Treadwell.
Please, call me Murray.
All right, all right,
sure thing, Eddie.
Okay, listen, break a wing.
( chuckles )
I know, I know, I know,
you hate those jokes.
Listen, just keep
a stiff upper beak.
( laughs )
I'm sorry.
All right, bye-bye,
bye-bye.
Oh, heck.
That was your husband
on the phone there, Carla.
Why was he calling you?
Well, he's upset.
He wanted me to ask you,
find out why, you know,
you won't go see him.
How can I, Sam?
I can't afford
a plane ticket to Seattle.
Well, now I could
loan you the money.
Great.
But who could get
the time off?
If it's for the sake
of your marriage,
I'm sure we could
work something out.
If you'd like to take
a leave of absence
for say, a year,
that would be fine.
I-I really, I don't know
why everybody thinks
I could just
pick myself up and go.
I got two newborn babies.
Take them.
Tykes fly free.
Yeah, usually in the
seat right next to me.
Look, I can't go,
so let's just drop it, okay?
Geez.
Just came up
for a drink order.
Carla, Eddie's afraid that
you're ashamed of him.
Well, I'm not.
Well, tell him.
Don't tell me.
I will!
The minute he gets back.
You're not afraid to fly,
are you, Carla?
Me? Afraid to fly? Me?
( laughing )
( cackling )
( maniacal laughter )
( laughing )
Well, it must be something.
I am not afraid to fly.
I'm not!
I'm afraid to crash.
MAN:
Did you have
a bad experience...?
Yes, I did!
First time in an airplane.
It was on my honeymoon
with Nick.
We're going to New York--
short flight, no problem, right?
Well, suddenly, the plane
hits turbulence, right?
Me and Nick were thrown
all around that bathroom.
I haven't flown since.
Sweetheart, that
was just one time.
I mean, look at me.
When I was playing ball,
I must have flown
200,000 miles,
and I don't remember
anything happening.
'Cause you were
always drunk.
Damn right.
Good afternoon.
Hey.
Oh, hey, Frasier.
Yeah. You're just the man
I'm looking for here.
You looking for my camaraderie,
Sam,
or do you want some
free psychiatric advice?
Uh... that
free thing there.
Good.
Come on. What do
you say, Carla?
Oh, no way, Sam. Uh-uh.
I like my head this size.
Just keep him away from me.
He's the only
shrink we know.
Oh, stop, Sam.
You're embarrassing me.
What's the problem?
Well, Carla wants
to visit Eddie
on the West Coast,
but she's
afraid to fly.
Well, do you mean,
by afraid to fly, what?
Um... she's claustrophobic,
agoraphobic, or acrophobic?
Death-o-phobic.
Well, you know, Carla,
I've done a lot
of reading lately
about fear of flying.
I've always wanted
to conduct a workshop
for people with your problem.
I'm sure I could scare up
a few people like you.
Oh, no pun intended.
None noticed, I am sure.
No way, Frasier.
I am not going to
wind up in your office,
strapped to some table
with electricity shot
through my head.
Carla, that's not
part of the therapy.
Oh, yeah? What about Diane?
Now, look. I never
treated Diane
with any kind
of shock inducement.
Of course,
now I wish I had.
No, no. The key
to this therapy,
you see, is, uh...
desensitization.
Over a period
of sessions,
we slowly break
down your fears
until you're ready
to get on a plane.
And, at the end,
we all take
an actual flight.
Yeah? Well,
fly this, Orville.
( phone ringing )
Cheers.
EDDIE:
Hey, Sam.
Oh, hey, Eddie.
Long time
no hear. Yeah.
How you doing?
Oh, the show? It's okay.
It's kind
of a hockey players' reunion.
Listen.
Did you talk to her, Sam?
I mean, what did she say?
No, listen. The problem, Eddie,
is not that
she's afraid to see you.
It's that she's afraid to fly.
Carla, afraid?
Carla's not afraid
of anything, Sam.
See, that's
just an excuse.
I mean, she's
ashamed of me.
You know
something?
It's just
not working.
I'm going to quit.
No, wait.
Hold on. Hold on.
Listen, he's so sure
you're ashamed of him
that he wants to quit.
Really?
Yes.
Give me this phone.
Eddie?
I'm coming to see you.
I'll be there in about a week.
Really?
Aw, gee, Carla.
I got the biggest smile
you ever saw on my face.
I wish you could see me.
Eddie?
Before we take off,
I'd like to commend you.
It's been an
intense week,
but here we are, finally,
at the end of our journey.
Or should I say, perhaps
the beginning of the end
of our journey.
I guess
we're all set.
Let's get this show on the road.
Dr. Crane, uh...
I... I hope you don't mind.
I brought along a little
Saint Christopher's medal.
Oh. Well, no.
If that helps you, that's fine.
Oh, great.
Anybody else want one?
Now, now, Carla.
All religious artifacts
must be stored
either below the seat
in front of you
or in the overhead bin.
There, now.
Isn't this fun? Huh?
Now...
we're going to take off
in a few minutes,
so what should we all be doing?
People?
Well, we should be focusing
on our happy place.
That place where
we most like to be...
where we're most relaxed.
Can you see it?
Excuse me, sir.
We'll be taking
off shortly.
Would you
please sit down?
Oh, yes, of course.
Just a moment.
All right, now,
you're in your happy place.
Hmm?
You're at peace with the world.
( engines roaring )
Oh, God.
Now, just stay
in your happy place.
If it's the beach,
just imagine
that that sound
is the gentle rippling
of the water.
Carla,
where's your
happy place?
On the floor of my stomach,
clutching the earth
with both hands.
Good. Good!
Oh! Uh... Dr. Crane...
I've forgotten
where my happy place is.
I think yours
was in the Berkshires.
Oh, yes.
Mine is in
the Berkshires.
Look, everybody can be
in the Berkshires if they like.
The Berkshires is an expansive
and wonderful wooded wonderland.
That's going to go up
like a Roman candle
when this baby
crashes into it!
MAN:
Ladies and gentlemen,
we've been cleared for takeoff.
So please, sit back, relax.
Thanks for flying with us.
Did he say, "Thanks
for dying with us"?
Just relax.
I'll be sitting
right here beside you.
If you're a little nervous,
go ahead and grab on to me.
Afternoon, everybody.
MEN:
Norm! Norm! Norm!
What's the story, Mr. Peterson?
"Bobbsey Twins
Go to the Brewery."
Let's just cut
to the happy ending.
Uh-oh!
We got the Cheers review today.
Oh, God! Here it comes.
Well, at least you'll all know
I didn't
compromise myself.
And that we probably
got a horrendous review
and I'll get fired.
I can still look at
myself in the mirror
and say, "Would it
have killed you?"
"Hurrah, hurrah for Cheers,
the best bar in Boston."
Oh, you slept with him.
I did not.
"Warm, inviting, a delight
from top to bottom."
The bar or you?
I did not sleep
with him.
Oh, stop it. I think
I respect you more
now than I ever did.
I did not sleep
with him.
You just have
a filthy mind.
Nobody else in
here thinks that,
so just shut up.
How was he?
I did not sleep
with him.
( phone ringing )
Yeah. Cheers.
As a matter of fact, she is.
Hold on one second.
It's your boss.
Hello.
Mr. Drake.
Did you happen to catch
our remarkable review?
Good? Oh, it was fantastic.
Yes. We're all very proud.
Yeah, well, you know,
we work pretty hard...
No! I did not sleep with him.
Good air in...
and the bad air out.
That's good.
Nice, easy
breathing.
Now, there.
Don't you all feel better?
( plane creaks )
Now, now. Remember
what we learned.
Meow, meow, meow.
ALL:
That's just a little kitty cat.
C-A-T: Clear Air Turbulence.
Now... now that
you're all relaxed,
we can take this opportunity
to, uh... well, further discuss
the irrationality of our fears.
Anyone?
I...I... I just wish
I had more control.
I think I'd feel better
if I were flying the plane.
Trust me.
That doesn't help.
How do you know?
I was a pilot
for this airline.
You were?
I was flying
a jumbo jet--
full plane--
and it occurred
to me that
all these people
had their lives
in the hands
of someone like me.
I couldn't
go up again.
Forget the pilot!
What about those mechanics, huh?
I mean, what if
one of those guys
has a bad day?
Forgets to screw
in a lug nut?
Carla, they're
trained technicians.
Aren't they
in a labor dispute?
Yes, but
it's almost over.
Well, what happens
if we get hit by lightning?
Oh, now, I'm sure the plane
is designed to handle that.
Or if a teeny,
tiny little bird
gets in the engine?
God! What bird would be flying
at 30,000 feet?
We're at 30,000 feet?
This plane
is too heavy
to be up that high!
If anything happens,
we're all just going
to drop like spit
off the Prudential Building.
Carla, now
you're being silly.
Listen, statistics prove
that this is...
The hell with statistics.
Does the words
"ice on the wings"
mean anything
to you?
Oh, that is simply the sun
glinting off the wings.
Does that look
like ice to you?
ALL:
Meow, meow, meow.
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow.
Will you stop that
incessant caterwauling?
Meow, meow, meow.
Why aren't
they serving drinks?
Hey, Fras, you okay?
I'm fine. Fine.
You look
a little green.
I'm perfectly all right.
Where is that
damn cocktail cart?
What was that?
What?
That pinging noise.
I heard it.
I heard a ping,
a ping, ping.
What, have you
all gone deaf
or something?
Hey, hey, ease up.
Do you feel cold air
rushing in here?
No.
My God!
There's a leak
in the fuselage!
Calm down, Frasier.
Oh, God, look!
It's the wings!
They're flapping
around like
a wounded duck!
We're all gonna die!
Frasier! You're
not in your
happy place.
What do you mean?
In a grave?
We're going down!
I got to get out of here!
Mommy!
Frasier!
Honest, Eddie.
I'm flying out
tomorrow night. Yeah.
Frasier's class taught me
how stupid it was
to be afraid of flying.
Oh, me, too.
I can't wait to get you alone,
strip you out of that penguin
outfit, and climb all over ya.
We're sharing a room
with the three little pigs?
Well, they're used
to huffing and puffing.
All right. See you then.
Sam, you don't
really think Miss Howe
would do anything she
shouldn't have to get
a good review, do you?
No, Of course not.
Then why do you
keep teasing her?
Well, haven't
you ever noticed
how her chest
kind of heaves
when she's angry?
I always avert my eyes.
You're kidding me.
No.
I'm a leg man.
Excuse me, miss?
I couldn't help
but overhear
your conversation.
I've had a fear
of flying for years,
and I think it's time
that I confronted it.
How can I get
into that class
that worked
miracles for you?
I can do
better than that.
The doctor's over
there. Hey, Fras?
I'm in my happy place.
Sign up early.