Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Let's just concentrate on
the, uh, left side, okay?
Yeah.
We have a boy.
No, no, wait, wait.
It's a girl.
It's a boy again.
This is weird.
All right, maybe it's a girl.
I-I...
Still trying to figure
out what Carla is, huh?
No, Cliff, we're trying to find
out what sex my babies are.
See, if the ring goes back
and forth, it's a boy.
If it goes around
in a circle, it's a girl.
And if it just dangles there
doing nothing, it's a Clavin.
I can tell you
something
we used to, uh,
do on the farm.
We'd take a fresh
laid chicken egg
and we'd put on a spoon
and hold it over
the woman's stomach.
If it dipped down,
it was female, if not,
male.
So how often did you predict
the sex of the babies?
Never. This was to predict
the sex of the chicken.
All right,
you take a spoon, right?
( piano plays )
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't
you like to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always
glad you came
You want to be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You want to be where everybody
knows your name
You want to go
where people know
People are all the same
You want to go where
everybody knows your name.
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
Good afternoon, everybody.
Sam, you got you room
for one more tosspot?
Let me have a beer, will you?
You betcha.
How you been
there, Frasier?
Well, you know how it is for
a psychiatrist this day and age.
Divorces, hopelessness
over financial situations,
rampant paranoia.
Thriving, never better.
Oh, and get this.
I just heard a little bit
of information about
someone with whom
we're all acquainted.
Is it juicy?
Well, yes.
Could it embarrass
someone?
Oh, most definitely.
Is it me?
No.
Spill it.
Well, I had lunch today
with an ex-colleague of mine
who attended
the University of Connecticut
at the same time
as a certain Miss Rebecca Howe.
Now, it seems
that this
particular Rebecca Howe
was known as--
well, let's just say it--
the party girl on campus.
( exclaiming )
CARLA:
Our Rebecca?
Miss Granite Panties?
The one who goes through life
with her knees bolted together?
It's got to be
a mistake.
SAM:
Yeah, yeah...
So, does anyone know
what college ours went to?
It wouldn't surprise me one bit
if it was Rebecca.
I don't know.
No, I mean, it's us
quiet, reserved types
who, when properly stimulated,
turn into your average
churning hunk of burning funk.
Now, Cliffie, uh,
can you tell me exactly
at what point in your life
you came to that big
fork in the road
where reality took a left
and you hung a sharp right?
Excuse me, is there
a Cliff Clavin here?
Uh, would Mr. Clavin
know what this is about?
Yeah, I'm a neighbor
of his, Jim McNulty.
His mother
said he'd be here.
All right,
just a minute.
Uh, Mr. Clavin, you here
for a Jim McNulty?
Uh, yeah, yeah, sure.
Uh, you know how it is.
Some guys in bars
don't like you to
know they're here.
Hey, Cliff,
remember me?
Yeah, yeah.
Jim McNulty.
You own a house
down at the corner.
You ever going to take
those Christmas lights down?
Yeah, as soon
as a weekend goes by
you don't have
another garage sale.
Listen, I, uh,
I've been going around
to good neighbors
like yourself
hoping I can get
your support.
Well, uh...
what am I looking at here?
Oh, it's a petition
agreeing not to sell out
to these big developers
who've been trying
to buy up our houses
and build mini malls.
( chuckling )
Jimbo, Jimbo, Jimbo.
You know,
new development
only increases property values.
I wouldn't sign that petition
if you beat me senseless.
You know, it
may be too late,
but let's give it a try.
You know, I'll never understand
people like you.
You got no conscience,
no sense of community,
no interest in keeping
our neighborhood beautiful.
If you, uh, want
to beautify the neighborhood,
why don't you stay indoors?
Yeah, at least
I don't live with my mother.
I don't blame you;
I've seen your mother.
Yeah, my mother's a saint.
( chuckling ):
Yeah-- Saint Bernard.
Oh, yeah?
Forget it.
Ah, I'm outta luck.
Somebody's already
using the pool table.
The lady in question.
Sam, Sam, find out
where she went to college.
Yeah, okay.
Afternoon, Sam.
Hey, boss.
How's business today?
Oh, pretty slow.
Me and the guys
just sitting around
talking about where everybody
went to... college.
You were?
Well, I was wondering
what it would be like
to go to... college.
Well,
picture a place
with 20,000 people
all acting the way you do.
Sounds like fun.
Listen, uh,
where did you go to...
college?
The University
of... Connecticut.
( all laughing )
Am I missing something here?
No, no, no, no,
not at all.
We, uh, we're just, uh,
such big fans of
their football team,
you know,
the fighting...
insurance salesmen.
Boy, oh, boy.
Don't you just love
this Yorkshire pudding, Ma?
That's a real delicacy.
The English didn't think so.
Actually, Yorkshire pudding
was invented in the late 1770s
during a beef shortage.
A person could be given
a little bit of beef
and soak up the gravy
with the pudding,
thereby fooling his stomach
into thinking
he was having a fuller dinner
than he actually was.
And you wonder why nobody
asks us out anymore.
So how was your day?
Ah, okay, Ma.
Oh, our neighbor,
Nut Butt McNulty
stopped in Cheers today.
He was, uh, circulating
some kind of petition.
The one to stop development?
Yeah.
I signed it.
( crashing )
You did?
Well, who in his
right mind wouldn't?
Besides you, of course.
( sputtering )
Ma, we-we-we're
for progress here.
If we don't stop these people,
we could lose our home.
Well, it's
probably about time
we got out of this
rattrap anyway.
Clifford.
This "rattrap" is where you,
for want
of a better term, grew up.
I think it's time somebody
looked at the scrapbook.
Aw, come on, Ma.
Not the scrapbook.
Yes, Clifford, the scrapbook.
Misty watercolor memories
of the way we were.
Oh. Look at this one.
Ah...
No, Ma. I'm not
gonna look.
You're not gonna
get me this time.
Oh, we had fun that day.
( laughing )
Ma!
It is not working.
Oh, I'd forgotten this one.
This has got to be
the handsomest picture of you
I ever laid eyes on.
Which?
Oh, Ma, come on.
My ears are even
covered with acne.
I'm your mother, Clifford.
I'm looking at your soul.
Ah, there's me sliding
down the old banister.
I always
thought you spent
entirely too much time
doing that.
Eh...
Eh, it was fun.
Oh, look, there's
your favorite
hiding place
in the closet.
Yeah, yeah.
You used to be
in there for hours.
Yeah.
Well, that's 'cause
you always locked
the door on me, Ma.
Well, look at the result.
You're a very
polite young man.
Oh, now there's
where we planted
the elm tree in the yard.
Yeah.
Oh, you named
him Elmer.
Mm-hmm.
And look at our
Elmer now.
So tall and strong.
Just like my boy.
Yeah, yeah, I can remember
raising him from a sapling, Ma.
I even carved
my first slingshot
out of his branches.
And cried every winter
when the leaves fell.
Yeah, yeah, that tree is
like a brother to me, Ma.
Just imagine, you know,
something that I planted,
and I nurtured,
is gonna be there
for future
generations to enjoy.
Unless they chop it down
to put up a Jiffy Lube.
Come on, Ma, they wouldn't
do that, would they?
They'll do that
as soon as look at you.
Well...
Oh, Ma, no, they won't.
Oh...
No, Ma...
They're not gonna
cut down my tree!
A-and they're not gonna
touch this house either!
And they're not
gonna take our land!
That's my boy.
Where are you going?
Well, it may sound
a little bit silly
and all, Ma, but, uh...
I'm gonna go out there
and sit in my tree.
You got right ahead.
Never fails.
Well, uh,
interestingly enough,
Yorkshire pudding
was invented in the 1700s
during a beef shortage.
All right, stop everything.
I've got a major news flash.
I just had lunch
with Miss Howe's
former college classmate
and it seems that she
had a nickname at UConn.
Give, give.
Well, he wasn't sure
how she came by
this appellation,
but it seems that at some point
during her little
sojourn there,
she became known
as "Backseat Becky."
( all laughing )
Boy.
What do you
suppose that means?
Woody.
What that means
is when Miss...
Cliff, Cliff.
Why don't you
let someone who's
been there, tell it?
Wood, she likes to do
her cushion pushin'
on four wheels.
Miss Howe?
Really?
You know, uh, back
where I come from,
we used to say something
about girls like that.
What?
"Let's date 'em."
Oh, looky here. You know,
something tells me
I'm going to be completely
obnoxious about this.
What's so funny?
Oh, we were just talking
about nicknames, you know.
Different funny nicknames
that people have.
Did you ever
have a nickname?
As a matter of fact, no.
Really.
Nothing, huh?
Not a Spark
or Lefty or...
Bubba or something?
Sorry.
Guys, we ought
to give
Rebecca, here, a
nickname, uh...
You know, something
that, uh, kinda
fits her personality.
All right.
Kinda dignified.
Kinda businesslike.
Kinda reserved.
Let me think. Oh, yeah.
Anybody?
ALL:
Backseat Becky!
( moans )
Gee, that,
uh, that works for me.
I kind of like "Bubba."
Oh, God.
Then you probably know
the whole sordid story.
Well, actually, no.
Well, that's because
there isn't one.
Hey, hey, come on, come on.
Don't worry about that.
Listen, the truth is
I'm looking
to buy a new car,
and I, uh, I need
an expert opinion.
Uh...
now what-what...
what model do you think
has the best rear shocks?
( laughter )
Have you driven
a Ford lately?
I guess she gives new meaning
to the term "four on the floor."
All right, all right.
If you insist
on an explanation,
I will give it to you.
You know how sometimes
as a joke,
you call someone
the exact opposite
of what they really are?
Well, I was really shy
in college,
so my friends thought
it would be a huge gas
to call me "Backseat Becky."
( faint chuckle )
Well, it's simple,
it's, it's logical,
and we don't believe
it for a second.
Wait a minute.
I-I believe her.
Us virgins have
to stick together.
I told you the truth.
If you don't want
to believe it, fine,
just believe whatever you want.
All right,
here's the real truth.
I was very aggressive
in college, a real go-getter.
I never took a backseat
to anyone.
No. No, no.
No, Mr. Cronin,
I'm not listening.
The case is closed.
I'm not taking
any offers,
and that's final.
I'm sorry if I've
upset you, Mrs. Clavin.
Clifford, would you
tell this gentleman, please,
we're not selling
our house?
I was just
trying to make an offer
on your house,
and your mother
won't listen.
Well, that's because
she has got more sense
in her bony little frame
than you have
in your little finger.
Reverse that.
You are not going
to run the Clavins off our land.
I don't care
what you offer us,
you just can't put
a price on love,
family and our memories.
Take it or leave it--
$250,000.
$200 and...
Oh, my God,
we're rich.
But Ma, Ma,
you can't do this.
A Clavin cannot be bought off.
I'm only a Clavin
by marriage, Clifford.
Oh...
Oh, guys, you gotta help me.
She's going to go
through with this.
Well, why don't you offer
to buy the place back?
Sammy, I don't have
enough money for a down payment.
Wait a minute.
Can either of you guys
lend me $50,000?
( chuckles )
I'm sorry, Cliff, you
never paid me back
that million
from last week.
Well, it's been
a pleasure
doing business
with you, Mrs. Clavin.
Thank you.
Uh... uh...
There!
Now what are you going to do?
Well, first I'm going
to take this contract
down to the office,
and then I'm going
to call my wife
and ask her what I'm supposed
to pick up at the grocery store.
Ah, Ma,
but after all we've
been through together.
Just last night you were saying
how much the house meant to you.
Last night I was poor.
Tonight I'm not.
I never thought
I'd have the chance,
but now
I can go to Florida.
Florida? Oh, for
crying out loud.
Who'd ever want to live
in that stinkhole?
Clifford,
I'm doing this
as much for you
as I am for myself.
You're 39 years old.
It's time to cut the cord.
Ma, I am not
leaving that house!
Clifford...
I am not leaving
that house!
Well, I'm afraid
you're going to have to.
Oh! Oh, yeah, fine.
Go off by yourself.
See how you like it.
After a week of cooking
your own meals,
doing your own dishes,
washing your own hair,
you'll be back.
Oh, well, well, well,
if it isn't the ultimate
driving machine.
Okay, okay, I give up.
Look, I'll tell you
the real story,
but it's kind
of personal
so can we do this
in private?
Sure, you bet.
You bet.
Say, if you're
too embarrassed
to say something,
feel free
to act it out.
I was living in a
women's dorm on campus...
Mm-hmm.
...and one night
a fire broke out.
Ah.
Well, I didn't have time
to change my clothes,
so I had to run out
to the parking lot
wearing only a teddy;
black,
but see-through.
All of a sudden,
I was caught
in this fire engine's
headlights.
I didn't know what to do.
I looked all around,
and suddenly,
I spotted this
open convertible.
I climbed in,
and I slunk down
to the backseat.
Suddenly, this
hulking fireman
was standing over me.
He was magnificent.
I looked in his eyes.
I knew what he wanted,
and I wanted it, too.
I peeled off his black
rubber raincoat.
He ripped off my teddy.
I can still feel the
heat on my flesh.
But it wasn't the fire--
it was us.
When it was over,
I opened my eyes,
and I noticed
we weren't alone.
Others had watched
and not said a word.
And that's why I'm known
as "Backseat Becky."
Satisfied?
Thanks for the
story, Carla.
Here's your ten bucks.
Yeah, the $20 one
would have killed him.
So wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Why do they call you
"Backseat Becky."
That will cost
you a hundred.
Hey, you know,
you're kind of a pig.
Maybe we can be friends.
Excuse me.
I've got to find
Norm Peterson.
Does Mr. Peterson know
what this is about?
Never mind.
There he is.
Norman.
Hi.
You got to help me.
I'm desperate.
What?
Cliff's locked himself
in the house.
No, I've tried everything.
He won't budge.
Ours is the last house
on the block
scheduled for demolition,
and that's today.
I'm at my wit's end.
You got to help me.
I'll talk to him.
I'll see what I can do.
Oh, thank you, Norm.
I hope he doesn't
try anything crazy.
The last thing on Earth
I want to see
is my son's face
on the 11:00 news.
There's a whole city out there
that agrees with ya.
( machinery clattering loudly )
( clattering continues )
( whistle blows )
( machinery stops )
...the world's biggest ass!
Clifford,
now take off
those silly handcuffs.
I can't.
I flushed the key.
Norman,
go outside and see
if you can find some tin snips.
Ask for Biff.
He loaned us the hard hats.
Clifford, sometimes I
really worry about you.
Look what they did to Elmer.
I'm sorry, dear,
but what can we do?
Come on, Ma,
you're the one who taught me
that if you believe
in something,
if you really want it,
then you're just going
to have to fight for it.
The house is sold.
They're going to tear it down.
Well, then I am going
down with it.
Clifford,
does this house really mean
that much to you?
Yeah, Ma.
Yeah, it really does.
( voice breaking ):
Then it means that much
to me, too.
I don't know what we'll do.
We'll find a lawyer.
We're going to
fight this together.
We'll save our home.
Oh, Ma, together?
Really?
Really, son.
Oh!
( Cliff shrieks )
What are you
going to with that thing?
Cut your handcuffs off.
Yeah? Well, that's
a little bit dangerous!
What? No, no. I'm wearing
a hard hat. It's okay.
A hard hat?
Get that thing away from me!
Cut the post!
Isn't that a little drastic?
No, Ma, I think we're going
to remodel in here anyway.
( engine revving )
( grunts )
There.
I think we're going
to beat this thing.
So do I.
Now we're going
to find a lawyer.
Okay.
But first,
I want to treat you boys
to a Popsicle!
( laughs ):
Oh, Ma.
( wood creaking )
What was that?
Ah, probably just a
squirrel on the roof.
( wood creaking )
NORM:
Big one.
( loud creaking )
Uh-oh! Ma!
( metallic creaking )
( crashing )
Imagine...
we got a quarter of a million
for this dump.
( door slams shut )
( glass shatters )
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.OpenSubtitles.org