(Woody)
cheers  is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Sam, uh, more change,
please.
Boy, lilith's really
burnin' up the phone there.
What's the matter?
Oh, you don't want to hear
about our troubles.
Well, then again,
since i've suffered
through so many of yours...
we're having a devil of a time
finding a babysitter
for little frederick.
Jeez,
what we wouldn't give
to get away together.
Oh, me, too.
I live for that.
Really? Y-y-you could
use a vacation?
No. I want you guys
to go away.
So, you don't have
any relatives or friends
you can ask to watch the baby?
Oh, well, i-i'd gladly
ask my parents.
Of course, they're dead.
Well, as for friends, i...
sorry. Stupid question.
Frasier, good news.
I finally found a woman
with whom we can leave
our baby for one night.
Oh, great.
Tell me about her.
Well, she's 79 years old,
she can't see her hands
without her glasses,
but she assures me
she can smell smoke.
Lilith, this is wonderful.
At last we'll have a night
alone together.
Yes, it's just
what we need.
Our relationship
is at a point
where the rekindling
of romance
is both appropriate
and welcome,
to say nothing of timely.
Well, stop, lilith.
You're getting me hot.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Making your way
in the world today
takes everything
you've got
taking a break
from all your worries
sure would help a lot
wouldn't you like
to get away
sometimes you want to go
where everybody
knows your name
and they're always
glad you came
you wanna be
where you can see
our troubles
are all the same
you wanna be
where everybody
knows your name
you wanna go
where people know
people are all the same
you wanna go
where everybody
knows your name
hey, cliffie, your beer
tastes a little flat today?
No.
I don't know.
Seems like it's off
by maybe a hop or two.
Well, it probably
has something to do
with that new, uh,
pasteurization process.
You know, they put it in
big, uh, sterilized vats...
ahem, yeah,
who gives a hoot?
What? No long-winded
explanation?
Hmm.
Cliff just isn't
himself today, is he?
Well,
it's not just mr. Clavin.
I'm feelin'
a little strange, too.
In fact, this whole place
feels weird.
Well, you know, woody,
the japanese believe
that every house
has its own energy,
what they call
its  wa.
Now, eastern culture
submits
that if this  wa
is somehow in disorder,
everyone that enters
therein will feel
a sense of disconnection.
Mr. Clavin, i know
why you're not yourself.
Dr. Crane is yourself.
Damn it.
These decorations
are all wrong.
This is st. Patrick's day,
the busiest night
of the year,
and our name is misspelled
on every single item.
"Faith & begorrah,
from your friends at chees."
Rebecca, the decorations
are the least
of our problems.
I agree.
You're right, norm.
I think unpaid bar tabs
come a lot higher
on our priority list.
Damn it, would you
look at how
they misspelled "cheers"?
Uh, what i'm talkin'
about is
if you guys want to worry
about somethin',
why don't you worry
about what evil,
rotten practical joke
gary's old town tavern
is gonna play on us this year.
No, no, no, no, no.
We're not gonna continue
this feud with gary, ok?
What are you talkin' about?
This st. Paddy's day.
It's one of the busiest nights
of the year.
It's when gary
wheels out the big guns.
He can't do anything worse
to us than he did last year,
remember that?
The place was packed
and gary and his goons
filled our stairwell
with potatoes.
Yeah, just my luck,
i was sittin'
on the bottom step
tying my shoe
at the time.
Lucky for me you guys
were able to dig me out.
I'd hate to be
the 2nd member of my family
buried alive by potatoes.
Well, this year things
are gonna be different.
Now, after that
potato incident,
i went over there
and i had a little chat
with gary.
I said we gotta cool it
because this stuff
is ruining our business,
and he agreed.
So we drew up this little
document to that effect.
"We, the managers
of cheers and gary's
old town tavern,
do solemnly swear
to cut it out."
That ought to
hold up in court.
I'll have to do something
about these decorations.
What are you going to do,
replace 'em?
(Rebecca)
no, there's no time
for that.
I have to go to the deli
and buy some cheese.
People will be expecting it.
Can i fill up your beer
there for you, norm?
Uh, no, thanks.
I'm not quite finished
with this one.
I'm sorry, i'm sorry.
I'm full.
Aw, man, that-that's it.
You know,
what--what's going on
around here today?
Everybody's actin' weird.
It's time to give
old tecumseh a belly rub.
There you go.
Who's tecumseh?
You know,
the old wooden indian
by the door.
Isn't that phil?
Where--where is he?
Did--did you guys move him?
Well, spread out.
We got to find him here, guys.
This is very weird.
I could swear
i saw him here yesterday,
and the day before
and the day before that.
No, no, no. That was me.
Sammy, he's not here.
Who in his right mind
would want to walk off
with tecumseh?
(All)
gary.
Oh, man.
Boy, you know, fun is fun,
and i like being
humiliated as much
as the next guy, but...
yeah, but this,
taking tecumseh, that--
that crosses the line!
Sammy's right.
I'll tell you what,
he can take cliffie,
he can strip him naked,
he can paint him green,
tie him up like a shamrock,
drag him
through the streets
of boston,
but this is going
too far.
This time, it's personal.
Hey.
(All)
get gary! Get gary!
Get gary!
[People chattering]
ah, st. Paddy's day,
the day st. Patrick
drove all the snakes
out of ireland.
Boy, if that isn't
the biggest freudian dream
of all time.
Oh, 5 more irish coffees,
woody.
Oh, gosh, i wish sam would
hurry back from gary's.
I'm at my wit's end here.
How can you tell?
Hello, duckling.
Sugarpants.
I've been anxiously awaiting
our appointed rendezvous.
Hey, dr. Crane,
mrs. Dr. Crane.
So you guys are here
on your night off, huh?
You have a marvelous
grasp of the obvious.
Well, that's what comes
from working with your hands.
So what are you guys
gonna do?
Well, we plan to
recreate our very first
romantic liaison.
If memory serves,
we began with a lovely meal
at melville's,
and then an after-dinner
drink here,
and then we adjourned
to lilith's tastefully
decorated condominium
where we engaged
in an evening of lovemaking,
which i might say,
was rather, um, meaningful.
Not to mention
sweet and sweaty.
Well, i'm not hungry,
you've had your drink.
I say we jump
right to the final stop
on our itinerary.
Do you think the people
that live in that condominium
now would mind?
I don't see why.
We're an attractive couple.
Carla, how come
we can't tell miss howe
what sam's doin' to gary?
You know her.
She thinks that anything
that d-destroys property,
costs money,
or wastes time is stupid.
I don't know, she's got
an attitude problem.
Yeah, what is with her?
[Men singing]
ho! Ho! Ho!
Hoo, pow!
Pow, hoo!
Yo-ho, caballeros.
Did you head them off
at the pass?
Oh, yeah. Yeah,
we just shut down
gary's old town tavern
on one of the busiest
bar nights of the year.
[All cheering]
yep.
Yeah, we got padlocks
on all the doors,
front and back.
We got toxic
spill warning signs,
we have police tapes
blocking off
all the entrances.
I mean, people are
gonna be afraid
to drive down the streets.
[All cheering]
oh, and, uh,
to top it all off,
my friend normie here
sent 38 pizzas
over to gary's house.
Actually, i've sent 'em
over to my house.
So if anyone
wants to come over,
remember, we got to
get to 'em before vera.
Otherwise we got nothing left
but the crust.
[All chattering]
morning, everyone.
(Sam)
hey, hey.
(All)
norm!
What are you
up to, norm?
My ideal weight,
if i were 11 feet tall.
So, we have any retaliation
from the old garmeister?
No, no, no, no.
But that's because
we outsmarted him
once again.
We had a man inside
the whole time.
(Norm)
all right.
Yep. I stood exactly
where tecumseh stands
all night long.
It's given me
a new appreciation
for tecumseh
and everything he does for us.
You stood there
all night long?
What a stupid thing to do.
Oh, yeah?
I stand there
for one night
and you think
that's stupid?
He stands there for years,
and you rub him for luck.
Who's the stupid one, carla?
Hey, i hear you guys
shut down gary's last night.
Oh, now, he started it
when he stole tecumseh.
When you draw first blood
like that,
you got to expect
anything to happen.
(Norm)
right.
[Chuckles]
hey, hey, hey, hey.
What?
(Cliff)
they're bringing
tecumseh back.
Oh, yeah!
We brought gary
to his knees
and now he's returning
our statue
as a token of surrender!
[All whooping]
[all cheering]
oh, good.
Tecumseh's back.
Yep. Gary sent him.
Gary? No,
i had him revarnished.
Doesn't he look shiny
and new?
You wanna sign
for this, lady?
Sure.
Uh, say, rebecca,
so you mean that--that--that
gary had nothing to do
with tecumseh
being missing?
Absolutely not.
Uh-oh.
What's wrong?
We shut down gary's bar
on one of the busiest nights
of the year.
We did that
for no good reason at all.
What?
What are you talk--
what did you do?
Well, uh, sweetheart,
you remember this, uh,
treaty you and gary signed?
Yes.
Gentlemen, we're at war.
I don't understand
why you guys think
it is so cool
to play these stupid
practical jokes.
Honey, it's what keeps
the child in us alive.
Otherwise, we'd be
just mature adults.
Yeah. I'd lie awake at night
worrying about that one.
Listen to me,
all of you,
i want you to call gary
right now and apologize
before he gets the idea
of getting even
and blows us to bits
with an all-in-good-fun
toilet explosion.
You're right.
There's that attitude.
Apologize.
Yeah, right.
A lot of good
that would do.
Gary just gets meaner
when he smells weakness.
I got to
respect the guy.
Well, one thing is clear,
he's gonna retaliate, ok.
In fact, he may have
already put some
deadly plan in action.
This beer
you just poured me, sam,
could be filled with toxins.
So what do we do?
We take our chances.
Hey, woody,
open that door there and
see if gary's done anything
to the outside of the bar,
will you?
Snow.
Gary made it snow.
Gary can't make it snow,
grain brain.
Oh, it's a good thing,
'cause we'd never
be able to top that.
Hold it. Hold it.
He may have planted
somebody in the bar.
Now, you see
any strange faces?
Just, uh, glance around
nonchalantly.
Come on,
gary's smarter than that.
He knows we'd be
on the lookout for a stranger.
So he'd plant
somebody we do know.
Yeah, probably try to
turn one of our own
against us.
So the idea is,
who do we suspect
the least?
I think it's me.
Oh. Come on, woody.
How could gary
turn you against us?
I don't know.
But if he can
make it snow--
he didn't make it snow!
He didn't make it snow,
you idiot!
All right, just calm down.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Calm down.
Look, i just
can't help it, sam.
It's this waiting.
It's making me crazy.
I mean, you know gary.
He always retaliates.
I know, i know.
And with great cruelty
and force
and always
within 24 hours.
Boy, i really do
respect that guy.
(Norm)
carla's absolutely right.
Every time
that damn door opens,
i keep thinking to myself,
this could be the big one.
Excuse me.
Is the manager here?
Why? Who wants to know?
I'm the fire marshal.
You're due for your routine
6-month inspection
for safety code violations.
Oh.
[Laughing]
ahem, well, we're really glad
you're here.
Why don't you
have a seat?
Can i take your hat?
Thanks.
Sure.
Yeah, you probably
want to be checking
if this fire extinguisher
is fully operational.
Of course.
Ok.
What are you doing?
Well, this hat
is now up to code.
What are you doing?
Well, we're just--
we're just, uh,
demonstrating
our fire preparedness.
Gentlemen, uh,
seltzer drill.
(All)
seltzer drill!
Hup! Seltzer drill.
Yo! Yo! Whoa.
[Laughing]
what are you doing?
Oh.
These--these pants
were a tinderbox.
You guys are crazy.
Yeah. Whoo!
[All singing]
whoo!
(Rebecca)
sam, excuse me.
Will you be sure
to let me know
when the fire marshal
gets here?
Fi-fire marshal?
Yes. We're due for our
routine 6-month inspection.
Be sure and tell me
when he gets here.
Oh, don't worry.
I--i have a feeling
he'll be in touch.
Guys, guys, guys, guys,
we're going nuts here.
I tell you, man,
it's just sheer luck
that--that no one was hurt
in this situation,
other than rebecca.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
This might be part
of gary's master plan.
What? What is?
Yeah, keep us on the edge,
put us off balance.
Yeah, mr. Clavin's right.
You know, i think gary's
probably playing with us,
like a rat
with a mouse.
That's cat and mouse,
woody.
Cat and mouse.
Sam, a cat and a mouse
don't play together.
They're mortal enemies.
They don't even
know the same games.
Think before
you speak, sam.
All right, all right,
all right, but what do we do
about gary, all right?
What are we supposed to do?
Just sit here
and wait and worry?
Well, what other choice
do we have?
Fail-safe.
What?
Huh?
Sure,  fail-safe.
Our situation here
greatly parallels that film
of the early 1960s
that delighted and, uh,
disturbed audiences
of that time.
So your idea is
we-- we schneid ourselves
before gary
does it to us?
Should do something
to ourselves
to get back
for what we did to gary?
Oh, that's crazy.
Come on.
All right, wait--wait--
wait a minute.
It might just convince gary
not to do anything to us.
We'd be the master
of our own fate.
Yeah.
And, fellows,
bottom line is,
we'd be getting it over with.
All right.
(Sam)
what do you think?
I'll buy it. All right,
sammy's right.
I say
we screw ourselves!
(All)
screw ourselves!
Screw ourselves!
Carla, where are sam
and woody?
Oh, you'll find out
soon enough.
Don't worry
your flat little head
about it.
You did not
answer my question,
and for your information,
my head is not flat.
All right,
but it's not little.
Say, carla, uh,
where's the inner circle?
Oh, uh, sammy and the guys
had to do something,
but they'll be back soon.
Oh, don't tell me
i missed something.
No.
Now, carla, i expressly
posted my beeper number.
If anything juicy happens,
i'm to be paged.
Frasier, an observation.
You are spending
way too much time here.
So, uh, how was
your night off?
Bet you spent
a lot of time worrying
about that kid of yours, huh?
No, not a bit.
We had a wonderful time.
We knew he was
in good hands.
So we just sat back
and relaxed.
Well, had a much needed
and healthy
night away from him.
Oh, that's terrific.
Oh, by the way,
your sitter called
and she said that
frederick rolled over
by himself
for the first time.
What? And we missed it?
We must be
the worst parents
in the world.
Frasier, let's rush home,
fall to our knees
and beg his forgiveness.
I'll never get over this,
not until the day i die.
New parents,
they're always suckers
for that gag.
Well, my friends,
we did it.
We've saved the bar.
[All cheering]
(sam)
where's the photographer?
Are you the guys?
No, we are the men.
Now, take a photograph
of us in all our glory here.
Gentlemen, step right up
in a line.
All right. Yeah. Get right...
there we go.
Ok, smile, men.
This is for the sunday paper.
Fellas, count of 3.
1, 2, 3.
[Camera clicking]
and here we go.
ok. I got it. Thanks, guys.
Hope it grows back.
Doesn't always, you know.
(Carla)
man, you guys!
You know,
when i dreamed this gag up,
i never thought
you were gonna go through
with it.
I just thought you'd get
some rubber skull caps
or something.
Hey, come on,
give us a little credit here,
will you?
When a man has a dirty job
to do, he does it.
W-wait a minute,
what's that behind your ear?
Nothing. No, no,
don't take it off.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
[All exclaiming]
what the hell?
Guys, we're talking
about my hair.
Oh, yeah. So?
Without my hair,
i'd be just
just one of you guys.
Pardon me, sammy,
if that fails
to bring a tear to my eye!
Fellas, i tried to do it,
i swear to god,
but, man, i love my hair.
All right, fine.
You got a problem
with this?
Yeah!
Let's just step outside
right now.
[Men clamoring]
oh, no, wait,
hang on a second, here, huh?
What are we doin'
to ourselves?
I mean, it's bad enough
that gary made us
look like fools,
and now we're fightin'
amongst ourselves.
This is not
part of the deal.
Yeah, woody's right.
Thank you,
mr. Peterson.
Now, let's just relax,
shave sam's head,
and discuss this...
[all shouting]
hey, hey, guys, listen up,
listen up.
I've got great news.
Yeah, listen up.
Now, listen, there's no need
to retaliate
against ourselves.
What do you mean?
Gary's has been closed
for the last month.
He's in florida, while his
place is being remodeled.
He wasn't even open
on st. Patrick's day.
He doesn't even know
you guys did anything to him.
Isn't that a howl?
This is the worst thing
gary's ever done.
We've got to teach
gary a lesson.
He must never do
nothing again.
Men, there's only one thing
left to do.
Get gary.
(All)
get gary! Get gary!
Get gary!
First, we shave sammy!
No, get gary!
Shave sammy!
Get gary!
(Sam)
get gary! Get gary!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/y34y
Help other users to choose the best subtitles