Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Quite a night,
huh, Norm?
Yep.
Yeah.
I can't believe
old Sammy wants to be a dad.
Yep.
He's got to be real careful
about choosing a mother.
A lot of things
to consider.
Like, for example,
how the genes match up.
Yeah.
Wish my parents had given that
a little bit more thought.
Yeah.
Maybe I'd be able
to jump a little higher,
run a little faster.
You know, there's
a jumping gene in my ma.
It's called the "J" gene.
It's... it's recessive.
You know, so, if
my ma had gotten matched up
with a guy
with a dominant jumping gene...
You know, let's see.
Like, uh... Carl Lewis.
I'm telling you, Norm,
it could have been
a whole different playground
for little Cliffie Lewis.
Cliffie, I hate to interrupt,
but, uh, we're here.
Normie, how come
you always drop me off at least
six blocks away from my house?
Well, this time it's a mile.
Get out.
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
CARLA:
Previously on Cheers...
No more "Rebecca the jerk."
No more "Rebecca the goonball."
"Rebecca the loser."
"Rebecca the mother"!
I'm going to have
a brand-new human baby!
I can't wait!
You know, a new life!
A new life that depends
completely on me.
(fabric ripping)
Can you believe it?
I forgot my coat.
Oh, I'm just so
excited about this!
I don't know.
I'm going to be a mommy!
Rebecca, honey?
Honey?
What, Sam?
Are you sure you're
ready for this?
Well, don't I
look ready?
Maybe I'm thrown off
by the coatrack.
Oh, I hate it
when I do that.
Careful, careful.
Well, you think
we're ready, don't you?
I mean, you don't
think that we're
rushing this, do you?
Do you need a little time
to think it over?
No... sweetheart, sweetheart,
come on, turn around.
I think we're both
very excited by this.
You want to be a mommy, right?
And I want to be a daddy.
I think that the decision
has been made here.
Sam, just give it a yank.
Ow! Ooh!
Are you hurt?
No, no. I'm fine.
Okay, what do you think?
You want to give it
till tomorrow?
(high voice):
Please.
Hey, everybody, guess what.
My buddy just
bowled a 300!
Great. Like
anybody cares, huh?
A round of drinks on me!
All right! Way to roll
that melon, buddy!
MAN:
There you go.
Here you go, bud.
Oh, sorry, missy.
What for? You think
I won't enjoy a cigar
because I'm a woman?
I'll save it for the
George Sand Film Festival.
(Frasier chuckling)
You see, what
you don't understand
is that my wife
just made a...
a very funny
literary reference
to a woman that
used to dress as a man,
and lived in France.
Was he a bowler?
Sure. What the hell?
Hey, uh... why don't
you have the, uh...
smokers sitting in
the smoking section?
Oh, of course.
Where's my head?
Probably in the pumpkin patch
wondering when
the mix-up occurred.
Sammy, we have
a smoking section?
Yeah. Over by the piano.
We have a piano?
Oh. I gotta turn my head more.
Hi, Sam.
Hi. Sorry about last night.
Oh, no. Don't
worry about it.
You feeling better?
You didn't
bruise, did you?
Sweetheart,
it's not a peach.
So...
you, uh... still
want to be a mommy?
Do you still
want to be a daddy?
I do if you do.
I do.
Great. All right. Great.
I'll... I'll be
right back.
Hold it. Hold it.
Wait. Wait.
We have to
sit a second.
What?
Look, I don't
want this to be
that we just do it.
I want this to be special.
I mean,
what's going to happen
when our child asks us
about the night we conceived?
What are we going to say?
How about, "Mind
your own business"?
Sam, be serious.
I know. I know.
Let's do something that
you have never done
before with a woman.
All right, all right.
Okay, okay, okay.
Let... let... let's do something
that you've only done once.
Okay. All right.
You got, uh...
You've got, uh...
Let's just have a nice,
simple, romantic evening.
All right. Now,
that I can do.
That I can do.
Tell you what.
You got a
fireplace, right?
Yeah.
Well, there you go.
It's a perfect evening.
Dinner, fire,
a little Jiffy Pop.
Sam, don't be crass.
No, no, no.
I was talking
about popcorn.
Oh!
That was funny.
Oh, you've got a date!
All right.
Wait a minute.
Woody, we're out of here.
You're in charge of the bar.
Well, why bother, Sam?
Whenever you
put me in charge,
nobody ever
listens to me.
I just get laughed at,
and get drinks
poured over my head.
If anyone does that to you,
you just sic Carla on them.
I'm talking
about Carla.
Oh.
All right,
listen up, everybody!
Whenever Rebecca and I
aren't in the bar, uh...
Woody's in charge.
(everyone laughing)
That better?
Kind of. At least
it's not a margarita.
Those get salt in my eyes.
Listen, I'm...
I'm out of here, guys.
I'll be back
in a couple of hours
depending on
how things go here.
Where're you going, Sam?
It... it's kind of personal,
Norm.
Ah! Uh, let me
get that for you.
Oh.
Here we go.
Sammy's acting
kind of weird, huh?
Yeah.
Can't you beer butts
figure it out?
Sam's been searching
for weeks
to find a perfect woman
to have his baby.
Obviously, he's given up
and asked Rebecca.
No way. Something that big,
Sammy would have told us.
Why do you assume
the rest of the
world lives by
your outdated code
of male bonding?
Do you think
that every man
goes around
telling his buddies
when he decides to
sire an offspring?
Frasier did.
Anyhoo...
(coughing)
Woody, can you do something
about that smoke?
Don't worry, Mr. Clavin,
I'll take care of it.
(coughs)
Excuse me, sir.
My name
is Woody Boyd,
and I'm kind of
in charge
here tonight.
Well, my friend
over there
is kind of bothered
by your smoke,
and so I was hoping you
could move to the back
to the smoking section.
I think that would really be
the considerate thing to do.
You can tell
your friend this.
(coughing)
So, Woody, what
did he say?
(coughs)
Wow. I'm impressed.
Where did you learn
how to cook?
When I was a kid,
my mom thought that
all boys should do
a little bit of cooking.
I never knew that.
Oh, yeah. I have
a sensitive side.
Matter of fact, why don't
we put on some music
and see how long it
takes you to find it.
Where do you keep
your Johnny Mathis?
I don't think
I have any.
Oh. Well, who needs music?
Allow me.
♪ Look at me... ♪
I didn't know you
could sing that high.
I couldn't
before the coatrack.
(humming "Misty")
(giggling)
What?
Nothing.
I'm just nervous.
Oh, come on. Nothing
to be nervous about.
Oh, no. I mean,
we're going to make
the biggest decision
of our lives.
I mean, don't you think
that's a little bit scary?
Come on. You can't...
can't pressure yourself
like that.
I mean, you know,
once we do this,
there's no turning back.
No, no, no, no. Come on.
That's just the thing
you can't think about here.
"After tonight, everything
will be different for life."
Or, uh... "I may have done
this a million times,
but this is the
one that counts."
I mean, you, uh...
you start doing that,
you're not going
to be able to do it.
Sam, you're not thinking
about it, are you?
No, no. Don't be silly.
Oh, you're right, Sam.
Let's just go for it.
Uh... Right now?
It's now or never, Sam.
Uh...
Let's make a baby.
No, you know...
but... but right now?
What's the matter?
Nothing's the matter.
Don't be silly.
It's just that,
uh... you know,
not everything's right
right now, you know?
Uh... we don't
have Johnny Mathis.
Yeah, that's it.
Uh... tell you what.
Why don't I, uh...
Why don't I go
to the record store?
I'll be right back.
No! Sam...
If we're going to make a baby,
I'm going to need my Johnny!
What's wrong, Sam?
Sam, what is it?
I... I... I...
What? What?
Is it an accident?
A fire?
Do you want us
to follow you?
Sam, look. Just pull
yourself together
and tell me what it is.
I... can't.
Yes, you can.
Look. Just organize
your thoughts,
form the words,
and tell me.
I can't.
Sam, if you want
me to help you,
you're going to have to
tell me what the problem is.
I am!
Well, then, what is it?
I can't!
You can't what?
Oh, dear Lord.
Am I to assume
that Sam Malone
is unable to...?
You gotta help me, man.
All right, Sam.
Let's, uh...
Let's examine
this problem. Uh...
Okay.
What is the difference
between this experience
and the thousands of times
that have gone before?
All right. Well, uh...
It was with Rebecca.
You've been intimate
with Rebecca before?
Yeah. No. It...
It's not sex. I mean,
we want to have a baby.
We...
What we're trying to do is, is
wholesome and natural
and beautiful,
and it's turning me off.
(door opens)
Sam, your whole life,
has been a string of
meaningless, albeit enjoyable,
sexual encounters. Now,
for the first time,
you're engaging
in a meaningful,
productive pursuit
See, it's a common conflict
between what we call
recreational sex and
procreational sex.
What?
Well, dirty sex
and clean sex.
Oh.
Now, it is this conflict that is
making you unable to function.
Oh. Oh, yeah.
That's good.
All right. Wow.
For a minute there,
I thought maybe
there was something wrong
with the seal on my microwave.
Now, Sam,
what you're gonna
have to do is, is
keep your mind thinking
of dirty things.
You see what I mean.
Skip everything about a baby.
Forget that Rebecca's
gonna be a mother.
Forget that you're
gonna be a father.
Instead, concentrate on the
heat, the passion you generate.
Trick your body into
thinking of this
as just another tawdry
one-night stand.
Come with me.
You can do it, Sam.
You have to.
You owe it to
men everywhere.
Yeah. All right,
all right, all right.
Think heat.
Think heat. Think heat.
Think heat, think heat.
Not yet, not yet.
Hey, Woodrot.
What's with the cigar
party back there?
Well, the smoking section
wasn't big enough,
so exercising
my powers as a manager,
I moved everybody
back into the pool room
Yeah, well, if
you'd exercise
your brain,
you'd realize
there are no vents, and the
windows are painted shut.
It's like Clavin in the
middle of July back there.
Well, what do
you expect?
There's no vents and the
windows are painted shut.
Don't worry, Carla,
I've installed a fan.
CARLA:
Oh.
All I gotta do is
some simple wiring.
(phone ringing)
Cheers.
It's nice to see
Woody in charge, huh?
Seems like only
yesterday he, uh,
couldn't find his
way around the bar,
and he got lost
in the storeroom.
That was yesterday.
Phone call for you,
Chalk Face.
Thank you...
Velcro Top.
I've been waiting
to use that.
Hello?
REBECCA:
Lilith.
Yeah?
Ha-Has Sam been there?
Uh, he was, but he just left.
Did he say anything?
Not to me. Why?
Can I trust you?
Of course
you can trust me.
I'm a professional.
If you have a problem,
I'm more than equipped
to help you work through it
in a rational manner.
Woody, two beers.
Shut up. This is juicy.
I'm sorry. Please continue.
You know, Sam and I
are trying to have a baby.
All right, tonight
when we were...
Just when things got all...
you know, heated
and involved, well...
he left for no
apparent reason. I mean...
I don't think Sam
was turned on.
Oh, my God. The seventh sign.
Now, look, what
am I doing wrong?
A-am I, am I not hot enough?
Am I not sexy enough?
Actually, Rebecca,
perhaps you're too sexy.
What do you mean?
And thank you.
Well,
Sam is the type of person
for whom sex has always
been down and dirty.
Now that he's trying
to father a child,
dirty sex is the furthest
thing from his mind.
He wants it clean.
So what do I do?
Well, don't act hot
and sexy, that's for sure.
Just keep reminding him
that he's making a baby.
The evening should be
sacred and holy.
That'll get his engine running.
I got it, Lilith.
Thank you so much.
All right.
Who was that on
the phone, dear?
I was just
counseling Rebecca.
And I was counseling Sam.
Recreational versus
procreational sex?
Exactly.
They're so lucky to have us.
CARLA:
Woody!
We can't
breathe in here.
We need you to turn
on that stupid fan.
All right.
It's all ready to go.
All I gotta do
is throw a switch.
(switch clicks)
(fan running)
(yelling)
Woody!
(knocking on door)
Honey? Oh...
Thank God you're still here.
I'm sorry I ran out like that.
Sam, don't say
another word.
Everything's going
to be just fine.
Oh, yeah. Oh, this is hot.
Mmm...
With heat like this, you'll
fertilize my egg in no time.
Yeah, uh...
Anyway, anyway, uh...
Just... Why, I tell you,
you are looking
so sexy tonight.
Yeah...
I'm about to grow your
child inside my womb.
Hotcha, hotcha, hotcha.
And then I'll give
birth to a new life,
and you'll be there
to cut that cord.
Are you gonna be talking
like this all night?
You...
You ain't heard nothing yet,
O, giver of life.
Giver....
Excuse. excuse me
just a second.
Hang on.
What...
(mutters)
REBECCA:
What's going on
in there... Daddy?
Uh, I'll be right out, Mommy.
Uh, I mean... Mama.
Hello.
Norm.
Yeah.
Uh, what are you
doing there, man?
Uh, where's Woody?
(gagging)
He's otherwise engaged.
Well, uh, Norm, Norm,
let me, let me talk
to Frasier, will you?
Yeah... Frasier.
Sammy.
What is it, Sam?
Listen. This is
not working, man.
(water running)
I'm thinking hot,
and all she keeps doing
is talking
about mother and stuff.
You must keep it hot,
Sam. Trust me.
I'm trying. I'm trying.
Sam, where are you now?
Uh, I'm in
the kitchen,
but don't worry.
She can't hear me.
I'm, uh, I'm running
the water here,
You can do that?
Whenever I hear water running,
it gives me the urge
to go to the bathroom.
Well, thanks a lot, man.
In fact, just hearing it
now, over the phone...
Lilith, would you...?
Frasier!
Sam?
Lilith.
Is everything all right?
Uh, Yeah, sure. No, it's fine.
Let me talk to Rebecca.
Um, all right. Okay. Hold,
hold on a second, will you?
Yeah, it's for
you. It's Lilith.
Excuse me.
Lilith?
Yes?
It's not working.
I've done everything
you've told me to do,
an-and he still has a problem.
Sounds to me like you're
still being too sexy.
Well, I don't know how...
You know, you are so kind.
Redouble your efforts.
You must remain wholesome,
no matter what.
Trust me.
I'll do my best.
All right.
All right, Rebecca,
That's it. No,
no more talking.
Just down and dirty
from here on out.
(both moaning passionately)
Oh, Sam...
as long as we're down
here on our knees,
Yes?
I think we ought to
take this chance to...
thank God for the great gift
He's about to give us.
Oh... that's it.
I give up.
What's the matter?
How do you expect me
to get in the mood
when you're talking
about babies and cords
and God and stuff?
Well, I thought that's
what you wanted to hear.
Where did you get that idea?
Lilith.
Lilith!
You talked to
Lilith about us?
Oh, come on,
I thought
this was just supposed
to be between you and me.
I can't believe you shared
this with somebody else.
Besides, Frasier said
we're supposed to act hot.
Sam...
if you were having a problem,
why didn't you just tell me?
Well, no. Wait, wait.
Who said I was
having a problem?
Well, weren't you?
Maybe.
Sam.
Oh...
You could've done
both of us a favor
if you had just told me
what I was doing wrong.
No. Oh, come on, you
weren't doing anything wrong.
It wasn't you.
It was me.
I mean, I've had sex
millions of times,
but it's, it's never
had a purpose before.
Well, that's not true.
It had a purpose, but, uh...
It didn't...
it didn't have a goal.
No, it had a goal.
It just...
It's complicated.
Sam, Sam, look. You
don't have to explain.
I just wish you'd been able
to talk to me, that's all.
Yeah, you're probably right.
I mean, if we can't
even talk to each other,
what kind of parents
are we gonna make?
Not very good ones.
Sam, maybe we're
not ready for this.
Maybe.
Shoot.
Well, uh... I guess
I'd better go, huh?
Okay.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You okay?
Oh, yeah.
♪ I am as helpless as a kitten
up a tree... ♪
(both chuckle)
How about that?
Johnny Mathis.
Say, I don't suppose your
neighbor is single, huh?
Yes, he is.
Oh.
♪ I can't understand ♪
♪ I get misty... ♪
Bye-bye.
♪ Just holding your hand... ♪
♪ Walk my way ♪
♪ And a thousand violins
begin to play ♪
♪ Or it might be the sound... ♪
(moaning):
Oh, baby...
Would you stop
saying that!