(Sam)
cheers  is filmed before
a live studio audience.
[People chattering]
hey, hey, guys, take a look.
Isn't that one
of the righteous brothers?
Yeah. You see, robin colcord
flew him in to sing
to rebecca earlier.
Wow! Which one is he?
I think
that's righteous brother #2.
No. That's-- that's
bill medley.
Hey, tall, dark,
and pipes
down to your shorts.
What are you doing
back here?
Well, my plane for reno
doesn't leave
for another 3 hours
and i didn't
have anywhere to go.
So, would you like
a drinking buddy?
You bet! Hey, guys!
(All)
hey!
So, bill, can we
buy you a beer, huh?
(Bill)
sure.
All right!
Ok! Let's see.
Uh, everybody pony up
6 cents.
Hey, bill.
[All clamoring]
did you ever
sing with the beatles?
Do you have
your own--
whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. Wait!
Whoa. One at a time.
I--i--i hope you don't mind
these questions, bill,
but, after all,
we are, uh, paying
for that drink.
Oh, no, no.
I love them.
Matter of fact, this is what
it's all about.
Being with the people
and talking about music
with the fans. I mean,
you guys are really
knowledgeable and aware
of what's goin' on.
Thank you.
And i dig it.
Now, what was your question?
Oh. Well, mr. Medley...
(bill)
mmm-hmm?
How come
you changed your name
from righteous?
Makin' your way
in the world today
takes everything
you've got
taking a break
from all your worries
sure would help a lot
wouldn't you like
to get away
sometimes you want to go
where everybody
knows your name
and they're always
glad you came
you wanna be
where you can see
our troubles
are all the same
you wanna be
where everybody
knows your name
you wanna go
where people know
people are all the same
you wanna go
where everybody
knows your name
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
hey, woody.
Hey, sam.
Is, uh, rebecca here yet?
Oh, no.
She left a message.
Um,
"i'll be back later.
Right now
i'm on top of the mold."
What?
Give me that here.
Oh, woody.
That's not an "m."
It's a "w."
She's going to be
"on top of the, uh, wolb."
Let me see this.
No, it says
an "o-u" there.
You see, cliffie?
She's "on top
of the wa-wa-waoud."
It's "top of the world."
"Top of the world."
The expression is
"top of the world."
No, no, no.
Look at it, doc.
Read that.
Well, i stand corrected.
She is indeed
"on top of the wolb."
Poor kid.
Huh?
What do you mean, sammy?
After you guys left last night
at little wally's,
she went into the ladies' room
to get some burger grease
off her blouse or something
and guess who pulls up.
Robin colcord
with another woman.
Aw, come on.
That figures.
No sooner
does squire colcord
put an end
to rebecca's celebrated
4 years of celibacy
than he's off baling hay
with some other wench
the very next night.
The man is absolutely
nothing more
than a rich, spoiled,
narcissistic philanderer.
I hate myself
for envying him so.
Well, if rebecca's
still riding high,
i guess she doesn't know
about robin's other babe.
How'd she miss spotting him
at little wally's?
Ah, come on, carla,
you know that place.
You can't see your hand
in front of your face,
what with the vapors
coming off wally's food
and, you know,
off of wally himself.
So, how'd you
handle it, sammy?
Well, you know me,
daddy cool.
I figured if she came
out of the bathroom,
she'd see him, so...
well, i jumped in.
I think i handled it
pretty smoothly.
Fire! Fire!
[Women screaming]
i'll get you out
through the window here.
No, no, no,
you two can use the door.
Why can't i use the door?
Are you kiddin' me?
You walk through that door
with all that grease
on your blouse,
one spark, you'll go up
like a roman candle.
Oh, smart idea, smart idea.
Ok, good.
[Grunting]
it's too small!
It's too small!
All right, all right.
Ah, shoot. Don't panic.
Uh--uh...
oh, i got it. I got it.
Here. Maybe i can squeeze you
through here, you know.
Take off all your clothes
and rub this soap
all over your body.
All right. Ok, fine.
Plan "b." Plan "b."
Wait! Wait!
Let's just get
out of here! Now!
I got it. All right,
all right, put this jacket
over your head.
I'll lead you out.
All right. Good. Sam,
that's good.
But what about you?
Uh, take off your blouse.
Put it over my head,
i don't know.
Sam!
Come on,
quit kiddin' around!
Careful, flames!
Wow. Great looks
and all that savvy.
Sam, i swear, if you
had a spigot in the middle
of your forehead,
i'd marry you
in a second.
Well, i hope that fire
didn't do a lot of damage.
I love little wally's.
Woody, there was no fire.
I just made that part up.
Well, she must have looked
like a darn fool
with your coat
wrapped around her face,
running through
the restaurant screamin'.
No, not at little wally's.
Well, you did good work,
sammy, fine work.
I don't know, guys. Thank you,
but the more i think about it,
you know, the more i wonder
if i did do the right thing.
I mean, she should know
what that guy's up to
before she gets in too deep.
Maybe i should tell her.
Don't, sammy.
Take it from a mailman.
People want to kill
the messenger.
Or at least overturn his cart
and kick the mail
around the hallway.
You know,
i agree with cliff.
There's a great deal
to be said for discretion.
You know,
it's entirely possible
that rebecca
may grow tired of robin
all on her own.
Thus avoid the heartache.
And on the other hand,
as one who was cuckolded
by a lover deeply trusted,
the longer led on,
the--the harder the fall.
I'm just not sure
that rebecca can--
can be as strong
and forgiving
as i was when...
that bitch diane dumped me.
Ah, you know, sam,
i had this cousin, skeeter,
who was in the army
a bunch of years ago.
Well, he never saw any action.
Although he did
blow off his thumb
in a mortar accident.
Big show-off.
Anyway, um, he was going out
with this girl,
and she went
to the kiwanis dance
with this other guy,
laird danielson.
I saw them
kissing and hugging
behind the propane tanks.
I was pretty much
in the same spot
as you are now.
What did you do?
Nothing. I'm waitin'
to hear what you do.
I'm gonna tell her.
There he is, my hero.
He was probably too modest
to tell you all,
but this man rushed me
through a burning building
with his coat over my face
and then led me
out of the fire.
And i am telling you
the fire was so close
that i could feel the flames
licking my ears.
It was hot, all right.
Anyway, sam, i just
want to thank you again
for saving my life.
Listen, there's, uh...
i probably should have
told you this last night.
[Clears throat]
sit down here, will you?
This is, uh, not going to be
very easy to tell you, here.
Um... come on,
how do i start?
Ixnay, ammy-say,
the imey-lay!
The what?
[Gasps]
robin.
(Robin)
rebecca.
My sweet baby.
A budding rose.
I brought it myself
because i didn't want you
to miss even a moment
of its bloom.
Oh, my god.
This is so cool.
Oh, robin, i can hardly wait
till we're alone together
again tonight.
Oh, yes, about tonight,
i'm terribly sorry.
An emergency board meeting
has been called.
How about a late supper
afterwards?
Yeah, well,
the meeting could last
through the night, you know.
I could last
till the morning.
What say we put that
to the test tomorrow night,
huh?
All right. I'll rest up.
Ole.
Ow!
Are you ok?
No.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm just gonna go
put this in water.
Sam, i want to thank you
for your discretion
last night,
that is, if running
alongside a screaming woman
with a sack over her head
can be called discretion.
That wasn't a sack,
that was my jacket.
Really? Please buy
one for me, huh?
Well, at any rate,
i want to thank you.
And as a man of the world,
i'm sure you've been
in similar circumstances
and know how embarrassing
it can be.
It was nice to find
an ally in a sticky situation
like that.
Ally nothing.
I just didn't want to see
rebecca get hurt.
Nor do i.
So i hope you'll keep up
your continued silence,
i mean, if the event
should ever repeat itself.
"Emergency board meeting."
You got another date tonight,
don't you?
Sadly, um, yes.
I don't think
i want to help you, pal.
Sam, you surprise me.
You and i have
the same weakness.
Beautiful women.
I hoped,
perhaps, men like us
shared a common bond.
Oh, no, we don't
share anything together here.
You know,
rebecca's my friend.
You got a lot of nerve
to think i'm gonna
help you cheat on her.
I see, you're taking
an ethical stand.
Well, let me counter
with this.
One phone call from me,
and you can
have your bar back.
Why do you think
that you can always
buy anything--
the whole bar?
Uh-huh.
No down payment?
Cheers will be yours, sam.
Ok.
I don't feel very good
about this, though.
Yes, well,
you can, um, print that
on your cocktail napkins.
Well, i'm off for
a strenuous board meeting.
I thought i got
all that thorn out,
but it still feels like
there's something in there.
[Ice cubes clinking]
ah.
Oh, sam, you said you had
something real important
you wanted to tell me?
Yeah.
I think i just made a deal
to buy back the bar.
That's wonderful!
Isn't that fun?
You get the bar.
I get robin.
[Chuckling]
don't you feel great?
[Door opening]
[door closing]
i...
feel...
bad.
You've lost
that lovin' feelin'
hi, there. Welcome to cheers.
We're glad to have you here.
Whoa, that lovin' feelin'
hi, there. You look
like a couple in love.
This is a place for love.
Does this place for love
have a waitress?
We've been waiting 20 minutes.
Well, i could take your order.
Oh, might i suggest
2 hot toddies and a walk
hand in hand
along the charles?
To be honest with you,
susan and i haven't been
getting along lately.
Give us
whatever you're havin'.
Sammy, i'm tellin' you,
if she doesn't cut out
that mushy stuff,
she's going to lose
that lovin' feeling
from the neck down.
Oh, come on.
It's not that bad,
is it?
Elaine, honey,
your break time is over.
[Playing that loving feeling
by the righteous brothers]
i can't believe
she's got a harp in here.
Yeah.
Well, look how great
it slices these eggs.
Oh, oh, oh
elaine, elaine, sweetheart,
i never thought
i'd say this to a woman,
but please,
give your fingers a rest,
will you?
Would somebody give me
a hand with this?
Oh, yeah, yeah,
i'd be happy to.
I wonder if you know
that the, uh, harp here
is the grandfather
of modern-day guitar.
Yeah, it seems
that early minstrels
were much larger people.
Never mind.
I'll lug it myself.
Huh? Well, suit yourself.
I hear, they, uh, had hands
the size of small dogs.
Sammy, you got
to stop rebecca.
You just got to tell her
before this goes any farther.
Yeah, come on, sammy,
put us out of our misery,
will you?
Yeah, sammy, come on.
She's thinkin' of replacing
the beer nuts with these
little candy hearts
that say, "hold me."
"I'm yours."
"Lovey-dovey."
Hey. "Free beer."
Oh, no, mr. Peterson.
Fool me once.
It's gotta be told now,
sam.
"If it were done
when 'tis done,
then t'were well
it were done quickly."
I'm sorry?
Move it, pal!
No, i, uh,
no, i've thought about it,
and, uh, i'm not
going to say anything.
I just, you know,
i think i'm doing
the right thing here.
I mean, come on, you guys,
what she doesn't know
won't hurt her.
Well, sam, you've proven to be
a big disappointment to me.
Aw, come on, man,
don't--
no, no, no. You know,
i always modeled myself
after you.
Well, i mean,
not the way you're always
hung up on your looks,
that's kind of shallow,
really.
And not the chasing
after women part,
because that's kind of silly,
but the other part.
There is no other part.
Yeah, there is, sam.
There's a part of you
that's always lookin' out
for your friends.
I mean, that's the thing
about you that's made you
my hero,
but now, leaving miss howe
on the hook like that,
i may have to go back
to my old hero,
st. Thomas aquinas.
Guess what?
I found somebody
to sublet my apartment.
Why? You're moving?
Well, i can't expect robin
to live in my little hovel.
Um, you two are gonna
move in together?
Well, you know, i think
it's the logical next step.
You know, everything's been
going so well for me.
Man, i love the '90s.
You've lost that--
hey, you start
singin' again,
it's gonna be
a very short decade.
Uh, sweetheart,
wait. Listen.
Don't-- don't move out
of your apartment, honey.
Uh, i got something
i got to tell you.
Sit down here for a second.
What is it?
I know
this is the last thing
that you want to hear,
and i sure as hell wish
i didn't have to be
the one to tell you.
Well, just go ahead
and tell me.
Robin is seein' other women
behind your back.
What?
There--there was no fire
last night, sweetheart,
just robin and some tall,
auburn-haired babe
with legs up to her eyes.
How can you do this to me?
What?
I mean, just because
you're jealous,
the first chance you get,
you have to try
and submarine robin.
You need help.
Real help, not frasier.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Listen to me a second here.
I'm telling you the truth.
I thought
that you were my friend.
I am your friend, damn it.
I'll tell you
how good a friend i am.
Robin was gonna buy
this bar back for me
if i kept my mouth shut.
Oh, brother!
How low can you sink?
Do you really expect me
to believe a stupid story
like that about my sweet baby?
Honey...
the guy doesn't have
a board meeting.
He-he's with that woman
right now.
I-- fine, fine.
I'm just gonna
prove you wrong.
I'm gonna go over there,
i'm gonna wait outside
that board meeting.
No.
Yes, i am.
And then he's gonna come out,
and i'm gonna see him,
we'll smooch a little bit,
and then we will laugh
about you and your stupid
pitiful lies.
[Door closing]
well, i don't care
if she doesn't believe me,
i'll tell you...
you know, i--i feel good
about myself
because i told the truth
and you know, when it comes
right down to it,
i'll be able
to live with myself.
Sammy, come here.
Yeah? What?
You could have had
the bar back, you jackass!
Surprise, darling!
[Both screaming]
what's going on? Oh!
Robin, who is this?
Who am i?
Who are you?
Well, i see introductions
are in order.
Christine davi,
new york city ballet,
rebecca howe,
proprietor of cheers.
Sam was right.
Oh, god, why does this
always happen to me?
How can somebody
as beautiful as i am
be such a loser?
Robin, i thought
we had something.
You're seeing her, too?
Well, this evening is off
to a rollicking start.
Robin, i am not
the kind of person
who fools around
with just anybody.
Are you saying i am?
Ballerina, why don't you
make like a swan and die?
Robin, i need
a one-woman man.
And i am
It's just that
i'm still looking
for the one woman.
But you can both take heart.
I've got it
narrowed down to 3.
You two and a little
chargee d'affaires
in the french consulate.
Well, i don't care
who you are.
I have my self-respect.
No one treats christine davi
like this.
Oh, uh--uh...
christine, uh...
so...
now i guess
it's down to 2.
Rebecca, you don't know
how lucky i am
to find
someone so understanding
and compassionate as you are.
Not so fast, robin.
I have a little
self-respect myself.
You're gonna have to choose,
robin, right now.
Is it gonna be me
or your
chargee d'affaires?
Well, honestly,
i don't know.
Fine.
Then promise me you'll
think about it a while.
Hi, sam.
Hello.
Well, i guess
i owe you an apology.
Ah, i'm sorry.
Feeling all right?
Me? Fine.
Well? Did you tell him
to take off?
No, sam. That would be
the easy thing for me to do.
Why, did you let him
off the hook?
Did he promise that he wasn't
going to see any more women?
No, sam. That would be
the easy thing for him to do.
Well, what are we
left with here?
A deeper understanding
of our relationship
and, uh,
what we, as mature adults,
are gonna do
to make it work out.
You bought that?
For your information,
robin wants very much
to get married.
He does?
Yes, he does. To me.
Or one other woman.
He narrowed it down.
That's a nice touch.
Sam.
Oh, come on.
Something worth having
is worth fighting for.
No. You sold out.
I absolutely
did not sell out.
I merely entered
a fair contest
where the payoff
would satisfy any woman's
wildest dreams.
You really believe that?
[Choking up]
i believe
every single word.
[Sobbing]
oh, boy.
What am i gonna do?
I feel so cheap
and so used, i think.
Oh, god, sam.
I can't do this to myself.
I'm gonna have to break it off
with robin.
Well, it's the right thing
to do.
Oh, god, why do i feel
so miserable?
It's never the right thing
unless you do feel miserable.
I know.
I'm just gonna--
i'm just gonna tell him
it's over.
I'll just say to him, um...
that's it, sweet baby.
I mean, you know,
robin colcord is not worth
me losing my dignity.
Oh, yeah.
Dignity...
why not?
I've tried everything else
in my life.
Rebecca, i knew
i'd find you here.
That's fascinating.
Everyone else in the world
at the end of the evening
goes to their homes.
You people come to this bar.
This is your chance.
You give him hell.
I'm going to make him wish
he'd never been born.
Robin...
mr. Colcord--
rebecca, i'll be brief.
You were very understanding
about that little incident
back in my limo,
and i think that kind
of understanding
should be rewarded.
So i'd like you to have this.
It's a diamond bracelet.
It's not much, really,
though it does come
with a security guard.
[Scoffs]
[whispering intensely]
it's gorgeous!
No.
Robin, you know,
i don't love you
for your money
or your diamonds
or the fact that you can buy
my friends bars.
I love you because i think
you're a very interesting man
and i thought
you cared about me.
Oh, i'm sorry.
I'm ashamed of myself
for trying
to buy your feelings.
I want to tell you
that i'm still the same man
and i still care for you
the same as i did before.
Well, by that,
do you mean that you
care for me, but you still
want to see other women?
Exactly.
But i should like to point out
that if i'd offered
this bracelet
to my  chargee d'affaires,
she would've snapped it up
in a blur.
I admire your standards.
You know, this definitely
puts you in the lead.
I must go.
Would you care to join me?
Did you hear that?
I am winning.
I'm winning.
You've got to... listen...
listen to me
for a second here.
Come on, you're giving up
something very valuable
and very important.
You're gonna regret this
the rest of your life.
[Gasps]
you're right.
I will take that bracelet.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org