Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Woody!
Have you finished counting?
Sure have, Miss Howe.
CLIFF:
Ah, come on, Rebecca.
What, guess-how-many-beans-
in-the-jar bit?
That's so corny.
For your information,
corny is in.
America wants
to return to the innocence
of their teenage years.
Yeah, the '70s
were great,
weren't they?
Anyway, this contest
will run all month,
and all of Boston
will be playing
the game
for a fabulous
all-expense-paid trip
to where?
BOTH:
Atlantic City!
For just guessing
how many jelly beans
are in this jar.
Uh... 3,500.
Woody, is that
the correct number?
Nope.
Off by 163.
Woody!
You are not supposed
to tell them that.
Now we have to do this
all over again.
Do you have any extra
jelly beans back there?
Sure, there's a whole bag
at the end of the bar.
I hate when the black ones
get stuck in your teeth.
( piano plays )
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always glad
you came
You want to be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You want to be where everybody
knows your name
You want to go
where people know
People are all the same
You want to go where
everybody knows your name.
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
Hey, guys,
guys, guys, guys.
Watch this.
Hi, gorgeous.
Want to go out with me?
I've got a little cold.
Oh... next week?
I'm busy.
The week after?
Maybe.
You saw it.
You were there.
Sam Malone
just scored a "maybe."
Yow!
Well, well, this calls
for a celebration.
Waters all around.
Why, what?
Oh, this is truly sad.
I mean, a guy who would
never settle for less
than eight dates a week
is doing back-flips
over a lousy "maybe."
Hey, come on, that's progress
for me and Rebecca.
Face facts.
You had it once but you lost it.
You ain't nothing but Clavin
in a good shirt.
Yeah, I guess we're gonna have
to go shopping for a new hero.
Oh, guys, guys, I can't
believe my ears.
Well, Sam, your ears are
the least of your problems.
You think I'm losing it?
What, you need proof?
No, no, no. Not necessary.
No, no, listen, I want
to prove to you guys
that I'm still your king.
Everybody, please.
Focus your attention
on the door there.
The Amazing Sammy
will now make love
to the very next woman
who enters this bar.
Be right back.
SAM:
No, no, no. Hold it.
Hey, employees are ineligible.
I quit!
We're closed.
SAM:
Too late,
too late.
My lovely volunteer.
NORM:
Sammy, you're amazing.
SAM:
Yeah?
Now, I want to assure you that
we've never met before.
If you watch very closely
you will notice,
that at no time does my hand
actually leave her body.
You know, she's exactly
like a girl I took out
last night.
You mean "tore out."
Excuse me.
Boy, is it hot in here
or is it just you?
I'm sorry, did you just say
is it hot in here
or is it just me?
Yep.
If you like, there's more
where that came from.
Are you for real?
I've been asked that question
many times,
and by women a lot
more naked than you.
( both laughing )
You know,
I've heard about men like you,
but I can't actually say
I've ever met one.
I'm on a roll here.
My name's Sam Malone.
My name is being withheld
for security reasons.
Well, that's very clever.
Maybe too clever.
What's it mean?
It means I'd like to order
a Manhattan.
I'd like you to put a cherry
in it,
and then I'd like you
to put a sock in it.
Your drink.
Greetings, all.
Ah, Doctor.
Doctor.
FRASIER:
Ah, Woody,
may I have a beer please
and a mineral water
for the little mother.
You know, Lilith and I
heard a little joke
the other day.
It seems a patient
walks into
his therapist's office
suffering from a case
of Korsakoff's psychosis
brought on by acute alcoholism.
Brain tumor.
Well, darling, it doesn't make
any difference.
Yes, it does.
Brain tumor is funnier.
You're right.
No wonder I didn't get anywhere.
She's a friend of Lilith
and Frasier's.
She's another one of those
boring,
cold-hearted intellectuals
with legs I could kill for.
Why, Sam?
I like your legs.
If you comb your hair
a little different,
no one will even notice
that ear problem.
Thank you.
And then the therapist said
"No, I said ten cc's,
not Tennessee."
( laughing )
Or was it Kentucky?
It was Tennessee.
Well, it was good.
( laughing )
I'll have to remember that one.
Hello, Lilith.
Hello, Frasier.
Hello, Sam.
I'd love to stay and talk
but I'm under a gag order.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize you were
a friend of the Cranes.
I'm Sheila Rydell.
Oh, how do you do?
Dr. Rydell
is a clinical psychiatrist
and also a fellow
at the Boston University.
Oh, well, thank God
she's a woman here at Cheers.
( pager beeping )
Doctors, excuse me a moment.
I need to call a patient.
Oh, yes, there's a phone
right down the hall.
This will probably
take a few minutes
so I'll meet you upstairs
shortly.
Fine.
Well, doctor, I have
a free phone right here.
I'm looking
for a little more privacy.
I have a phone in my bedroom.
Thank you, no.
FRASIER:
Honey bear, shall we?
Oh, by the way, Sam.
Yeah?
Re: Doctor Rydell,
I must say I concur completely.
You know, most women
who go into psychiatry
are real bowsers,
but, uh,
I wouldn't kick her off
the couch
for eating crackers, you know?
Frasier, I can hear you,
and so can your unborn child.
Will he be able
to escape from this one?
Let's watch.
What I meant to say was, um,
please, please, please
forgive me. And, um...
do you think we have time
to stop by Tiffany's
on the way home?
Good boy.
Boy, I tell you,
I want that woman.
Sam, she's carrying
Dr. Crane's baby.
No, no, not that woman.
The woman
over by the phone.
Oh, well, who doesn't?
Hubba, hubba.
Sam.
Yeah?
Mr. Cool, I hate to burst
your bubble again,
but didn't she just
shoot you down?
Hey, maybe you should
just stay away
from brunettes.
Except me,
of course.
Yeah.
No, no, don't you see here?
The good doctor and I
are sparing.
It's sexy, it's fun.
Just like one of those
old Spencer Tracy-
Audrey Hepburn movies.
Sammy, would you step
in my office, please?
A word in your ear.
You know, if I were you,
I'd approach
the good Dr. Legs there
on a professional level.
I would make an
appointment with her
and pretend there was
something wrong with me.
Cliffie,
that's a pretty good idea.
Yeah, who gave it to you?
It's mine.
It, uh, came right
from this brain.
Hey, everybody,
Clavin got a new brain.
So what do you think?
Uh... What kind of problem
should I make up?
Well, uh, how about this?
I once took one of my kids
to the school psychiatrist
and he said the kid
had kleptomania.
Anything come of it?
Got a couple of pens
and a leather appointment book.
Yeah, or you could try
using my problem.
I've always had this terrible
fear of being a failure.
You are a failure.
Well, then I've licked it.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
I've got a suggestion.
This is surefire.
It's going to get you
where you really want her.
Impotence.
Ooh-ooh-ooh, no.
No, that's a word us guys
don't even like to say.
Wait a minute, take it from me.
We women are pushovers
for this kind of stuff.
Hey, there are two things
that women like to do
more than anything else
in the world.
And one of them is
to cure a guy of impotence.
What's the other thing?
Give it to him again
if he gets out of line.
No, I tell you,
I don't care
how hot that lady is.
That's... I just couldn't
say something like that to her.
Okay, so I tell her
that I'm impotent.
Mr. Malone.
Oh, it is the same
Sam Malone.
I hope this is
a professional visit.
Oh, I'm sad to say yes.
Doctor, I need to
unburden myself here,
and I figured that you
were the one person
maybe I could talk to.
Of course.
Sit down.
Now take your time.
Tell me what's troubling you.
Well, Doctor, as you know,
I'm a young, healthy male.
But recently I've...
Oh, heck, I'm not going
to mince words with you here.
Lately I haven't been able to
get the old evan root cranking.
Excuse me?
Um, well, it's like... uh...
it's like my favorite shirt
is a little light in the starch.
Are you trying to say
that you're impotent?
No, don't, oh,
don't use that word.
Oh, I see.
Yes, well, uh,
arousal dysfunction is
a fairly common problem,
but it can be
very, very, very distressing.
Oh, it is.
It is.
How does this problem
usually manifest itself?
Oh, it's too painful
to talk about.
I could demonstrate if you like.
No, thank you.
No, no, you're probably right.
With my luck, it would work,
you know...
Like when you take your car
to the mechanic, you know.
Of course, this isn't
my field of expertise,
but you're in luck.
My associate,
Dr. Heimlich Mueller
is conducting
a group session
at this very moment.
I'm sure he'd agree
to let you join in.
Actually I was kind of hoping
that you could handle it.
Oh, don't feel uneasy
about Dr. Mueller.
Those charges linking him
to the Gestapo
were grossly exaggerated.
Excuse me?
He was merely a consultant.
Actually, his technique
is somewhat controversial.
You'll have to go in there
and proclaim
your sexual disorder
to the group.
You want me to say that
in front of other people?
Oh, there are only a half dozen
men in there just like yourself,
and of course the 20 or 30
observing nurses.
Just go in there, stand up
and say "I'm Sam Malone,
and I no longer
function as a man."
No! No, no!
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no, no, I'm...
Listen, there's been
a misunderstanding here.
I didn't say "impotent,"
I said "impudent."
Yeah, I'm a smart ass.
See?
There's nothing wrong
with me, no, ma'am.
Then the cure worked.
That'll be $150.
Pay the receptionist
on your way out.
Oh... You-you've been...
you've been putting me on.
And that was very unfair of me
considering
how honest you were being.
All right, I admit that
I was making up that stuff
just because, well, you're...
a beautiful woman
and I just wanted to see
a little more of you,
that's all.
I see.
Well, actually, that's
kind of flattering.
Not very many men would come in
here and humiliate themselves
and tell some
childish, idiotic lie
just to spend five minutes
with me.
I'm a romantic.
So what do you say,
you want to go out to dinner?
I suppose I could use
a bit more romance in my life.
All right, great.
I'll call you,
next week sometime.
How about tomorrow night?
Great.
That's good, that's good.
All right.
Yeah, thanks very much. Ha.
( tape rewinds )
Um... excuse me.
See, I...
You didn't have that
tape recorder on, did you,
when I was making up
that stuff about imp...
Don't worry, Sam.
The moment you walked in here
I was aware you were faking
the whole thing
and I turned the recorder off.
Oh, good.
Well, thank goodness.
( laughing )
And I turned the intercom on.
Okay, boys,
closing time.
Let's move on out.
Probably want to go home,
get some rest,
so you can be back for
your 9:00 a.m. shift.
It's one of those days
I hate to see end,
you know what I mean?
Mm-hmm.
Hey, I got some
new videos.
You guys want to
come over my place?
New videos, great.
Yeah, yeah,
Ma had our home movies
converted to tape.
There's a great one of me
all dressed up as Peter Pan.
Ma's Captain Hook,
she's tying me up.
( chuckles ):
It's great.
For Halloween, huh?
No, no, it's a little game
we used to play
to help me sleep.
You know how
crazy teenagers are.
Well, Sheila, why don't you
hop up to the bar there,
I'll fix us
a little nightcap.
Oh, Sammy, you mind
if I take off early?
I want to put the little ones
to bed myself tonight.
Put them to bed?
Hey, it's 2:00 a.m.
Oh, right, they're
probably not home yet.
Ah, well, I'll get some sleep.
Hey, listen, don't forget
to put up the barstools.
Don't worry about it.
We'll do it later.
I hope so.
But take care
of the stools, too.
Sam, I had a really lovely time
with you tonight.
Well, you sound
a little surprised.
Well, I am a little.
I guess a lot of the men
I go out with
tend to be a little stuffy.
But you're so relaxed
and easy to be with.
And I must admit, I've never
seen a man do a puppet show
with lobster claws before.
Well, you were
a lovely audience.
Thank you.
Hey, and thank you for not
coming on like a psychiatrist.
What does that mean?
Well, I know you guys
always have your meter going.
And I was afraid you were
sitting there thinking
all sorts of weird,
head-shrinking things.
Well, as a professional,
you learn to keep those things
to yourself.
So you were thinking
those things?
Sam, I really prefer to divorce
business from pleasure.
Absolutely.
No, you're right.
Were they bad things?
Sam, I really think
it's a mistake
to pursue this matter
any further.
Oh, great.
I bet you wouldn't say that
if you were thinking
good things.
I mean,
you'd probably
come right out and say it if
you were sitting there thinking,
"Whoa, you know,
this guy is really together
and I'm lucky to be with him,
and boy, the hair."
So come on, tell me.
Really, Sam, no.
Hey, come on,
I can take it.
It'll be fun.
Sam, would you just
please drop the subject?
Okay.
Boy, you brain benders
are all the same, aren't you?
I mean, you want
two years of a guy's life
and every penny he earns
before you give him
one little simple diagnosis.
You know, I think
you're full of blabber.
I don't think you know
anything about me.
I think I do.
Yeah? Then why don't
you tell me.
All right, Sam, if you insist.
I do.
My professional
opinion of you
is that your every thought,
word and deed
revolves around sex.
You have nothing else
in your life.
Without constant sex,
you'd probably just shrivel up
into a little,
dried anchovy and die.
Well, who wouldn't?
I mean, that's it?
No bad stuff?
Sam, there's nothing
but bad stuff.
You're an aging lothario
who uses sex to cover up
massive insecurity,
a fear of true intimacy,
fear of a relationship
and quite frankly,
not only a fear of dying,
but a fear of living, too.
You're one sick cowpoke.
I resent that.
You know, you were
shoveling down that
lobster tonight
like there was
no tomorrow.
You know, you even ate
the green stuff
and this is the thanks I get?
Sam, you forced me to tell you.
What did you want me to do, lie?
Of course, yes.
Oh, Sam, come on.
Why don't we just
forget the whole thing
and go back to my place?
What?
You still want
to go to bed,
even though sex
is supposedly
the only thing
I have in my life?
Exactly.
And so I assume
you're rather good at it.
You would actually
have sex with somebody
you don't even respect?
Isn't that what
you do with women?
Yeah, but I cover it up.
I mean, how long have you
lived in America, lady?
Oh, Sam, come on.
No, listen, I think
you ought to take a hike.
I'll tell you what,
send me a bill
for another hundred and a half,
I'll deduct the lobster.
Well, I'm sorry
if this was painful,
but maybe it was good
for you to have heard it.
By the way, if you change
your mind about the sex,
I can be beeped anytime.
That's so pathetic!
Oh!
( groans )
Are you locking up?
Hey, let me ask you something.
Do you think that my life is
empty and void of any meaning?
Yep.
Don't forget to lock up.
Oh, b...
Tough night on
the dating circuit, Sam?
Oh...
Do you believe... my...
My date told me that there
was nothing in my life
except women or sex.
By the way,
you look hot tonight.
Come on, Sam,
you have a lot going for you.
Yeah?
Like what?
There's...
Ooh, I could go on and on.
See you later, Sam.
Wait a minute.
Come on, answer the question.
What do I have in my life
that isn't women or sex?
Come on, Sam,
you're a passionate guy.
I bet you have a lot of things
that you care deeply about.
Yeah, like what?
Your job.
It's a great way to meet babes.
You love your car.
Babes love it.
Sailing.
Babes on waves.
See?
Then the doctor was right,
I'm a shallow guy.
I mean, everything I do
is to impress women
or revolves around sex.
I guess I'm nothing more
than a hot, manly
machine of love.
Um, uh...
Sam, wait.
What about the Stooges?
They're all right,
they're over at Cliff's.
No, no, Sam.
What about the Three Stooges?
Oh, yeah, great.
I like the Three Stooges.
That helps a lot.
Wait a minute, Sam.
Think about this.
Do women like
the Three Stooges?
No, they hate them.
All right.
Are women impressed that
you like the Three Stooges?
No, some of them
even think they're stupid.
When you're watching
the Three Stooges,
do you think they're sexy?
No, when you watch
the Three Stooges,
nobody has time to think
about sex or women.
Hey, wait a minute.
That means
I do have another
interest in my life.
I like the Stooges
for themselves.
Hey, whoa, I'm okay.
Nyuk, nyuk, nyuk!
( imitates Curly )
That's fine, Sam.
Come here, porcupine.
( squeals )
Knock it off.
Come on, try it,
you'll like it.
Come on, do it.
All right.
There you go.
Come here, porcupine.
( loud smack )
SAM:
Ooh.
Hey, the Stooges don't bleed.
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.podnapisi.net