Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Hey, Sam. Sorry I'm late.
Had to stop at the drug store.
That's okay, Woody.
Yep.
Had to make another embarrassing
trip to the drug store
to get a little, uh...
Protection?
Yeah.
You know, Kelly and I want
to have a family and all,
but we figured we'd
wait until after that raise you promised.
Hope you got a lot
of protection.
Well, as usual, you know,
I'm a little embarrassed
and nervous when I go in there,
so I buy a whole bunch of stuff
so it doesn't look
like I'm just trying
to get some... you know.
Protection.
Yeah. So I got some
paper plates...
batteries, flashbulbs,
Skol...
some gum...
Chia Pet...
oh, eyeglass repair kit...
Yeah.
Oh, notebook paper...
and... VO5.
Where's the, uh...
where's the protection?
See you in about an hour, Sam.
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Hi, Ma.
Hey! Look who's here.
Serafina!
What are you
doing here? I need to talk to you.
You're pregnant.
REBECCA:
Carla, that is
a rude and unfair thing to say.
There's a million reasons why your
daughter would want to talk to you.
I am pregnant.
Then again, you raised a slut.
Sit down.
Now, oh, God...
first of all...
are you getting sick
in the morning?
A little bit, but I
haven't had to "Clavin,"
if that's what you mean.
And to answer
your next question,
no, it wasn't planned.
Oh, Serafina...
I have been praying
that this day wouldn't come,
but I can't say I'm
all that surprised.
In fact,
I have this little speech
I've been carrying around
in case it did happen.
"Dear Serafina,
soon you will be 14 and able
to think for yourself."
Mom.
I'm 18.
That's right, you are.
None of this applies.
(groans)
So, do you know who the father is?
Yes.
Oh, honey, I'm so proud!
It's Pat McDougall,
the guy I've been going with.
Isn't he that retired cop
who's just living off
his disability? That's right.
And now he wants to marry me.
Do you love him?
Yes.
Then don't marry him.
What?
The worst thing you could do,
Serafina, is marry for love.
You know, when I first met
your deadbeat father, Nick,
I loved him, too.
Even when he knocked up
my sister, I said...
hey, look, the guy
is just trying
to get in good with the
family at my wedding.
But for the next ten years,
all he did was cheat on me,
treat me like dirt and keep
me in maternity clothes.
Mom, it's not like that-
Pat's a good man.
He loves me and I love him,
and we want to build
a life for our baby.
Please give us your blessing.
Well... you're not
gonna get that alimony
by staying single.
Mom, you're the best!
Hey, my daughter's
getting married!
Hey!
Oh!
This'll be interesting.
Yeah.
Finally, a wedding where
I don't envy the bride.
Thanks, Ma-
you won't regret this.
And listen, Pat and I are
gonna pay for the whole thing.
Oh, no, no, no, no,
you are my daughter,
and you're in love,
and I'm gonna make you
the best reception I can-
we're pulling out all the stops.
You know, there is an elegant,
tasteful restaurant upstairs,
and as luck would have it,
I am boinking the owner.
Hey, Hill! It's Carla.
Come on down here,
we got to talk.
Hill? What are you doing?
Come on.
You don't have to
have it up there.
Have it down here at Cheers.
Oh, no, no, we can have
the reception here,
but we got to have
the ceremony upstairs. Why?
Every wedding we have
at Cheers is a disaster.
Uh, remember you and Diane?
This place is jinxed.
No, it's not- you're just
thinking of the bad ones.
What about, uh,
Barry and JoAnne?
Barry! Come here.
Barry, how's it going
with you and JoAnne?
Where have you been, in a cave?
All right, Miss Tortelli,
just what is it?
My daughter Serafina has just
announced she's getting married.
Congratulations.
When's the baby due?
SERAFINA (calling):
Here I come, Mom! Get ready!
What do you think?
SAM:
That's great, Serafina.
You look great.
Kind of sleazy for
a wedding outfit.
Sam, that was my wedding dress.
When I say "sleazy,"
I mean sleazy in a beautiful
young bride kind of way.
Carla, is that Cap'n Gus
and his Polka Pirates?
It's my daughter's
wedding, isn't it?
Ah, Miss Tortelli,
there you are,
an hour behind schedule, I see.
You're as prompt
as you are lovely.
What do you want, Hill?
And by the way, you have
your toupee on wrong.
The hair goes on the outside.
Miss Tortelli, I'm
here to remind you
that this wedding must be
over by 11:30 on the dot.
That's when I open for lunch.
You open for lunch at noon.
I know your family-
they leave at 11:30;
At 11:31 the
Orkin man arrives.
And please also
remind your guests
that even though
this is a wedding,
it is still a restaurant.
No shoes, no shirt, no service.
Hi, everybody.
Hey, Kelly, Woody.
I'll go put this on
the gift table, Woody.
Uh, hey, Woody, what'd you
get for the happy couple?
Ah, well, strictly
between you and me,
went up in the attic,
dug up one of our wedding gifts.
One of the ugliest things
I ever saw.
We couldn't wait
to get rid of it.
Ah, yeah, so you just
thought you'd, uh,
pass it on to the
happy couple, huh?
Good thinking.
So, uh, what is it?
Oh, a set of
Star Trek steak knives.
FRASIER:
Woody, damn it!
That gift was
from Lilith and me!
They're delightfully whimsical
and-and very utilitarian.
Uh, I-I'm sorry Dr. Crane.
I didn't realize.
Well, all right, Woody.
To tell you the
truth, I, I was doing
the same thing you
were doing. I...
Fobbing off a gift
that we thought
was the worst thing
we ever got.
Thanks a lot, Fras.
That was from Vera and me.
You and Vera gave those away?
You better not tell Ma.
Hey, there.
Remember me?
Yes, I do.
You're Carla's son, Gino.
And I did not appreciate
the nude photos of
yourself that you sent.
You know, it's the best I could
do at the machine at the mall.
Gino, would you
forget about it?
I'm not gonna go out with you.
You're much too young for me.
Oh. Yeah, right.
Coo-coo-ca-choo,
Miss Howe.
Thanks for everything, Mom.
Oh, honey, you know,
I got to admit
that I wasn't too crazy
about this at first.
But after spending this last
week getting the wedding ready
and being with you
and everything,
I got to say it's been
the best week of my life.
Me, too.
Ah, am I in time
for the nuptials?!
Daddy!
Nick.
My little girl,
you look so beautiful.
(giggles)
Are those implants?!
Carla...
it's been a fortnight.
You colouring your hair?
I cannot believe this.
What else could
possibly go wrong?
Hi, gang at Cheers!
Sorry I'm late,
but I had to park the car.
And then I had walk
from the car to here.
How did you find out
about this?
My cousin Eddy called me.
He-he told me he
read it in the paper.
So I figured, uh, my invitation
got lost in the mail.
Daddy, I'm so glad you're here.
I can't wait for you
to meet my fiancé.
Stay right here;
I'll bring him down. Okay.
Hey, Nick.
Hey, Sam!
Hey. You, are not
welcome here.
Now, you just do us all
a favour and leave, okay?
You have no right to be here.
I have a right to be here!
I am the father of the bride!
I have a responsibility to give
away the hand of the betrothed!
It's what's called
loin entitlement.
You smelly little wart.
See, Kelly, we're not
the only couple
who has cute little nicknames
for each other.
Carla, I have to be
honest with you.
When I heard about
this wedding,
I was very hurt that
you excluded us.
After all, a marriage is
a time for forgiveness
and healing.
We drove 22 hours to get here.
We even bought a
beautiful present.
(snaps twice)
It's a set of Star
Trek steak knives.
Anyway, I have a
right to be here.
I'm, uh, I'm gonna stay.
Yeah?
You can just drive
22 hours back.
SAM:
Oh, come on, Carla.
It took them
so long to get here.
And-and, you know,
he is her father.
Oh, fine, fine.
You want Nick to be at
my daughter's wedding?
Well, you can have him.
Just have a great time!
Oh, come on, Carla.
Yeah, women, women.
Isn't it enough
we sleep with them?
So, uh, Nick, what have you
been up to lately, huh?
Oh, uh, well, we still live
in the glamorous
environs of Las Vegas,
although we recently did move.
We didn't like
our old neighbourhood,
so we just drove our house
to a better one.
Oh, uh, so how's
the career going, Nick?
Last time we chatted,
you were talking
about marketing some kind
of a, slot machine
for the home.
Oh yeah, "Flush and Win."
It was a great idea.
The only problem is that
people had a difficult time
retrieving their change.
Yeah, but I'm onto
something very big now.
And this is an opportunity for
me to include you, my friends,
in this future affluence.
Well, you know how I hate
to be apart from Vera...
Wait, wait, sit,
sit, hear me out.
I know I've had some crazy
schemes in the past,
but this is then and that
was then and this is now.
This is completely legit.
I have an opportunity, to
purchase, an orang-utan act.
Did he say
"purchase" or "join"?
Just need a couple of backers.
Hear this: three apes,
some banana oil,
and a broad that's
had all her shots.
Nicky, we missed you, lad.
CLIFF:
Hey, uh, Nick,
if you want somebody
to invest in that,
uh, act of yours there,
for Vegas,
you ought to go talk
to blondie over there.
Yeah, she's loaded.
Thank you.
Listen, you come to
Vegas, you're comped.
Excuse me, young man.
Hello Miss.
I'm Nick Tortelli.
Hello. I'm Kelly Boyd.
I can tell by your organda
that you have taste
and discernment.
Thank you.
Knock, knock.
Who's there?
Opportunity.
Opportunity who?
This is gonna take some time.
People, people,
it's getting late.
Now no one admires the sight
of a beautiful young bride
more than I, but the lunch
rush is the lunch rush.
Say John, I, I bet you'd like
to meet Carla's first husband.
Oh, my God!
Nice to meet you.
Please.
My profession requires
that I handle food.
Daddy, this is my fiancé, Pat.
Nice to meet you, sir.
Aw, enough of
the chit-chat.
Step into my office.
How do you propose to,
uh, support my progeny?
Well, I'm a retired
police officer
and currently living
off disability.
What is the nature
of your injury?
Whiplash.
Very good, difficult
to disprove.
Very bright.
Thank you, sir.
Bright enough to invest?
Pardon me?
Bright enough
to place your future
and the future of
your entire progeny
in the orang-utan act?
Come on, Carla, don't do this.
He has no right to be here.
I raised those kids.
He just split.
Yeah, I, I know that.
I made all the sacrifices.
I had to bear all the
burden, he did nothing.
Nothing. Well, what are you
gonna do, you know, the guy's here?
(drawer slams)
(yelling in pain)
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Sam, those kids are
all I got, okay?
I know.
They're all that matters to me.
He doesn't care about that.
He doesn't care who he hurts.
(knock at door)
Yeah, but...
Sam, Sam could you
hurry it up a bit?
Captain Gus has just played the
polka version of "Hava Nagila."
He's managed to
insult two cultures.
I'm not, I'm not
doing any good here.
Please, please talk
to her, will you?
All right, Sam.
Uh, Carla, look, I know what
you're going through.
I mean, you've sacrificed
your whole life for your kids
and now, on the big day,
Nick swoops in and tries
to hog all the glory.
Look, it happens all the time.
One parent uses the child as
leverage against the other.
Really, Doc?
Oh yes, yes.
Often in a broken marriage
the child becomes nothing more
than, a helpless pawn in the
war between the two adults.
Of course that hasn't happened
with, with Lilith and myself
because she's gone.
But, uh, she'll be back.
Oh, I know she'll be
back, you know why?
'Cause I have Frederick.
Yes, sir,
he's my little trump card.
Thank you very much.
He is, you know.
I have a plan.
(laughs evilly)
You're Nick, right?
Yes.
I'm Rebecca Howe.
I work here
in the bar with Carla.
And I just want to say
you must be very proud.
Oh I'm very proud.
Yes.
I know the last thing
that I would want to do
is introduce a dark note,
but if you don't get your hand off
my butt, you're gonna lose it.
NORM:
Sammy, how'd it go in there?
Oh, not good.
She refuses to come out.
I don't know...
Don't worry about it, Sam.
I'll handle it.
Carla, at times,
can be very obdurate.
She also can be
very recalcitrant,
intransigent and immovable.
Nicky got one of those
word-a-day calendars.
We played word games
all the way from Las Vegas.
I'm insipid.
Carla.
Go home, Nick.
You don't deserve to be here.
Carla, listen, I, I understand
your feelings very well.
I know some people probably
thought I was a bad father
and maybe I was and maybe I
wasn't, and maybe I was.
I speak to you from the bottom
of my heart and guts,
that these last few years
without family
has been very empty for me.
All I've had is Loretta.
No offence.
None taken.
I've come to learn that the most
important thing is family.
Yeah, I know,
I come at this late date
for Serafina's wedding,
but I thought
it would be a first step,
in realigning myself
with my offspring
and them becoming truly
a paternity figure.
So you want to be a father.
You want to get back
in your kids' lives, huh?
Absolutely.
Come over here.
Let's go.
Over here we have...
ten kids.
Some of them are yours.
Identify three,
and you can stay.
Otherwise you're out of here.
Is this a test?
You're stalling.
Give me some time
to gather my momentum.
So, Miss Howe,
we've got five minutes.
You want to tear one off?
That's mine!
Okay, that's one.
Hugo, my beloved.
Hugo.
Sorry, Nick, that's
not your kid.
You know you people
could help me.
FRASIER:
I wouldn't be much good.
I thought your last
selection was correct.
Uh, I think it's about time.
Let's start the ceremony.
Oh, that's Serafina.
She's one of mine.
Aw, forget it Nick.
Let's face it,
you can't do this.
Aw... Loretta.
Hit the road.
Go on, kids, go on upstairs and
get ready for the ceremony.
Come on, let's go.
What's happening?
Your mother doesn't
feel I belong here.
She says I'm unwelcome.
Mother, you can't
send Daddy away
on the most important
day of my life.
Listen, Serafina,
you've gotta understand...
No, this is not about you.
It's about me-
my wedding, my day.
Have a nice life, baby.
Wait one minute, Daddy.
Look, Ma, I know all the
things you've done for me.
I know you don't like Daddy,
but like him or not,
he is my dad.
I know he's been
a bad father...
never around when you need him,
a louse, a jerk,
a liar, a deadbeat.
You tell her, honey.
You know, all my life
I've always pictured
that someday I would
walk down the aisle
on my father's arm,
just like any other girl.
Not like every
other girl, Serafina.
My father wasn't
there to give me away.
And how'd that make
you feel, Mom?
Pretty rotten.
Sayonara, Serafina.
Oh wait, Nick.
You can stay.
Really?
Thanks, Mom.
Look, you, listen...
you do anything to ruin
my lovely daughter's wedding,
and I will choke you
until your eyes bug out.
(voice breaking):
It's just like The Waltons.
LORETTA: ♪ What are you doing
the rest of your life? ♪
♪ North and south and east
and west of your life? ♪
♪ I have only one request
of your life... ♪
Carla, look at
our kid out there.
She's pregnant, married
to a retired cop.
We must have done
something right.
Yeah.
Maybe our other kids
will turn out okay, too.
That is my most fervent wish.
(phone ringing)
Cheers.
Oh, just a second.
Mr. Tortelli,
it's for you.
For me?
Hello.
What?
What? When?
(yelling):
All right, I'll be on it!
Loretta, let's go!
WOODY:
What's the matter?
One of the orang-utans
went nuts and bit a kid.
I've got to rush to Vegas
before they put him to sleep.
The orang-utan or the kid?
I didn't ask.
Thanks again
for everything, Mom.
I'm happy.
Serafina, I really
want to apologize
for the way I acted
this afternoon.
And I promise I'll be on my best
behaviour at your next wedding.
Oh, Ma.