Last time on Cheers:
Hey, Sam, me and Eddie
are getting married!
She's, uh, quite a catch, Ed.
Seems that Eddie and I picked
the one day of the century
when all the planets
and constellations
are in perfect alignment.
So we either get married
by 4:00 p.m. today,
or we wait until the year 2042.
This is going to be
an interesting wedding,
the two most superstitious
people in the world.
Hey, hey, don't say that.
It's bad luck.
Our love can conquer
any bad luck
that comes our way.
Hey, that's my mirror.
( shrieks )
I mean it, Anthony
and Annie moving in...
You don't want
to come and live
in my little, tiny
overcrowded house.
Your ma hating me...
I'm so happy to meet you.
Car-la.
Anthony hating you...
You are not my father...
and you never will be.
Twins...
I had twins once.
It was the happiest
day of my life.
Every time one
of these little,
piddly things came up,
I kept thinking you were going
to say the wedding's off.
The wedding's off.
Afternoon, everybody.
ALL:
Norm!
Hey, Mr. Peterson,
would you like a beer?
No, I'd like
a dead cat in a glass.
Men, you are looking
at one sharp bargainer.
Not only did I get
Carla and Eddie
eight sterling-silver
place settings, but
I also got Bruce to throw in
matching weenie tongs
and lemon zester.
That's great,
man, except...
the wedding's
been called off.
Ah...
So what happened?
Eddie freaked out
about being a father?
No.
Eddie's mom met Carla.
Hate at first sight.
Yeah, how'd you know?
Well, that's the "law" part
of "mother-in-law," see.
So Eddie's not going
to marry Carla
because his mother
doesn't approve.
I tell you,
it's pathetic
to see a grown man so tied
to his ma's apron strings.
Well, that reminds me,
Mr. Clavin, you mother called
and said she couldn't make it
for dinner tonight.
Oh, great. What
am I supposed to do
with that casserole--
just throw it away?
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
( piano plays )
¶ Making your way
in the world today ¶
¶ Takes everything you've got
¶ Taking a break
from all your worries ¶
¶ Sure would help a lot
¶ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ¶
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You want to be where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ You want to go
where people know ¶
¶ People are all the same
¶ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ¶
Mr. Malone,
remember that reception
you talked me into?
Well, it seems that the bride
is in my office
and she's having a little
problem with the groom.
She wants him to die
with festering boils.
It's just the usual
prenuptial jitters.
It'll be all right.
It will not
be all right.
I invited my boss,
and he's really
excited about this.
Now, if Mr. Drake
shows up here
expecting a reception and
there isn't a reception,
I'm gonna have egg
all over my face.
Actually, uh, you know,
most complexion experts
swear by the old
egg facial.
It tightens one's pores.
Although yours look
pretty tight to me.
I want to talk
to you a minute.
Miss Howe, I think I can get
this wedding back on track.
Thank God.
Yeah, but I have
one little condition.
You pull this off and you can
have anything you want.
Really?
Except that.
Actually, all
I want to do
is get rid of
these stupid uniforms.
Mr. Malone, ever since
you have worked here,
you have done nothing
but whine about
these uniforms.
Now, I put a great deal
of thought into them
and I happen to think
they make a statement.
Oh, yeah.
They say I'm a lima bean.
All right. Fine, fine.
If you insist on
keeping these uniforms,
then there'll be
no wedding,
no wedding reception,
and you and Mr. Drake
can spend an intimate evening
watching 40 quarts
of guacamole turn black.
Fine, fine.
Get rid of the uniforms.
Okay.
Woody.
Yo.
Get on the phone.
Tell the church we're running
a little bit late.
Cliff, see if you can
catch up with Eddie there.
You betcha.
Norm,
stay in the office
and make sure Carla
does not trash it.
Yes, you.
Frasier. Go pick up
Carla's gown, will you?
Right. Oh, say,
if anybody needs me,
Just tell them
I'm at Gown-O-Rama, tra-la.
That was all
well and good.
Thank you.
How do you plan on getting the
bride and groom back together?
I'm going to rely on my wits.
Well, you're
halfway there.
You better believe it.
Sam.
Father Berry at Carla's church
said we gotta hurry
because he's got
two weddings
planned after Carla's,
a bake sale,
a slide show of the Knights of
Columbus' trip to the Holy Land,
and a CYO hootenanny.
Thank you, Woody.
Sam?
Mmm?
I'm, uh... I'm thinking
of becoming Catholic.
We'll talk about it later.
Hey, Sammy, I got Eddie.
Great. Where's Mama?
I tipped the cabbie to
take her back to the hotel.
You already paid
back that buck.
I'm not gonna
marry her, Sam.
I mean, I can't go
against mémère's wishes.
Maybe some day,
after Mama gets to know her
and starts to like her....
Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
What about the planets
and the tea leaves?
I mean, if you don't
marry her now,
you're going to have
to wait till 2042.
Sam, it's no use.
I mean, maybe Carla's right.
Ever since I saw her
on our wedding day,
we've had nothing but bad luck.
You know, I happen
to think that it's bad luck
to be a jerk to the woman
you're in love with.
Now, come on, Eddie.
Just talk to her.
Okay. I guess I could
just talk to her.
Great, great,
great, great, great,
hold that thought.
How's it going?
Pretty good,
pretty good.
It better be,
or my butt's in a sling.
Is there room for two in there?
Eddie's arm.
His neck.
How's it going?
Oh, not too bad.
I don't think
we've broken anything vital yet.
Eddie's foot.
Sweetheart.
Eddie's femur.
Sit down.
Hey. Stop, stop.
Would you give the guy
a break, please?
He had to break a mirror, right?
He had to spill the salt.
He had to thumb his
nose to the Fates,
and look what happened.
They turned him into a wuss.
The important thing is
that the wuss came back.
Does he have a note
from his mommy?
Oh, come on,
just talk to the guy.
I don't talk to
spineless jellyfish.
All right, fine.
I'll just, uh,
go out there
and tell him to leave.
Hey.
Does he look really
pathetic and cute?
Have you ever seen a puppy...
in the rain?
Well...
I guess I can
let him off the hook,
but first!
He has to come in here, get down
on his knees and sweat blood.
He was hoping you'd say that.
You're smiling.
The wedding's on.
Oh, yeah.
This uniform is almost off.
Old engineer Sammy's
got the matrimony express
right back on schedule.
Eddie. Eddie, Eddie.
Wait a minute, man. Whoa.
Where you going?
I can't face her
right now.
I mean, even if I did
change my mind
and decide
to stand up to Mama,
Carla would never forgive me
for the way I ran out.
I mean, if I went
in there right now,
she'd tear my head off.
Come on, Eddie.
I think you're underestimating
Carla just a bit here.
What, you don't think
she'll be mad?
No, I don't think
she'll stop at your head.
SAM:
Norm...
Listen, she wants
to forgive you.
All you two need is a few
moments together in private.
Okay, but could we
do it out here,
where there are
plenty of witnesses?
All right. Okay.
Just sit down right here. Relax.
If he even looks at the door,
break his legs.
Sam!
The wedding frock
you ordered.
I got some pretty weird looks
on the bus with this thing.
There was also one
rather interesting invitation.
Sam.
Father Berry.
The other wedding party's
starting to stack up
in the vestibule.
Ah, I can't talk
to him now, man.
I-I gotta talk to Eddie here.
I just talked to Eddie.
I gotta talk to Carla.
Carla?
Mm-hmm.
Carla.
Father Berry?
Listen, Sam can't talk
right now, but, uh...
while I got you on the phone,
can I ask you a question?
Do you have to pay
any membership dues
to be a Catholic?
I told you
I wouldn't
talk to him
unless he comes
in here begging.
Come on. Carla, we don't
have time for this nonsense.
Hey, I got an idea.
Get out of your clothes.
Oh, Sammy,
any other time I'd love to,
but, really...
Well, I just think that,
you know, uh, you're sweaty.
You're tired,
Maybe you'd
like to change
into something else.
Well, hey, like this,
for instance.
No way.
Oh, come on.
Just, just try it on.
You know, see how it fits
in case you want
to get married someday.
Years from now.
Well, you know,
I might not be pregnant then.
Right.
Come on.
Oh, what the heck.
This might be the
last chance I get
to see what I look
like in one of these.
Yeah.
Besides, I'm out 36 bucks.
Eddie, Eddie.
Sammy.
I know what you're doing here.
You think I'm going
to get all decked out
like Miss Bride
of the Year,
take one look
in the mirror
and forget all about
being mad at Eddie.
and I'm going
to go out there,
and Eddie's going to
take one look at me
and forget all about
his mother. Then,
we'll march down the aisle
and live happily ever after.
Am I right?
Yeah, that's basically it.
You got a problem with that?
Nah, just checking.
Here I come.
Woo-woo.
Sam...
Do you really mean "woo-woo,"
or are you
just saying "woo-woo"?
No, no. I don't say
"woo-woos" lightly. Huh?
Holá.
Okay.
Ah, look at you.
( laughing )
Okay. Let's
give it a shot.
All right.
Sammy, zip me.
Well, I'll be darned.
These things go
up, too, huh?
Oh, Carla.
You look...
That's the nicest thing
anyone's ever said to me.
( phone ringing )
EDDIE:
Oh... Oh, listen.
Let's get to the church.
We have to get married
before 4:00.
Hot dog!
Care to help me
with my pants?
( happy humming )
Carla? It's your church.
Would you tell them
we're on our way.
Well, that's just it.
They had to go ahead
with the other wedding
and cancel yours.
I knew it.
I knew it!
You're out of uniform.
MONSIGNOR:
Dear friends, you have
come together...
CLIFF:
It sure was nice
of the Monsignor
to let Carla and Eddie
get married here
in the rectory chapel.
NORM:
Yeah, it was kind of nice
of us
to buy all those raffle tickets,
too.
FRASIER:
Good Lord,
it's crowded in here.
But on the upside,
it does satiate any desire
I might have had to visit Tokyo.
Edward, have you come here
freely without reservation
to give yourself
to Carla in marriage?
Edward?
Carla, where's Edward?
Carla? Where's Carla?
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Lady with a baby.
Excuse...
Would you get off the dress!
All right, all right,
all right.
Crank it up, Father.
All the forces in the universe
say we have to be done by 4:00.
( bell tolls )
Oh, no!
Do you, Edward Raymond,
take Carla Maria Victoria...
Hurry! Hurry! Please, hurry!
Angelina Theresa Apollonia...
CARLA:
Oh, rat!
Why couldn't my parents
have named me Judy?
Go on, go on, go on.
Hey, here they come!
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the moment
we've all been waiting for.
Appearing for the first time
anywhere, the happy couple,
Mr. and Mrs. Eddie LeBec.
( drum roll )
( cheering and applause )
That's a keeper.
Hey, guys, it's
your wedding day.
Show a little teeth
here, all right?
I can't, Sammy.
We were pronounced
man and wife at 4:01.
We might as well have
been pronounced dead.
We're doomed.
Music, music!
Aw, come on, you guys.
Think about all
the wedding gifts
you got to open
over there.
Yeah.
I guess I should
be grateful
Eddy didn't fall down
the church steps
and break his leg.
How is it, anyway?
I think I just
wrenched it a little.
They don't look
too happy to me.
No. They do look married,
though.
What's that
ugly-looking thing?
It's not an ugly thing.
It's a Wabby.
What's a Wabby, Webecca?
It's a "Women of Boston
Business" award.
I'm very proud of it.
It happens to be
very prestigious.
Thousands of women
have won it.
What's it doing
out here?
You trying
to impress your boss?
I'm glad
you reminded me.
I'm completely
forgot he was coming.
Yeah, sure you did.
Hey, you know,
every time Evan Drake's name
gets mentioned
you get a little red
around the gills.
Do you have
a crush on him
or something?
I beg your pardon.
He happens to be
a married man.
Although not happily.
Oh, you do have a crush on him.
How cute!
"Oh, Evan, Evan."
Great stuffed mushrooms,
Cliffie.
Try the Swedish
meatballs.
They're out
of this world.
Yeah.
Ooh, try 'em together!
Together!
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Do you plan on leaving
any hors d'oeuvres
for latecomers?
Hey, you snooze,
you lose.
Ooh-ooh! Rumaki!
Come on.
And now it's time
for the traditional first dance,
and we all know who's going
to start it.
Holy cow, it isn't me, is it?
Let's welcome
the happy couple Carla and Eddie
to the dance floor.
¶ The greatest love
the world has known... ¶
Hit me again, Harley.
Third time's the charm.
So, uh, where's your
big-shot lover boy?
A: I told you
he is not my lover boy.
B: The big shot SOB
is in a meeting.
C: Choke on it.
There's a happy pair.
Say cheeseburger.
Uh, no, no.
All right,
that was a good one,
even with Miss Howe's eyes
kinda gimpy like that.
Oh, Norm, look.
We forgot about
the dessert table.
And we call ourselves
guests.
Ma, you want
to trade partners?
Why not?
I'm going to die.
I'm going to dance
with my mother,
all right?
How about a cup
of coffee, huh?
Why would I do that?
Well, because I've seen
a lot of ladies hit
the champagne in my time.
One minute
they're doing
just fine.
The next minute
it kind of sneaks
up on them
and they're doing
all sorts
of wild and crazy...
Why am I giving you coffee?
So, Eddie,
what's Mother Tortelli
like in bed?
What are you
looking at,
pretty lady?
I'm looking at you.
Well, I'm looking
back at you.
I think I'm beginning
to see you
in a whole new light.
Why don't you tell me
what you see?
You have a really weird face.
Your eyebrows
are growing together
like a big old
ugly caterpillar.
Oh, look,
they're cutting the cake.
And now as the hour draws late,
it's time for the bride
to throw the bouquet.
Okay, come on, come on,
everybody.
You all ready?
Okay, heads up,
you old maids.
Dr. Crane,
a girl's supposed
to catch the bouquet.
Well, then the girls
should have been
a little bit quicker.
Here, knock
yourself out.
I think it's time
for me to pack it in.
Uh, you know,
I don't think
you're in any condition
to drive, Miss Howe.
Let me give you
a lift home, all right?
I don't know.
I've never been alone in a car
with such a hairy guy.
Are you sure you weren't
in The Planet of The Apes?
Can anybody else
please take me home?
There's room in our car.
You can sit on my lap.
Darling, you're
married now.
You don't have
a lap.
Come on.
You think I'm so ugly?
I'll let you get a bag
and put it over my head,
all right?
Just a minute.
Let me get my bag.
And yours.
I'm not crazy
about the way that girl flirts.
And now, folks,
as the lucky couple gets ready
to embark
on their new life together,
let's all throw some rice,
the symbol of fertility.
Ow!
Oh, ow!
Ah!
I can't go
out here, Eddie.
Why?
No, it's too dangerous.
I'm okay.
Who are we trying
to kid here?
We're living
in the shadow
of the curse
we brought
on ourselves.
I can't go on
with this.
Come on, Carla.
No, no, no.
I think maybe
we should get
an annulment.
Oh, would you two
stop it?!
I can't believe...
This should be the happiest
day of your lives,
and all you've done
is moan and groan
all day long.
I mean, come on.
It's one thing to play along
with this superstition stuff
for, you know, for some fun,
but you're letting it
interfere
with your happiness here.
You two
are wonderful.
You got everything
in your life
to look forward to.
Please, please, come on.
Trust me.
Nothing bad is going to happen.
( phone rings )
You got my personal word
on that.
I mean, superstition,
it's for the birds.
Just go on
with your normal life.
Woody, do you mind?
All right, fine.
Go ahead. Answer it.
It's probably
just somebody who wants
to, uh, know what time
the bar closes.
We close at 2:00.
Eddie, it's for you.
Some guy
from the Bruins.
Maybe, maybe you oughta...
Probably just want
to congratulate me
on my wedding.
Yeah, right.
That's it. That's it.
Hello.
Oh, hiya, Frank
Yeah, how's it going?
It's Frank.
Yeah,
uh-huh.
Uh-huh.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah, thanks a lot.
Good-bye, Frank.
Do I smell a bonus?
They cut me from the team.
They're going
with the youth movement.
They tried to trade me,
but nobody wanted me.
I'm sorry, Carla.
I guess
all the superstitions
finally caught up
with us.
Wait a minute.
I can blame a lot
of things on superstition,
but you aren't
the greatest goalie
in the world, honey.
What are you saying
to me, Carla?
Well, you know,
the end of last year
you were losing it,
and now you're older,
and your reflexes are shot.
Oh, thanks a lot.
I'm feeling a lot
better already.
And if that wasn't
because of superstition,
then maybe the twins
aren't bad luck either.
Could it be possible
that I'm just having twins
because the eggs split?
Whoa, whoa!
And maybe your mother hates me
because she's stupid.
And Anthony hates you
because he takes after
his no-good rat-faced father.
And all those things
that we thought were bad luck
had nothing to do
with superstition.
It was just...
life.
Unfortunately,
it happens to be my life.
What the heck?
I'm married and in love
with a great guy.
So, I guess
that evens things up.
No, it doesn't.
But it makes life worth living.
But it's something.
So let's get on with it.
What do you say,
hubby?
I say let's get on
with the honeymoon, eh?
See you at 2:00 A.M.
Somebody's got to work
in this family.
Hi. I'm Mrs. Eddie LeBec.
What'll you have?
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.OpenSubtitles.org