DlANE MEETS MOM
- Hello.
- Hi, what can l get you?
- l'm a phone company repairman.
- l'm a bartender. Ernie Pantusso.
Phil Ryan.
l got a call to come down here.
There must be some mistake, Phil.
l didn't call for any repairman.
- l think Sam put in a call, Coach.
- He did?
He didn't say anything to me.
l'd better give him a call
and find out what this is all about.
Bum luck, Phil, phone's out.
Give him a couple of seconds.
l hate to impose, but since they
got you here on this royal goose chase,
would you take a look at the phone?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Lucky thing he happened by here.
Sometimes fate takes a hand, Coach.
Hi, everybody. l bet you're surprised
to see me on my night off.
Yeah, we didn't hear your broom pull up.
What are you doing here?
l'm having dinner upstairs
with Frasier and his mother.
She's a seafood aficionado,
we think she'll like the bouillabaisse.
You're having dinner
with Frasier's mother?
You deduced l'm having dinner
with Frasier and his mother
when all l did
was say it in your presence.
No flash cards, no crib notes
on your sleeve? Uncanny.
We're a little edgy tonight, aren't we?
But l can't blame you. Meeting Mom
is a big step in a relationship.
Granted, meeting your prospective
fiancé's mother,
especially an eminent psychiatrist,
trained to analyse a person's behaviour,
could be a nerve-racking evening,
for somebody who's going to be there,
but l'm not. Good night.
- Chickening out, Diane? - Not at all.
They're 1 2 seconds late.
Get back here.
Sit down and have a glass of wine.
Coach...
Sit down, honey, and relax.
Everything will be fine.
Just remember, don't snap your gum,
don't chew with your mouth open,
and for God's sake,
don't play with your bra straps.
- l'll try to remember.
- Trying's not good enough.
l'll have to write it down for you.
- Afternoon, everybody.
- Norm!
- What would you say to a nice beer?
- Going down.
Coach, do me a favour and don't make
a big fuss over me today, OK?
- You got it.
- No cakes, candles, party hats, singing.
- None of that.
- OK.
You know, because it would be
so embarrassing.
And no gifts, all right?
And don't ask how old l am today.
Normie, is today your birthday?
Coach, you remembered?
Everybody, it's Normie's birthday.
Let me buy the birthday boy a drink.
Please, you're making
too big a deal out of this.
There you are, my darling.
At last you two meet.
The woman who gave me life
and the woman who gives me life.
Oh, Frasier.
Forgive me. l lose my head
in the company of beautiful women.
- Dr Crane...
- Oh, please, dear, call me Hester.
- Hester, it's a pleasure.
- lt's my pleasure.
Let me take your coat, Mother.
Diane...
- Here's the list of tips l promised.
- Thank you, Coach.
l also added instructions
for a dainty way to dispose of gristle.
Frasier, she's lovely.
He's made no secret of the fact,
but even he didn't do you justice.
Well, in an anxiety-provoking situation
such as this,
one tends to respond with exaggerated
compliments. Let me just be frank.
You are the most strikingly handsome
woman l've ever laid eyes on.
Something exciting is happening here.
Exciting, but not surprising.
l say by the end of the evening
you two will be thick as thieves.
Only if we can't resist the temptation
to pig out on cheesecake.
- Hey, Doc, Vic's ready for you upstairs.
- l hope everybody's got an appetite.
l'll never eat again.
Let me hurry on up and make sure we've
got a good table. l'm thick with Vic.
Well, Mother...
- Boy, did you see that?
- What?
Frasier purposely avoided
drawing me into the conversation.
l noticed that, too, Cliffie.
What's his problem?
He knows how well versed
l am in his field, Coach.
l've embarrassed
many a professional so-called expert.
Actually, Cliff, l think you've
embarrassed everybody you know.
As long as you're saying it,
it's not bragging.
- Norm! When did you get here?
- 36 years ago today.
- lt's my buddy Norm's birthday today.
- ls that right?
l think the birthday of one of my best
customers deserves some bubbly.
- No, no, no.
- Maybe you're right.
- Just kidding!
- You got me!
Open this up, Coach. Congratulations,
and many happy returns.
Just don't go singing ''Happy Birthday''.
Cos l'd really hate that,
if you sang ''Happy Birthday''.
Yeah, just because it is my...
Cut it out! Come on, now!
- Norm!
- Are you OK?
- You OK, buddy?
- Yeah, yeah. l'm all right.
That sucker nearly hit me.
Hold still now.
Why don't you
sit down here for a second?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
- How many fingers?
- Three.
- Not you, Coach.
Sure, after l give him the answer.
- You sure?
- l'm fine.
The primary symptom
of postprandial trauma
is the blurring of the metatarsals.
- Cliff, shut up.
- Fine, l'll shut up.
Go ahead and wallow in ignorance.
We're re-entering the Dark Ages.
- Do we gain an hour or lose an hour?
- Would you guys cut it out?
Why don't you see a doctor?
That thing hit you pretty hard.
Play it safe, go to the emergency room.
l'll pay for it.
No, it doesn't even hurt any more.
Normie's right. l got hit all the time
in baseball. l never saw a doctor.
- You'll keep my glass chilled?
- Yeah.
Yeah, terrific, Normie, l'll pass that on.
Everybody, Normie's just fine.
They're just keeping him in
overnight for a few more tests.
A lot of people miss the whimsy in Jung.
He's given me many a chuckle.
l wrote one of my favourite papers on it.
lt's entitled, ''Hello, Jung Lovers.''
How clever.
Oh, dear. l hope l haven't dominated
the conversation tonight.
Nonsense, the wine and your verbiage
went perfectly with our meal.
Listen, why don't you two have
a seat and l'll get us a fine cordial.
Will you trust me to make the selection?
l have a little treat in mind,
l'd like to surprise you with it.
Frasier, you're mad, but l love you.
Three cans of Schlitz.
Listen carefully.
Stop seeing my son or,
as God is my witness, l'll kill you.
- Something to munch on.
- Yum, yum, yum.
Now listen to me.
l have a gun, l know how to use it.
Here we are.
Doesn't that look lovely?
What do you call it?
- lt's a delightful pear liqueur.
- Sounds delicious, doesn't it, Diane?
l think she likes it.
l hate to leave your company again,
but l must visit the men's room.
You know what they say, you only rent
a Château Lafite Rothschild.
l'll go with you.
Diane, there are some things
a man must do alone.
lf you love me, you won't do this now.
Well, it's a peculiar test
of a man's affection,
but l think l'm up to it.
l've just had an inspiration.
What say we go to an intimate cabaret
and hear some jazz?
That's a wonderful idea, Frasier.
How do you feel about it, Diane?
Diane, you're white as a sheet.
Are you OK?
l'm a little tired, Frasier.
- Why don't you two go without me?
- We wouldn't think of it.
No, l insist.
l'll be fine. l'll call a cab. l wouldn't want
to spoil your fun. Please.
She's tired. Don't press her.
Go home, dear. Rest.
You need a night on the town
like you need a hole in the head.
l'll be fine, thank you.
Very well. l'll call you later.
- How did dinner go?
- She wants to kill me.
You've got to start picking up
some checks, Diane.
Sam, l have to ask you a question.
And promise me
you won't make a joke out of it. OK?
- l promise. What's up?
- Do you think l'm crazy?
Yes.
Now the joke is out of the way,
will you help me?
l know this is a strange question,
but it's important.
Do you think l'm...crazy?
Yes.
You're incapable of a rational
conversation, only flip remarks.
Wait a minute. Do you mean
are you crazy, like seriously unbalanced,
like losing your grasp on reality?
- Yes.
- Oh, well, then...
...yes.
When you're ready to discuss this
as an adult, then we will talk.
Do l sense a bit of tension between
you and dear old Mother Crane?
l don't want to blow this
out of proportion.
Doesn't every woman feel
their mother-in-law-to-be
is an evil, dark-hearted,
psychotic murderess?
- l mean competitor.
- What exactly did she say?
l don't remember it word for word.
Something about,
''l have a gun
and l know how to use it.''
Before she left, she said l needed a
night on the town like a hole in the head.
That's kinda cute.
You think a death threat is cute?
Not as a rule, no. But...
...your sense of humour
is not exactly your strong point.
ls it possible
that this lady is joking with you?
Anything is possible,
but what's funny about...
...a hole in the head?
God...
ls it possible?
l feel so foolish.
She must think l'm a twit.
Don't worry, when l first met you,
l thought you were a twit, too.
Boy, this gal is a real kidder.
l mean, we're talking veritable goose.
We're having lunch together,
so l can show Hester
that l can give as good as l get.
- Afternoon, everybody.
- Norm!
- What's up?
- Everything that's supposed to be.
Norm,
l hear you spent the night in hospital.
- l'm OK, though.
- Good.
You can just take care of this
at your leisure, l suppose.
$683?
- To have your head checked?
- lsn't that something?
They did a whole battery of tests on me.
- The important thing is l'm OK, isn't it?
- Well, no. l mean, yes, but $683!
The cost of diagnostic testing
has gone up dramatically.
l read recently
it's running to billions every year.
Gee, l didn't know so many people
got hit by corks.
- What did they do to you down there?
- Mostly routine stuff.
l did take care of one other little matter.
- Like what?
- l had a little mole removed.
- And you stuck me with it?
- Norm, where did you have a mole?
That must have been the one
on your butt there, right?
Norm, l didn't know you were that...vain.
Who's ever going to see your rear end?
You're just about to, wise guy.
l think you took advantage of me, Norm.
l figured you'd want to throw in the mole.
Makes a nice birthday gift, you know.
You want to be hard-nosed,
l'll pay for it.
No, no.
Happy birthday.
- Thank you, it's just what l wanted.
- You're welcome.
l know it's a little early, but l wouldn't
say no to a tummy tuck for Christmas.
l'll think about it.
Diane, look who's here.
lf you have knees,
prepare to slap them now.
Hello, dear.
- You're feeling better?
- Much better.
lf Sam will let us steal you away,
l have reservations for three for lunch.
Sounds good.
Hester, l've been thinking a lot
about our little talk last night.
l hope you've been thinking
long and hard.
l have.
Frasier, l came to a decision last night.
lf we marry, l think we should commit
mommy dearest to a rest home,
making sure that beating and starving
are the only forms of recreation.
Diane!
l beg your pardon?
ln fact, l feel like slapping
your face right now.
Take me out of here this moment.
lt's a joke, come on.
l'm obviously kidding.
We won't put her in a rest home,
we'll have her with us always.
We're going to have her stuffed.
And l'll even slit her throat
in the process. Thank you, Sam.
l've never encountered such hostility,
personally or professionally. l'm leaving.
No, just a minute, let's all take a beat.
The three of us
are going into Sam's office
and we'll work this thing through.
There's got to be a logical explanation.
And there'd better be, Diane.
lt's all a joke. Hester,
you're with me on this, aren't you?
lf terrible threats constitute jokes,
no, l'm not with you on this.
OK, time to take stock here.
l'm not crazy, right, Diane?
Right you are.
A whole year of my life.
Hester, l was trying to joke with you
like you were joking with me.
lf you weren't joking,
you threatened my life...
- l what?
- What?
She said that if l didn't stop seeing you,
she'd shoot me.
This was obviously a mistake.
You know perfectly well
you threatened my life!
l will not stay and be talked to like this.
Frasier, she is a rude,
boorish, spiteful woman,
who, for some reason
l don't understand, resents me terribly.
- Mother, please.
- Liar, liar, pants on fire.
- Diane!
- l'm not lying. She is.
lf you love me, you'll stand up for me
now when l need it.
Frasier, l'm asking you
to leave with me now.
Frasier, this is the most important
moment in our relationship.
lf you abandon me now, that's it.
Mother, why did you threaten Diane?
- You believe her?
- Yes.
Oh, God!
l've lost you.
Frasier, l did say those terrible things,
but, believe me, l had good reason.
OK, she said them,
but she had good reasons.
- Not good enough!
- They'd better be good!
The best in the world.
l wanted to save you from ruining
what could be a brilliant career.
l just can't stand the picture
of you being married
to a pseudo-intellectual barmaid.
No offence intended.
None taken. Ç ne fit rien.
Mother, l can't believe this of you,
a woman who has always been the most
gentle, rational human being l've known.
My dear boy, you know l would never
follow through on my threat to kill her.
As l was pricing revolvers this morning,
l realised how irrational
my feelings were.
But don't you understand?
l'd rather see you shovelling sherbet
at Howard Johnson's
in a silly hat and an apron
than make a bad marriage.
Mother, you don't understand.
We're not going to have a bad marriage.
And l'm not going to shovel sherbet.
But l would be happy doing it
if Diane were at my side.
Oh, Frasier,
l never realised how much
this woman meant to you.
Of course,
l don't really understand why.
l never understood your spider collection
either, but l grew to accept that.
Diane, she's reaching out. Please.
Doctor Crane, l'm sorry
if l made a bad first impression,
but l think, no, l know,
it was a wrong impression.
l may be a diamond in the rough now,
but l'm a dreamer,
and l have a habit
of making dreams come true.
When and if l marry Frasier Crane,
l will be the kind of wife and family
you'll be proud to know and claim.
People will get tired hearing
you boast about your daughter-in-law.
Diane, l see l've handled this so badly.
Well, yes...l suppose
l've made a few mistakes myself.
- Let's go out and come in again.
- l'd love to.
This is the most incredible moment
of my entire day.
l'm going to take you two future best pals
out to the finest lunch in town.
- Sounds good
- OK.
l need a glass of water.
You two, go ahead, l'll catch up with you.
That's OK. lt's free of charge.
l understand you used to date
that woman.
l want to know how much you'd charge
to start things up again.
- You don't have enough money.
- How would you know?
There isn't enough money.
- l know what you mean.
- l don't think you do.
- l think l do.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, yes.
English ( en)