Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Oh, shoot!
It's a minus!
I'm not pregnant.
Well, we only started
trying last night.
I guess
we can't expect
to get pregnant
the first time.
Well, I thought
that's what the fourth
and fifth times were for.
Fifth time.
You imagine that?
I'm only up to three.
I just want to be
pregnant now.
Rebecca, why don't you
approach this
from a scientific point
of view?
Make a simple
plot-point graph,
and chart
your basal temperature
at a fixed hour
each morning.
After a couple of months,
a pattern will emerge,
thereby making your peak
fertility days absolutely
predictable.
Good idea.
Thanks, Lilith!
Whew, boy!
You guys went through all that?
No, we just got ripped one night
and tore one off.
Remember that,
sugar, huh?
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Look, guys,
postcards from Woody.
Eh?
Hey, all right.
Listen to mine.
"Dear Miss Howe, I'm having
a great time on vacation.
"I miss everyone there,
but I miss you most of all.
Love, Woody."
What does yours say, Sam?
"Dear Sam, I'm having a great
time on vacation.
"I miss everyone there,
but I miss you most of all.
Love, Woody."
"I'm having
a great time
on vacation.
"I miss everyone there,
but I miss you most
of all. Love, Woody."
Cliffie?
Well, "Dear Mr. Clavin,
"I'm having a great time
on vacation.
Love, Woody."
Hey, Frasier,
Lilith.
What'll you have?
A scotch, Sam.
And whatever my Neanderthal
husband will have.
You two fighting?
No, on the contrary,
Sam,
I insist that
she call me that.
Frasier's been captivated
by a new theory of masculinity
which suggests within each man
is a hidden primal beast,
softened by years
of civilization
and sensitivity.
He saw it on Sally Jesse.
Yes, and they got a really cool
name for this beast.
It's called
the "Inner Hairy Man."
Or in your case, dear,
"The Receding Hairy Man."
She thinks it's all
very childish.
No, I don't.
Oh, tell your
little friends
all about your
big field trip.
Primal journey, Lilith.
You see, I'm just gonna
get into my car and go.
Out on the open road.
I'm taking a week off.
I'm gonna get in touch
with my hidden beast.
Ah, good luck.
Thanks, Sam.
You know, actually I was gonna
invite you to join me.
You see, I get
a little nervous
when I drive at night.
Oh, yeah, it'd be nice, but, uh,
Woody's on vacation, you know.
CARLA:
Oh, well, that's
okay, Sammy.
I could get my nephew
Frankie to help out.
He's a good kid,
real sweet, Frankie.
Of course,
he's never been in a bar,
but he'll be okay.
Oh, I don't know about this.
You know, this is my livelihood,
my business.
I don't want
to just turn it over
to somebody because
they're family.
He'll work for minimum wage.
I'm in!
Great!
Great.
Hey, this is great.
So, uh, where are we gonna go?
Desert? Mountains?
Well, actually, Sam,
the location doesn't
really matter.
This is more of a
spiritual journey,
an heroic quest.
You know, you know, if we, uh,
drive to California,
we could go see Disneyland.
Ooh!
Yeah.
Perhaps you could find your
manhood on the giant teacups.
Yeah, a road trip
to Disneyland.
Sounds fun.
You want to join us, Norm?
Well (stammers)...
I'm sure you two gentlemen
have something to do.
Oh, no problemo.
I got a couple of weeks vacation
coming up.
Really?
Oh, yeah, my supervisor
reminds me daily.
Well, Cliff, I, uh,
I don't know if my car is
big enough...
Oh, let's take my wagon.
What do you say, Norm? Huh?
The four of us tooling
down old mother road,
getting in touch with
the old hairy man-mobile, huh?
I don't know.
I don't think I could handle
sitting still
for six hours a day.
Well, yeah,
it'd be more like ten.
Oh, then I'm in.
SAM:
Boy, I'll never forget,
when I was 19,
Buck, my best friend--
he was a teammate of mine
in the minors--
he and I, uh, hitchhiked
all across Route 66.
Boy, best time
of my life.
Yeah?
Do they still have the place
where the Cadillacs are
sticking up out of the ground?
Oh, yeah, Cadillac Ranch,
in Merrimac Caverns.
All right.
Yeah, once I lost
a Hopalong Cassidy watch there
when I was ten.
Yeah, it just slipped
right off my wrist.
Yeah, you wouldn't believe it,
but as a youth,
I had very fine-boned wrists.
I can't tell you how many
people mistook me for royalty.
It's true.
Oh, what the hell!
We'll make it a group thing.
All of us will get out
and try to get in touch
with our tribal
instincts.
There you go.
Oh, give me strength.
Oh, come on, Lilith,
be happy for us.
We're all dropping
our inhibitions.
We're gonna go out and find
our manhood on the open road.
Yeah, like men!
Yeah, like manly men!
Real men!
Like those chicks
in Thelma and Louise!
(cheering)
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What happened here?
Ah, the eight track's acting up
again there, Sammy.
Grab the butter knife
out of the glove compartment,
will you?
Yeah.
There you go.
Here we are.
Well, at least we still got
the A.M. radio.
So, how far
have we gone?
Oh, about
a hundred miles.
Yeah.
Well, it's
minus 38.
Why minus 38?
Well, my trip meter
only sets back to 38.
Well, let's see.
What's a hundred minus 38?
Well, why don't we just,
uh, drive 38 more miles?
Then we'll know
we've hit a hundred.
Hey...
I didn't know
you were good at math.
Yeah, well, you know,
I used to be an accountant.
What you reading
there, Fras?
Oh, uh...
It's called
Iron John.
It's a best-seller
about getting in touch
with one's masculinity.
Mmm.
So you're actually gonna try
to read in a moving car?
Doesn't that make you sick?
No.
I always get sick
when I read in a car.
The car bounces around,
you know, your eyes try
to follow the words there.
You can smell
the gas fumes.
Pretty soon, you start sweating
and gasping for breath.
What's the problem?
I'm sick.
You know, I'll bet it's
from reading in the car.
I'm telling you.
(inhales)
(moans)
What?
I didn't say anything.
Yeah, but you were
thinking something.
No, I wasn't.
Yes, you think I have the
hots for Carla's nephew.
I didn't say that.
'Cause I do.
No kidding?
Oh, like you don't?
You've only been
sitting there
for the last four
days staring at him.
And it's worse with you,
because you're married.
That's slutty.
And what about you?
You're ogling him
and meanwhile,
you're trying to conceive
a child with another man.
Yes, but he is not my
husband, so that does
not make me a slut.
It's perfectly natural.
One can be married
and still be drawn
to the odd magnificent butt.
For once I'm with you, Doc.
I agree, but you know
what I really notice in a guy?
His eyes.
Yeah, but that magnificent
butt thing is right up there.
Yeah, well,
this guy has both.
And talk about biceps.
Whoa. You're
getting me hot.
Who are we talking
about here?
Your nephew, Frankie.
That is so sick!
Carla, surely,
as a woman, you can see
how your nephew might be
considered... desirable.
Sure. You start
thinking like that,
and you end up
with Woody's family.
Just look at you two.
You're acting like a couple
of construction workers.
Carla's right,
Lilith.
I mean, we're treating
men just the way
we hate to be
treated by them.
Oops, I dropped my purse.
I'll get it for you.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you again.
Okay, I got one.
When was the last time
you guys cried?
Huh? Cliffie?
Uh... well, I guess the, uh,
it's probably my,
uh, junior prom.
Oh, no, no, no. Cliffie,
this is not that story where,
uh, you got stood up
and you had to take your ma
and everyone laughed at you
and pantsed you, is it?
No, no, I said junior prom.
Yeah, you see, Ma was
putting on a boutonniere,
and a pin stuck me in the chest,
I got a staph infection.
Hmm.
How about you, Fras?
Well, the day we left
for this trip,
my son gave me a,
a picture.
And you cried?
I cried because
it was so beautiful.
Good luck finding
that hairy man.
Well, at least I can
get pricked by a pin
and not almost die.
What about you, Norm?
Well, there was
one time, uh,
we thought Vera was
pregnant, and...
then it turns out she wasn't.
I'm sorry, Norm.
You never told me
that, buddy.
Well, it turns out,
she was lying.
She didn't tell me
till after the wedding.
I must have cried for a week.
How about you, Sam?
Oh, you guys
should see him.
(cooing):
He's sleeping
like a little baby.
Aw, it's so cute.
(tires screeching)
(yelling)
What seems to be
the trouble, Sam?
Well, I know a little bit
about engines, and...
it seems like what
we got here is
a burned piece of meat.
Yeah, how is my, uh,
hobo steak coming?
Oh, yeah, well, I
threw that on the engine
back in, uh, Lukachukai.
At the risk of hearing
your answer, Cliff,
why would you do
something so stupid?
Oh, well, you,
you cook in there.
You see, you put your
food on the engine,
and then you can drive
and cook at the same time.
Oh, hey, it looks like the
vegetable kabobs are about done.
Maybe they're a little
bit too crisp, huh?
SAM:
Come on, let's
get back in the car
and go find a motel, huh?
Yeah, all right.
Hey, Cliffie, I can't
turn the key here.
Well, yeah, it's got a security
device on it there, Sam.
Oh.
Yeah, what I do
is turn the wheel
all the way to the left
and then, uh,
crank the key
as hard as I can.
(keys jangle)
SAM:
Oh, man.
Look at that. I just broke
the key off in the ignition.
I said "as hard
as I can," Sammy.
That's just great.
What are we going to do now?
Looks like I'm going to have
to hot-wire the car here.
Hey, wh-what am
I thinking about?
I've had my cellular phone
the whole time;
we can just call
for help.
No, come on,
come on, come on, come on.
Frasier, where's
your hairy man?
We can save ourselves here.
Yeah, hot-wiring's easy.
Buck showed me
how to do it
on a trip
across the states.
God, that guy was a whiz
with anything mechanical.
Yeah, here you go.
All you got to do is take
these two wires here
and connect them.
(electricity crackling)
You, you okay there, Sammy?
Diane?
Yeah, well, uh, you know
what your friend Buck, uh,
didn't, uh, reckon
on there, Sammy,
was that Cliff Clavin
anti-theft device.
Yeah, you see
old Mr. Car Thief
gets the shock of his life,
the doors automatically
lock shut,
and the alarm goes off.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
The doors lock
automatically?
Yeah, but the alarm's
supposed to be going off.
You know, it must
be on the fritz.
Our ears should
be ringing by now.
Oh, I'll just have
to do it manually.
You locked us out of the car!
(cell phone ringing)
My phone!
My phone is ringing!
All right!
And the doors are locked!
Well, break the damn window!
Are you kidding me?!
You know how much
those windows cost?
We don't have time
to argue here, Cliff.
You're not breaking
those windows.
(ringing continues)
You just try it, young man.
You're gonna have
to come through me...
(glass breaking)
You're gonna pay for that,
I hope you know.
(ringing continues)
Hello? Hello?
If it's Vera,
I'm not here.
Yes, this is Frasier Crane.
Oh, thank God
somebody called.
The batteries are
getting sort of low.
Look, I don't
have much time.
Excuse me?
Y-Yes, I understand
the Democratic party's
in trouble, and I'd
love to contribute,
but I'm in a little
trouble myself right now.
Oh, damn!
The batteries are dead!
SAM:
All right. Okay.
Let's, uh,
take it easy, Fras.
Nobody panic.
We'll be all right.
FRASIER:
Great.
We're lost, can't
start the car.
Way to go, Sam.
SAM:
Oh, now wait a minute.
Don't blame me, you know.
It's Cliff's fault for wanting
to see America
like the pioneers.
We should've stayed
on the main road.
Did Charles Kuralt
stay on the main road?
Look, I'm not the one
that fell asleep at the wheel.
I wouldn't have fallen
asleep at the wheel
if you hadn't given me
that extra shift.
Well, we were behind schedule.
Yes, I believe that
was your fault
for getting your fat butt lodged
in that cavern.
Well, I was looking
for my Hopalong Cassidy watch.
Do you mind?!
SAM:
Ah, come on, you guys.
Can we stop arguing
for, like, ten seconds here?
Geez, Buck and I went across
the entire United States
and we didn't argue once.
You know, frankly, Sam,
I'm getting a little tired
of hearing about Saint Buck!
If he was so wonderful,
how come none of us
has ever met him?
Because ever since he got
into the Hall of Fame,
he won't return my phone calls,
so I have to hang around
a bunch of losers
in a stupid bar!
Does that answer your
question, Mr. Hairy Man?!
Oh, I'm sorry, guys.
I didn't mean
anything by that.
It's just that, well,
he asked the question.
You know, I, I hate
to bring this up, but, uh...
we could really be in some,
some serious trouble here.
Oh, come on, man.
Hey, listen,
at least we, uh,
we've got each other
here, right?
I mean, you know,
here we are
out in the desert,
back to nature.
I mean, look, look
at this air here.
It's clear. It's fresh.
I mean, isn't that
why we came out here
in the first place?
Yeah, yeah.
Look at the stars, guys.
Look at that.
Got to be a million
of 'em up there.
Kind of makes you feel
insignificant, huh?
Yeah, I don't
feel anything.
(sighs)
Frankie?
Yeah?
I need you to move
those big boxes
to the other side
of the poolroom.
Gosh, Miss Howe,
it's the fifth time today.
I'm getting kind of sweaty.
Well, then take off
your shirt, you goose.
I could have gone
with those guys
on that little road trip,
you know.
I know.
I just wasn't here
when they decided to go.
So you've said.
They, uh, probably
tried to call me
and hung up on my machine.
Hmm.
Sometimes it doesn't
record the hang-ups.
Mm-hmm.
You're not much
of a conversationalist, are you?
Where is everybody?
Probably in
New Mexico by now.
You know, I could've
gone with 'em
if they'd just left a message.
No, I-I was talking
about my nephew
and Rebecca
of Horny Brook Farm.
They're in the back.
Frankie's helping
her move some boxes.
I'll just bet he is.
You know, I'm getting
a little sick of the way
she's throwing herself
all over that guy.
I mean, it's disgusting.
Carla, I've never
seen this side of you.
Yeah, well...
You know, Frankie's sweet.
One day he's going to meet
a nice girl and settle down.
And in the meantime,
it's my job
to keep him
away from sleazy women
looking for a quick one-nighter.
You mean women like you?
Ironic, huh?
Oh, Frankie.
What?
I thought I told you
to stay away from Rebecca.
Look, the woman is a tramp.
All she wants you for
is your body.
Miss Howe? She seems so nice.
(chuckling):
Are you kidding?
She has had every man
in this bar.
Every single one.
What?
That's right. Most of 'em,
ten, 20 times.
Look, you're a good boy,
Frankie. Now, go, go.
Get out of here,
before it's too late.
Now, go.
Run like the wind!
Go! Don't ever
come back!
I won't.
You know what I'm going to do
on the way home?
What?
I'm going to stop
at Saint Michael's,
and I'm going to pray
for her soul.
You do that.
How the hell did
he ever get in my family?
PAUL:
Hey, Rebecca?
Yes?
Rumor has it
you've, uh, slept
with every guy in the bar.
What?
So, uh, how come
you haven't
done the wild thing
with old Paul, huh?
I never get included
in anything.
CLIFF:
We're going to die out here.
They're going to find
our bleached bones.
Look, let's just
relax here, everybody.
Everything's going
to seem better in the morning.
Oh, yes, Sam.
"In the morning."
When the desert
sun comes up.
By noon, it'll be 120!
Forget it, Doc.
You're never going to see 120.
At 110, your lungs explode.
Cliff, that is ridiculous!
Oh, yeah?
Well, would you like
to make a friendly wager
on that?
How many hours have
we got till sunup?
About four, I'd say.
Well... I've lived
a good life.
The only thing I
regret is I didn't get
a chance to say
good-bye to Lilith
and Frederick,
to tell them how
much I love them.
Well, at least you've got
somebody
to carry on your name, you know.
I-I don't have anybody.
If I die out here,
it's me dying alone.
No, you're not, Sam.
You've got us.
Ah... here we are wasting
away in the desert.
I never pictured
that the four of us
would go out like this.
How did you picture it, Cliff?
Well, I pictured, uh,
Sammy getting topped
by a jealous husband.
Norm, I figured you'd,
you know, heart attack.
Frasier here...
Cliff, I, I don't
want to hear it.
You bet you don't.
Oh, look at that.
The sun's about
to come up.
FRASIER:
Say, uh,
where's, where's Norm?
Oh, he's asleep
in the back here.
Yeah? Well...
well, he's not asleep anymore.
Oh, hey, he's gone!
Well, he's got to be
around here someplace.
Norm!
Normie!
Here, Norm!
You, you don't suppose some wolf
dragged him off
in the night, do you?
Well, maybe we ought
to take a look for him.
FRASIER:
Not me.
I don't want to meet the wolf
that can drag off Norm.
(horn toots)
Norm!
Thank God you're safe!
Yeah.
Where'd you
get this thing?
It came complimentary
with the room.
What room?
At the resort.
What resort?
The resort just over the hill,
where I spent the night.
You mean you
stayed in a resort
while we slept here
in the dirt?!
Why didn't you come
and tell us?
How could you do
something like this?!
You guys want to yell
at me some more,
or do you want to make
the breakfast buffet?
It stops in ten minutes.
Well, naturally,
the buffet.