Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Oh, Sammy, look who's here.
Harry the Hat.
Aw, man, how many times
am I gonna have to chase
that guy out of here?
Grab your wallets, everybody.
Hello, Harry.
Hey, Sam.
What you doing, trying to
sell some bogus watches,
some knock off's to my customers
and try to cheat 'em?
Sam, that hurts.
This is no knock off.
That's a $5,000 Rolex.
But it's on sale for $2,500.
Is this a real Rolex, Harry?
Yeah.
Whoa.
Hey. Sounds like a
Rolex, doesn't it?
Oh, look at that-
still ticking, too.
Uh, Sam...
Hey, do me a favour.
Just, just take
your bogus goods
and peddle them
someplace else, will ya?
So Harry, are you interested
in buying the watch?
No, but I think my
friend Sam might be.
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
All right. All right.
But now, the band I'm looking
for is gonna have to be able
to do all
the old Irish standards.
Yeah. "Danny Boy," "Galway Bay,"
"When Irish Eyes Are Smiling,"
that kind of thing.
You think you can handle that?
All right then.
Okay, I'll get back to you.
Yeah, adios to you too, Manuel.
Oh, well, I see
you're getting an early jump
on Saint Patrick's Day.
Yeah. That's right.
You know, this time tomorrow
when Gary's still decorating
Olde Towne Tavern,
this place's gonna be open,
people are gonna be flooding in.
That's a good idea, Sam.
You're damned right.
Hey, finally, for the first
time, St. Patrick's Day,
Cheers is gonna do
more business
than Gary's Olde Towne Tavern.
Yes!
I wouldn't be too
sure about that.
He's beaten you
ten years running.
I know but I've got a feeling.
You know, lucky 11?
We can't lose
this time, Dr. Crane.
We're pulling out
all the stops.
We've got, a two
for one special,
we've got balloons,
we've got a live Irish band,
we've got Mr. Peterson
mixing up some green beer.
Oh, hey, how's that
beer coming, Norm?
You want it fast or
you want it good?
Come on, you've been working
on it for three hours.
And I'm prepared to work on it
all night long, Sam,
because damn it, I care.
Normie, watch this.
(knocking)
Hey, Carla. You-you through in there?
CARLA:
Hold your horses. I'm coming.
Shut up, everybody.
Hey, look, everybody.
It's our little
leprechaun, Brill O'Head.
Keep talking, Clavin, you'll
lose your left Blarney Stone.
This outfit is ridiculous.
I mean, I want to beat Gary
as much as the next guy,
but I'm not wearing this, okay?
I think it kind of looks nice.
Yeah, I think it
looks kind of sexy. That's it.
Please, please.
Hey, everybody,
I've got great news.
I applied to the Boston
League of Businesswomen,
and they might let me join.
Oh, who are they?
Oh, it's this very
prestigious organization
that helps raise the stature
of women in society...
and that kind of crap.
Sam, I need a couple hours
off tomorrow because
they want to interview me.
Honey, it's the
busiest day of my year.
What difference does it make?
She doesn't do anything anyway.
You know what?
Why don't you take
the whole day off?
You're a peach.
Hi, everybody.
(booing)
What the hell do you
want here, Gary?
Well, you know, in the spirit
of Saint Patrick's Day,
I thought I'd come over here and
give you guys a chance
to call off our little bet
and, uh, save yourselves
the supreme humiliation.
I'll tell you what, Gary,
we're gonna win this
lousy bet this year.
Not only that, we're gonna make
ten times more money than you.
And you know why?
Because we've got a strategy.
Well, you know, if you're so
sure of yourself, Malone,
maybe you'd like to raise
the stakes a little bit
and make it more interesting
than the usual 100 bucks?
What you got in mind?
Oh, just a little something
that the loser has to do.
What are you doing?
Oh, I don't know, Gary, uh...
Well, okay well,
if you're going to be chicken about it.
Oh, I'm not being chicken,
because we're gonna win anyway.
So, we've got a deal?
Uh, all right. All right.
Yeah, yeah.
But wait a minute, what is the,
uh, what are the ground rules?
Malone, there's only
one rule, no rules.
Just the way I like it.
Great.
May the best man win.
Sam, may I have
a word with you? Yeah.
I strongly urge you
to reconsider.
Listen, why do you think Gary's
so willing to up the stakes?
I mean, it stands to
reason that he thinks he's going to win.
No, no, he's bluffing.
What makes you think that?
Well he-he's beaten us
ten times in a row.
And not one of those times
has he raised the stakes.
He's running scared.
Well, don't I feel stupid.
All those degrees really don't
do much, do they, Doctor?
Sammy, what's up?
I thought you wanted to get
an early jump on Gary.
Yeah, I did. That's
why I'm here at 9:00.
9:01, Sam.
Some of us were
here at 9:00.
Hey, relax, will you.
It's in the bag.
I fixed it so Gary
can't ever win.
Yeah?
Yeah? What'd you do?
Yeah, you're gonna love this.
You know that-that sign
he's got outside
his window there,
"50 cent beer,
Saint Patrick's Day Special?"
CARLA:
Yeah. Yeah, well I added a zero.
I mean who's going to pay
$5 for a beer, huh?
Good one, Sam.
Yeah.
Sometimes I scare myself.
It's 9:02, Sam. Let's go.
All right. Sorry.
$5 beer.
(laughing)
Yeah, let's see him top that.
(gasps)
See now, that,
that's not right.
Gary did it to us again.
Walled off from the keg.
I want him dead, Sam.
His family, dead.
His friends, dead!
SAM:
Oh, now see, this, this is,
this is the lowest thing
a person can do.
This is pure evil.
Yeah.
Why can't we think like that?
Tell me about it.
I thought you left Woody here to
guard against things like this.
WOODY (voice echoing):
Sorry, Sam. I fell asleep.
They walled Woody in the bar.
Woody, you all right in there?
Well, I'm feeling
light-headed and woozy, Sam.
That's the way I want to feel.
Somebody tear this thing down!
New Armani, new hair.
Am I ready for the Boston League
of Businesswomen or what?
I just have to get my resume
and then I'm on my way.
Is this in any way my fault?
No, sweetheart.
Okay then wish me luck.
Bye-bye.
Yep. Crisis solved.
Where'd you get the beer?
I've got a few squirrelled away
around the bar for emergencies.
I always kind of figured it
would be a nuclear thing,
but I think this qualifies.
Where would you like us
to set up, Mr. Malone?
Oh, hi. fellows.
Uh... uh, yeah, why not?
I'll tell you what,
right over there.
Thank you very much...
Hey, come on, Norm, Carla,
listen we can still win
this thing, right?
We, we've got
the green beer, we've got the band.
All we've got to do is
get rid of this wall somehow
and hustle like
there's no tomorrow.
All we need is, uh, well, a little
winning attitude, right? There you go.
A little positivity.
Hey, fellas,
do me a favour,
play us a little something
to get us in the mood.
Yeah.
♪ They broke
into our Dublin home ♪
♪ The dirty English dogs ♪
♪ They took away my sister ♪
♪ And they beat my
da with logs ♪
♪ Limey scum, limey scum ♪
♪ I toss a bomb
and still they come... ♪
Everybody.
♪ Limey scum, limey scum... ♪
♪ And everywhere I looked ♪
♪ Was death, death, death ♪
♪ Everywhere I looked ♪
♪ Was death, death, death. ♪
(one person applauds)
And now, for a sad song.
(mournful melody)
♪ 'Twas a baby's crib
that floated... ♪
No! No! No! No!
No baby's crib!
Stop it.
Here, get the hell
out of here, will you?
Take your money.
Go on, get out.
Go to hell.
Let's face it;
It's over, huh?
Might as well tally up and
see what we've got there.
Yeah, Woody, what's the total?
Well...
(adding machine keys clicking)
$1 million,
five hundred thousand.
Decimal point, Woody.
Oh. Hold everything.
$150 even.
Hey guys, bad news.
I just came from Gary's.
He's raking in the money,
hand over fist.
And then again why shouldn't he?
I mean, he's charging
five bucks a beer.
Looks like we lost again.
Well, Sammy, guess you're
gonna have to fork over
that 150 to Gary.
Uh, actually, we
raised the stakes, remember fellas?
Oh, yeah, how much
do you have to pay?
Well, it's, it's not money.
It's uh, it's more like
a, a little favour, actually.
Oh yeah? What is it?
It's, it's something
that people do everyday.
Uh, uh, I'm going to,
uh, need, uh,
you three guys
to help me out here.
Hey, just once I'd like
to be included, huh?
All right, Paul, you're in.
Thank you. Thanks,
I owe you Sammy.
Well, what do we have to do?
Uh, it's no big
thing, really, Norm.
We've just got to go over
to Gary's and... (mumbles)
What?
Uh, it's no big deal.
Fellas, all we've got
to do is, is let him (mumbles).
What?
Just get your coats and follow me.
I'll tell you on the way over.
Hey, Sam, what's the big deal.
Why don't you just tell us
what we have to do?
All right, you got to...
(all screaming)
SAM:
Well, what do you think?
NORM:
Well, let's get it over with.
Yeah, yeah, all right, Gary.
Go on. Go on. Go on.
Okay, I want to see
some big smiles.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Gary's Olde Towne Tavern has the
privilege of presenting an act
so humiliating, so embarrassing,
so degrading
that it could only happen
to the men of Cheers!
Let's hear it for them!
(whistles, applause)
Gentlemen?
(cheers and whistling)
Whoo! Whoo!
And three, and four, and...
♪ Getting to know you ♪
♪ Getting
to know all about you ♪
♪ Getting to like you,
hoping that you like me ♪
♪ Haven't you noticed? ♪
♪ Suddenly I'm bright
and breezy ♪
♪ Because of all the beautiful
and new things ♪
♪ I'm learning about you ♪
♪ Day by day. ♪
(cheering)
It was the low point
in my life.
Never ever have I been naked
and not had fun.
I tell you it was degradation.
I thought we were
a lot tighter the second show.
How am I ever gonna show my face
in here again?
Paul, it's not your
face that's burned into my memory.
You know, I kind of found
the whole thing,
uh, quite exhilarating.
Exhilarating?
I meant humiliating.
It was really humiliating.
Uh, guys, you've been really
good to me,
so I'm gonna be good to you.
You need a finish.
Yeah, that's real funny.
That's real funny stuff.
I'll tell you something, man.
I'm gonna get you- I don't
care how long it takes,
how much money it costs,
how many lives are lost,
I'm gonna get you, Gary,
once and for all.
Oh, I hope not
because I'm still shaking
from that terrifying
five-dollar-beer prank.
Yeah, well, I'm still
gonna get you.
Sammy, let's just give it up.
No! Never!
I tell you
I'm gonna get that guy.
I don't give a...
Oh, you know...
Oh, yes,
yes-yes-yes.
There's one guy who can help us
out here, fellows.
I'm calling in Harry the Hat.
(all exclaim)
You know, my underwear's
a little tight.
It's funny, mine's
a little loose.
(both scream)
HARRY:
Let me get this straight.
Over the years, Gary has put
sheep in your office,
had exterminators shut you down,
and then yesterday
he built a brick wall
around the bar
and had you perform naked?
Listen, we need your help bad.
I'm sorry, Sam,
I'm not interested.
Oh, all right, fine.
Fine, Harr.
What is your price?
No, I don't want
your money, Sam.
Besides, if I did,
I could take it.
I kind of like you guys.
So let me give you a piece of
advice: stop trying to top Gary.
You're never gonna beat him.
Face it.
You're a bunch of losers.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
It's your nature you know?
It's the way God made you.
You're part of his master plan.
If it weren't for you guys,
how would we know
who the winners were?
No, we're not losers.
All right, fine,
have it your way.
Woody, give me a beer, huh?
Sure.
CLIFF: Yeah, but don't
forget to charge him, Woody.
Get some money out of him.
Yeah, all right, all right.
What do I owe you, Woody?
Well, that'll be two dollars.
Hey, you know, I got
a lot of change here.
Will you take all this
and give me a 20?
Well, you know,
be careful of that Woody.
I think he's pulling
his flimflam
short change thing here.
Really?
Yeah, yeah.
Count the money.
Oh... oh, this isn't right.
Aha. Yeah, see?
You gave me too much.
Huh?
That's your tip, Woody.
Oh, no, I'm not falling
for that.
I'll just keep
the two dollars for the beer.
Yeah. See, Harry?
We're not as stupid
as you think we are.
No, I guess you're not.
Here's your wallet, Cliff.
Wow, he's good.
Very good.
Aw, who are we kidding,
you guys?
We might as well just quit.
Hey, wait, wait a minute.
What are you saying?
You mean after
Gary's done to us,
you're just gonna roll over
and die?
You're gonna walk away?
You're gonna be a quitter, Sam?
Yeah, Carla, that's exactly what
I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna quit!
I'm tired of losing to the guy.
Tomorrow I'm gonna go
over there.
I'm gonna make my peace with him
once and for all.
Well, go.
But I'm not lettin' him
off the hook.
This is personal now.
And I don't know what,
I don't know,
but I swear I am gonna do
something to that guy.
Look, Carla,
we're willing to give in.
You should, too.
It's not like you had
to dance naked over there.
No, but I had to look at it
on videotape.
Gary's selling videotapes?
No, He's giving them away
with every five-dollar beer.
Can you believe it?
The League rejected me.
Why?
Because they said I was
too self-involved
and that I wasn't
community-minded enough.
So now I have to spend
the next six months
doing community
service. Yawn.
Woody, get me a charity
on the phone.
Which one?
How the hell do I know?!
Just make sure it's close by.
And I don't want one
that's real depressing.
And no weekends!
(knocking)
(engine starts)
Oh! Oh!
Oh, God! Oh, God!
Oh, God!
Oh, Carla!
(hushed):
Carla!
I just came back from Gary's!
Wha, what were you thinking?!
Are you crazy?!
I really got him good,
didn't I, Sam?
Got him good?
Honey, we're in
serious trouble here!
What are you talking about?
Malone!
You went way too far this time.
You're gonna go to jail
for this!
I swear to God, Gare, we had
nothing to do with this.
Wha-what are you talking about?
Just yesterday, you swore
in front of witnesses that,
that you were gonna ruin me.
You said you'd do anything!
That's true, Sam.
I was there.
What the hell
were you thinking, Malone?
Did you think you were
gonna get away with this?!
Well, forget about it.
I'm gonna call the cops.
The cops?!
Wait a minute!
Putting a rat
in a heating system
isn't even a misdemeanour!
Carla, sweetheart, please,
you're just making things worse.
My, my bar is ruined!
Please, man, don't bring
the cops into this.
Listen, I-I'm begging you.
I'm on my knees here.
No, you're not.
Oh...
Please...
Oh, and this is supposed
to be enough?
Help me out here, will ya?
Come on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sam! Ha-ha, I gotcha!
That's news.
What's, what's going on here?
You fell for it.
It was a trick.
What is a trick?
I saw your bar being bulldozed!
Somebody bulldozed your bar?
I bulldozed my bar.
You see, I sold my property
to a commercial developer,
and he's going to put a shopping
centre on my old spot.
I'm getting a million bucks
for it.
But the best part is,
you guys have humiliated
yourselves at the feet
of the master one last time.
Yeah, well, the joke's on you.
We happen to need a shopping
centre in this area.
Sam, I hope you don't mind,
but since I don't have
a bar anymore,
I invited the developer
over here to, you know,
help me celebrate.
Sam, I'd like you to
meet your new neighbour,
Rutherford Cunningham.
Real nice place you have here.
Nice to meet you.
Sam, is it?
Yeah.
A bottle of your
finest champagne.
(phone rings)
WOODY: Cheers.
Oh, Gary, uh, phone for you,
the bank.
Oh, yeah. Sam, do you mind
if I take that in your office?
It's big business,
that sort of thing.
Sure.
Bank's not used
to million-dollar deposits.
So, Sam!
It's good to see you again.
Now what's that I heard about
the finest champagne?
Did you do this?
Did you, did you destroy
his bar?
No, I didn't.
Gary did.
He's the one hired
the bulldozer.
Me? I'm just an interested
land developer
who's gonna come up a little
short on funds...
say about a million bucks short.
I have the same problem
with a decimal point.
(Gary screams)
Excuse me.
I believe that's the sound
of my check bouncing.
Mr. Cunningham?
Uh, where's,
uh, Mr. Cunningham?
Uh, he left.
Uh, why, Gary?
Uh, no reason.
Oh, man!
Oh, you are terrific!
If you guys ever need any more
help, you just give me a call.
Oh, thank you, Harry.
Ah, don't mention it.
I guess I've always had
a soft spot for you lunkheads.
Hey, how are we ever
gonna pay you back?
Sam, you already have.
Aw, what a guy, huh?
Wonder what he meant by,
we already have
paid him back, though?
Oh, I don't know.
You know, probably that warm
spirit, the camaraderie,
something like that.
Yeah, yeah, he stole
all my money.