Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
(phone ringing)
(answering machine clicks)
WOODY (over machine):
Hi, this is Cheers.
Well, it isn't actually Cheers,
it's Woody Boyd.
Cheers is actually the bar,
and as such,
it couldn't be expected to talk.
SAM:
Woody, start again.
WOODY:
Why? I'm doing fine.
Anyway, uh, there's no one here
to take your call right now.
Well, actually,
if you called right now,
we could take your call,
but if you call when you're...
SAM:
Woody, would you cut it out?
It's sounding stupid.
WOODY:
I am not.
W-W-Why do you always treat me
like I don't know
what I'm doing?
SAM:
It sounds stupid, Woody.
WOODY:
It does not.
(machine beeps)
Hi, Sam, this is Woody.
Uh, I guess you were right.
It does sound stupid.
I'll change it tomorrow.
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
(door opens)
Hey, everybody.
How's it going?
Hey, Norm, look at this.
I just got myself
a brand-new video camera.
Ooh, nice one.
Looks kind of expensive.
Oh, yeah, it is, it is,
but it-it'll pay for
itself in no time at all.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Yeah, I plan to stage
some footage for those programs,
you know, like
America's Funniest Home Videos,
Rescue 911, Nightline,
stuff like that.
Cliff, I don't think
Nightline is staged.
You are so naive.
(door opens)
Good afternoon, everybody.
Hey, Doc.
Hey.
So, what's new?
Got a message
for you here, Fras.
Yeah, here we go.
Shauna called you.
(patrons hoot)
Now, settle down, class.
Shauna is my secretary.
(all hooting)
My temporary secretary.
She's all of 21 years old,
for God's sake.
(all hooting)
Come on, stop it, you guys.
Have a little class, will you?
So you going to
try and bag her?
No, I am not.
Although it's not entirely
out of the realm of reality.
It does seem that the lass
has a... a thing, for Dr. Crane.
(laughs)
(chuckles) Good for you.
Well, I mean, after all,
it's not so hard to believe.
I've been keeping myself
in pretty good shape.
You know, I've been
Nordic Tracking it every night.
Don't you worry, Peter.
Your parents' 50th
anniversary party will go off
without a hitch.
We'll provide
everything you need...
the food, the drinks, the
decorations, the works.
Sign here.
I can't thank you enough
for all your help.
Good, then we'll see
you on Sunday afternoon.
You'll find every
detail will be perfect.
Terrific, now all I
need is a photographer.
Hey, whoa, whoa, hey.
Whoa, whoa.
Excuse me, there, buddy boy.
I, uh, couldn't
help overhearing
that you're looking
for a photographer?
That's right.
Well, you are in luck.
I'm Clifford Clavin,
one of the best camcorder
jockeys in all of Boston.
If you're
in the video business,
why are you dressed
as a mail-man?
Costume party down at
the Directors Guild.
Yeah.
So, what do you say?
You want me to do your
party for, for 50 clams?
Sounds terrific.
I guess I'm pretty lucky
to have run into you.
Yeah.
I'll see you on Sunday.
Hey, you betcha.
Huh, huh, huh?
What do you think, Norm, huh?
It's the beginning of a
whole new career there.
Yeah.
Speaking of which, uh,
I could use an assistant
for my video endeavours.
Uh, what do you say?
I could start you off
at 20, uh, 15 bucks.
15 bucks?
I could use the money.
I've got to get Vera
a Christmas present.
Uh, Christmas was
a couple of weeks ago.
Oh, my.
(door opens)
Hi, Dr. Crane.
Oh, hello, Shauna.
(patrons hoot softly)
You, uh, left some papers
on your desk,
and they looked important,
so I thought
I'd bring them over.
Well, you didn't really...
I mean, these weren't
that important.
There's no need, uh,
these could have waited.
Oh, I-I don't mind.
I-I wasn't doing
anything anyway,
and besides,
it gives me a chance
to see you
outside of the office.
I think you look
even better in here.
Yes, uh, dank
basements flatter me.
(laughing)
Oh, Dr. Crane.
Can I ask you a question?
Well, yes, go right ahead.
Well, this is probably
against the rules,
but would you be
at all interested in,
you know,
seeing each other
outside the office sometime?
(hooting softly)
Uh, well, uh,
oh, uh,
gosh, Shauna, I, uh, you
know, I'm-I'm terribly busy,
and of course there
is my son to think of.
Oh, hey, listen,
I-I don't want to make you
feel uncomfortable.
Um, tell you what.
Let me just go check and see
if you have any messages,
and then I'll be on my way.
Are you crazy?
Did I just hear you turn
down a date with that girl?
Come on, man, reel her in.
Oh, Sam, you don't seem
to understand.
Look, I just came
off a seven-year marriage.
It's hard to...
think of replacing Lilith.
Just go to the morgue
and open any drawer.
Listen, listen, listen, listen.
I'm not, I'm not saying you
got to replace the corp...
replace Lilith.
All I'm saying is, you know,
ask-ask her out on a date.
Well, perhaps...
i-in a few days maybe.
No, come on, do it now.
Ask her right this sec...
I tell you, if you don't,
I'm gonna ask her out.
You got one minute on
the old Sammy clock.
All right, by George,
I'll do it right this minute.
Attaboy.
Frasier Crane
is back in the game.
(laughs)
No messages.
Uh, Shauna, uh,
what you were saying
before, uh,
about our seeing
each other, um...
Well, uh, to put it this way,
uh, about, you know,
you and me, uh...
You got about 30 seconds.
Would you really like
to go out with me?
(chuckles)
You bet I would.
You know, uh, I have an idea.
Instead of going out,
why don't you come
over to my place
for dinner on Sunday night?
Uh, your place?
Uh, well, I'd be delighted.
Uh, can I bring anything-
a dessert maybe?
Oh, no, Dr. Crane.
Don't bring dessert.
I'll take care of that.
You're going to get dessert!
I told you we're closed.
It's a private party.
Employees only.
Please.
I'll tell them I own the place.
I do it all the time.
For the last time, go home!
Ow!
Carla, will you stop being
rude to the customers?
It was Paul.
Oh, I'm sorry, I couldn't
see through the glass.
(door opens)
Okay, here we are, Frederick.
(chuckling):
Hey.
It's my pal Freddy.
Go to your Uncle Sammy there.
Here we go.
Oh, Sam.
Listen, I can't thank you
enough for volunteering
to fill in
when the babysitter cancelled.
I mean, if you hadn't offered,
I wouldn't be able
to see Sauna tonight.
I mean, I mean...
Shauna.
Wow, boy,
there's a slip for you!
(Frasier and Sam laugh)
Aw, it's my pleasure.
You're looking good, Freddy.
Okay, now, I brought
some of his toys here.
We've got his,
uh, his choo-choo.
Hmm.
And his blankey.
Mm-hmm.
And his toy soldier.
Here you go.
Ooh, cool.
And, uh-
well, let's see...
bag full of educational crap
that Lilith got him.
Ah.
And his, uh, favourite book
The Runaway Bunny.
You keep that
book away from me.
How come, Carla?
I have eight kids.
I've read that book
a thousand times,
and every time I read it,
I bawl like a baby.
Oh, no kidding.
"Once there was a little bunny
Stop it. No, stop it.
"who wanted to run away..."
(continues reading) Stop it!
Stop it! Stop it!
Frasier, can I take
Freddy a minute?
Well, of course.
You remember Auntie Rebecca?
Hello.
Good boy, Frederick.
Yeah, take them both,
take them both.
There you go.
Thank you.
All right, Sam, now listen,
here's a list of numbers.
Here's, uh, my beeper.
This is, uh, Shauna's house.
And this is Lilith
at the eco-pod.
They got a telephone
at the eco-pod?
Well, no, it's just
for emergencies,
but, uh, listen, call her,
yank her chain for me.
I won't have a chance
to do it tonight. (laughs)
I'll see if I can get to it.
Thanks. Oh, and, uh,
one other thing I need
to discuss with you.
Very important,
uh, in, uh, private.
Could you just join
me in the men's room?
In the men's room?
That's a little weird, isn't it?
Oh, Sam, get your head
out of the seventh grade
for God's sake!
We're just two men having
a private conversation.
All right, okay.
Well, don't go in with me!
How would that look?!
CLIFF:
Oh!
All right, hey, there you are.
Okay, everybody, just relax.
Don't mind me.
Pretend like I'm not here.
There you are.
Everything's all set.
I took the liberty of making
name tags for everybody.
See? Hello, my
name's Rebecca.
And this one is for you, Peter.
And your name is?
We're all family.
We know each other's names.
Well, let me make one
out for you anyway.
B-I-T-C...
Come on, man.
I got a party out here!
FRASIER:
All right, Sam, please.
This is very important.
(door unlocks)
(hums)
What do you think?
Oh, it's super.
Really?
Oh, you're ser...?
Oh, I'm...
no, I'm sorry.
No, uh... oh, I can't
lie to you, man.
This is just, uh...
Well, it's-it's not you.
(laughs) Damn, you know...
It looked so good
on the Styrofoam head.
Oh, hell, Sam,
who am I trying to kid?
Oh, this is ridiculous.
I'm gonna call
Shauna and cancel.
Oh, well, wait a second.
Wh-What are you doing, man?
She likes you.
Didn't you hear what she said?
"Oh, no, Dr. Crane,
don't bring dessert.
I'll take care of that."
(both laugh)
Oh, I'm just... I'm just
too old to be dating.
Oh, stop it! Come on,
you were a ladies man
before you met Lilith,
weren't you? Well, yeah.
Yeah, you were!
Hey, look at that.
Look at that.
You are
a good-lookin' man.
Well, I'm not exactly a...
a dog.
(chuckling)
Come on. Go over there,
enjoy yourself.
You know, all you've
got to do is
bring a little champagne,
some flowers,
sweet talk her a little bit.
Before you know it,
it's time to go home.
Or maybe, you don't go home.
You know what I mean?
(both laughing)
Is that the way, uh,
most dates go for you, Sam?
No, now come on,
now, don't do that.
See, this is not a test.
You're not expected
to perform at my level.
The thing is just to...
enjoy myself, as myself.
Yes.
Okay. Thanks, Sam.
Yeah, yeah.
Now, Frasier Crane...
is gonna go get some
before it gets cold.
(laughs)
Oh...
Everything okay in here, Sam?
Yeah, yeah,
no problem just, uh,
you know, I had to help
Frasier out with something.
(clicks tongue)
We've got bigger problems, Sam.
Those things are back!
(doorbell chimes)
Well, come on in,
Dr. Crane.
Dinner's on the table.
How old are you, like, 90?
Okay, so this button's
the "on-off" button.
This, uh, this button here
makes it louder or softer.
And these two
buttons right here
make everything
bluer or greener.
Those two are my favourites.
Have a ball there.
Poor kid.
Probably don't let him
watch enough TV at home.
Yeah.
It's a wonder why some
people even have kids. Oh...
Great shot.
Oh! Hey, listen, ma'am,
would you mind holding
this in your lap
and just tilt it up
at an angle like that?
I want to do
a slow tracking shot.
Hi, sexy.
What are you going to be
doing after work tonight?
Trying to forget you
asked me that.
Well, you do great work.
Look for your, uh,
credits in the end titles,
there, sweetheart.
Cliffie, what's this red
blinking light mean?
Oh, that means
the battery's dead.
All right, give me the spare.
I'll slap it in for you.
Actually, I don't, I don't
have a spare there, Norm.
Okay, uh, no problem,
just give me the power cord.
We'll find an outlet.
These come with power cords?
What are you...?
What are you telling me?
That this camera doesn't...
this camera is useless?
These people paid us
good money, Cliff.
What are we going to do?!
Relax, will you, Norm.
We'll-We'll figure
out some kind of a plan.
Well, you'd better
come up with something.
All right, here.
Here's what we'll do. All right.
We'll just carry on and film
as though nothing's wrong.
We'll pretend
the camera's working.
Then in a couple of days
when they call us for the film,
we'll say,
"We dropped it in the mail.
It must have gotten lost."
All right?
We got the 50 bucks,
nobody's the wiser.
Great, great, as long
as you have a plan.
Norm, you know,
in a couple of weeks,
nobody here's gonna remember
some stupid
anniversary party. Yeah.
(clinking)
Attention, everyone!
I've waited
50 years to say this.
Wait a minute, Dad.
Say it into the camera.
We want to preserve
this moment forever.
Hey, guys, come on over!
Okay, coming right up!
Come on, Norm.
Let's go capture this
moment on video tape.
I-I don't know
why it's taken me so long
to say this to you kids,
but I love you,
every one of you.
Cliff, you've got to tell them.
It's not my fault
the guy took 50 years
to tell his kids he loved them.
I mean, what kind
of father is that anyway?
All right, so there was
one moment in the whole thing.
Big whoops.
I mean, you know, with all
the drinking and yelling,
nobody's gonna
remember anything.
Grandma! Grandpa!
I flew 34 hours
in a marine cargo
plane to get here.
But it's worth it all
just to say,
"Happy Anniversary,
I love you!"
(gasping, applause)
Oh, Terry, my baby boy!
Thank God we're getting
this on tape!
(sotto voce):
Yeah, thank God.
My God, Terry.
They wouldn't tell us
if you were alive or dead.
There's one thing
that kept me alive.
I was thinking about
coming home to you.
Oh!
All right, Cliff, come on.
What are we gonna do here?
You got to tell them.
All right,
look, look everybody.
My boss here has
an announcement to make.
Uh, yeah, everybody.
I've got to go on my break.
My assistant will take over.
All right, now, let's, uh,
squeeze in tight everybody.
So...
you're, uh, Shauna's family.
You know, when Shauna
invited me for dinner,
she didn't mention
that we'd be having dinner
with her whole family.
(Frasier chuckles)
Interestingly enough,
many young people today
are choosing to move
back in with their parents.
We call it the, uh,
"Full Nest Syndrome."
It wasn't her choice.
Well...
Shauna's made
some bad decisions.
She's not real good
on responsibility.
Well, I must say that she, uh,
she handled herself quite
well this week at my office.
Thank you,
Dr. Crane. See?!
Oh, yeah, Doctor,
I forgot I was getting
a professional opinion.
Where did you go to school?
Harvard.
Well, la-di-da.
And is this what they taught
you at Harvard?
How to take advantage
of my daughter?
Sir, I am not taking advantage.
I was merely invited for an
innocent little dinner.
Oh? Just "an innocent
little dinner"?
Mind if I check your wallet?
There's no need for that!
I don't like this, Shauna.
But why not, Daddy?
Isn't this the kind
of guy that you always
wanted me to date?
Is this the choice you give me?
Either some silver-spoon egghead
or that hippy?
Why are you bringing up Rick?
I thought I was
forbidden to see Rick.
"Rick"?
That's her old boyfriend.
Okay, I get it.
All right, thank you,
Shauna, for inviting me to be
a little pawn in your game.
Now, if you'll excuse
me, I'll just be going.
Oh, no,
please stay, Dr. Crane.
Everything is fine.
Everything is just fine.
Uh, Tater Tots?
I don't know
why he likes Shauna.
She's only big up there,
'cause she stuffs.
Shut up, Todd!
He would have found out,
in, like, a year.
Make him shut up!
(motorcycle approaching)
And whom else have we invited
for dinner, tonight, Shauna?
If I'm right
and this is in fact
the worst night of my life,
it would be Rick.
Well, you know that drop-out's
not allowed in this house.
Shauna!
Rick!
You came for me.
You really do love me.
Oh, please.
That's it,
I'm calling the police.
Daddy, why can't you like Rick?
Can't you see that
we're in love?
Don't you run out
on me, Shauna!
I'm your father!
(door slams)
Don't lock that door.
(pounding on door)
I think I'll just be going now.
Why? Everything
is just fine.
It's just fine.
Now, who's got room for dessert?
So I guess, Freddy, uh,
you know what they're
saying is that wherever
the baby bunny goes,
the mommy bunny is...
is there waiting for
him to take care of him.
I guess I, uh,
must have touched my eye
with some of that, uh,
salt from the peanuts.
(crying):
Me, too.
That's it, yeah.
Let's do the good-byes now.
Wave, yes.
See you later.
Had a good time.
We're gonna need
a lot of copies of this.
Oh, yes, sir.
Well, you'll get 'em.
All right, sir.
You'll get those copies,
all right.
We're going to jail, Norm.
What do you mean "we"?
I'm only the assistant here.
(groans)
Everybody,
I have something to say.
I want you all to know that
you have given me the strength
to do this.
(gasping, murmuring)
This is too much, Cliff.
Either you tell them
now, or I'm going to.
Yeah, well, I guess I'd better
before Bigfoot walks in here
and starts singing
"The Anniversary Waltz."
I guess if you give me the tape,
we'll be going.
Oh! So you want
the tape right now?
Uh, I tell you what,
how about if I take
a shot from up here,
one last shot.
Norm, uh...
Everybody, over here!
Turn this way, uh...
let me see those
pearly whites, huh?
Okay, everybody smile.
Okay, we'll just
back it up here, Norm.
Back it up.
(clears throat):
Open the door, Norm.
Okay, back it up.
That's good.
Okay, I'm just
gonna back it up.
Everybody wave, yeah.
Run like hell!
Yahtzee!
(laughing)