Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
No, I don't
remember her name.
(wind whistling)
Sammy?
Yeah. Yeah.
It's Mike Dukakis.
SAM:
Yeah.
It's Michael Dukakis.
Let's go say
hello to him.
We can't.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
What'll we call him?
Uh, Governor.
Ex. Ex-governor.
Ooh, yeah. Your Honor.
There you go.
You... Your
Ex Honor.
No, no, no, no, no.
Yeah.
Mike.
Michael.
Duke! Duke,
Duke, Duke!
Duke! Duke! Duke!
Hi. How're you doing?
SAM:
Hi.
(both laughing)
We said hello to
Michael Dukakis!
No, no, we said hi to Mike!
Michael.
No, no.
Duke. Duke.
Duke. Duke. We said
hello to Duke.
(theme song begins)
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always
glad you came
You wanna be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You wanna be where
everybody knows your name
You wanna go
where people know
People are all the same
You wanna go where
everybody knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Oh! Uh, uh.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, Rebecca.
Uh, 2:15.
Hey, Sammy, here you go.
Thanks, Carla.
Phew! That was close.
What the hell was that?
Sammy's vitamin E.
It's Valentine's Day.
Duh!
Oh, yeah.
That's that stupid date
he goes on once a year
with that-- what is that--
Lauren person.
NORM:
Stupid?
This is not some
stupid date, Rebecca.
For the last
20 years,
Sammy and Lauren have met
for one night each year.
It's kind of like Sammy's
version of commitment.
Actually,
it's a lot like
my version of commitment.
SAM:
Hey, Carla,
how long have you had this
bottle of vitamin E around, huh?
I don't know.
A while. Why?
What is with this date
you go on every year?
I mean, you know, to me,
it just... it just seems silly.
(men gasping)
Uh-oh!
Come on, guys.
Guys, she just
doesn't understand.
You see, sweetheart, first
time Lauren and I met,
we went up to
this cabin, and
we had a night
that was totally
romantic and erotic.
I guess you'd
call that silly.
If you liked her so much,
how come you only
see her once a year?
I don't know. I don't
know. It was her idea.
You know, she
never told me why.
I keep meaning to ask
her, but then I forget.
This year's going
to be different, though.
I'm gonna pin her down.
No, I better not do that.
Actually, I'll forget again,
won't I?
Well, I still say
it's a stupid way
to spend
Valentine's Day.
Yeah, but
that's 'cause
you don't have a date.
Oh, yeah? I happen
to have a date
with two very sweet gentlemen--
Ben and Jerry.
Hey, you know,
it's just a made-up
holiday anyway.
You know, some big fat
greeting card tycoon
trying to get rich
off of dopey cards
and candy hearts.
Don't be depressed
about that.
Yeah, maybe
you're right.
If you're gonna be depressed
about anything,
it should be the fact
that you're only making
seven bucks an hour,
your skin is starting
to flake at the hairline,
and you're a year closer
to death.
Thank you, Carla.
But, hey,
if it makes you feel any better,
Happy Valentine's Day!
Woody, a couple
of pitchers, please.
Sure, Dr. Crane.
Uh, if you're
buying beer
for your friends
back there, Fras,
you know, I'm,
uh... I'm available.
(laughs)
Well...
Actually,
they're not friends.
It's a therapy group I have
for men who have trouble
relating to women.
(laughing):
Well, set
'em up, Wood.
Ah, Frasier.
Here you are.
And where are the
dysfunctional men?
Throw a rock.
They're in the pool room.
Come along, ladies.
Why don't you go on ahead
into the poolroom and...
make yourselves as comfortable
as five women totally hostile
to their own bodies can be.
After you.
So, uh,
what's going on back there?
Well, Frasier and I are both
treating same-sex groups
with relationship disorders.
And recent studies suggest
that there are benefits
to be gained by bringing
these two groups together
for interrelations
under controlled
social circumstance.
Say what?
Well, come on.
Surely you've all seen,
uh, Love Connection.
Oh!
G... Guys! Guys!
What are you doing out here?
Dr. Crane, there's...
there's...
Yes, I know.
There's girls in there.
But you see,
you're missing the point.
This is exactly the type
of situation
we've been training for.
This time it's the real thing,
not just me in a wig.
Whoa!
Man, those stairs are slippery.
Woody, I think we could use
a little salt out there.
These pretzels could
use a little salt, too.
My blood pressure's
actually dipping.
Boy, those patients of mine
are really hopeless.
Well, heck,
bring them
out here.
This is the
hopeless room.
Yeah, I don't know, Dr. Crane.
Haven't you ever thought
that it's kind of tough on them,
doing all that counseling stuff?
I mean, I was raised to believe
that if you have a problem,
you lock it away
in a secret place.
You keep it bottled up
good and tight.
And if it gets full in there,
you just keep forcing
the pain down
and clamping it in.
Good advice, Woody.
Tick, tick, tick.
Well, guys, I'm all packed
and ready to go.
Hey.
You sure you got
everything, Sam?
Yup.
And then some.
Oh! Oh,
you dog!
Hey!
You dog!
Well, hey,
I'm out of here.
No, no, no.
No, you don't,
Sam Malone!
SAM:
What?
You don't just
leave here
on your 20th-anniversary date
with Lauren just like that.
We got something special
cooked up for you. Carla,
hit it.
(fanfare plays)
Ah, look at him go.
So proud,
so majestic,
so regal.
(thudding, Sam grunting)
CARLA:
Woody,
you never salted
those steps, did you?
Hey, I'll get to it.
Let me see.
I don't believe
there's a fracture,
just a serious sprain
right around lumbar three.
Does it hurt
when I do this?
(groaning)
That's good.
Ooh. Why? Does that mean
I'm gonna get better?
No. Because it means I know
what I'm talking about.
You see, Lilith, I could
so have been a real doctor.
Hey, give me a hand here,
will you, Woody?
Oh, geez.
Time's a-wastin',
my friend.
Oh, Sam, you're not
seriously thinking
of still going on
this date, are you?
You bet I am.
NORM:
All right!
(men cheering)
Sam, I seriously
urge you
to stay off your feet
and in bed.
Well, that's part of
the plan, there, Fras.
Hey, Woody, can you do me
one tiny little favor?
Sure, Sam.
What is it?
Can you get me up to my car,
then drive me to Vermont,
then get me
into the cabin?
What's in
it for me?
Well, you could use
that new gas card of yours
to fill the tank.
All right!
I'll feel so grown up!
All right, Sam.
I'm gonna drive
you up there,
and I don't want you
to worry about a thing.
I'm a very
good driver.
Great. Great.
Just go, please.
Ding, ding, ding.
What are you doing?
"The captain is requesting
that all passengers please
fasten their safety belts."
Oh.
(groans)
C-Can you get that
for me, please?
Sure, Sam.
Where is that
seat belt?
(grunts)
Here it is.
Ow!
That hurt!
I'm sorry.
(clicking seat belt)
Nice and snug.
Here we go.
(car engine starts)
Ignition, lights,
parking brake,
mirror, signal.
(turn signal clicking)
Blind spot.
Vermont,
here we come.
(brakes squeal)
Lord have mercy!
What? What happened? Aah!
Well, I didn't think
that pigeon was gonna
fly away in time.
Why do they always wait
till the last minute?
What, do they think
that's funny or something?
Aw, I don't know, Woody...
All right. All
right, Sam, hang on.
We're gonna pull out again.
Mirror, signal, blind spot.
(turn signal clicking)
There.
"Exit 19.
Concord Street."
"Exit 20."
"Route 125."
Woody...
Hang on, Sam.
"93 North."
Oh, no, please,
don't read all the road signs.
Oh, fine, Sam.
Would you like me
to ignore the speed limit, too?
I wouldn't mind
if you approached it.
Meow, Sam.
(rattling)
Sam, I hear some rattling.
Is your door
closed all the way?
No, it's not.
Here, I'll get it.
No, no, hang on.
I-I'm gonna
pull over as soon as
I make this turn.
(sighs)
No, don't undo
your seat belt!
Give me a break.
Will you lighten up?
Whoa!
(thudding)
Now would that have happened
if you'd been wearing
your safety belt?
Now boys,
girls,
I have an orange
under my chin.
I am going to attempt to
pass it to this lovely woman,
whom I do not fear.
Now you see,
isn't that fun?
Whoa!
Now, why don't you
have a crack at it?
Edward, how about you?
Come on.
Here we are.
That's lovely.
Okay. Ready?
Yes. Good, good,
good, yes.
I don't think I want
to do this, Dr. Crane.
Oh, all right!
And what would you
suggest that we do?
Stare at one another?
Lord knows you've all had
enough practice at that!
You're pressuring
them, Doctor.
Oh, you're right, darling. Uh...
You know, perhaps
we should try
a different approach.
You know, there is
a technique pioneered
in the early 60's,
which is thought
to be without peer
in producing the social
effect that we seek.
I'm referring,
of course, to...
Twister!
LILITH:
Left foot blue.
(door opens)
Oh, yeah.
Ah, this place is going to see
some action tonight.
Oh, Sam, you've still
got a little gravel
stuck to the back
of your neck.
Yeah? Well, I like
it like that.
Just get me
on the bed there.
You can take off and come
pick me up in the morning.
(car approaching)
Oh, hey, that's
Lauren's car there.
Oh, great! I'm really looking
forward to meeting her.
No, no, man. You g...
you got to get out of here.
If she sees you, she's gonna
think something's wrong.
It'll ruin the mood.
Just quick-- get out the window.
Go on!
Oh, sure.
"Quick, out the window."
Not exactly the undying
thanks and gratitude
I might expect after driving
200 miles through the snow.
Would you just shut up
and move your butt?
Oh, that's much better, Sam.
That'll keep me warm
on the drive home.
Sam, there's a door here.
Why'd I go
out the window?
Would you get out of here?!
Go on!
Happy Valentine's Day, Sam.
Happy Valentine's Day, Lauren.
Aww... wait.
Why? Wh-what are you doing?
I want to get a running start.
No-no!
No! No! Lauren!
Nooooo!
Now you have to play
by the rules.
The bottle is clearly
pointing at Jill.
Now, Jules, you
have to kiss her.
I pass.
For the hundredth time,
you cannot pass!
Okay, I quit.
Perhaps it's time
we admit our failure.
It was a well-intentioned
experiment,
but we realize now
that you're not ready
for this type of
social interaction.
I guess we can only
conclude by saying,
"Oh, well."
FRASIER:
No!
I'm not giving up!
How difficult can it
be to kiss a woman?
Be a little assertive
for once in your life!
Now you see how
easy that was? Again.
Again!
Class dismissed.
Let's go, hon.
(Lauren moans)
Sam, is something wrong?
Mm-mm, why?
You're biting your lip.
Mm.
Usually, you bite my lip.
(chuckles)
I'm sorry.
I have an idea.
Ow!
(sultry music plays)
Let's dance the way
we used to, Sam.
(chuckles)
You know something,
we always dance.
W-Why don't we just, uh...
why don't we just sit
very still, huh?
Yeah, i-it could become
a new tradition for us.
Come on, Sam,
let's slow dance.
(grunts):
No!
You like that, huh?
Hey, I've got a great idea here.
Let's, uh, tell you what.
You want to learn that new dance
that's sweeping Boston?
I'm game.
What do we do?
The guy kind of stands
like this, very still.
And sometimes
he leans up against something.
And pretty soon his legs
start to tremble.
Sort of the way
yours are now.
Yeah, yeah.
There, you like it?
(snapping fingers)
Well, what does
the girl do?
Usually she runs for some ice.
You don't want to dance,
do you, Sam?
No, you know, the truth is,
I really don't.
Sam, what's going on?
What do you mean?
Never mind.
I think I know.
(music stops)
I mean, it's obvious.
I'm not exactly as young
as I used to be and, um...
Oh, sweetheart, wait a minute.
Wait, is that what you think?
Well, it's okay.
You can level with me.
I've gotten too old for you.
Oh, no. Listen, age has nothing
to do with it.
You-- you are still
as young and sexy
as that first day
and night and next morning
that we met.
Really, Sam?
Then why are you acting
so standoffish?
Yeah... oh, honey, I've got
to level with you here.
Sweetie, I fell down
the steps today.
I threw my back out.
I can barely move.
Oh...
Well, I'm not surprised,
a man your age.
Hey, look!
That cute guy,
with the hairy knuckles,
he just left me a five buck tip
inside this Valentine.
How 'bout that?
So what?
I thought that we...
didn't care...
about that...
stupid made-up...
Valentine corporate garbage.
That's just
what losers say
when they don't get any.
But I got one,
and at 11:40.
Right under the wire.
Whoa, I almost pulled
a Rebecca that time.
That's not very nice, Carla.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I almost forgot.
Guess who called you
to wish you a Happy
Valentine's Day?
Who?
Nobody!
Well, don't you
worry there, Rebecca.
Nobody's a loser
on this day.
I'm not going to, uh,
let you leave the bar
empty-handed.
What's this?
It's a Valentine's
card I got for Ma,
but I, I think it
suits you better.
Gee, Cliff, thanks.
Hey! Carla!
I did get one!
So, uh...
what am I gonna get for it?
What do you mean?
Eh, come on, baby,
swing a little.
What?
Well, according to Fras, uh,
babes like guys
who are assertive.
Aw, come on,
Robin's not here,
Sam's out of the picture.
You've had the rest,
now try the best.
Happy Valentine's Day, Cliff.
Thank you.
Cliffie, uh, where--
where is ev...
Cliffie?
(snaps fingers)
Cliffie!
Thank you.
I've had 20-20 vision
all my life.
Now when I go
to a restaurant,
I have to have someone
at the next table
hold the menu so
I can read it.
(both chuckle)
No, you know what the worst
thing about old age is?
It's when you get so old that
the skin under your arms
starts getting loose
and hanging like turkey wattle.
I thought that
only happened to women.
Yeah, that's what I meant.
I just, you know, I hate
to see it, that's all.
Has your doctor put
you on a bran diet?
Oh, yeah, God...
Oh, I tell you--
oh, thank you. Oh!
Last year was the worst.
You know, I went in for this
stomach problem.
Turned out I had a stone
the size of a golf ball.
Took me a month to pass it.
Sam, has your hair
started turning gray?
Hey, hey. You're getting
a little personal there.
Aren't you?
Sam, look, it's
getting light out.
We've been
talking all night.
Oh, hey, how about that?
Wow! You know, that's...
that's a first.
Kind of nice to know
that we have
something in common
besides our bodies.
Oh, yeah, we have
the deterioration
of our bodies.
Yeah.
Well, I've got
a long drive ahead.
I better get started.
Oh, no. Wait, wait.
Wait a second here, listen.
Honey, y-you can't go now.
I mean, we barely spent
the night together.
W-Why can't you stay?
Oh, Sam, I would love to,
but you know how this works.
Just one night a year.
Yeah, but that's
a stupid rule, you know that?
I never have understood that.
W-Why can't you stay?
I have to get to Portland
by Presidents' Day.
There's a linebacker
I always meet there.
You, you do this
with other guys?
Well, you have other
women, don't you?
Well, yeah, but not once a year.
I mean, I thought I was
special to you.
Oh, Sam, you are.
You'll always be
my Valentine.
Next year.
Yeah, all right.
Bye-bye.
Listen, I could start seeing you
on Arbor Day, too.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, great!
Don't you see another guy
on Arbor Day, though?
I did, but he died.
How?
Happy.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
We'll do it next time.
Thank you...
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4j2cd
Help other users to choose the best subtitles