Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
MAN:
If you look on your left,
you'll see the historic
public garden,
which in colonial days was used
as a public grazing area
for privately owned livestock.
On your right are some
of the historic brownstones.
Oh, my God, step on it, Harry!
He doesn't know what he's
talking about!
It's that
know-it-all mailman!
You wanna know the real...
I'll tell you the real story!
The Clavins got here
before the pilgrims!
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
This damned headache.
I've had it all day.
I can't seem to shake it.
Oh, you know, those
dilated veins there
will just add to your
discomfort there, Doc.
On the other hand,
there is a possibility
that what you have
is not a headache at all
but rather an earwig
that's crawled
into your auditory canal
while you were asleep
and who is
at this very moment,
uh, chewing its way
through your cerebral cortex.
Sam, may I have a glass
of water, please?
I... I'll just take
another aspirin.
That ought to do it.
Frasier, hold it, I
know just the thing.
I'm really good
at massage.
Just sit down,
relax...
There--
how is that?
(hoarse):
I didn't get any water.
Carla, can I ask you
a favor?
No, Woody, I'm
not going
to work for you
this afternoon.
I've already taken
over your schedule
for the past couple of
days, and I'm sick of it.
You can just tell
your girlfriend
you'll see her
after work.
Well, actually,
I was gonna ask
if you could get
off my foot.
Oh.
Speaking of shifts, Sam, uh,
can I leave early?
Kelly hates it when
I'm late for a date.
Henri doesn't care
for it much, either.
Henri?
That slick French
make-out artist always trying to
grab other people's women
with some phony line?
Yeah, that's the guy.
I always
liked that guy.
Yeah, well, Kelly
likes him, too.
He goes on every
date with us.
Yeah, well, just
as long as he's stopped
making those jokes
about stealing Kelly from you.
He has?
Why didn't you
tell me sooner, Sam?
No, no.
I hate those jokes.
No...
Woody, I don't know that
he has, I was just asking.
Oh.
Hey, Sam, I hear you're getting
a big refund from the IRS.
I am?
Two can play
that little game, Sam.
Oh, there you are,
my poor darling.
And you've still got
your headache, haven't you?
Oh, I can see
it's gotten worse
by those tiny little pressure
wrinkles around your eyes.
Maybe that's just
fatty tissue.
It'll go away.
Oh, no, no, once you
get those fat bags,
they're there to stay.
Describe the pain
to me.
Is it a sharp,
stabbing pain?
Is it a dull ache?
Is it a
pressure headache?
Or is it a
throbbing headache,
one that just pounds
and pounds
and pounds...
Lilith, if you don't
stop it, my head
is going to explode
all over this bar!
All right!
Hey, Paul,
get out here!
Frasier,
I'm concerned.
I think it's time we
tried alternative medicine.
No, no, I am not going
to wear a crystal
or dissolve herbs
under my tongue
or listen to some aging hippie
playing the whale flute.
That's not why
I went to college,
although,
when I went to college,
I did all those things.
I'm talking about acupuncture.
No, never!
It's worked for thousands
of years.
The Chinese people
have been practicing it
since the Stone Age.
Why do you insist
on closing your mind
to such a
time-honored remedy?
'Cause it'll hurt!
I'm calling Dr. Lee.
How's your
headache, Frasier?
Oh, fine.
She's into alternative
medicines these days.
WOODY:
Hey, Henri.
Kelly.
Woody, I have a
riddle for you.
How long
will it take
for me to steal
your girlfriend?
I give up.
Then it won't
take long at all.
Such an operator,
it makes me sick.
Yeah, it makes me mad
just to look at him.
Hello, fellows!
ALL:
Hey, Henri, how you doing?
Hey, Henri, how are you doing?
Sam, how is my favorite
American chaser of women?
No, I'm not doing
that anymore, Henri.
You know, I... I've reached
that point in my life
where my priorities are
beginning to shift.
I think I want to settle
down and raise a family.
Ooh, that's a good line.
Does it work?
No, no, no, I'm...
I'm really serious
about this, Henri.
I... I'm gonna go
through with this.
Sammy, don't worry,
I will not steal
your precious line.
No.
You... you gotta
understand...
Hey, Henri.
I've got a letter here
for you-- looks important.
I even had to sign for
it and everything.
Henri, why are you getting
your mail here?
Because I feel this
is my second home,
and sometimes I
get letters postage due.
Oh, mon dieu.
KELLY:
Oh, no.
What is it?
Oh, this is terrible.
Henri's visa
has expired,
and he has to leave the
country in two days.
Help me out with
the "terrible" part.
I am being kicked out,
just because I
am not a citizen
and I have no job
and I have no prospect
for a job
and I have no wish
for a job.
Wait a minute,
they can kick
you out of the
country for that?
No, no, relax, you...
you were born here.
God bless America.
Hey, amen.
Oh, I will miss
this great country.
I have been in love with it
ever since I
got my first glimpse
of that big, beautiful woman
in the harbor.
Ah, yeah,
Lady Liberty.
She told me her
name was Kiki.
Oh, Woody, isn't this
the worst news ever?
Aren't you
gonna miss Henri?
Yeah, it's the worst
news I've ever heard.
Hey, Henri,
sorry to see you go--
don't be a stranger.
Woody Boyd,
why are your hands
behind your back?
Are you
making crossies?
Well, if I was
making crossies,
then I could tell
you that I wasn't,
and I still
wouldn't be lying,
so, Kelly, no, I'm
not making crossies.
Oh, Woody.
Stop it, Kelly, I hate it
when you yell at me.
I don't think you
know how much
Henri loves this country,
and for you
to stand there and act happy
that poor Henri is leaving.
Well,
that's just...
Kelly,
try to control yourself,
this is a public place.
Oh, Kelly, do not
be angry with Woody.
I have not always
played fair with him.
Ah, well,
maybe in another time,
in another place,
we could have
been friends.
Oh, gee, Henri.
Yes, I will miss America,
but you know, Woody,
I will miss you
most of all,
because to me,
you are America.
You are what this
country is all about,
and now I will never
see it or you again.
Adieu.
What kind of a country is it
that kicks a guy
like him out
and lets a guy like me stay?
I'll tell you what country...
U.S.A.! U.S.A.!
ALL:
Hey, Woody,
what you doing?
Well, now that Henri's
going back to Europe...
Yeah?
I can finally be
alone with Kelly.
I can look her
in the eyes
and let all my feelings
pour out spontaneously.
Yeah.
I have them written
down on these cards.
When I ask Kelly
to marry me,
I want to
get it right.
I better put these
in my hiding place.
Well, how come you
have to hide them?
Carla got a hold
of them once.
You should have seen
what she had me saying
on card nine--
I couldn't even pronounce it.
Oh.
Give me a boost, Sam.
Oh, hold on.
Here we go.
All right.
(grunting)
Okay, I got it.
Hey, look,
here's my wallet.
I left this thing up here
six months ago.
See, I never even thought
to look up there.
All right,
I can drive again!
Oh, God.
Ah, that headache's still
bothering you, huh, Fras?
Oh, yes.
Yep.
What do those things
feel like, anyway?
You've never
had a headache, Norm?
I don't think so.
How... how do you get one?
Oh, it's a variety of reasons.
Usually stress or tension.
Hmm?
Job-related anxieties,
day-to-day pressures.
Come again?
It's like, um...
when you eat ice cream too fast.
Oh, I hate that.
Frasier, I've got
Dr. Lee outside.
Lilith, I thought I
made it perfectly clear
that I will not
submit to acupuncture!
Well, then, perhaps you'll
allow the doctor
to practice acupressure,
a simple massage
using the body's
pressure points.
No, I'm not having
some spooky quack
practice the mysteries
of the Orient on my body!
FRASIER:
Well...
you know, Lilith, perhaps I'm
being a bit too Eurocentric.
Right this way, Dr. Lee.
So, I understand you're having
a little problem with headaches?
Oh, yes.
You are going to, um...
warm the oil, aren't you?
Hello, Woody.
Woody, you are so sweet
to see Henri off.
Well, that's just the
way I was raised.
So, Henri, what time
does your plane
leave American
airspace?
Yeah, personally,
I say good riddance.
Yeah?
Yeah, then the charms
of the French
have always
been lost on me.
I mean, when W.W. Three
rolls around,
they'd better not come
to old Cliff Clavin
to pull their fromage out
of the fire, no, siree!
I've got plans.
Yeah, when those
missiles start flying,
I'll be in a
fully stocked-up,
juiced-up Winnebago,
heading at 65 per,
armed to the teeth, right
to the border of Mexico.
Yes, sir.
Those cockroaches
and Cliff Clavin
are gonna do just
fine, thank you.
What a wonderful
civilization you'll build.
Amen.
Gee, Henri
looks so sad.
Oh, he's been
like this all day.
I've tried to snap him
out of it,
but nothing worked.
We even played that game
he invented:
"Shower Rescue."
It is no use.
Oh, Henri,
I wish there was some way
we could fix things
so you could stay.
WOODY:
Well, there's not.
It's too bad-- let's
get going, Henri.
Well, there is one way,
but it's...
it's too much to ask.
Oh, come on,
Henri, tell me.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
It would require
some individual
to make a great
sacrifice.
Well, we'd better get
to the airport.
You only got six hours.
Stop it, Woody.
Henri is trying
to tell me something.
Hey, you know
what they say,
"first luggage on,
first luggage off."
It was nothing.
Uh, just a crazy idea
that I could find some
American citizen
to marry me
and thereby allow me
to remain
in your beautiful country.
What a foolish dreamer
I am.
Okay, we better get Henri
to the airport.
Let's bring
the car around.
Un, deux, trois...
Henri, I just had
a great idea!
Really?
You could marry me!
Oh!
Kelly, how can
you do this?
How can you
marry Henri?
Woody, it's just a little trick
so he can stay in the country.
It's nothing
serious.
Exactly.
We'll get married,
go on our honeymoon,
come back
and get divorced.
We're going
on a honeymoon?!
Oh, goody!
Oh, yes,
we have to.
The immigration people
are very thorough.
Sometimes they even bug
the honeymoon suite
to see if you are faking.
Only you will
not be faking.
Kelly, I'm
telling you,
I don't like this idea.
Really?
No, not one bit.
Sorry, Henri, but I
guess I can't marry you
because my boyfriend
won't let me.
Very well.
I... I understand.
Woody loves you very, very much.
So much that
he is willing
to snatch away
my one chance
to remain
in my adopted homeland.
♪ Oh, beautiful ♪
(voice breaking):
# For spacious skies... #
They really are spacious,
you know!
Look at
him, Woody.
Please let me
marry him!
Please,
please, please!
Forget it.
Kelly,
I-I love you, and I don't want
to see you with another man.
I-I forbid you
to marry Henri.
Well, Mr. Woody Boyd,
the mask has
certainly come off.
If you're so
small-minded that
my marrying another
man makes you take a
rude tone of voice...
...maybe you're not
the man I want to marry
right after
I marry this man.
Come on, Henri,
we're leaving.
WOODY:
Kelly,
if you open that door,
that's it, it's over.
All right,
Kelly,
if you go up those
steps, it is really over.
Kelly, if you keep walking
down Beacon Street
and take the left
on Charles, it's over!
(loud groaning)
What the hell
was that?
You've never heard
your husband groan?
Oh, what a shock!
I'm sure Frasier
is benefiting
from an especially
thorough massage.
FRASIER:
Oh! Oh. Oh! Oh!
Sam, could
I ask you a favor?
Sure.
Would you discreetly pop
your head into your office
and casually determine
what's taking them so long?
I would do it myself,
but Frasier always says
I'm so smothering.
Yeah. No
problem, honey.
(clears throat)
Relax, Lilith.
Everything's fine.
Norm, Cliff,
get in here.
I wonder
what that was all about.
Uh, Paul?
I got 50
bucks says
he passes out before
she gets to 100.
Oh. I got, uh, ten
that'll cover that.
NORM:
All right.
I'm in.
LILITH:
Excuse me.
That's my husband
you're wagering over.
Put me down for 20.
So, what'll
you have, Kelly?
Oh, nothing.
I'm just here
waiting for Woody.
I really have to
make up with him.
I just feel like
my whole life has come
crashing down around my ears.
Uh-huh.
There's a five dollar minimum.
Kelly.
Woody, I'm so sorry.
Well, I'm sorry, too, Kelly.
We should have never
had that terrible fight.
It was all
my fault.
Well, at least
we're back together.
Now let's never fight again,
even if we have
genuine disagreements.
Woody, I
don't think
you and I will
ever disagree
on anything again.
Well, I've got to go.
Where are you going?
To City Hall
to marry Henri,
Mr. Forgetful.
I'll call you
after the wedding.
Love you.
You okay?
Sam, have you ever loved a woman
who was on her way
to marry someone else?
Well, once in the
back of a limo,
but I'm not
proud of it.
What am I supposed to do?
Aren't you tired of letting
that guy walk all over you?
Well, yeah, but...
Well, then,
go stop the
wedding, man.
Give her that speech
you've been practicing.
You're right, Sam.
Out of my way, everybody.
I'm going to bust up
a wedding.
All right, Wood.
And ask Kelly
to marry me instead.
(whooping, applause
& chatter)
There you go...
Give me a boost, Sam.
Yeah, all right,
there you go.
WOODY:
Okay.
Just a little
higher, Sam.
Okay, I got 'em.
Let me down.
Okay. Here we go.
Let me down, Sam.
I did.
What-What are you doing, man?
You holding on there?
No, I must be stuck.
Well...
don't panic here.
We-We'll get you down.
(yelling)
All right.
Uh, let me...
let me climb up there
and see what's going on.
No, no, Sam,
there's no time!
Go break up
that wedding!
Go-Go ahead!
Uh, Carla?
Yeah?
Just help him
out there, will you?
WOODY:
Aah!
Oh! Ow!
I'm telling you, Paul,
you got to get out here!
And so, by the authority
vested in me,
by the Commonwealth
of Massachusetts...
SAM:
Wait, wait,
wait, wait!
I here...
Stop, stop!
Hey, they don't love each other.
This wedding's a sham!
Oh, I-I'm sorry.
It's the wrong wedding.
No, it's the
right wedding.
I don't
love you.
I never have,
and I never will.
Anyhoo...
And so, Kelly and Henri,
by the authority
vested in me by the
Commonwealth of Massachusetts,
I now pronounce you...
Whoa! All right, all right,
all right, hey, whoa.
Sam, what are
you doing here?
I-I... Well, I'm here,
because there's a certain guy
who loves you
very much, honey,
a lot more
than Henri ever could,
and someone I think
that you have overlooked.
Well, sure, Sam,
there's always been a
spark between you and me.
It's understandable, honey.
Just pre-wedding jitters.
It happens
to everybody.
Now, you ready
to go on?
I think so.
Very well, then.
Friends, we are gathered
here today
to...
Stop this wedding!
She doesn't love him!
It's a disgrace!
Aw, now, come on!
He's right.
They're all right.
Let's face it--
it won't work,
and the whole
world knows it!
(crying)
Sorry.
So, you see, Kelly,
when I said
that someone was
in love with you,
see, I wasn't referring to me.
Woody is the person
I'm talking about.
You see, he's the guy
who loves you.
Oh, I get it.
Yeah.
I love him, too, Sam.
Oh, there you go.
Thanks, Sam.
Well, Henri,
you ready
to marry me?
Friends, we are gathered here
today to join this man...
Would the bride and groom
please turn around?!
All right, stop
this wedding!
Woody!
Kelly, you can't go
through with this.
I can't let you
marry Henri.
Woody, we've been through this
a million times.
It's just so Henri
won't get deported.
Oops!
You're wrong, Kelly.
He's using you.
He-He wrote that
letter himself.
He's not going
to be deported.
He-He's just trying to
steal you away from me.
How did you
figure that out?
You mean, I'm right?
Wow! Score one
for the Indiana school system.
HENRI:
I am sorry, Kelly.
I was trying
to take you away from Woody
and have my way with you
and divorce you and take
half your money.
Can you ever forgive me?
Oh, I can't stay mad at you,
you silly.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait a second
here, wait a second.
You telling me this
whole thing was just
so you could steal
somebody's girl
away from him?
Yes.
Oh, man, that's
beautiful.
That's beautiful.
Ah, oh, that's
great, man.
Let me ask
you something
here, you know.
When you're in the middle
of a trick like this,
now is there just
one part of you
that-that feels a
little bit guilty?
Oh!
(both laughing)
I thought
you'd like that.
You know, I have
to tell you, man,
it's nice to be
around somebody
who finally gets
this kind of stuff.
I hope you're not upset
with me, Woody.
Heck, no, Kelly.
In fact, I got something
I want to say to you.
How do you pronounce this?
Oh, darn that Carla.
All right, well, I'll
just have to wing it.
Kelly,
uh...
We've been going out
for a lot of years now,
and I love you,
and you love me, and
I want to spend the
rest of my life with you.
What I'm trying
to say is...
will you marry me?
Of course I'll marry you, Woody.
Oh, Kelly, you've made this
the happiest day of my life!
Mine, too.
I know I forgave Henri
and everything,
but I'm still
a little miffed at him.
I can't believe anybody would
pull such a dirty trick
just to get a girl.
MAN:
So two complete
strangers break in
and tell us not
to get married!
Why should we care?
Honey, c-could we
at least go steady?
MAN #2:
It happened
to you, too?
MAN #3:
Yeah, twice.
We've got to get locks
for those doors.
Uh, so you see,
our visas have just expired,
and, uh, we are going
to be deported.
Oui.