Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
(phone rings)
Cheers.
Uh, hang on a second,
I'll check.
Yeah, the refrigerator's
running.
Thank you for asking.
What?
(chuckles)
How could it possibly get away?
No, a refrigerator doesn't have
the power of movement.
Well, yeah, sure, I get it,
but see,
running-- the way you're using
it-- c-can only mean working.
See, it's a--
it's what we call a homonym.
I'm sorry, too.
Boy, Mr. Peterson,
some people.
(whistles)
Well, you tried to
explain the joke.
That's the problem.
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Hey, uh, Dr. Crane,
after you're done with
that paper, can I have it?
Well, actually, I planned
on saving it, Woody.
See, there's an article here
on the ins and out
of buying diamonds
and I was thinking
of buying Lilith a brooch.
Oh, okay, uh... see, I was
wanting to clip the coupons
'cause I'm trying to make
it to my next paycheck,
but, uh, I don't want
to cut up your article
on jewels
and diamonds.
Here's the paper,
Woody.
You know, Lilith and I
are actually making
some economic concessions
as well.
Well, for instance, I decided
not to buy that new BMW.
Really?
That's right.
So, uh,
what are the coupons for?
Food.
You know what?
I'm going to stop talking now.
Top of the morning to you.
So, uh, how do you like
my outfit there, Norm?
Cliff,
you're my friend.
I haven't judged you in the past
and I'm not going to start now.
Hey, uh, listen
up, everybody.
I've got an announcement
to make here.
Yours truly has been selected
by the USPS for a reenactment
of the first mail delivery down
the venerable Boston Post Road.
Yeah, I'm going to be,
uh, riding a horse
on the last leg
from Hingham to the Central P.O.
(chuckling):
Yeah, that's why I'm dressed
this way.
What way?
Oh, you know, this,
this crazy looking outfit.
Boy, are you
splitting hairs today.
Cliffie, Cliff, you
can't ride a horse.
You're afraid
of horses.
How do you know?
I know you're afraid
of that little carousel
in front of
the market.
That was
a safety concern, Norm.
Is that why you
were screaming,
"Stop, stop, we're
all going to die"?
I was concerned
about the kids, Norm.
Is that so wrong?
Boy, Cliff, I am so jealous.
I used to love horses.
You know,
when I was a little girl,
every weekend
I would ride my pony,
an-an-and I would feed my pony
sugar cubes
and little bits of chocolate
and, and Snickers.
They really like that.
And sometimes I would give
my pony some Snickers,
and then I would eat
some Snickers.
And then other times
I would eat all the sugar cubes
and the chocolate
and the Snickers
before I ever got
to the stable.
And then one time
my riding instructor told me
I couldn't ride my pony anymore.
Why, Miss Howe?
Well, he said that I
had... outgrown it.
I don't want to talk
about this anymore.
CLIFF:
Well, I hope you'll all,
uh, tune in tonight.
Uh, the, uh, local news
is going to show
my triumphant ride
to the post office.
(chuckling):
Yeah, it's a big moment
for me.
Yeah, it's, it's a high point
of my career.
No, it's a high point
of my entire life.
Hey, why's Cliffie dressed
like that?
I forget.
(sing-songy):
Sa-am.
What are you doing
down here, Hill?
Hair Club For
Men meeting?
Oh, I didn't see you
down there, Miss Tortelli.
Although frankly you do...
(sniffs)
...announce your presence.
So, have you
decided what color
you're going to dye
your head for Easter?
Why don't you just scuttle
under the office door
and get Sam?
Sam, Hill's here!
Don't tell me.
Pizza for lunch?
Hi, John.
What's up?
Sa-am, we have a problem.
You know,
I got to be honest
with you, John.
The way you pronounce
my name really bugs me.
How would you like me
to pronounce it?
Sam, just Sam.
You try it.
Sa-am...
All right,
John, uh...
what would you say if you were
going to order a ham sandwich?
I don't eat ha-am.
Never mind.
What, what
do you want?
My busboy informs me
that the Dumpsters are full.
Our Dumpsters
are full.
What's the
big problem?
Aha!
They are not our Dumpsters.
They are my Dumpsters.
If that's confusing,
perhaps I'll have
a likeness of your face
painted on the Dumpster with
a bold line drawn through it.
In fact, I'll do that anyway...
just for a giggle.
Perhaps
I'll have buttons made up.
I'll make it a whole thing.
Hey, Hill, you can't order us
around like that.
Sammy can do anything he wants
with his trash.
Yes, I see today he's
dressed it up in an apron.
I guess you know all about
dressing up, huh, Hill?
Sam, if any more
of your refuse
is deposited in my Dumpsters,
I'll have them emptied
in the center
of this bar,
and if it happens
again,
I'll do something
your customers will notice.
Can you believe that guy?
Him and his niggling
little nit-picking details.
I mean, who cares
if I stick stuff
in his Dumpster?
Actually,
Sammy,
you know, Dumpsters
are kind of expensive
to maintain and empty.
He's been kind of generous to
let you use them for so long.
After all, the guy's
running a business.
Good point, Norm, good point.
Speaking of business,
w-w-what do you think
we ought to do about, uh,
your bar tab here, hmm?
We could throw it
in our Dumpsters.
Hey, Miss Howe, Mr. Hill put
a lock on the Dumpster.
What should I do with this?
Well, just set it
down someplace.
All right.
Cliffie, you want to, uh, pass
me the sports page, please?
Mr. Peterson,
that's just a bag of garbage
you're talking to.
Come here, Woody.
Maybe if we all cut
Cliff a little bit
of slack, he wouldn't be
such a "bag of garbage,"
as you put it, okay?
Do you believe
that guy?
He stuck a padlock
on our Dumpsters.
You know, just once, just once
I would like to do something
to really stick it to him.
Sammy, forget
about it.
You'll never
beat that guy.
Hmm, you're right.
Who am I kidding?
I'm no match
for that guy.
He's too evil.
What am I thinking? Wha...?!
All this time,
there's somebody in this bar
who's so mean, so nasty,
so full of hate
that they could take on Hill
in one second.
Well, I don't know, Sam,
I'm kind of busy right now.
What about Carla?
She can be pretty mean.
Good idea, Woody, good idea.
Carla, come here,
I got a job for you.
Yeah, what do you want me to do?
I want you to
get even for me.
I want you to take all your
meanness, all your nastiness,
and unleash
it on that...
knobby-headed weasel
John Allen Hill.
You want
I should make him cry?
Yeah.
That's perfect.
Yeah, make the
little man cry.
Yeah!
Consider it done.
Yeah, right, now, how are you
going to make him cry?
You don't think
I can make somebody cry?
No, actually, I don't.
Maybe you're right.
Uh, say, Rebecca.
Mm-hmm?
When you were
a little girl, why did you
stop riding that pony?
Was it because
you got too fat?
Just too damned fat?
So damned fat you broke
the back of a horse?
What's the matter, Becks?
Your eyes seem a little shiny.
(quavering): It's just an
allergy or something.
(sobbing):
If anybody needs me,
I'll be in my office.
You know, I really like
Cheetos, but, uh...
Orange fingers?
I hate that, too.
At home I use a great big spoon.
I'll try that.
What's this?
Oh, that's a flier
that Mr. Clavin wanted me
to pass around to the customers.
Well, why didn't you?
Because it's a flier
that Mr. Clavin wanted me
to pass around to the customers.
We've had trouble
in that area before.
"Tune in tonight
"to catch letter carrier
Cliff Clavin recreate
"the historic first
mail delivery
on the Boston
Post Road."
(chuckles)
"This is a proud moment
for Cliff Clavin
and every American."
Hey, it's right now.
Let's tune in.
Oh, this is a great
Barnaby Jones, though.
This is the one where he goes
undercover as a swinger
to solve a jewel heist.
Well, we'll, uh,
flip back and forth.
All right.
ANNOUNCER:
The crowd here at the
Central Post Office is waiting
for letter carrier
Clifford Clavin,
who we understand
is an award-winning equestrian.
Mr. Clavin seems
to be running late
and his whereabouts
are currently unknown.
In other news...
Ooh, I hope everything's okay
with Cliffie.
So, uh, Barnaby's a swinger?
Ha, wait till
you see him. He wears
hip-huggers, gold
chains, platform shoes.
(phone ringing)
Cheers.
Oh, yeah, hang on,
just a second.
Hey, Mr. Peterson,
it's Mr. Clavin.
Cliffie, where are you?
I don't know, Norm,
somewhere in the combat zone.
Naked! Naked! Naked!
Hey, Norm, you got
to come and get me.
This horse has got
a mind of its own.
(horn honks, horse neighs)
Whoa!
(tires screech)
Man... Cliffie's in trouble.
I better go look for him.
Shoot, they never
rerun this episode.
I don't think I've seen
the ending of this one.
The jewels are
in the dog's collar.
Oh. Thank you, Phil.
Gee, Carla, you were up there
with Hill
a long time. What happened?
I don't want to
talk about it.
Hey, what did you
say to him?
Just shut up and get
out of my way, you stupid,
dirt-eating farm boy!
Ouch! I'd hate to be
on the receiving end of that.
(sighs)
What is going on?
In this bar?
I don't ask.
(grunts)
Now, apparently you're upset
over something.
(grunts)
Or not, I don't know
you that well.
Carla, now just, just relax
and try to breathe.
Just breathe.
(deep breaths)
All right, now is it
out of your system?
All right,
now talk to us.
(screams)
No, Carla!
Carla!
(grunting)
Carla, what has
gotten into you?
First of all,
you have to promise
to never repeat this to anybody.
I swear.
That goes without saying.
Okay. I just did a really,
really, really bad thing.
When I was up there with Hill,
I just kind
of lost control.
(gasps):
You didn't break something
really expensive, did you?
Oh, no, worse than that.
Did you hurt him?
Worse.
Oh, no, did he have
a heart attack?
No, worse.
Oh, he's dead?!
Oh, you guys!
You don't get it!
I didn't kill him.
I slept with him.
Yikes.
You had sex with Hill?
John Allen Hill?
Upstairs John Allen Hill?
It was so crazy.
I marched into his office
and I started calling him
bald and wrinkled.
And he started calling
me short and ugly.
And before I knew it,
our clothes were off
and we were
insulting each other
against the filing cabinet.
But Carla, I mean he is,
he's a...
You know what I call him?
The Bullet.
Carla, I, I believe
I understand what happened.
You two have a classic
attraction/repulsion
relationship.
It's really a fairly common
phenomenon.
People who are constantly
at odds with one another
very often have rivers
of passion raging between them
until one day
the banks overflow
in a torrent of unthinking,
unreasonable emotion.
Plus the guy's practically
a contortionist.
I can't believe I did this.
I betrayed Sam.
I went up there
to take on his worst enemy,
and I ended up having
a nooner with him.
Oh, I just hope Sammy
doesn't find out about this.
Oh, Carla,
you're going
to have to face
Sam sooner or later.
He's bound to find out.
Yeah, Lilith's right.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Okay. Well, I'll just
catch Sam tonight
when nobody else is around
and I'll tell him the truth.
I'll tell him that what happened
with Hill was a one-time thing
and it'll never happen again.
Unless...
I accidentally
catch a glimpse of those
wiry, bantam legs of his.
Evening, everybody.
ALL:
Norm!
Hey, Mr. P.
How goes the search
for Mr. Clavin?
Not as well as the search
for Mr. Doughnut.
I found him every
couple of blocks.
(sighs)
Poor Mr. Clavin.
Who knows what
happened to him.
I'm kind of worried
about him, really.
Why don't you give me the phone?
I'll check the hospitals
or something, shouldn't I?
Uh, Mass General?
Hey, Normie, I got dish.
I'll call you back.
It's about Carla
and that Hill upstairs.
Yeah? Spill it. What?
(whispers)
Eeww!
Frasier, Frasier,
did you hear about
Carla and Hill?
Did I hear?
Who do you think told Paul?
Wow, Carla and Hill.
I saw it coming.
You didn't have
to be Kreskin.
Frasier, I cannot believe
that you revealed
what is essentially
a professional confidence.
Sweetheart,
did she pay you a dime?
No.
Then why are we having
this discussion?
What's everybody talking about?
Woody, when, uh,
Carla went upstairs
to, to see Hill today,
she, uh...
well, they...
did the deed,
you know what I mean?
I'm not following
you, Dr. Crane.
Carla and Hill,
they rocked
each other's world.
They thumped.
What?
They had sex.
Carla and Hill had sex.
What?
Come on, Sam.
Even I got it that time.
Carla?
Wh...
Are you all happy now?
Your gossiping
and rumor-mongering
is resulting
in a possible rift
between Carla and Sam.
Rather than allow her
the time and space
to open up to Sam
in her own good time,
you all have been behaving
like a gaggle of fishwives.
Well, hey, you
blabbed first, girl.
Sammy, I don't know
what to tell you.
I guess... all the insults
and the venom,
and the blood hatred just
kind of turned us on.
It's the old story.
Guess so.
Oh, Sammy, I let you down.
I slept with the enemy.
Please forgive me.
Please don't be angry.
No, I'm not angry.
It's just... well, the
way I see it, uh...
you let down the whole team.
It's like, you know,
bottom of the ninth,
one out, runner on first,
you're up at bat.
Coach tells you to bunt.
Team expects you to bunt,
the runner on first
expects you to bunt,
fans expect you to bunt.
But instead of bunting...
you sleep with John Allen Hill!
No! No!
Hey!
Take it easy!
You're supposed to forgive me.
How can I forgive you?!
You slept with that
evil, little dwarf!
Is it my fault the guy
is such a turn-on?
Oh, stop-- oh, yuck,
yuck! Oh, God!
Stop it! Stop!
I have never once
said anything
about anyone you have
ever slept with!
Oh, right!
What about Diane?!
Every morning you
threatened to stick
a hand grenade in her
mouth and pull the pin!
You hated her!
I disapproved of her.
Oh, come on, Carla,
you hated her!
You hate everyone!
That's not fair!
Oh, right!
I'm sorry, I forgot.
You don't hate
John Allen Hill!
That's it!
That's it, thanks a lot
for your forgiveness!
I'm out of here!
(groaning)
Oh, dear.
(faucet running)
Sam.
What, Woody?!
You're angry, aren't you?
Yeah! I am!
You're hurt.
You're down.
You're confused, aren't you?
Yeah. Yeah, I am.
Yeah. I was, too,
the first time
I made this mistake.
Just remember,
the men's room
is the second door
on the left.
Hey, everybody.
PAUL:
Hey, Cliffie, you're back.
You deliver that
letter all right?
Yeah, it took a little doing.
But I, uh, finally delivered it.
It was three hours late.
You know, but it turns
out, that the, uh,
original letter was
three weeks late, so, uh,
I was able to shave
a little time off.
Where's Norm, Woods?
He's out looking for you.
Oh, boy.
(TV switches on)
All right, I guess I'd
better go find him.
(channels switching)
Hey, look, it's
that Cannon episode
where he dresses up as
a pimp to save the runaway.
Norm's a big boy.
He can take care
of himself.
Naked! Naked! Naked!
Excuse me, I'm, uh,
looking for a guy
wearing a funny costume,
riding a horse.
Try the place two doors down.
Okay.
Freak.
Naked! Naked! Naked!
(doorbell rings)
CARLA:
Coming.
Who is it?
Sam.
Hey.
How're you doing?
Fine, and you?
Fine.
So, uh, where are the kids?
How should I know?
It's only 1:30.
I, uh... I came
to apologize.
I blew up.
You know, you've got to know
I didn't mean any
of that stuff.
It's just...
ah, that Hill guy, man.
Something about him just
makes me act crazy.
Nah, forget it.
I forgive you.
I know you didn't
mean that stuff.
Oh, honey...
I just hope you can forgive me.
Oh, of course I can.
Come on, you don't think
I'd let that stuff
get in between us, do you?
You're my best friend.
Oh, Sammy, you're
my best friend, too.
Oh, I know what it's like.
It's probably just...
one of those things, right?
Exactly, it was just one
of those things.
Yeah.
I've been thinking
about this.
I'll tell you what
I'm going to do.
Tomorrow morning,
I'm going to go up,
I'm gonna talk to Hill
calmly, you know,
and ask him nicely, maybe I
could use the Dumpster
until I can buy
one for myself.
I swear to God I'll do it
bright and early.
Well, not too early, Sam.
I have a feeling I may
be in a little late.
Okay, so it was just
two of those things.