Goodnight, Dan.
Be careful going home now.
Boy, that guy
sure chewed your ear off, Coach.
Yeah, but what a nice guy.
You know something?
That's the first person l ever met
that was on the Titanic.
- He survived the Titanic?
- l forgot to ask.
l would've loved to hear that story.
l figured you'd heard it. Big boat,
hit an iceberg. Bang! Down it went.
Any interesting stories, call me.
lt's one of the joys of bartending.
You want interesting?
Forget the Titanic. Come here.
Glen, tell him
what you told me earlier. Go ahead.
l know all the words
to the Bonanza theme song.
Go ahead. Let him hear it.
We got a right
To pick a little fight, Bonanza!
lf anyone fights any one of us
He's gotta fight with me
We're not a one
To settle up and run, Bonanza!
Any one of us starts a little fight
Knows he can trust on me
One for four, four for one,
This we guarantee
One for four, four for one...
- Howdy, sports fans.
- Norm!
- What'll it be, Norm?
- Fame, fortune, fast women.
Yeah? How about a beer?
Even better.
How's the search for work, Norm?
Good news, everybody.
l'm no longer looking for a job.
l'm now begging for one.
- l don't believe this.
- What now?
That was my mother. She just flew
into town and she's coming here.
No kidding.
We finally get to meet her.
- This is very strange.
- That you have a mother?
No.
That you have a mother
that wants to see you?
No. That she's coming over here.
l didn't think Mommy'd be caught dead
in a place like this.
What are we, too grungy or something?
Yeah, inside an hour ago,
l'm in the tub.
You're taking this too personally.
You shouldn't.
- lt's just Mommy doesn't like bars.
- Bars can be very sad places.
Some people
spend their whole lives in a bar.
Just yesterday, some guy sat
right here next to me for 1 1 hours.
- What kind of a life is that?
- Pitiful.
The sad thing is,
he'll be sitting in a bar right now,
drinking a beer,
going on and on about nothing.
Diane, if your mom is anything
like you, everyone will love her.
She's nothing like l am.
She's very eccentric
and a little hard to take at times.
Yeah, worlds apart.
Diane, if your mother's so rich,
how come you're not?
l didn't want to go through life
being handed money on a silver tray.
For you.
Thank you.
There she is. My little baby.
Mommy.
Hello, darling.
They didn't get near each other.
How can anyone miss Diane's mouth?
So, this is a bar.
Yes. This is where l work.
Let me introduce you.
Mother, this is Sam,
who wouldn't say anything to
embarrass me, so wisely says nothing.
How do you do?
Hi.
This is Carla Tortelli. She says even
less than Sam and she's very busy.
Down there we have Norman
and his friend Cliff.
They lost their tongues in the war.
Ernie Pantusso.
You can call him Coach.
- Or use my other nickname, Red.
- Red?
As a player,
his team-mates called him Red.
Because your hair was red?
No, ma'am. Because l read a book.
He's very sweet though. Very sweet.
lt's nice to finally meet you,
Mrs Chambers.
lt's nice to meet you, Sam.
Diane's told me about you.
You're almost as handsome
as she says you think you are.
There's a compliment
in there someplace.
lt's very nice of you
to come all this way.
l thought so, too,
but you know what tomorrow is?
- No. What?
- Your wedding day. Congratulations.
My what?
lf you're not married
before tomorrow,
l lose my share
of your father's estate.
My God! Why?
Darling, when he died,
you were still a little gawky girl,
with your nose in a book
and a terrible facial tic.
Your father was worried
that you would never find a mate,
and that you would have
a lonely life.
So he made me promise
that l would have you married
ten years after the day he died.
He even put it in his will.
So, if you're still single,
l'm cut off.
Why have you waited to tell me?
Father's been dead ten years.
You know how time flies
when you're having...
- Grief.
So, if l'm not married by tomorrow,
you're broke?
Put your mind at ease.
l'll never be broke.
l'll either be rich or dead.
The choice is yours.
You're seriously asking me
to get married?
My attorneys have assured me
that it need be in name only,
just for a few days.
There's no other way.
This is the craziest thing
Father ever did.
Not even close, dear.
Excuse me, madam.
l dropped the bags off at the hotel.
- Thank you.
- Nice to see you, Boggs.
l'd be honoured
if you'd consent to be my wife.
l said ''in a pinch'', Boggs.
- Now wait over there.
- Yes, madam.
Darling, think hard.
There's so little time.
Don't you know anyone who'd be
willing to marry you for a few days?
Well, l'm afraid there's no one
l'm steadily dating at the moment.
Excuse me,...
..rich lady.
l couldn't help overhearing
your problems.
Your daughter has a hot thing
for the bartender.
l do not!
She likes Red?
He's dumb enough to be your father.
Not him. Sam.
l care nothing. l feel nothing.
Sam who?
Come off it. We've all noticed
how you two go around,
looking at each other
like lovesick cows. Admit it.
He's got you
steaming under the silks.
- This happens to be my mother.
- That's why l'm being delicate.
Diane, is this true?
How about the two of you?
l'd rather marry Boggs.
l could make you very happy.
Sorry, Boggs.
Just a figure of speech.
Thank you, miss.
Diane, he's not a bad-looking fellow.
His cologne's an affront to society
but what harm would it do to ask?
Mother, no.
Darling, please.
l wish l was as strong as you are,
but l'm not.
Without money,
l don't think l can make it.
Alright, l'll ask him. Sam?
- What?
- May l speak with you a moment?
- l might as well come to the point.
- That'd be nice.
Would you be willing to marry me?
Boy, this cologne
must be doing its stuff.
You see, my very eccentric father
put a very strange clause
into his will.
Providing that if l'm not married
by tomorrow,
my mother will become destitute.
So, if we could get married, just
long enough to satisfy the attorneys,
it would really help her out
and l would consider it a favour.
l'd consider it a joke.
Marriage and me do not mix.
No, it's not marriage.
lt's a business arrangement.
Just for a couple of days
and then we'll get divorced.
Listen, l've been married before.
You haven't.
Take my word,
marriage changes people.
No woman in the world can hear those
words and not start believing it.
That's a very sexist thing to say.
No, it's not sexist
because no man can resist it either.
Why, Sam,
that's a very romantic thing to say.
The difference is, with men,
they get over it in an hour.
With women, it goes on for years.
lf you're worried about me,
l'm only doing this for my mother.
Yeah, right.
l promise you that l will not feel
any emotions toward you.
l learned a long time ago never to
trust anybody wearing a wedding gown,
especially a woman.
Forget l asked.
- l'm sorry.
- Never mind.
l'm sorry, Mommy. He said no.
Oh, dear.
Hell.
- OK, Diane.
- OK what?
OK, we'll... get married.
- Really?
- Yeah. You bet.
Mr Malone, how wonderful.
You're both wonderful.
Thank you very much.
l'm still rich. l'll get the Justice.
Come along, Boggs.
- Thanks for changing your mind.
- You're welcome. l wanted to help.
- What you're doing is very noble.
- Thank you.
Where do you want to go
on our honeymoon?
l should've known.
As usual, Mr Malone
has his brains caught in his zipper.
ls this the first wedding
in Cheers?
No, Frankie Flaherty
got married in this bar.
He met Janet in that corner, proposed
to her here, right in front of me,
they married there,
had their first fight by the piano,
she caught him in the poolroom with
a woman, shot him dead in the alley.
That's an incredible story.
- Want to know where he's buried?
- Where?
He ain't. He's cremated.
- Thank God!
- Here's his ashes.
- We've got the licence.
- What took you so long?
While l was there, l paid my
water bill and registered my bicycle.
Know what they ask
for a bicycle licence?
- Sam, shut up.
- Sorry, dear.
l'd like to introduce you
to Mr Harrison Fiedler,
Justice of the Peace,
who will perform the ceremony.
- Hi, Just.
- We need witnesses.
Yep. Every accident
needs some witnesses.
Sammy, please, l'd be proud
to be your best man.
l'm honoured. Thank you.
The day Diane walked in,
l knew you'd get together.
Coach, this is just temporary.
l knew that, too.
How come you never got married?
Well, Norm, Coach, it's unfair to ask
a woman to be the wife of a mailman.
Watching him get up every morning,
strapping on that mailbag,
hitting those mean streets, never
knowing if he's coming back or not.
Right. Somewhere out there
is a beagle with your name on it.
Excuse me. l think we should begin.
Are you ready, Mr Fiedler?
l'm ready. May l have the licence?
The groom's name is Schwinn?
That's my bicycle licence.
Excuse me.
Diane, do you think
we could we lose the aprons?
The aprons. Carla, the apron.
Gee, l didn't know
it was going to be this formal.
- Are you OK?
- Fine.
Just a business arrangement.
l do appreciate it for Mommy's sake.
You're welcome.
Just remember, no emotions.
lf l feel anything romantic,
l will run screaming from the room.
And l will clear a path for you.
Would the bride and groom
come forward, please?
We are gathered
in the presence of these witnesses
for the purpose
of uniting in matrimony
Diane Chambers and Sam Malone.
The contract of marriage
is most solemn
and not to be entered into lightly,
but thoughtfully and seriously
and with a deep realisation
of its obligations
and responsibilities.
Any two people
who have come to this point
clearly feel the love and joy
that they find in one another
can surmount whatever obstacles
lie in their path.
Sam, do you take...?
Do you mind?
What?
Never mind. l'm sorry, please go on.
- Sam, do you take this woman...
- What did l do?
l saw the leer.
- Leer? Come on, Diane.
- Please.
Please go on.
Sam, do you take this woman
to be your lawful...?
She's a customer in my bar.
l smiled, that's all. Go on.
She's a woman.
Well, l'll be darned, so she is.
To have and to hold
from this time forward...
- lt was just a look.
- Just a look?
This is just a look.
This is what you did.
Can we get on with the ceremony?
- To have and to hold...
- Wait a minute.
What's the big deal? You're beginning
to sound like my wife.
Excuse me. We are getting married.
l may not be asking for 50 years
of love, honour and obey,
but it would be nice if, during
the ceremony, you didn't drool.
You really are demanding.
l don't understand why you're trying
to make me so crazy.
l don't understand
why you chose now
to demonstrate your lack of class.
l'm the one doing you the favour.
- Don't do me any favours.
- Children, please.
Butt out, Mom. This is
the stupidest thing l ever did.
Stupidest thing? There is
no stupidest thing you ever did.
Everything you do is equally stupid.
lncluding not throwing you out
when l saw your stupid face!
- Sam, do you have the ring?
- Shut up!
That's it. We're making a mockery
of marriage and it's all my fault.
There'll be no wedding here today.
Fine.
- l hate your guts and l always will.
- That goes double for me.
l understand
they wrote their own vows.
You know, 30 minutes ago,
l was a wealthy woman.
- Now l can't pay for these drinks.
- Don't worry. The drinks are on me.
l don't want your charity
and l don't want your pity,
but l will take your money.
Well, if it hadn't been
for dear old Dad
and his strange clause in the will,
you would never
have been in this predicament.
You mustn't think ill of your father.
He was concerned. He loved you
very much. You know that, don't you?
- Yes, l guess l do.
- ln a strange way, he loved me, too.
Unfortunately,
he loved a good joke more.
Spencer, wherever you are tonight,
l hope you're frying.
You two are still here?
We'll lock up.
How are you getting home?
How are we getting home, Mommy?
Boggs is waiting outside to drive us.
l'm sorry about this afternoon.
l'm sorry, too.
l told you,
weddings do weird things to me.
l must admit,
l got a little swept away myself.
l think l owe you an apology, too,
Mrs Chambers. l'm sorry.
What l asked you to do was unfair.
Are you alright?
Actually, l...
l'm really quite afraid.
Afraid of what, Mommy?
l'm afraid of being poor.
l was poor before l met your father,
and it took me years to really forget
how being poor felt.
Excuse me, madam.
Could l have a word?
- What is it, Boggs?
- l heard of your tragedy.
l'd be honoured
if you'd consent to be my wife.
- lt's too late for that.
- No. l meant you, madam.
Why, Boggs, have you lost your mind?
l mean, l've only accepted
your familiarity over the years
because l was afraid
of class warfare.
l am aware of that.
However, in view of the developments
in the last half an hour,
our stations have, shall we say,
grown a little closer.
Now, then, Boggs...
Madam, it so happens,
l have a considerable
sum of money stashed away.
Really?
- Where did you get it, Boggs?
- From you and yours, madam.
l've been embezzling from your family
for close to a quarter of a century.
Why, Boggs, how clever of you.
Exactly how much
money do you have?
As l recall my Emily Post,
a lady does not ask her chauffeur how
much he stole from her dead husband.
Let us just say,
l am very comfortable.
Shall we go to dinner
and talk about the future?
Bon appétit.
You know, Boggs, l must confess,
l've always found the back of
your head enormously attractive.
l sensed it, madam.
Would you do me a favour, madam?
- What's that?
- Would you drive?
Kinky.
(ENGLlSH)