Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
CLIFF:
Hey, Doc.
What's with the getup?
As of this day,
I am changing my ways.
You know, not too long ago,
I used to be a healthy,
robust individual.
Then I set foot in this bar.
Started sitting around for hours
when I should have been jogging.
Started to gorge myself
on snacks and sweets
instead of health food.
Well, now that I'm
back on the road
to better health, I'm
taking you with me.
What, uh... what
do you mean, Doc?
Well, I've
signed us up
for a physical
fitness program.
Geez, I don't
know, Doc.
Sounds like an awful,
awful lot of work.
Yeah, I already took
into account
your legendary sloth,
and to make it
easier for you,
I've hired a trainer
to come here in person
to help you exercise.
We tried that once.
What, you had
a trained athlete
who came here and...
and helped you
work out?
Yeah.
Well, what happened?
Uh, hey, I don't
know, ask him.
Uh, Paul?
Any you guys read
Andy Capp today?
(laughing)
(coughing)
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Okay, guys, hurry up
and get your lunch orders in.
Dip 'n Fry closes in 20 minutes.
Yeah, if we don't hurry,
they'll change the grease.
So, I... I can't seem
to make up my mind here.
Cliffie, every day you
stare at that damn menu,
and every day you
order the wing dings.
Well, maybe I
would like
something different
today, Norm.
Yeah, okay.
Sammy, I'm gonna
have the, uh,
baked potato, please,
with, uh, sour cream
and butter,
and, um, put some cheddar
on there, please.
Oh, and, uh, some jack cheese.
Bacon bits?
No, no, I'm watching
my cholesterol.
Cliffie?
I'll have the, uh...
wing dings.
(gasps)
Oh...
Isn't that precious?
I can hardly wait
till Sam and I
have our baby.
Carla, do you
think I'm
gonna make a
good mother?
Nope.
What do you mean?
You asked me a question,
I gave you an answer.
Yeah, but
I'm serious.
Well, I'm sorry,
I'm just being honest.
No, you're not
being honest.
You're being mean.
Sometimes you
get a two-fer.
So you are saying
that you don't think
that I can take
care of a baby?
You kidding?
I don't think you
could take care
of an egg.
Oh, come on.
No, really,
really.
I'll bet you five bucks
you can't take care
of this egg
until Friday night
at closing time.
Five bucks?
Yeah.
You're on--
thanks.
(splatters)
Okay, I was
practicing.
Now, start!
Norm, are you busy?
Oh, good one.
(giggles)
Thanks, I thought
of it last night
in the shower.
(laughs)
Norm?
Yeah.
Frasier and I were wondering
if you would paint
our living room today.
Today?
What's the rush?
Well, yesterday,
little Frederick
was playing fireman...
Mm-hmm.
...with the mustard
and ketchup squeeze bottles
and, uh, he put out
our living room wall.
He is a dickens.
I found it difficult to
keep a straight face.
Well, I'm really
kind of taking this week off.
From what?
From Vera--
she's visiting her mother.
Ooh, nothing serious,
I hope.
No, no, no, no,
they're just changing that tire
that hangs from her ceiling.
(laughing)
I can take care of you guys.
I can use the work.
Let's go check it out.
Tell you what, I...
I think I can swing
the whole thing today
for, uh...
what do you say, $400?
Uh, that's a little pricey,
isn't it?
Uh, right, well,
say $200 and, uh,
you supply the food
and the beer?
$400, it is.
Say, Norm, what kind
of roller is that?
I don't know, Fras.
They have, uh, different
kinds of rollers?
Uh...
yeah, probably do.
Suppose, uh,
some of them
are better than
the others?
Uh, yeah, yeah,
I suppose.
This one's okay, though,
Fras, trust me.
Oh, oh, yeah, no.
I was just wondering
about rollers.
Don't you have anything to do,
you know, like work or anything?
No, no, don't have
to work today.
And, Lilith doesn't
let me watch TV
during the
daytime, so...
Say, is... can I help
you with anything?
I mean, stir the
paint, maybe?
No, uh, they, uh...
they shook it up
over at the, uh,
paint store.
Yeah, right, those,
uh, those machines
that, yeah, shake
the paint, yeah.
Yeah.
Say, you know,
that's...
I wonder who invented
that-- that's...
There's a guy that really made
a worthwhile contribution,
you know?
I mean,
if he was a guy.
I mean, he could have been
a woman, I guess.
Isn't that interesting?
Oh, why would I assume
just right off
that that would be a man?
Frasier, I'm starting
to miss Cliff.
Right, right,
right.
How's Norm doing?
Oh, fine, I guess.
(awkward laughter):
Oh, say,
you know, Norm, the...
the guy on This Old House
says that you
should apply paint
with, uh, vertical strokes.
Yeah,
what's This Old House?
Well, it's a show on PBS.
What's PBS?
Tell me you didn't see that
coming a mile away.
Well, you know, I...
I was just
trying to point out that, uh,
it seemed a little silly
for a... a television show
to waste all that, uh, air time,
um, explaining to
paint a certain way
when you can just slap it on
willy-nilly.
Look, I'd love
to stay here all day
and defend myself,
but I can't reach
that top spot
so I'm gonna go home
and get my big ladder.
Well, you could
reach it
from the top
of the ladder.
Oh, no, no, you see
that, uh,
sticker on the ladder there?
You're not supposed to go
above that step.
Oh, come on, you're
just being a big baby.
Look, you're almost done,
and, uh,
you know, you don't want it
to dry two different colors.
Oh, don't tell me-- the
guy from This Old House?
Well, look, if he
wasn't a professional,
he wouldn't be the guy
from This Old House,
he'd just be some guy,
all right?
Now, come on,
get up there.
No, what, I'm...
I'm gonna get hurt,
fall down? No way!
Oh, all right, you big baby,
I'll do it myself.
Frasier, come on now.
Hand me that roller.
Frasier, relax,
will you?
Whoa!
Aah!
Okay, so maybe it is
a little hazardous.
Norm, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
All I can say is I
am so, so sorry.
What else can I say?
I know something you
can stop saying.
Here you are, Norm.
Oh, thank you.
FRASIER:
Now, Norm,
Norm, here,
don't lift up your neck
like that.
Remember what Dr. Feld said.
You've got a bruised disk
and you don't want
to aggravate it
by moving
in any way.
Well, at least it won't
affect my lifestyle much.
Can you just drop me off
at home, Frasier?
Okay, Norm,
just be careful.
No, no, we... we
can't take him home.
Vera's out of town.
Can you imagine Norm
just sitting there
all alone in
his house,
helpless in front
of the TV?
Hang onto your hat,
but yes.
Look, Lilith,
the least I
owe Norm is...
is the comfort
of our home.
I mean, at least until
Vera comes back.
I see what this is.
You want your little friend
to stay over.
Well, he doesn't
move much.
All right, if you clean up after
him, you can keep him,
but the first time
I have to do it, out he goes.
Do you hear that, Norm?
You can stay!
Say, listen, tell her you want
to watch some television.
800.
Literature.
808.83.
Short monologues.
Boy, Mr. Clavin, you sure know
your Dewey Decimal System.
(phone ringing)
Cheers.
Hey, guys, it's Norm.
ALL:
Norm!
Hey, what's
shaking, man?
(laughing)
Where's he come up
with these things?
That's great.
So how
are you doing, huh?
Ooh, ouch.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Well, uh, we're gonna
miss you around here.
Take it easy.
Yeah, all right,
bye-bye.
Poor guy-- whoa.
What?
Threw his back out over
at, uh, Frasier's house.
Can't move--
Lilith's taking care of him.
Ooh, poor Norm.
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
Oh, I hope... hope
it's not serious.
I mean, if anything,
uh, happened
to the big guy, I don't
know what I'd do.
Yeah, it's too bad
it takes something bad
to happen for us
to really appreciate him.
Yeah, yeah,
it really makes you
stop and think, huh?
Flip you for his stool.
Heads.
Hey!
Lilith, um,
could you put a head
on this, please?
Norm, for two days now,
I've been seeing
to your every need.
I think it's time we
had a little talk.
Oh, great,
could I go first?
'Cause there's something I've
been really wanting to say.
(takes deep breath)
Lilith, you and I
are very different people.
I mean, look
at you.
You're successful,
ambitious,
you've got a...
a great career,
lovely family.
Me, I'm just a guy
who sits on a barstool
and hangs out all day
with his dorky friends.
I don't know, I guess I've
always sort of felt...
sorry for you.
The point I'm tryin'
to make here, Lilith,
is that even though
I don't understand
half the stuff
you guys talk about,
quantum physics
and stuff...
Oh.
Oh, quantum, that,
that's easy.
Once you accept the duality
of light
as both a particle and a wave...
Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, whatever.
Who, who cares, really?
The point is, Lilith,
that I realize that you've
been trying to help me.
And I appreciate
that.
And in the future,
I, for one, will not be so quick
to just blow you off.
Sadly, Norm, that's one
of the nicest things
anyone's ever said to me.
Thank you for that gift.
(doorbell rings)
Oh, uh,
could you get that?
That's probably the pizza
that I ordered.
I had to put it
on your MasterCard.
Uh, thank you for that gift.
Yoo-hoo!
Anybody home?
Hey, Lilith,
how're ya doin'?
Normie!
Cliffy!
Hey, how's
it goin'?
Well, I was in the
neighborhood,
so I thought
I'd stop in.
Yeah? You finished
your route?
Well, no,
they can wait.
Heck, there's, uh,
nothin' happenin' today.
Well, I, uh, the biggest
thing today is, uh,
some old lady wrote
some guy sayin'
that she was
his natural mother.
It's a soap opera
out there, Norm.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, well,
Norm and Cliff in my home.
Usually at this point
I wake up drenched in sweat.
Oh, now
there's an image, huh?
Now, now, Cliffy.
Back off now, Cliff.
Lilith and I have
been talking.
Turns out she's just
regular folks.
Sure. Sure she is.
Yeah, so, uh,
what's a guy gotta do
to get a drink around here?
(doorbell rings)
Cliff,
this is not a tavern.
This is my home.
Do you see a bartender?
Do you see any beer?
Ho, there he is!
Sammy!
All right!
Normie can't come
to the beer,
then the beer comes
to Normie!
All right!
Hey, Lilith,
want to get us some
glasses there?
You know, Norm,
it's a little bit strange
watchin' TV
at eye level.
You get used to
it, though.
No, actually, you probably won't
get used to it, Cliff.
Remember,
you're just stopping by.
Oh, I don't know
there, Lilith.
I mean, uh, Sam's pourin',
you got ESPN.
It's just like Cheers.
Yes, but it's not Cheers.
This is a private home, and
comfortable though it may be,
I'm sure you have
other things to do.
You know, Cliff, Lilith's right.
You've got your route to finish.
We'll be here when you get back.
Uh, gentlemen,
I'm afraid the party is over.
As enjoyable
as this has been,
I'm going to have
to ask you to leave.
Well, this must
be the place.
He drives
like a maniac.
How would you know?
You were playing
with my radio
the whole way.
How can you listen
to that crap?
Oh.
SAM:
Hey, guys, huh?
What'll you have
here?
How about a beer?
Oh, listen, everyone,
Norm needs peace and quiet.
For that matter,
so do Frasier and I.
So if you don't mind...
Wing dings!
Get 'em while they're hot!
Paul! Phil!
Good to see you.
Say, listen,
those directions weren't too
complicated, were they?
Oh, no.
Look, honey,
it's Phil and Paul!
May I see you in the kitchen,
darling?
(crash)
I'll just, uh,
I'll put in another batch.
(soul music playing)
Frasier.
Doctor, are you listening to me?
Yes, yes.
Now please continue.
I hate it
when you do that.
Say, what time is it?
It's 1:00 in
the morning,
and your friends are
still downstairs.
Oh, just try to ignore it,
Lilith.
It's only for a couple more
days.
I will
not ignore it!
Now go down there
and get rid of them.
I can't, dear.
I'm the one that hurt Norm.
I feel responsible.
But you're not responsible
for the others.
Yeah, but, you don't
understand, dear.
You get one,
you get them all.
It's like a hive
mentality.
Norm must
be their queen.
Get rid of
them, now!
And if I don't?
Would you like to ever see me
naked again in the '90s?
You know, that would
be more effective
if you didn't use it
every time
you ever want me
to do something.
♪ ♪
FRASIER:
All right, people,
enough is enough.
(music stops)
SAM:
Oh, come on, man.
(music resumes)
Stop it right now!
(music stops)
I want you people out
of my house!
Gee, Lilith,
what's wrong?
You've taken
advantage of our
hospitality.
You should be ashamed
of yourselves.
Lilith, don't you think you're
overreacting a little bit?
(phone rings)
Cheers.
This is not Cheers.
Call back, huh?
And you!
I thought you were
getting rid of them.
Well, I asked them to leave,
and they said no.
You never asked us
to leave, Fras.
Shut up, Cliff, I'm
in a little pickle here.
I will not have my home
turned into a circus.
There is only
one person
who has any right
to be here.
Is it me?
Fat chance, mister!
I'm talking
about Nor...
Where the hell is
Norm?
Well, he said his back
was feelin' better
so he, uh, hit
the bricks.
Yeah.
I think he went
to Cheers.
And you people are still here?
If you're not gone
by the time I get back,
Frasier, you're a dead man!
Do you hear me?
(door slams)
Carla...
I did it.
It's almost closing time,
and here's my little egg.
Safe and sound.
Pay up.
Darn the luck!
(sighs)
Say, uh, you don't have
change for a 20, do you?
Where did you get
all that money?
Well, I bet some
of the guys
that I could make you
carry an egg
around the bar
for three days running.
I won 150 bucks.
Here's your five.
Go crazy.
The important thing
to remember here is
that I proved my point.
What did you prove?
That you could take care
of an egg?
(chuckles)
You know, babies are a lot
bigger and heavier.
Now, if you could,
say, uh,
carry a watermelon...
say,
between your legs,
from one end of the bar
to the other,
and cluck like a chicken,
now, that would prove
that you're ready
for motherhood.
Good night, Carla.
Here's your 20,
Carla.
I thought
she'd do it.
Norm!
Oh, no,
Dr. Sternin-Crane,
you're supposed
to yell "Norm"
when he comes
in the door.
Don't worry.
It took me a little while
to get used to it, too.
What's wrong, Lilith?
What the hell are
you doing here?
Well, my back started feelin'
a lot better, and, uh,
I was really getting
kinda tired of those guys.
Norm, perhaps you'll
understand an analogy.
Have you ever
had a dog
and the dog
had fleas?
But then when
the dog left,
your house was
still infested?
Oh, yeah,
that happened to me.
Only it wasn't a dog.
It was a pig.
And we had fleas the size
of golf balls.
Woody, I'm not
interested.
I'm trying to have a
conversation with Norm.
Whoa, golf balls, huh?
It got so bad we had to bomb
the whole house.
Wow.
Those flea bombs
are great, huh?
What's a flea bomb?
Stop it!
Just stop it!
I came by to tell you
that your behavior has been
unconscionably rude.
You let your friends
overrun my home,
and then when
you leave,
you don't even have
the decency
to take them
with you.
That's all I
have to say.
Good night.
Wait, wait, Lilith,
Lilith, wait a minute.
Now, look, you're
absolutely right,
and I'm sorry.
(sighs)
Well, you're
up already.
You know, why don't
you just relax
and have a drink?
Well, come on.
You-you took
care of me for two days.
The least I can do is
buy you a drink.
Come on, come on.
Look, you can sit on my stool.
Huh?
Yeah.
Woods, scotch.
I may as well.
My house is filled with people
who hate me.
They're all angry at me
because I spoiled the big party.
I'm the wet blanket.
I'm the drudge.
I'm the big party pooper.
Stop me when you disagree.
I will.
You know, Norm,
you may find this surprising,
but I'm somewhat off-putting
to most people.
No, no, it's,
it's true.
I don't have many
friends.
I've never been very good
at making friends.
I think it's easy,
Lilith.
Um, you just have to relax
a bit, you know?
Just sort
of loosen up.
You mean just be myself?
No.
Uh, you weren't
listening.
Just relax.
Loosen up.
Okay, I'll try it.
(sighs)
Oh, wow, this feels much better.
See?
I've been looking at
this all wrong.
I'm going to go back
to my house,
and I'm going to be the life
of that party.
And it won't be
that disorganized,
carousing fun they've
been having.
It's going to be good,
clean, organized fun.
We'll play Pictionary,
then Boticelli,
then it's Charades
till dawn.
I'll rush home
and type up a party schedule.
I'll make copies.
Oh, I wonder if they have a copy
center open at this hour.
I know.
Why not make a game out
of trying to find one?
Frasier, it's Norm.
Get out of the house
while you still can.