Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Oh, boy, that's the third time
you beat me, Mike.
- I guess I owe you another beer.
- No, that's okay. I gotta run.
I'll take a rain check
on that one, huh?
Lost again, huh?
Yeah, I don't know what's the matter
with me.
It seems like that guy just has
my number, you know?
Forget about it.
Next time he comes in here,
you just challenge him
to some ltalian arm wrestling.
- Oh, I never tried that.
- Come here.
Give me your arm.
Okay, now, I'm gonna pull
as hard as I can,
and you resist me
with all your strength.
- All right.
- Go.
I beat Carla!
And I'm not even ltalian.
You wine them.
You dine them.
Tell them how pretty they are.
Buy them fancy presents.
Finally, you get up the nerve to ask
one of the little dears to marry you.
What do you get
for all your trouble? Squat.
I thought you'd pretty much gotten
over that Diane problem of yours.
Oh, it's not as serious as it sounds.
See, this is the one-year anniversary of
the day Diane deserted me at the altar.
To repress my bitterness would be
detrimental to my recovery.
So on this day, and on this day alone,
I'm going to spew out my venom
and exorcise the blond demon
that haunts my soul.
Well, happy anniversary.
Holy moly guacamole.
Terre Haute, lndiana.
Oh, I wouldn't throw her out of my bed
for eating crackers.
Why else would she be there?
Yeah, that's very humorous, Normie.
Yeah, in light of the fact that
a leading woman's magazine
just recently completed a survey
which showed that postmen
are the most desired lovers
right after--
Rock stars and heart surgeons.
Well, you know what they
say down at the P.O...
"Postmen deliver daily."
Have we had this
conversation before, Norm?
Cliffie, we've had every
conversation before.
Boy, when people start finishing
each other's sentences, they're--
Spending far too much time together.
Say, Woody, let me have
another beer there.
Hey, did you hear
the one about the--?
Shepherd and the parrot? Yeah.
That was a good one.
- I had a very nice time, Brian.
- Me too.
Well, well, if it isn't
Kitten With a Whip.
That's funny.
Sam, I'd like you to meet Brian.
Brian, this is Sam.
And...?
Oh, this is, yeah, April.
April, that's Brian.
Hi.
- And I'm obviously, I guess, Diane.
- Oh, right, yeah.
- So you two have a good time?
- Oh, very nice. Very nice time.
- Yeah, we had a great time.
- Yeah, we had a fabulous time.
It was just a movie
and a burger afterwards.
Oh, but what a film. And the ground
beef was excellent, very lean.
Listen, I wanna thank you
for giving me a ride home.
That's a great car you've got there.
Yes, Brian has a wonderful car too,
and it gets excellent mileage.
What kind of mileage you get?
Thirty-five on the highway,
26 around town.
Thirty-two and 24. Sorry.
Well, thanks again.
Good night.
What a putrid display.
You know, people come here
to relax and enjoy themselves.
They don't wanna look at that.
Do you?
Yeah!
This is sick.
Brian has a big-screen TV.
- April has a satellite dish.
- You are so childish.
Excuse me, are you the owner?
Yeah, that's right, Sam Malone.
Hi. Phil Schumacher, campaign
manager for Janet Eldridge.
She's running for re-election
to city council.
Listen, the councillor is just down the
street on a walking tour of the district.
Would it be all right
if she came in to meet the folks,
and perhaps answer some questions
for the newspaper reporters?
- Sure. Why not?
- Great. Thanks a lot, Sam.
Hey, how about that? We're a stop
on the old campaign trail.
Oh, Sam. You're so politically naive.
Janet Eldridge is an
old-money conservative
who consistently supports
big-business interests
over badly-needed social programs.
She's a real political opportunist.
Well, if she's that bad,
I'll have her out of here in a flash.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Councillor Janet Eldridge.
She's got until Christmas,
then she's out of here.
I could use your support
in the upcoming election.
Yeah, right.
You got fame, money,
power and looks.
- What you need, I ain't got.
- I need your vote.
I need a man. But you don't see me
going around bars begging for one.
I give. I know when I'm overmatched.
I'm glad I'm not running against you.
She's smooth. I'll give her that.
Sam, I'd like you to meet Councillor
Eldridge. Councillor, this is--
"Mayday" Malone needs
no introduction to me
or anyone else in this town.
I was a big fan when you pitched for
the Sox. I think you're just wonderful.
Well, it's mutual.
- Oh, you're a fan of the councillor's?
- No, I think I'm wonderful too.
Hey, hey, hey, Sammy.
Unless these tired old eyes
are deceiving me, pal,
there's something going on
between you and the councillor.
I don't think so. No, no, no.
Watching that woman work this room
has brought me to a decision.
You've decided to work it too
for a change?
I'm going to campaign
for Janet Eldridge's opponent
- in the coming election.
- Is that right?
I've voted for him before,
but he really needs my help now.
Would anyone like to join me
in this campaign?
Working side by side untiringly
to carry James Fleener to victory?
I would.
James Fleener is the finest man
to enter public life in the last decade.
I'd be honoured to work for him.
All right. He needs all the help
he can get.
Who the hell is James Fleener?
- Boy, oh, boy, is Miss Eldridge pretty.
- Yeah.
You know, back home in Hanover,
everybody on the town council
has a paunch and smokes
big, smelly cigars.
Don't you have any women
on the town council there?
Yeah.
Sammy, I've been noticing
she just can't take her eyes off you.
- You gonna ask her out?
- What are you talking about?
Well, look at her.
She's a good woman, Sam.
She deserves it.
I don't know.
Yeah, politics makes
strange bedfellows, Sam.
So do you and anyone or anything.
I guess she's a little out of your league
when you come right down to it, huh?
Yeah, what's the matter, Sam?
She too much for you?
I just don't think it's a good idea
to hop into bed with someone
who could raise my taxes.
Councillor Eldridge will take
a few questions now.
Jerry Baker, Boston Star.
Councillor, do you support the effort of
the so-called Grant Avenue Coalition
to overturn the city council's rezoning
of that neighbourhood
for commercial use?
I voted in favour of rezoning
and would do so again.
My reasons are a matter of public
record. No, I do not support them.
Clifford C. Clavin, U.S. Postal Service,
South Central Branch.
In view of the carnage taking place
in our postal routes,
are you in favour of beefing up
our leash laws to include
Iife imprisonment for
the canine offenders?
I think that's a bit drastic,
but I am in favour of doing all we can
to support our overworked
and underpaid postal carriers.
You do a wonderful job.
That woman has got my support,
and I will deliver you the postal vote.
Too bad it'll be to the wrong address.
My name is Diane Chambers,
and I have a question.
- Do you work here?
- How come no one ever knows that?
Yes, I'm a waitress and proud of it.
In a work-ethic kind of way.
Councillor, you have been accused
of being out of touch
with your constituency.
Do you expect this stroll
through the neighbourhood
to make up for four years of neglect?
- Hold on just--
- It's all right.
Miss Chambers, I represent every
one of the people in my district.
If I don't get out and talk
as often as I'd like,
it's because I'm in my office
or at council meetings
or in conference with civic
and business leaders 1 6 hours a day.
I've never missed a vote
in my four years on the council,
and if I'm elected again
I intend to work even harder
for the people
I am privileged to represent.
Good, Diane,
you got her on the ropes.
Tom Edwards, Boston Sentinel.
Oh, excuse me, I think this gentleman
had his hand up first.
Yeah, I'm not a reporter,
I'm just a voter.
But I have a very important question.
Do you like Chinese food, and if so,
have you ever eaten it in the bathtub?
Yes, and no comment.
Well, in that case I have
a follow-up question here.
What are you doing for dinner
Thursday night?
The offer is very tempting, Mr Malone,
but I will have to respectfully decline.
- The campaign keeps me very busy.
- I understand.
What I won't give up
for the people of this district.
- Thank you all, ladies and gentlemen.
- Thank you very much.
Look at that, Norm.
She shot Sammy down.
Impeachment proceedings
should begin immediately.
She may be out of touch
with the common man,
but she can sure spot
a common roach.
- Sam?
- Yeah?
This is Janet's private number.
She wants you to call her.
- Guys, Janet's private number here.
- All right!
Sammy! Sammy! Sammy!
Fleener! Fleener! Fleener!
Okay. Fleener!
- Sammy! Sammy!
- Fleener! Fleener!
Say, Diane...
...did you happen to hear
that Sam is going out
with Councillor Eldridge
again tonight?
I believe I heard something like that.
Did you know it was for dinner
at the governor's mansion?
I recall someone mentioning it.
Did they also mention that
they were going in a limousine?
- A limo?
- Not a limo.
A limousine.
So, what are you
doing tonight, Diane?
Frasier and I are going canvassing
for Jim Fleener in the neighbourhood,
and then we're stuffing mailers
into envelopes later on.
Well, that sounds like fun too.
- Evening, everybody.
- Norm!
- Norman.
- What's happening, Mr Peterson?
The question is, Woody,
why is it happening to me?
Well, you're a little late there, Normie.
Where you been?
Well, I was at Hurley's Market.
I took Vera out for a little grocery
shopping, then a little dinner.
Oh, gee, that's nice, Mr P.
Where did you go to dinner?
Hurley's Market.
They were giving out those little
sausage samples on toothpicks.
By the way, guys,
for your information,
a dozen appears to be
the cut-off number.
Say, did you hear that I'm going to
the governor's place tonight for dinner?
Yes.
There was a rumour in the air.
Back when there was air.
You got a second here?
Listen...
...you know that ice cream stuff they
serve in the middle of dinner there?
- Is it okay--?
- Sorbet.
Sorbet, right, sorbet.
Is it okay if I were to ask
for chocolate sauce with that?
- I think it's wise not to.
- All right, all right.
And for God's sake,
remember that a bowl of warm water
- with a slice of lemon in it--
- I know, I know.
It's a finger bowl,
it's not lemon soup.
You know, nobody would've known
that time if you hadn't screamed.
You certainly have been at
the councillor's beck and call lately.
I never thought I'd see you
so controlled by a woman.
What happened to the Sam Malone
who once said to me,
"Hey, we're gonna do
what I wanna do from now on"?
You left him in a restaurant
with a face full of fettuccini.
That doesn't mean I didn't like him.
"Wim with Jim?"
I thought it up.
It's very Joycean.
If that means stupid, I agree.
Frasier, put the box
in the back, please.
If you're looking for something to do,
you can start stuffing the envelopes.
I've been stuffing all day, Diane.
Frankly, the task has lost its
considerable power to charm me.
Frasier, that's a defeatist attitude.
We don't need quitters
on the Fleener team.
- Hey, Sam, you're on TV.
- Oh, yeah, look at that.
- Nice-looking threads, Sam.
- Yeah.
Janet picked out the suit. She really
knows what looks good on the tube.
Carla,
even though we have our differences,
and we're frequently at odds,
there's one thing we very much have
in common:
We both like Sam.
And I'm concerned about him.
I think he might get hurt by this liaison
with Janet Eldridge.
Yeah, you're right.
He's having a lot of laughs
and a hot time with a beautiful woman.
The man is a glutton for punishment.
This is no romp, Carla.
It's more serious than that.
And the worst part is that she's just
using him. I mean, it all adds up.
He's an outstanding sports figure,
he's attractive, and in this town
it doesn't hurt that he's lrish.
- He's a vote getter.
- So what?
So when the election's over,
it's "So long, Sam."
And I think he's really going to be
hurt by this. That's "so what."
You are full of beans. Women come
and women go in Sam's life.
He's just having a few grins,
and I can prove it.
Hey, a word over here, heartthrob.
Coming at you.
Cliffie, Cliffie. I got this one.
You know, Sammy,
I've been thinking.
You have got a great set-up
with this Eldridge babe.
You're going to all these
high-toned parties,
meeting a lot of fancy people,
driving around in big cars.
And the best thing is,
you are getting to do to a politician
what they've been doing
to us for years.
You know, Carla, sometimes
you got a lousy sense of humour.
Sorry.
"A few grins," Carla?
- Boy, you look fabulous.
- Thank you. So do you.
Well, thank you.
Listen, I am famished here.
Do you know what kind of sorbet
they're serving?
- No, I was curious about that myself.
- Well--
Before we go I have to make
a couple of phone calls.
- May I use your office?
- Yeah. Right under the whale there.
Look at the size of that limo.
Hey, Your Excellence?
- Does it have a TV?
- Yes, it does.
Go and take a look at it if you want.
Oh, hot dog!
- Oh, boy, the exuberance of youth.
- Yeah. Wide-eyed and innocent.
Well, I guess those days
are long gone for you and me.
Yeah, yeah.
Thanks, Edith. Yeah, I'll talk to you
tomorrow. Bye-bye.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
Councillor Eldridge.
Please, call me Janet. What can I do
for you? It's Diane, isn't it?
Yes.
I'm speaking on behalf
of everyone here at Cheers,
and I would just like to say
that we're all very fond of Sam.
And, frankly, we're a little worried
about him.
We wouldn't like to see him get hurt.
What are you getting at?
Janet, I've made no secret
of my opposition to you politically,
but let's retract our claws
for the moment, shall we?
Let's stop hissing at each other.
Do you have a problem with cats?
No.
But it's the consensus of opinion
around here
that you're using Sam
to get re-elected,
with total disregard for his feelings,
and we don't think that's
a very nice thing to do.
I see.
Well, I'll be honest with you, Diane.
That's exactly why
I started seeing him.
So l-- We were right.
Well, I'm warning you,
I have some influence with Sam.
Yes, I know.
He thinks a great deal of you.
Anytime I wanted to--
He said that?
Yes.
He mentions you often.
And Sam is a man of few words.
Well, he only knows a few.
Yes.
He is a simple man in many ways,
but I think that's his strength.
I mean, I never met anyone
who didn't like him.
Well, good.
But I don't understand
why we're standing here
chatting so enjoyably when you just
admitted that you're using Sam.
That's not what I said, Diane.
You didn't let me finish.
Please.
Well, when I first started
seeing Sam,
perhaps I had ulterior motives
in mind,
but my attitude toward him
has changed dramatically.
I've learned that Sam has something
that's pretty special.
I've never experienced
with any other man
the feeling I have when I'm with him.
When we're at a fundraiser
or something like that,
I'll watch him across the room
talking with some people,
and sometimes a feeling
comes over me so strong
that it nearly makes me ache.
Oh, God.
I sound like a silly schoolgirl.
That's the truth.
Does that make you feel better?
It certainly does.
I'm awfully glad
we put this matter to rest.
You like Sam. And Sam likes you.
No one's going to get hurt.
Well, "wack to berk."
Boy, you're really good.
You almost had me fooled there.
But I don't believe a word you said.
When this campaign is over,
Sam's going to last about as long
as your campaign promises.
Well, back to work.
And I would like to thank
each and every one of you.
- This is a victory for all of us.
- Yes!
Well, not quite all of us.
I guess that's about--
I guess that's about it. Thanks.
Thanks, Diane, for all your help.
Nobody ever worked harder
for me than you.
In fact, I think you worked harder
than I did.
You did your best.
That's all that matters.
Say, listen, did you know
you're out of liquor?
And now I would like
to bring up a man
without whom I would not be
standing here tonight.
- Sam?
- Yeah?
- Would you let Phil through, please?
- Oh, yeah.
My campaign manager,
Mr Phil Schumacher!
And this guy
has been such a tremendous
help to me in this campaign.
I'm sure he needs no introduction.
But for those ladies in the audience
who would like an introduction,
you're not gonna get one.
That was my last chance.
Looks like I blew it.
Me too.