- Answer that for me, will you?
- You bet, Coach.
Cheers.
Carla? Yeah. Carla, it's for you.
- Sounds like trouble with the kids.
- l'm not here.
- Carla.
- Give it to me. What is it?
Seraphina's where?
Well, cut her down.
No, l don't care if it helps
the TV reception. Cut her down.
And if l get home and you've flushed
the car keys again, you've had it.
By the way, any more problems tonight
and you're adopted.
Your real mother
is Doris Slobotkin, 555 8921 .
Think that's gonna work?
One-in-a-million chance
but l gotta take it.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hi, Diane.
Sounds like you had
a pretty nice day off.
Well, it was so nice l don't know
if l'm ready to talk about it yet.
However, if you insist.
l went out with David
from the Anthropology Department.
He took me up to New Hampshire.
We walked in the woods,
we communed with nature.
We stayed in a little inn
where John Adams slept.
Yeah, lots of guys
sign the register that way.
Well,
now l know why l didn't wanna talk.
l had a pretty nice day off myself.
Taffy and l went sailing
up at Marble Head.
Taffy?
Sailing?
You?
You got a problem with that?
No. lt's just thought your idea of
romance was brunch and a cockfight.
l love sailing.
After seeing Ordinary People,
l've tried to get my kids interested.
- Afternoon everybody.
- Ho, Norm.
How's life treating you?
Like he caught in bed with his wife.
- How about a beer?
- Yowza!
l gonna bring some company in.
- Who are you bringing in?
- My new superior.
l gotta butter him up a little bit.
Bring him in here for a drink,
catch some dinner upstairs.
- Why not take him to your house?
- My wife lives there.
Gotcha.
One things, you guys,
you don't know me in here, OK?
Why?
l don't want him to think
l'm a bar fly.
- Good.
- Don't call me Norm.
Gotcha, Norm.
Diane, would you get some singles
up at Melville's, please.
Aye, aye, skipper.
Coach, l'll be right back.
l'm gonna get some wine.
- Pardon me.
- Hi.
l'm looking for a Diane Chambers.
You're in luck. We've got one.
- l beg your pardon?
- l hope you only want one.
Do you sense this conversation
is an exercise in futility?
Thank you. My name is Ernie Pantusso
but you can call me Coach.
- Rebecca Prout.
- Hi, Becky.
Diane and l shared a suite
at Bennington.
No kidding? Sam and l
shared a Chunky Bar in Cleveland.
- Where is Diane Chambers?
- Upstairs. She'll be a minute.
Well,
l'll just sit at a table and wait.
Okey-dokey.
- Thanks for your help.
- You're welcome. Any time.
- Rebecca.
- Diane.
What a wonderful coincidence.
l never come into a place like this.
l'm doing research for a paper...
What the hell's going on here?
A serving girl.
Would you bring us a bottle of wine?
Only if l can spit in it.
lt's all right.
l know that you work here.
- Alright, how did you find out?
- l called your mother.
She took her head out of the oven
long enough to fill me in.
God, l've missed you.
l'll never forget
those long afternoons in the quad,
drinking champagne, eating brioche
with strawberry preserves.
Reading and talking Schopenhauer.
Well, enough Schope-talk.
That's the beauty
about being a mailman.
l don't have to play smoochy-woochy
with my superiors the way you do.
Cliff, believe me, it's worth it
for accounting. l love numbers.
God help me, l love them.
Me, l like the challenges.
Dogs, vicious kids,
those hard-to-find mailboxes.
You think accounting's boring?
l miss one digit,
a company goes in the toilet.
l'll tell you when it all makes
sense. Mother's Day.
Delivering a card to some old hag.
Watching her eyes mist up,...
..kinda gets me
right behind the old ballpoint.
You want to talk sentimental?
Take that same old crone.
Save her a couple of hundred bucks
on the short form.
Then l know
why the Big Guy put me here.
l actually get paid to stand here
and listen to great conversation.
Rebecca, there's something wrong.
You could always see
through my façade of gaiety.
Elliot and l have parted.
Rebecca, no. You and Elliot?
You were together for ever.
l know. lt all began when Elliot got
his doctorate in lchthyology.
His eye began to wander.
The first thing l knew, he'd taken up
with a student on a squid expedition.
A doctorate changes a man.
But there'll be others, right?
ln the meantime,
you still have your work.
You'd think so.
l used to find enormous comfort
translating Russian poetry.
- l know.
- But no more.
Even when l went back
over my favourite,
Karashnikov's Another Christmas
of Agony, it failed to soothe me.
''Mischa the dog lies dead in the bog,
The children cry over the carcass,
The mist chokes my heart,
Covers the mourners,
At least this year we eat.''
lf that didn't pick you up,
l'm at a virtual loss.
What l need is to blot out
Elliot's memory.
That's exactly what you should do.
l'm looking for a man.
Pardon?
Diane, l've been thinking about this
carefully.
l think what l need is something
l've never had before.
An evening
of unbridled bestial pleasure.
l want to burn
at the stake of passion.
Rebecca, you're very vulnerable now.
Please, don't do anything foolish.
l've never done anything foolish
in my life and it's high time l did.
The man l'm looking for
should be peasant stock.
Tall, dark, strong, hairy arms.
But most important, he should be
unintellectual. One-word sentences.
- Do you know anyone like that?
- No.
Diane, did you get the small bills?
Yeah. Right. Excuse me. Here you go.
l need a ten in silver.
Would you get it for more, please?
OK, Coach. l'll be right back.
You just sit very still,
sip your wine.
Slowly.
Damn.
- Hi there.
Come here often?
Just about every day. l work here.
l couldn't help noticing your arms.
Yeah,
l get a lot of comments on these.
They go all the way down to my hands.
- What's your name?
- Sam. Change.
Why? l like myself this way.
Sam. Two bourbons straight.
Diane, it's him. l want him.
Who?
The gay guy with the war wound?
You can't fool me.
He's exactly what l'm looking for.
You're not interested in him,
are you?
No, of course not.
Then l'm going for him
before l lose my nerve.
Sam,
that woman is a dear friend of mine.
She is going through
a very difficult period.
So whatever she asks you,
please, just say ''no''.
- What?
- ''No.''
- Diane?
- Yes.
Would you excuse us a moment?
Fine.
Would you object
to joining me in my hotel
for an afternoon of animal passion?
No.
- What's your name?
- Does it matter?
No.
Diane, Sam's not back yet.
So? Who cares?
l would if he took off with my friend
for two hours.
One hour.
And 53 minutes.
Sam always did like day games.
What do you say?
This looks a nice place.
What are you gonna have, strangers?
Let me get this, Mr Stabell.
l think l'll have a...
Perrier.
- Give me a beer.
- Wait a minute. A beer?
That sounds a refreshing change.
l'll have a beer.
Coach. Listen.
- Hold me to one beer tonight.
- One at a time?
For the whole night.
Here we go.
Two tankards of their finest ale.
Let's talk.
- Hey, Sammy.
- Hey.
- Diane, Sam's here.
- So?
l'm gonna be in my office back here.
Well, hey...
Nothing going on here, huh?
Dead.
l think l'm gonna stretch my legs,
get a little exercise, fresh air.
Gotta take it easy.
l have no respect
for a man who can't control himself
when it comes to drinking.
Me neither.
How could you do that
to that poor woman?
Do what?
Do what. Thank you, Mr Quickpants.
Rebecca is a very vulnerable person,
coming off a shattered relationship.
How could you go off with her?
She said, ''Would you mind?''
Would you mind.
Those three words are all that
separate you from a rutting pig.
That and my aftershave.
How dare you try to be funny
when l hate you?
Come on. What's the big deal?
We're all adults, aren't we?
Yes. Contrary to your assumption,
l am not a prude.
l have a healthy attitude toward...
..you know.
Answer me one question.
Are you proud of what you did today?
l don't kiss and tell.
The pig develops scruples.
Come on. Look, l'm just kidding
you. Nothing happened. Alright?
- He compounds it by lying.
- No lie. l swear, nothing happened.
You mean
Rebecca came to her senses?
No. l stopped it.
l get it.
You got angry because she considered
you nothing but a stud service?
No, l like that.
The problem was
that l couldn't shut her up.
No offence
but your friend is very boring.
She's depressing
and she's long-winded.
Those dismal Russian poems.
They don't even rhyme.
After listening to two hours' worth
of frostbite and famine,
l decided
to get my balalaikas out of there.
You turned a woman down?
Yeah. Here l am all primed
for a wonderful afternoon...
You can't admit the truth, can you?
What? What is the truth?
Decency finally won out. You did
the right thing. You were noble.
No. l was bored.
Unconsciously, you were sensitive
to her suffering
and you didn't want
to take advantage of that.
- Think so?
- Yes.
Sam Malone, you're a better man
than you're willing to admit.
Maybe you're right. Maybe l am kinda
turning into a sensitive guy.
Maybe l'll never
look at a woman again
and see her as a mere sex object.
No, scratch that thought.
lt was my favourite audit.
lt nearly cost my marriage,
but it was worth it.
Gotta go for the gusto.
l like your enthusiasm, Norm.
You're a workhorse.
Clydesdale.
You know,
l'm having one heck of a time.
l don't usually do this,
but let's have another.
- Coach, two more beers.
- Can't do it, Norm.
- No. lt's OK now.
- Norm, l'm not letting you down.
- You said one beer.
- All right.
- One beer for my friend.
- That's different.
He'll have a pitcher.
Diane,
l've come to say goodbye.
For ever.
- Rebecca, what's wrong?
- l'm not attractive to men.
What?
First Elliot and now what's-his-name.
Rebecca, l'm sorry.
Do you have to believe
in God to be a nun?
lt helps.
What did Sam do to you?
- Who's Sam?
- The bartender.
Nothing. That's the problem.
Diane, he found me repulsive.
No, Rebecca.
This must be a misunderstanding.
He climbed out the window.
l'm going back there to talk to Sam.
He must know that he's hurt you.
l originally wanted to be a dancer.
You're a pig.
l haven't moved.
How did l get back to pig?
- You have ruined a human being.
- Who?
Rebecca.
- She's sitting out there right now.
- Mother Russia? l'm not here.
Sam, she's crushed. l have never seen
this woman so depressed.
Believe me,
l have seen her depressed.
- l believe you.
- Well, you have to do something.
She is seriously upset. lt's your
fault for the way you rejected her.
- Wait, where are you going?
- l am going to bring her in.
No. Come on, give me a minute
to build a window, or something.
You're going
to restore her confidence.
What am l gonna say?
Just tell her
the reason you rejected her
wasn't because you found her
unattractive.
What was the reason?
l don't know. Tell her
that you belong to someone else.
That you lost your head for a moment,
that you're an uncaring worm.
l was laughed at by the other boys,
Norm.
Rebecca, may l speak to you in here
for a moment?
But don't they always laugh
at the graceful fellows?
Hello, Rebecca.
Hello... Again.
When l left the hotel, l may have
given you the wrong impression.
You see,
l thought there was a fire.
l'm sorry.
Rebecca, l might not have
been totally fair with you.
The reason l left was,
l'm kinda seeing another person.
l was afraid
this was going to happen.
You're making excuses
to spare my feelings.
No. This is true.
l really am seeing somebody else.
- Please.
- Rebecca.
You are a very desirable woman.
He does happen to be going
with somebody, that's all.
- Me.
- You?
We can tell it now. Yes. Today we had
a tiff right before you came in.
And Sam used you to make me jealous
and then when push came to shove,
he finally remembered what
a wonderful thing we have together.
lsn't that right, sweetheart?
Yeah. Sure. You bet ya.
Yes, Sam and l are deeply
and passionately in love.
l can't believe it. You two?
lt's incredible.
l'd never have put you two together.
Well, l know. lt does test
the limits of human logic.
But, like you, l was growing
bored with bright, articulate men.
- You were?
- Sure.
l was looking for meat and potatoes.
Sam here, the old side of beef,
really fit the bill.
You know, l was getting kinda bored
with beautiful, sexy, sensuous women.
l decided to go for pleasant.
Believe it or not, l actually prefer
a man who's thick and ordinary.
l guess l'm kind of old-fashioned.
l like a woman
who does what her man tells her.
Lookee there, my shoe's undone.
Will you get that for me, honey?
What, darling?
Would you tie
my shoesy-woosy for me?
She loves doing
these little things for me.
That's a little tight there, honey.
- How's that, sweetheart?
- That's much better. Thank you.
Well, all of a sudden,
l feel like l'm intruding.
l can see that
there's such emotion in this room.
Thank you for everything, Diane.
Rebecca, thank you.
lt was wonderful to see you again.
- l'll write you.
- Oh, good. Things'll work out.
Let go of me.
- You had the gall.
- Just get...
That's the kind of passion
l was hoping l'd find.
You'll find it, Rebecca.
(ENGLlSH)