Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Good evening, Mr. Clavin.
How lovely to see you again.
It's a trick, isn't it?
You're gonna hurt me.
Yeah, what's
the story here, Carla?
You've been acting
very strange all evening.
Why? What did I do?
Well, for example,
you've poured me three beers
without once flicking
the foam up my nose.
You haven't even
spit on anybody.
What is it, honey?
Trouble at home?
All right,
I'm gonna tell you guys.
I went to see
Madam Lazora this morning.
Your fortune teller?
Palmist.
Anyway, she told me that
my courtesy to others tonight
could result
in substantial wealth.
Ah.
And I'm
telling you,
tonight I'm taking
no chances.
What, you're not even
going to insult anybody?
Well, not unless
I can do it so subtly
that he doesn't know
he's been insulted.
No, tonight the bigger
jackass a guy is,
the more courteous
I am gonna be.
I'll start with numero uno.
Now, I do hope you'll allow me
the incredible privilege
of serving you
a beer, Mr. Clavin.
( piano plays )
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always
glad you came
You want to be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You want to go where
everybody knows your name.
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
You're in early
tonight, Frasier.
Yes, I'm meeting
a former colleague,
Dr. Lawrence Crandell,
for a pre-dinner drink.
He's in town
on a book tour.
Oh, yeah?
He's a writer, huh?
Ooh, I should say so.
He's written a raging
best seller.
You know, if I wasn't
so thoroughly happy
in my own life, I might
even stoop to being
just a bit envious of
a former colleague
who's now so widely
successful.
Well, that is if
you measure success
by dollars and cents,
popularity, personal fame.
I'm happy for him.
What's the book about?
Who gives a damn?
Sorry. It's, uh,
a marriage manual.
It's entitled, the, uh,
The Forever Couple:
The Joy of Loving
One Person
For the Rest
of Your Life.
Ah, science-fiction.
Those usually sell great.
But you know, success
does have its price tag.
He's been away
from his wife, Valerie,
for the better part of a year.
Jeez, you know,
I think I'd go crazy
if I was away
from Lilith for that long.
I don't even
like to think about it.
Yeah, I'll bet.
Well, I do think about it.
I don't enjoy it.
I'm sure not.
Well, I do enjoy it, but...
I'm not proud of the fact.
Frasier.
Larry, good to see you again.
Good to see you.
Have I told you how
thrilled I am
about the success
of your book?
Yes, you have.
It's a fabulous book.
You know,
I was just thinking
what a wonderful
gift it would make.
Have you read it?
Well, no, I was hoping
someone might give it to me.
Let me get you
a drink.
Oh, thanks,
black and white, neat.
FRASIER:
Ah, Lawrence,
this is Rebecca Howe.
This is Lawrence
Crandell.
How do you do?
Pleased to meet you.
And this
is Sam Malone.
Oh, not the Sam Malone?
Oh, you were
a hell of a pitcher. I saw you
strike out
Reggie Jackson.
Made him look
like a fool.
Oh, well...
I can hardly
blame him
for knocking you
off the mound
the next time up with
that line drive.
So, uh, Frasier told me
that you've, uh,
been baching it
a long time here.
It must be pretty rough, huh?
Say, why didn't you just
bring Valerie with you?
Well, you know,
she hates to travel.
Besides, we decided
this was a perfect
opportunity to test
my theories
about marital fidelity.
And I'm glad to say after
ten months of celibacy,
I can now pronounce
my principle sound.
( Sam whistles )
After ten months of celibacy,
I couldn't
even pronounce my name.
I make it a point to tell my
wife at least once a day,
"You're my world, you're
my life, I love you."
I'll bet my wife would
love to hear those words.
Could you give
her a call?
So the book's doing
pretty good, huh?
Yeah, it has been
received rather well.
In fact, this last review
is so embarrassingly good,
I should just wad it up
and throw it away.
But I need several
hundred copies first.
Is there a photocopy
machine around here?
Yeah, Rebecca's
got one in her office.
You don't mind,
do you?
No, help yourself.
That's very kind of you.
Any special instructions?
Yes, just push
the blue button.
It's right under the sign
that says, "This machine
is for photocopying documents,
not your butt."
All set?
Thanks again.
You're welcome.
Miss Howe, may I ask
you something?
Sure.
I hope you won't
take this the wrong way,
but my field
is human sexual dynamics.
And just now I had
the strangest impression--
please, tell me if I'm wrong--
that something happened
when you and I were introduced.
I sensed some spark,
some flicker
of response on your part.
Very subtle,
but unmistakable.
Was I imagining that?
I think so.
Well, my mistake.
I'm sure you understand.
Of course.
You-You-You are aware
I wasn't being judgmental?
Of course.
It's the response itself
that interested me.
Purely as a scientist.
And you
are quite sure
that on some very basic level,
you didn't experience
an undeniable attraction?
Positive.
Well, I'm glad
we cleared that up.
Still, I can't keep
from wondering...
...whether your subconscious
may not be trying
to tell us something.
I swear to you,
Dr. Crandell...
I mean,
when I hear
such facile denial,
it always sets off a little
alarm in my head.
Dr. Crandell.
Call me Lawrence.
Let me make this
as clear as I know how.
There was no attraction
when we met, or since.
I felt nothing.
I feel nothing.
Zero, nada, zip.
Zip.
Interesting unconscious
choice of word.
Try this word: out.
All right, sorry.
Man.
( knocking )
I give up.
You make me crazy with desire.
I can't keep my hands off you!
What do you want?!
Sign these invoices,
and then be gentle.
Why don't you
sit over there, Walter?
You suppose I might trouble you
for two brandies, Miss Howe?
Ask the bartender.
Of course we can help you.
Woody, uh, pour Dr. Crandell
a couple of our house brand.
Two house brands
on the house.
That's very kind
of you, Sam.
One seldom gets to sample
a good Nigerian Cognac.
Weren't you kind of
rude to Dr. Crandell?
Was I? Sorry.
Well, what'd he ever do to you?
I don't know.
Nothing. Never mind.
Your hostility
was unmistakable.
( sighs )
All right.
The man came on to me
in my office.
Dr. Crandell
came on to you?
What'd he do?
Did he touch you?
No, he did not touch me.
Make an indecent proposal?
Of course not.
Comment on your looks,
ask you for a date,
whistle, flash, what?
He asked
about my feelings.
The man should
be horse whipped!
Rebecca, of course he
asked about your feelings.
I mean,
it's his field.
The man
is an analyst.
He's written volumes on
human sexual attraction.
Wait, wait, so, uh,
then what happened?
I'll tell you what happened,
Mr. Smarty Pantses.
He... thanked me
politely and he left.
Oh, that doesn't seem
so terrible, does it?
Rebecca, I assure you,
you must have
misunderstood his intentions.
I mean,
he's in love with his wife.
They're the most happily
married couple I know.
Gee, I guess I could
have been wrong.
What if he was just being
psychological or something?
I should apologize
to him, huh?
I guess you should.
We'll be in touch.
Dr. Crandell, may I speak
with you a moment?
Of course.
Oh, I want to apologize
to you for having
that conversation and then me
getting a little bit upset.
I hope you don't think me rude.
Oh, of course not.
You answered
my questions honestly
in the spirit in which
they were asked.
So that's
the end to that.
Oh, good. Thank you.
That's all right.
You meet someone, you
find him unattractive,
even repulsive,
it happens.
Well, I don't think
you're repulsive.
No, no, please.
Don't think you have to
worry about my feelings.
I think you're
an attractive man.
Really, that's
very flattering.
As a matter of fact,
I'm really quite awkward and
uncomfortable around women.
As a matter of fact,
the very idea
of my propositioning you
or having an opening line,
or doing something
so blatant as...
Rubbing your foot
along my leg?
Exactly.
You're doing that
right now.
Oh, goodness.
Was that you?
I'm sorry, I thought
it was the table leg.
The supple, quivering table
leg that goes on forever.
A natural mistake.
You're still doing it.
You have a hole
in your sock.
Like it?
Dr. Crandell, I want you
to keep your foot
where it belongs.
Ow!
( phone ringing )
WOODY:
Cheers.
Dr. Crandell?
Telephone.
It's Mrs. Dr. Crandell.
Thank you.
I left
the number here.
Hello, honey, my darling!
My reason for living!
Oh, that slime ball hypocrite.
What?!
Get-Get over here.
That tears it.
( indistinct grumbling )
SAM:
What was
that about?
He toed my calf.
What?
Excuse me?
He was rubbing
his foot on my leg.
Well, perhaps he was just trying
to cross his legs
and he accidentally
bumped into you.
What do you think
I am, a nitwit?
I am telling you
that your distinguished,
happily married friend
was coming on to me.
Oh, please.
He was!
Do you realize that you are
impugning the reputation
of a man that literally
wrote the book
on fidelity in marriage.
You've insulted him,
and frankly, you've insulted me.
No, you know, I see
what's going on here.
You know, you just
projected your frustrations
on to somebody else,
because it's been too long
since you had
your tires rotated.
And I am telling you
that he is a lying,
hypocritical sleaze
who needs to be neutered.
Excuse me,
Frasier.
I think I better
be moving along.
Somehow I've antagonized
Miss Howe.
Rather than provoke any
further embarrassment,
I think it's best
to simply
remove my offending
personality.
Oh, Larry, must you?
No, no, Dr. Crandell, please.
Uh, you see, you got
to understand something
about Rebecca here--
she's had a very difficult
past few... life.
I've sensed some emotional
problems there.
It's a pity.
The nerve of that man
saying I have
an emotional problem.
I'd like to meet him in
a dark alley with a cleaver.
Thank you, sir.
No sirs.
While we're together,
you're not a chamber maid, and
I'm not a guest in the hotel.
We're just two vibrant
human beings ready
to snatch a moment's pleasure.
I like the way you talk.
Boy, I've never been
in one of these rooms
without my vacuum cleaner
running.
It's so...
um... quiet.
It is peaceful,
isn't it?
Oh, yeah.
but you know what's
really amazing about this?
I didn't even realize myself
that I was attracted to you
until you told me
you sensed it.
Well,
human behavior
is pretty much an
open book to me.
There's nothing
I haven't seen or...
or read,
or been told about
or seen pictures of.
Or short films.
Well, bottoms up.
Oh, yes,
oh, God, yes.
( knocking )
Oh, no, if they find me
in here, I'll get fired!
Oh, nonsense.
I'll get rid of them.
( chuckles )
Hi, it's Miss Howe.
May I come in?
Ordinarily I'd say yes,
but you see, I'm expecting
a colleague any minute.
So you see,
it's really not convenient.
I was just thinking
about something you said,
and I wanted
to clarify that.
Terrific.
We'll have lunch tomorrow
and clarify away.
That's a great idea,
but you know,
I have been through
so much stress
and so much anxiety
over this
that I have a terrible,
splitting headache.
Do you have any aspirin?
Aspirin?
Yes, if you give me
an aspirin,
I think it'll get rid
of my headache
and then I can leave
you in peace.
Right, aspirin.
Well, I'll try to find it.
Psst!
Get in there.
This is the stupidest
thing I've ever done.
You do nine stupid things
before breakfast.
Now get in that closet.
Now when...
when he admits
that he came on to me,
I want you to leap out
and catch him
in the act.
And then we'll prove
once and for all
that he is a lech
and I am not cuckoo.
One thing at a time, Rebecca.
CRANDELL:
Two aspirin coming up.
Two tablets, buffered.
I hope they go down well.
Bye-bye.
Dr. Crandell,
it's not really why I'm here.
It's not?
No.
Now, I know
you came on to me
and you know
you came on to me.
But I'm not leaving here
until you admit it.
All right, I admit it,
I came on to you, good night.
Ah-ha.
Ah-ha?
I didn't quite hear that.
Oh, for God's sake,
good night.
Um, please, if you could
just say it a little bit louder
and a little clearer
so that I know that
there's no mistaking it.
All right,
if that will make you happy,
I came on to you,
I came on to you.
You know, I'm beginning
to regret it.
Ah-ha!
Good night, Miss Howe.
You... Sam!
Would you get the hell
out of there?
Sam?
Whoa, boy.
These luxury hotels
have great closets.
Did you hear
what he just said?
Uh, no, I'm sorry,
I sort of had something
in my ear.
You had a woman in here!
Uh, as long as we got that
established,
if you need me again,
I'll be back
by the shoe rack.
Sam!
Remember our mission?
Now listen to me.
This proves that I am not crazy.
This proves that
he is just a lech.
I can explain.
Miss Johnson
is my executive secretary.
We have a great deal
of dictation together.
Now if you'll excuse us.
You sent for a violinist?
A violinist
to do your dictation?
Come on.
Now at least,
for God's sakes,
have the decency
to come clean
and tell Sam the truth.
Oh, all right.
I admit it, it's true.
I've been a very lonely man.
I thought this trip would put
my convictions to the test,
but I'm afraid
I came up lacking.
I'm sorry if I caused you
any pain, Miss Howe.
Well, at least
you finally admitted it.
Yes, I'm glad the
truth is out.
At last,
no more lying.
No more deceit.
( knocking )
WOMAN:
Lawrence?
Guess who?
It's my wife!
Hide!
I'm not going
in a closet.
Oh, come on.
You'll enjoy it.
I'll show you around.
Please, please, you must.
My career is at stake.
So is my marriage.
I've been faithful
to this woman
for 15 years.
Mostly because
she's the scariest bitch
you ever want to meet.
( knocking )
Lawrence, you all right?
I am doing this
for your wife, buster.
Uh, Rebecca, I want you
to meet Maria.
Hi, Maria,
nice to meet you.
What's your name?
Zol...
Hi, I'm Rebecca.
Lawrence?
Yes, coming, coming.
Oh, Valerie.
Darling, what an
enormous surprise!
What took you so long
to answer the door?
Well, it's this
plush carpet.
I caught my little toe.
What brings you here?
Well, when I spoke
to you on the phone
and I heard the hunger
in that voice,
I couldn't bear to
be separated from you
one more minute.
Champagne, Larry?
Oh, yes, they bring it
up every night.
It's a fabulous hotel.
Let's go get
something to eat.
You're not dressed.
Well, we'll go
someplace casual.
Well, at least put
on a coat.
It's cool out.
I'll buy one on the way.
Shall we?
Lawrence,
put on a coat.
Right.
Yes, anything
you say, dear. I'll just
( loud, sing-songy voice ):
go to the closet all by myself.
Get my coat all by myself.
I've never seen you
in that coat.
I just bought it.
If you don't like it,
back it goes.
No, Lawrence, put it on.
Put it on now.
Oh, that tailor.
Well, I'm stopping the payment
on that check!
Oh, I'm famished.
Let's go.
Whoever is in that closet,
come out this instant!
All right,
I want an explanation,
and I want it right this minute.
Otherwise, I am going
to divorce him.
I am going
to take his money,
and I am going to take his
reputation, and his career.
And after that I am going
to do the same for each
and every one of you.
And believe me, I can do it.
So who is going to come forth
with an explanation?
Um, we, uh, we're all here
to change the lightbulbs.
Mrs. Crandell,
I'm going to tell
you the truth.
because I feel that this
has gone on too long.
And as usual, I have to be
the voice of reason.
Forgive me for saying this,
but if I were in your shoes,
I would want to know.
Your husband came on to me
in a local bar.
Do you mean
he propositioned you?
Well, he didn't exactly
proposition me.
Well, what exactly did he do?
He asked me
about my feelings.
That is his field, you know.
That isn't all he did.
He rubbed my leg
with his disgusting foot.
She never gets tired
of telling this part.
Yes, yes, I admit it.
I accidentally brushed up
against her leg with my foot.
I apologized profusely.
He did not have his shoe on.
It was hot in there.
Would you believe
the humiliation?
A hole in my $50 hosiery.
Why you filthy...
Okay, fine, fine.
There is a chambermaid
in the room.
Explain it.
A chambermaid in a hotel?
Will wonders never cease.
You know, actually, we're going
to be running along here.
No, we're not going
to be running along.
All right.
How about the fiddler, huh?
I was lonely.
I was going to have him play
our song all night.
All right, all right.
So have your
loving husband explain
why the four of us
were in that closet.
You were there.
You mean you don't know?
Yes, I know.
Because you are
the scariest bitch
we would ever want to meet.
And you are
a little tramp.
Tramp?
Why,  I ought to put you...
I'm going
to kill your husband!
I'm going to kill him!
I'm going to kill you!
He's stupid, he's a fraud!
He's a psycho!
He's a...!
I'm going to hunt you down
and kill you like a dog!
And why don't you get yourself
some new socks, buster?!
SAM:
Um...
Uh, I can explain
everything here.
She just wanted to convince me
that she's not crazy.
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.podnapisi.net