Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
It's amazing
what they're making
for kids nowadays.
What?
Here's an ad for a toy
where you make a monster,
then drop him
in a vat of acid
and boil the skin
off his bones.
Oh, boy, Norm.
When we were kids,
we had real toys
to play with. Remember?
Oh, you're
damn straight.
You know, I was up
in my attic the other day.
Yeah?
Found my old Lionel train set.
Oh, now there is a toy.
Yeah.
Remember the hours you spent
sticking those tracks together?
Getting the little houses
just so,
and making sure those
tunnels were all straight.
Yeah. Smelling the electricity
burn up that transformer.
Hey, hey.
Did you ever have
one of those
electric cattle cars
where the cows come vibrating
down the chute?
I can move 40 head
in ten minutes, pal.
Go on! Get out of here.
You get out of here!
I could, too.
I got to get rid
of that thing though.
It's taking up lots of space.
I want to sell it.
Yeah, yeah. You'd get
a good price for it, I bet you.
Yeah. It's a collector's item.
Shoot
a little stick?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm the engineer!
Like hell you are!
It's my train!
Hey!
( piano plays )
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always glad
you came
You want to be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You want to be where everybody
knows your name
You want to go
where people know
People are all the same
You want to go where
everybody knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Sam, give me a double.
CARLA:
A little early
for that, huh, Doc?
Well, maybe you're right.
Cancel that double.
Make it a single.
Oh, skip it altogether.
No, on second thought,
you know,
make it a single,
a little extra nip.
Frasier, what's your order?
Cup of coffee.
You got troubles?
Well, I've... I've just been
invited to deliver a paper
at the State Psychiatric
Convention this week,
and I've got a first-class
case of the jitters.
You know, I have a...
a sure-fire way
of keeping
yourself calm.
Picture your
audience naked.
Oh, thank you, Carla,
for that old chestnut
from Speech 101.
Wait a minute.
I got a twist on it.
Picture them naked
and wearing black socks.
Oh, Carla,
that's ridiculous.
I can't see
that that would...
I told you. It works.
Okay, now
try this angle.
( laughing )
Now shut up.
Fine. You know,
I do see your point though.
That could do just the trick.
Thank you, Carla.
Sure. Oh! Here comes
a likely candidate.
Try it out on her.
Hello, Dr. Crane.
Miss Howe.
It doesn't work with everyone.
Miss Howe, I have
a message for you.
Mr. Sheridan is having
lunch up in Melville's,
and he's gonna
be coming down
to talk to you
when he's through.
Oh, great. Sheridan.
Another one of the legions
of presidents, vice presidents
and consultants this
corporation belches forth
every five minutes.
Boy, it seems like
you have to be a real loser
not to be at least
a vice president
in that company,
doesn't it?
I'm sorry.
He is undoubtedly here
to ask me some humiliating,
menial favor
that he couldn't
palm off on some other flunky.
You know,
today I draw the line.
Today, this gal
is going to shoot down
her first
corporate bigwig.
Oh, please.
The first time you try
to stand up to this guy,
you're going to crumble
like a bag of potato chips.
Oh, yeah,
Mr. Smart Guy?
Yeah.
Watch me.
I'm watching you.
Oh, Miss Howe.
Mr. Sheridan.
I'd like
to ask you a favor.
I see.
I'm going to New York
on a business trip
for a few days,
and I'd like you
to take care of my dog
while I'm away.
Well, I'm sorry,
Mr. Sheridan,
but I have plans
for the entire week,
and I could not
possibly break them.
I hope you understand.
That's fine. I realize
this is short notice.
Thanks, anyway.
My plans could be changed.
Please, sir, let...
let me do this for you.
Well, if you don't think
it would be any trouble.
Thank you, Miss Howe.
Oh, no, sir.
Thank you for the opportunity
of knowing your dog.
God, I make myself sick!
( chuckling )
What'll it be, Dr. Crane?
The usual.
( laughing )
What's so funny?
( Woody laughing )
( laughing )
( both laughing )
What's so funny?
It's a private joke, Sam.
SAM:
Hey, there,
Rebecca.
How do you like living
with Sheridan's pooch?
Sir Bronwyn the Gallant
from Fairhaven Manor,
better known
as Buster, is fine.
I, on the other hand,
am a nervous wreck.
What's the matter,
Rebecca?
Well, I knew
I was going to have
to take care
of the dog,
but I didn't know it was going
to be in a place that was huge
and kind of like a mausoleum
and is stuck way out
in the middle of the moors.
There are no moors
in Massachusetts.
I think they had them
flown in or something.
The point is,
this place is big and scary
and I really hate it.
Oh, and to make matters
even worse, last night,
the only thing I could get
on television was this movie
about this young, beautiful,
dark-haired woman,
that was all alone
in this
deserted house.
Hey, what about that scene
where the guy cuts her head off?
Woody, please.
There's no way
her head's gonna come off
in one clean cut like that.
Believe me, I've seen
my uncle butcher hogs,
and you have to hack
and hack and hack.
And when the gardener got it?
Woody, that's enough!
All right. Don't spoil
the ending for everybody else.
Yeah, but when you see it,
take my advice
and turn away when you hear,
vrooom-mm-mm-mm!
Vrooom-mm-mm-mm!
Woody! Woody.
I am just a tiny bit on edge.
Oh. Sorry, Miss Howe.
( whirring )
Stop it, Woody!
Some bar manager,
afraid of a blender.
Let me see here.
Rebecca Howe,
all alone and scared
in a big old house.
Sounds to me
like a job
for Sammy's
Security Company.
We get in
before the burglars do.
That's what I like
about you, Sam.
Your pants are always thinking.
Frasier, darling.
Hello, there, Peanut Butter Cup.
You know, you're late for lunch.
Yes, I know. I'm sorry.
Well, I'm sure you
have a very good excuse.
Well, actually, I do.
I started having lunch
at another restaurant,
then remembered we had a date.
Oh. Well, would you like
to watch me eat?
I wouldn't miss it.
( laughing )
What's so funny?
Oh, it's nothing, really.
It's just this
relaxation exercise
I've been doing.
I've been imagining
people naked and
wearing black socks,
you see, to relieve my
anxiety over my speech.
Frankly, it's
worked miracles.
I've been doing
it all week.
I haven't even
thought about it once.
When do you
present that?
My, God.
( rustling )
Buster, did you hear that?
Calm down.
Probably wasn't anything.
It was probably
just a tree branch
against the window.
Or Leatherface.
Oh, God! Oh, God!
( thumping )
Oh, God, Buster.
He's at the front door.
( Buster whines )
Good dog.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
( screams )
Oh, God!
How in the hell
did you get in here?
Well, you left
the back door open.
I just followed some guy
carrying a meat hook.
That is real
funny, Sam.
You almost gave me
a heart attack.
I'm... I'm sorry.
It's all right. I'm here now.
It wasn't funny. I'm sorry.
Right. I have to admit,
I'm glad you are here.
When the lights went out,
and the storm came,
I started getting
scared to death.
What happened to that $10,000
champion watchdog?
He's hiding
in the kitchen.
Oh, God! I can't
seem to calm down.
My heart's just
beating so fast.
Oh, yes, it is.
Sam, get your hand
away from that.
I was doing pretty good
till the lights went out.
Then this house really started
giving me the creeps.
Oh, well, hey
don't worry.
I've got some
candles here.
You brought your own candles?
Well, yeah. This kind of thing
happens in big, old,
spooky houses a lot.
I like
to be prepared.
Sammy carries
whatever he needs.
Sam, did you come out here
because you were concerned
I was scared,
or did you come out here
to get me in the sack?
Hey, I came out here
because
I was concerned
and scared that
I'd never get
you in the sack.
I'm kidding.
You know, Sam,
I really am glad you're here.
It makes me feel a lot better.
But a man
and a woman
can be together
in an evening
without ending up
rolling on the floor.
Well, I know that's
true of some people,
but, sweetheart,
we're good-looking.
Sam...
What?
Sit down here a minute.
I want to tell
you something.
Okay.
Now, believe
this or not--
even good-looking people
can spend an evening together
without having sex.
Have you ever heard
of conversation?
Yeah, I've heard of
conversation.
You know,
contrary to what
a lot of people think,
I'm not that dumb.
Here, come on. Try me.
Sit down. Let's conversate.
Okay, so what do you
want to talk about?
Sex.
You know,
sex is obviously
the only thing
on your mind, so forget it.
I'm going to bed.
Oh, that's
good with me.
I am going
to bed alone.
If you want
to stay here,
you sleep
on the couch.
Oh, come on.
I can sleep on a couch
at my place.
Fine. Go sleep
on your couch.
All right.
If that's
what you want.
I'll leave you
all alone
in this big,
old scary house.
Hoo!
I'm moving the table.
Don't pull a muscle.
I'm serious.
I'm moving the chair.
You're breaking my heart.
I got my hand on the doorknob.
I'm opening the door.
Sam, don't!
I knew it. Pajama time!
Not you! The dog!
What?
Buster!? Buster!?
Whoo! Boy, can
that sucker haul.
He's gone!
Well, hey, don't
worry about it.
He's a hearty breed.
Speaking of breeding...
Are you crazy?
There's a champion dog,
and I'm responsible for him.
If it takes me all night,
I'm going to find that mutt.
No. Don't.
Buster!?
Oh, hell.
Oh!
Might as well turn
the electricity back on.
So, please, i-if you find him,
you've got this number.
Okay, thank you. Bye-bye.
( doorbell rings )
Please, please, please,
let it be somebody
that found him.
Did anybody find the dog?
Listen, little lady,
we're not looking
for Aunt Fannie's
amethyst pendant here.
This is a highly
organized search party.
We're gonna conduct
this debriefing
by the numbers.
All right.
Alpha Sector report.
Negative.
Bravo Sector?
Charlie Sector?
Shut up, Cliff.
( phone rings )
Hello?
Yes, Mr. Sheridan.
Wow, you know, Norm,
I-I can't get over this place.
I think I'll do something
like this with my living room.
What are you
talking about?
You live in
28 square feet
and your bed folds
out of a couch.
You're gonna what?
Wha... All right, sir. Bye-bye.
Oh, God, he came home early.
He's on his way home
from the airport!
All right, men,
I suggest we fall back
to our original positions.
What are you talking about?
To the bar!
Back to the bar!
Yes, sir! Right away, sir!
( voice breaking ):
Well, I guess I deserve this.
I'm always doing stupid favors
for everybody.
( crying ):
I guess it finally caught up
with me.
No, no, don't do that, please.
I hate it when you cry.
( sobbing )
All right, all right,
all right.
Look, wait, wait,
wait, come on.
I'll tell Sheridan it was
all my fault, all right?
Fine.
Wait up, guys!
That's great.
Really nice.
Oh, God!
What is it?
A car.
It's Sheridan; we're doomed.
( doorbell rings )
( sighs )
Uh...
Woody! You found him!
Ah.
Oh, God, I don't know
who to kiss first!
Well, I just had
a breath mint.
Buster!
Hey, man, way to go.
Where'd you find him?
Oh, at an auto wrecking yard.
What were you doing there?
Just browsing.
Oh, Buster, Buster,
good old Buster.
Oh, no, that's not Buster,
that's Satan.
What?
SAM:
Who?
I was brushing the snow
off of the hubcaps,
and I saw Satan here chewing
through a tire, and I thought
you know, he looks just like
that picture of Buster.
So I borrowed him, in case
we don't find the other dog.
Woody, take him
to the kitchen.
I only hope we can fool Sheridan
with this flea bag.
He's no flea bag,
Miss Howe.
He's a trained attack dog.
Come on, sweetheart.
( phone rings )
An attack dog?
He brings an attack dog
into this house?
Come on, his heart's
in the right place.
Hello?
Oh, God, you found him?
Hm?
Oh, that's wonderful.
Yeah. Give me your address.
Uh-huh.
Okay, I'll come
and get him right now.
A neighbor at the end
of the road found him.
Here's the address.
You go get him.
I'm on my way.
Woody?
Bring Satan out here, please.
Woody, we found Buster.
You can take Satan back
to the junkyard.
But, Miss Howe, he hasn't
finished his snack yet.
I gave him something
out of the refrigerator.
Well, actually, he opened
the door and took it, but
I got out of the way.
Woody, whatever.
J-Just take him out of here.
Go, go, hurry.
Hurry, hurry,
hurry.
Sheridan's here.
He just drove up.
Woody, cancel that. Sam...
Yeah?
Uh, y-you go around the
back way and get Buster.
All right?
Woody, you take Satan
into the kitchen
and get him some kibble.
We hope that Sam gets back
in time with Buster, so
we don't have to use him,
but if he doesn't get back
in time with Buster,
then we have to convince
Sheridan that Satan is Buster,
until Sam gets back
and we can switch
Buster for Satan.
Or I could just put
steak sauce on my throat
and let Satan chow down.
Uh, I understand everything
perfectly, Miss Howe.
Come on, Sam,
let's get your kibble.
( both laughing )
I was just kidding, Miss Howe.
I'm back.
Where's my big boy?
Where's my Buster?
What, no hello?
No description of the trip?
No slides?
I finished early so I
caught a late flight.
( whistles ):
Here, boy!
Where are you, boy?
Here, Buster!
He is, um...
He's sleeping in the kitchen.
That's right.
Miss Howe, who's this man?
This man?
He's Woody.
He's my boyfriend.
Wow, Miss Howe.
Your boyfriend calls you
Miss Howe?
I was his teacher.
I got real lonely,
a-and I thought I'd call
him over here for company.
I hope you don't mind.
No, of course not.
Now, listen, I'm very tired.
I just want to say hi to my dog
and then go to bed.
So if you don't mind.
You want us to leave?
He wants us to leave, Woody.
Great! How about a
burger and a movie?
Then we can go
someplace and park.
Later!
First, I'd like
to stand here and
have a little chat
with Mr. Sheridan
about his trip.
Not now.
I want to see Buster.
No, Mr. Sheridan!
Yes, Miss Howe.
Come on, Buster, let's wrestle!
Woody, we can't
let him do this.
Well, don't worry, Miss Howe.
He won't attack unless he hears
the command word, "Cochise."
Cochise? Well, he's
never gonna say that.
Or unless he provokes him.
( vicious growling )
SHERIDAN:
Take that, big boy.
I got your tail now,
I got your tail!
Hey, it worked--
he thinks that's his dog.
Yeah, right. If he
lives, we fooled him.
Sammy to the rescue!
Sam, get that mutt
out of here!
What?
Sheridan's in the kitchen
with Satan!
This is no time
for folk singing.
Oh, oh, oh! Well...
what are we gonna do?
All right, go out the front,
sneak around the back.
I'll try to divert
Sheridan's attention
while you make the switch.
But remember, they
look exactly alike.
All right, all right.
Come on, boy,
come on.
Boy, Buster's frisky.
( chuckles )
I was playing "get my thumb,"
and he was practically bouncing
off the ceiling.
Well, I bet he
was just so glad
to have you back.
Yeah. Well,
I'm gonna
feed him now, Miss Howe.
No, I already fed him.
We ordered out.
Chinese.
( dogs growling, barking )
That sounds like two dogs
in there.
Mr. Sheridan,
there's something that
I've been wanting to ask you.
Is this a bowling trophy?
No, it's my late wife's ashes.
She was a good-sized woman.
Excuse me,
I want to see to Buster.
Mission accomplished.
I made the switch.
Satan's in the car.
Oh...
Well, there was only Buster
in there.
Good! Well,
I'll be going.
Bye-bye!
Good night.
Miss Howe!
Who's that man?
Uh, I'm her boyfriend.
That's right.
He's my boyfriend.
Miss Howe, we
have to talk.
Look at him.
You're not so tough
when you're not
running around loose, are ya?
( Cliff chuckles )
( blabbering )
I wouldn't do that
if I were you, Cliff.
If you look very closely,
you'll see he has
several tiny little mailbags
notched on his leash.
Yeah. Yeah, oh, yeah,
I'm real scared, Norm.
( chuckles ):
Look at me shake.
( blabbering )
Woody,
I thought you were gonna return
the hound from hell.
Oh, the guy's coming
for him tomorrow.
Unless, of course, you'd
like to reconsider
and keep him as our mascot.
That's exactly
what this bar needs:
a loaded weapon that goes off
when you say the word,
C-O-C-H-I-S-E.
Great! Spelled it right.
Greetings, all.
SAM:
Hey, Doc.
Oh, there's a sturdy fellow.
Hello, boy.
What's this?
"Don't say 'Cochise'
to this dog."
Woody, he didn't attack.
No, he didn't.
Maybe he didn't hear
the attack word.
Frasier?
Cochise!
Cochise. Cochise, Cochise.
REBECCA:
This is Buster!
I thought you were gonna
make the switch!
Well, I did, but they were
tearing at each other,
and it got confusing.
I was trying to separate them
and protect my goodies
at the same time.
Hey, if this isn't
Satan, then Satan is...
Chewing the spleen
out of Mr. Sheridan.
All right, Sam,
hand me the phone.
Woody, come around here
and untie Buster.
I've got to call Mr. Sheridan
and warn him.
We've got to make
another switch.
Hello. This is Rebecca Howe.
Yes, I need to speak
to Mr. Sheridan, please.
I don't care
if he's asleep!
Wake him up, this
is an emergency.
Well, all right, would you
please just go upstairs
and tell the man not to say the
word "Cochise" around his dog.
Well, wait-- I just remembered
the attack word isn't "Cochise,"
it's that other Indian name.
( laughs ):
Woody, what other
Indian name?
There are a million other
Indian names, my friend.
There's, uh, Crazy Horse,
Sitting Bull,
Pocahontas, Geronimo.
( vicious barking )
( yells )
WOODY:
That's it!
CLIFF:
Go away! Go away!
Hey, he's got Mr. Clavin
trapped in the men's room.
That's okay-- we can use
the one up at Melville's.
Oh, hey, hey, it's okay,
I got the, uh...
I got the number of that guy
from the auto wrecking yard.
I can call him and get
the counter-command.
I'll do it.
Oh, hello, Mr. Sheridan.
Sorry, I have
the wrong number.
Hello?
Hi. I'm calling for Woody.
We need the counter-command
for Satan.
CLIFF:
Get out of here,
you beast from hell!
( vicious growling )
Okay, thanks.
Did you get it?
Yeah.
Well, what is it?
( Cliff groaning in pain )
Good night, everyone!
( vicious barking )
Satan!
Good night, everyone!
( barking continues )
It doesn't work.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org