Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(car horn toots)
(theme song begins)
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always
glad you came ¶
¶ You wanna be
where you can see ¶
¶ The troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name. ¶
All right, okay,
here's one.
Hayley Mills, playing
herself and her twin sister
in The Parent Trap.
All right, all right.
Um, how
about Elizabeth Montgomery
as both Serena and Samantha
in Bewitched?
Ooh! Very nice!
Yeah. Yeah.
All right.
Cliffy?
Well, uh, Norm, I'd have to say
the, uh, queen of the genre,
Patty Duke, as both Patty and,
uh, the minuet-lovin' Cathy.
FRASIER:
Oh!
What's the topic du jour?
Actresses who have played
their own look-alikes
through the use
of trick photography?
No. Fictional twins
we'd like to see
making out
with each other.
WOODY:
Hey, Sam,
the new Boston
Merchants coupon
book is out,
and I got us in it.
Oh damn it, Woody!
I hate that thing!
Well, maybe you don't
understand how it works.
Yeah, I do.
Guy comes in,
gives you a coupon.
You give him a free drink,
he leaves,
you never see him again.
Well, then
you do understand.
Woody...
Well, what, Sam?
You think it
was a bad idea?
You think I shouldn't
have done it?
You think I'm a stupid
idiot, right?
No, no, that's... Yes!
Well, I...
I'm sorry, Sam.
I just thought it
would attract
new customers
to the bar.
Yeah, a-a bunch of
deadbeats and freeloaders.
NORM:
Yeah.
You don't want people
like that in here.
Another beer,
please, Wood.
Sam, that was John Allen Hill
on the phone.
He's on his way down.
SAM:
No, no.
I don't want to talk to him.
I hate that guy.
Sam, be a good businessman.
He's our upstairs neighbor.
We have to
live together.
Just try to be
civil to him.
All right, all right, all right,
I'll be good. I'll be good.
You know, I get the feeling
sometimes
he deliberately says things
just 'cause
he knows it's gonna
get under my skin.
Sam!
See? God...
Sam, it appears
we have a problem.
Do you know what this is?
Yeah. Yeah, it looks
like a manicure.
Nice one, too.
Wait. Is that a...
Is that clear polish,
or are they just buffed?
They're just clean.
Sam, I'm concerned.
Are you aware that your bar
is featured in this coupon book?
Yeah, I am.
Well, my concern
is how this will
affect Melville's.
I'm not anxious
to greet the type of person
you're obviously
hoping to attract.
What are you saying?
You saying that
you're better than me?
That your customers are
classier than mine?
Well, they're not.
NORM:
Hey, Sammy?
Will you settle a
bet for us, please?
Which one of our breaths
smells most like tuna?
Loser has to go through
the spanking machine.
What do you want me to
do, walk over and check?
I can tell you from here.
Oh, yeah,
right, right.
And none of your customers
have fish breath
when they come walking
out of your restaurant?
It's a seafood
restaurant, Sam.
Ah, all right, so
you admit it, right?
(grunting)
Well, looks like
the big boy lost.
Hi, guys.
Hey, Carla, I got
a message for you.
Your brother called.
Something about
a family meeting.
Oh, yeah?
There!
Uh, here's
your message.
That was my paycheck.
Carla, what's the problem?
Why are you so upset?
Oh, I hate family meetings.
They're nothing but a bunch
of complaining and infighting
and bickering and backstabbing.
And, of course,
sweet little Carla has
to play the peacemaker.
FRASIER:
Well,
I, for one, think
family meetings
can be worthwhile
encounters.
They encourage open
and honest communication
among the generations.
Did you have them
in your family
there, Fras?
No, I lucked out.
My family didn't want
to be close.
If you're lying to me, I'm gonna
rip out your slimy, gray tongue.
Whoa.
Sounds kind
of serious.
It's my mother.
Well, what's the matter
with her?
She had the dream.
What dream's that?
The death dream.
Whenever someone in
my family has it,
you can just start
divvying up the jewelry.
REBECCA:
What exactly
is this... death dream?
FRASIER:
Yes,
and, uh, why exactly
do you always do this...
when you say,
"the death dream?"
You just did it.
Carry on.
Well, the dream
is always the same.
There's a casket on a slab
in an empty room.
You walk slowly toward it.
Suddenly, the
lid flies open.
You see your
own face?
No, you see these feet,
'cause you're looking
at the wrong end.
Then, you look upward,
and there's your own face,
pale and bluish
with pennies over your eyes.
And that's when you bolt up
in bed screaming.
FRASIER:
Carla,
death is an earthly
scientific passage
predicted by either massive
physical injury
or progressive
bodily deterioration.
There is as little validity
in a supposed death dream
as there
is in the...
clichéd image of death itself
as a grim, bloodless ghoul
whose bony finger reaches out
to tap you on the shoulder
when your number's up.
Frasier, it's time
to go.
(screams)
Don't do that, woman!
For God's sakes,
put on some blush or...
SAM:
Honey,
it's kind of slow.
Why-Why don't you
take the day off,
go see your mom, huh?
Might I remind
you, Sam--
my mother and I
don't exactly get along.
You don't get along
with anybody.
Yeah, well, this is
different, and shut up!
The last time I saw my mother,
we had this terrible fight
about this stupid
family thing,
and I swore I
would never set foot
in her lousy place again
unless someone dragged me there
kicking and screaming.
So, that's it, huh?
You're damned right.
(clicks tongue)
Drag me, Sammy.
Really?
Do it. Drag me.
No! No! Cut it out!
I don't want to go!
No! No! I never want to see
that shriveled old bag again!
No! Put me down!
I don't
want to go!
Oh, Carla, Carla!
Oh, nobody would
believe you would come!
Oh, your sister
is in there with
your mother now,
and you go
next, yes?
Oh, she will be so
happy to see you.
Carla!
(laughs)
Sam, you remember Zia,
the hugger.
Yeah.
Oh, Sam!
Oh!
MAN:
You guys
want a beer?
This is kind of
a solemn occasion, Sal.
Malt liquor?
I'll pass.
So, Zia, how's Mom?
Carla, what kind
of question is that?
She had the dream.
So, she's really sick, huh?
No. She doesn't
have to be sick.
She had the dream.
Oh...
She'll be
dead soon.
Have you had lunch?
Uh, actually, yeah, I did.
Oh, then this
is dinner.
Oh, hey, thanks, Zia.
Eat up, Sam.
Our family believes in,
life is for the living.
(laughs)
Soon enough,
we'll all be dead,
rotting in the ground,
with a mouth full of worms.
Great linguini.
Thank you, Zia.
Oh, Carla,
your sister's finished.
Bitch.
Slut.
Oh, it's nice
to see them talking.
Mama.
Angeline?
No, Mama.
It's Carla.
Oh.
My purse is
on the dresser.
Mama, I didn't come here
for your money.
I came because
I feel bad
things got so ugly between us
the last time I was here.
So, you've come to
say you're sorry.
Well, I'm sorry we fought.
Then you're sorry.
I accept your apology.
Good. I accept
your apology, too.
I didn't say
I was sorry.
Well, then,
I'm not sorry, either.
Too late. I already
accepted your apology.
Damn!
So, here...
now that we've made peace,
I want you to have the ring
that my mother gave to me,
and her mother
gave to her.
Oh, Mama. The ring.
What's this?
I hocked it.
Come.
Oh, your father's hair.
Sorry, Mom.
And now, Carla,
there is something
you must do for me.
Oh, Mama, I know what
you're gonna ask me.
We're just gonna get
into that same fight
we had the last
time I was here.
I... It... It's just
too much to ask.
I can't do it.
It's the family tradition.
No.
I did it.
My mother did it.
Her mother did it.
Her mother did it
before her.
I said no.
I don't care
who did it.
Her mother did it.
Mama, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry you had the dream.
I'm sorry you're gonna die.
I'm sorry the family tradition
is gonna die with you.
But that is just
the way it is.
I can't do this for anybody,
not even for my mama.
Her mother did it.
Oh...
What's the matter, honey?
Oh, Sammy, Sammy.
It's this stupid
family tradition.
Since the beginning of time,
every woman in our family...
who has children...
...has named
one of her sons
with the first name
of her father
and the maiden name
of her mother.
And I just wouldn't do it.
I don't mean to take
your mother's side here,
but what's
the big deal?
It's just a name.
Oh, yeah, sure,
just a name.
Why, uh, what was your
father's first name?
Benito.
And your mother's
maiden name?
Mussolini.
Yikes.
Could I have some
more sauce, please?
(Mama moaning)
ZIA (gasps):
The death walk.
She's still here.
I feel her presence
like a shiv in my heart.
Mama.
I'm not rejecting you.
I just don't want to name
one of my sons Benito Mussolini.
Why not?
Because, back a few years,
there was another
Benito Mussolini.
Remember him?
I don't see why one
Fascist dictator
should ruin it for
the entire family.
Mama, you are the only one
who even cares
about that stupid name.
Everybody else agrees
with me, right?
Oh, you're
an ungrateful child.
You make me sick.
Bitch.
Okay.
Well, just forget all of you.
I hate this family.
I hate this house.
I just never want
to come back here again.
I swear it.
I swear it a million times.
I swear on my children's eyes,
I am never, ever, ever
setting foot in this stupid,
ugly, stinkin' rattrap again.
Well, there goes my ride.
How can her mother expect her
to name one of her kids
after Benito Mussolini?
Well, it could
have been worse.
What if her father's name
had been Adolf?
Yeah.
Yeah, and her mother's
maiden name
could have been Menjou.
Phew.
She really dodged
the bullet there.
Anyway, I gave her the day off
so she could just go home
and cool out, you know.
Well, very often
that's the best thing
you can do
when you're not getting along
with a family member.
Remove yourself
entirely from them.
Find some neutral place
where you can take the time
you need to be away from them.
You really
think so, Fras?
Well, that's...
that's why we're
all here, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
Great.
Four more freebies,
thanks to Woody's
stupid coupon book.
I'm sorry, Woody.
I didn't see you there.
Of course I'm there.
I'm always there.
Wherever there's
a stupid idea,
that's where
you'll find me.
Stupid old Woody Boyd--
father of stupid thoughts,
eye of the stupid storm.
I've got to be the stupidest guy
on the face of the Earth.
Woody, please
don't say that.
Why not?
Because you are giving
me a stupid headache.
Welcome to my private hell.
Hi, Sam.
How are you doing, honey?
Better.
I went home,
went to my bedroom,
shut off all the lights
and laid down on my bed.
Then... I started thinking.
What if I was dying
and Serafina refused to do
the one thing
that meant the most to me.
How would I feel?
So you apologized
to your mother?
No. I went out and
yelled at Serafina.
I felt a lot better.
So I went and yelled
at all the rest of the kids.
Then I started thinking,
why should I be
having all this fun
when my mom's dying?
So I decided I had to try
to do something for her.
Well, I've got a bunch
of these coupon books left.
They're only good
for a month,
but I guess in her case,
that doesn't matter.
Anyway, all the
kids were there,
so I figured it wouldn't
hurt to ask them
if anyone would fulfill their
grandmother's dying wish
and change their name
to Benito Mussolini.
Any takers?
No.
But I got two Madonnas
and an MC Hammer.
Well,
that's that.
I tried everything I can.
She didn't try
the coupons.
Sam?
God, I hate it
when he says that.
What? What? What're you gonna
nitpick this time?
What, am I mixing my drinks
too loud?
Am I using the wrong kind
of lightbulb?
Oh, excuse me, maybe
some of my bar air
accidentally wafted up
to your establishment.
Sam, you're on
the defensive.
I'm not on the defensive,
and you say that again,
I'm gonna pull the last
three hairs off your head.
Sam, I merely came down
to apologize
for my intrusive
behavior earlier today.
Really?
Yes.
I know I'd be resentful
if someone implied
that I should run my business
in a particular way.
It was out of line
for me to do so with you.
Oh.
Well... thank you.
I'm sorry, I am
a little defensive.
Well, no harm done.
In fact, to clear the air,
I'd like to buy a round
of drinks for everyone here.
(cheering)
Here you are, Sam.
I think this should cover it.
Oh, and I'd like
one of your special martinis
I've heard so much about.
Oh, I'm out of coupons.
Well, then, never mind.
Hey, Ma.
Gino, what are you doing here?
Well, Ma, I was thinking about
all that stuff you said,
you know about-about
making Grandma happy,
and I was talking it over
with MC and the Madonnas,
and I figured, heck,
if it'll keep
this family together,
someone's gotta do it.
Ma, I'll be Benito Mussolini.
Look, Gino,
do you even have any
idea who Mussolini was?
Well, no, I didn't before,
but then Anthony told me
all about him.
Ma, this guy
ran this whole country.
And do you know
what they called him?
They called him Il Duce.
Huh? The Dooch.
Hey, yeah, that's right.
It's me-- Dooch Tortelli.
That is a horrible name,
and I never want
to hear it again.
It sounds awful.
(phone ringing)
I hate that name,
and I hate Mama
for asking me
to give it to you.
Okay.
Carla, that was your brother.
He said to get over there
right away.
Your mother's going fast.
No.
I swore I'd never go back
in that house again.
I have my pride.
Okay.
Gino, want to grab her feet--
I'll get the rest of her.
Come here, come here,
come on, come on, come on.
No! No! Put me down!
Put me down!
I don't want to go!
Would you hoist me
a little higher, guys?
I'd like to have some butt left
when I get there.
Oh, no.
I'm too late.
Oh, Mama.
Oh, Mama, I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
I hope you can hear me.
I hope you can rest now.
I swear
on your memory,
that my Gino is now named
Benito Mussolini.
Well, it's about time.
I was getting bedsores.
You're not dead.
You're not dead at all.
You were never dying.
You just did
this to trick me.
And you were
all in on it.
We listen to our mother.
And we thought
it would be funny.
GINO:
Ma! No, Ma!
You, you never even
had the dream.
You just did this
to trick me
into getting to name
my kid that stupid name.
I had to.
You're stubborn as your
grandmother's mule,
who, incidentally,
you were named after.
I honor tradition.
Yeah, well, I'm gonna
give you something to honor
right in the labonz!
Ladies, ladies, please, please.
Please.
Stay out of this,
if you know what's
good for you, Paddy.
Listen,
I may be old,
but I can still instruct
others to hurt you.
Benito,
kick your mother
in the teeth for me.
Okay, Grandma.
Don't you order...
Don't you order my son around.
Gino, go punch your
grandma in the kidneys.
Okay, Ma.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
You, you're big,
throw Carla out the window.
No, I'm not gonna throw
her out the window.
All right.
I'll do it, sick as I am.
Please, please, I...
Mrs. Lozupone, I don't mean
to be disrespectful here,
but, you know,
you're not being fair.
You're asking
your daughter here
to-to name her son
after a very bad man.
And-and you faked death
to get her to do it.
I mean, these are
not your, uh...
typical mother things.
Are you saying I'm a bad mother?
Well, yeah, in this
case, yeah, I am.
(all gasping)
CARLA:
Sam.
What?
You insulted my mother.
In her own house.
With the food that we
cooked over her deathbed
still stuck
in your teeth.
Is that bad?
(all hissing)
(hissing continues)
That's great, Carla.
I'm glad
you guys made up.
Well, his name
is now Benito Mussolini.
Call him Gino, for short.
Yeah, she sounds
so happy.
She said that's the first time
they've all sat down
to a family dinner in years.
They ate, they laughed,
they even
got up and danced.
Those Italian families
sound so warm.
Yeah, I know
what you mean, Woody.
Gee, I often wish that I was
a member of an ethnic group.
Oh, it's...
Oh, it's just as well.
I hate hugging.
Frasier, it's time to go.
Boy, I-I sure married
the right woman.
Good-bye, Mama.
I love you.
Mmm.
See you next week.
Oh, wait a minute,
I almost forgot something.
Good night, Sammy.
(muffled):
Carla, please let
me out. Please.
Sammy, would you
stop whining?
It's a family tradition.
You cross Mama,
you sleep in the wall.
(muffled shouting)
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org