Coach, how about a beer?
Sam says I can't serve you.
You're a flimflam.
It ain't for me, it's for a friend.
He asked me to order it for him.
He did.
He wrote it down. "One beer."
Wait one minute, Harry.
Let me see that.
"One beer." Just had to make sure.
That'll be one buck.
I thought I had a dollar.
I got a ten. You got change?
Absolutely.
Here you go.
I have a buck after all. I don't
need change. Give me my ten back.
Right.
Here you go.
I don't want to carry all these
bills. Give me a 20 for the lot.
You got it.
Nobody move!
Coach, don't you see
he's short-changing you?
No. He's outsmarted me before,
but not this time.
How much are you giving him?
- 20 bucks.
- How much is he giving you?
Darn you, Harry!
Sam, I'm just trying
to keep in practice.
I'll give you a $30 bill,
and we're even.
What do you think?
- No such thing as a $30 bill.
- Wanna bet?
Get out of my bar!
You owe me $10! Is this a clip joint?
I'm sorry. Here.
You got the wrong idea about me.
I don't. You got ten seconds
to get out. Give me back my watch!
I'm trying to help you guys out.
If you wanna upgrade...
Out!
- Afternoon.
- Hey, Norm!
Gimme a beer, will you?
- How's life treating you?
- Like I just ran over its dog.
You're late. How come?
Vera dragged me to the mortuary
to arrange our funeral.
Thinking of dying, Norm?
No date circled yet,
but... Vera likes to plan ahead.
We're gonna get cremated.
What'll you do with the ashes?
I wanted to throw them
in her mother's face,
but I think we'll scatter them
on the Adirondacks.
- Hello, everyone!
- Hi, Diane!
Sorry I'm late, but you'll be
delighted when you hear why.
We were delighted you were late!
I had a fabulous discussion
with my art history professor.
I now feel I have
a full grasp of lmpressionism.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Do Kirk Douglas!
Sam, I'm sorry I was late.
Can I do anything
to make it up to you?
Yeah... but you wouldn't.
Cheers. Yeah.
Coach, your friend Walt.
Walt?
It's good to hear from you!
I'm so glad the operation's over.
I didn't tell you beforehand, but I
didn't think your chances were good.
It's tomorrow?
Don't worry, you'll fly through it.
It's a piece of cake.
Hello, everybody.
The famous sportscaster!
- Hi, Coach!
- Right on, man!
We watch you on the news every night.
Best sports report in town.
What do we have here? Hi.
Dave Richards,
an old team-mate of Sam's.
Diane Chambers.
I'm Sam's new waitress.
Sam have his brand on you yet?
Hardly.
Then it's your lucky day.
I'm incredibly good-looking,
incredibly rich and incredibly nice.
And incredibly married!
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- You are?
Yes. I'd hoped to reject you
based solely on your personality.
Too skinny.
Can I have Coach buy you a beer?
- No, I'm here on business.
- I noticed.
How would you like to be
my interview on the news tonight?
That's terrific!
Interview me?
I haven't been in baseball for years.
I understand. You're the best
reliever the Red Sox ever had.
You're still a big name in this town.
- We can do it here in the bar.
- You can't ask for more than that.
And besides, you owe me a favour.
- I do?
- Yeah.
That night in Chicago in 1 973,
with those two young...
...dollars I borrowed? Yeah.
Two young dollars?
Yeah, I hate it
when they're wrinkled.
I'm out of practice.
It's years since I did an interview.
Come on, Sam. It's good advertising.
It would help business.
Right. And we can all be on TV.
I'd like to see myself on TV.
No, you wouldn't. Trust me.
Trust me on that.
Come on. I haven't got all day.
Yeah, come on!
Everybody here
wants you to do the interview.
Almost everybody.
What do you mean?
Never mind.
Excuse me. Diane,
can I talk to you in the back room?
- Certainly.
- Thank you.
I'll be right back.
I have to discipline an employee.
- Can I watch?
- No!
OK, what's the problem?
Why do you think I have a problem?
You've got that "Sam's a chowderhead
and wouldn't understand
if I drew him a picture" look.
I do get that sometimes.
Sam, you're an ex-jockstrap...
Ex-jock.
That's ex-jock!
How many times I gotta tell you that?
What is the origin of the word jock?
I... From the French. Jacques.
Those "Where are they now?"
interviews on TV are depressing.
Any time you put a "former"
in front of a name,
even the most attractive,
bright guy...
Excuse me. Attractive?
Yeah. Even then...
I didn't know
you thought I was attractive.
Well, when the light
strikes you in a certain way,
and your hair's combed just right,
and I'm standing back a ways,
you're sometimes
somewhat unrepugnant.
Yeah, that's what women call me.
Tall, dark and unrepugnant!
The point I'm labouring to make here
is that when I see an old athlete
reliving his glory days on TV,
I can't help but feel sorry for him.
- I don't want to feel sorry for you.
- Feel sorry for me?
I resent that.
You don't have to feel sorry for me.
You know
who you should feel sorry for?
You should feel sorry
for the Flintstones!
I beg your pardon?
They're opposite
the six o'clock news,
and when people find out
Mayday Malone is on,
Bedrock is gonna be
a very lonely little town!
Martina Navra... No.
Martina Denavramammajamma... No.
Dave, let's do it!
Great. Give me 20 minutes.
I'll bring the crew right back.
You got it. It'll give me time
to slip into my shawl and blanket!
- Dave, this is a really good idea.
- Yeah, it's pretty good, isn't it?
About time you got around to Mayday.
I'm really excited
that he agreed to do the interview.
John McEnroe cancelled out on me.
So Sam was your second choice?
No. Gerry Cheever's
out of town with his horses.
- Third?
- ML Carr has laryngitis.
Fourth?
Jim Rice is out of town,
Robert Parish was last week.
And Becky Bannerman, the high
school gymnast, is on a field trip.
But Sam was the first retired guy
you thought of?
No. Well...
I said, Sam was the first
retired guy you thought of!
- The very first.
- He's honoured.
The Celtics got going pretty good,
eh?
I'm sorry. I wasn't listening.
I'm practising
my floating coin trick.
Pardon me?
Just a little something I do.
So it's a rigged-up coin?
No, it's just a half-dollar. Look.
It's a trick, right?
Strings, wires and stuff?
No wires, no strings.
I take the coin.
I hold it in the air,
about like that.
I let go of it real careful,
and it just stays there, it floats.
It hangs there.
What am I, a goof?
There's no way you can do it!
You got five bucks if I can't do it?
Ten! Ten bucks.
Wait. Am I being hustled?
You are gonna give me ten bucks
if I cannot do it?
You're onsville, pal! Come on.
- I couldn't do it!
- No, you couldn't!
- What happened?
- I'll tell you.
You just got stuck with ten bucks.
- Coach! Who is this clown?
- Which clown?
Harry, please!
Harry.
Sam, I'm going. I was just playing.
But whoever owns a Honda,
thanks for the lift!
Did he take you for anything, Norm?
Sorry? I was practising
suspending this coin in mid-air.
Here.
Carla, I'm fine!
He's gonna ask you what's
your greatest memory in baseball.
it's gotta be that double header
against the Orioles in '72.
He saved both games
with seven pitches.
Seven pitches.
Wait a minute.
You wanna talk about excitement?
Sam, tell 'em
about opening day in New York.
You come out of the bullpen.
Bobby Mercer's at the plate.
He hit a 400ft home run off me!
It was the most exciting thing
I ever saw!
Why would Sam wanna talk about
something bad happening to him?
You're right.
Sometimes I think
of the smartest thing to say,
and then it comes out so stupid.
That doesn't make sense.
You should have heard it
before I said it!
- Everybody ready?
- Yeah!
- Well, Mayday, knock 'em dead.
- Thanks.
- You ready, Sammy?
- Yeah. I am.
Dave, listen. I'd like
to do this, if you don't mind.
Yeah.
We can talk
about my greatest thrill in sport,
then I wanna talk
about my triumph over alcoholism.
Good. Very good.
It could be very powerful.
Then we could talk about Cheers,
what I'm doing now.
And we could talk about what I'd do
about the crisis in the Mideast.
Yeah. The Cubs got that
by three and a half games.
Should be a stimulating evening!
Ready.
A little bit more to the left, guys.
- Roll tape.
- Rolling.
Action!
l'm standing here in a popular
Boston watering hole called Cheers.
What's wrong with his voice?
Come on, Diane, this is television!
Cut the tape, Ernie.
- Come on, Sam!
- I'm sorry.
- I gotta start over now!
- You'll be alright.
Gee whizz.
- Roll it, Ernie.
- Rolling.
I'm standing in a popular
watering hole called Cheers.
Most of you will recognise
the guy standing next to me.
Maybe you don't
when he's not in his Red Sox uniform.
This is Sam "Mayday" Malone,
ex-relief pitcher
from the Boston Red Sox,
now owner and bartender at Cheers.
- How you doing, Sam?
- I'm alright, Dave, thanks.
That's great.
You've been out of baseball
for five years. Do you miss it?
I miss the fans. The people
of Boston were very good to me.
Yeah.
Tell us about some of
the great moments you had here.
I guess I'd have to say
one day in Baltimore.
You wanna tell us
a little bit about that, Sam?
Well, I was working both ends
of a double header.
It's the old story.
First game, bottom of the ninth.
I'm coming in
with a man on second and third.
We're holding on to a one-run lead
against the Birds.
Boog Powell's coming up.
I could feel the wind
from his warm-up swings.
He had the heaviest bat in
the League. Papers were full of him.
I figure the only way to get him is
to challenge him on the first pitch.
If I get cute, he'll kill me.
So I decide I'm gonna make him
wait on me, make him sweat.
I adjust my cap, go down to
the rosin bag, walk around the mound.
When I figure he's getting antsy...
Dave, John McEnroe called. Said he's
got something to get off his chest.
McEnroe.
Dave, what...
Sam, thank you. I'll catch you later.
- What happened?
- I guess he got a better interview.
No. What happened to the Boog person?
He grounded to third.
- Coach, let's serve some drinks.
- Right, Sam.
Tennis is a sissy game.
- Come on. We got thirsty people.
- Damn shame, Sammy.
No sweat.
I'm gonna be in back, cleaning up.
- That's our job, Sam.
- It's my bar, Carla!
Carla, will you watch my customers
while I'm gone, please?
Sure. I'll act geeky,
give 'em the wrong drinks.
- They'll never know you're gone.
- Thanks.
Sam, this could be
a crucial moment in your life.
It's vitally important
you handle your emotions properly.
The worst thing anyone
in a situation like this could do
is to repress his feelings.
Diane, get out, please.
You need to lash out.
To release yourself. Scream.
- Get out!
- Wonderful! Alright.
We need now to move away from brute
emotions into the more cerebral.
Tell me in one sentence what you
perceive to be your problem now.
You won't leave.
Let's come back to that.
Other people have been through
what you're feeling.
Even, in a slightly different way,
myself.
Would you like me to share
an experience from my life
when I was defeated and humiliated?
Diane, I don't wanna hear
a lead in a high school play story.
It's not a lead
in the high school play story.
I don't wanna hear an "I didn't
get asked to the junior prom" story.
It's not an "I didn't get asked
to the junior prom" story.
I sure don't wanna hear an "I didn't
get elected cheerleader" story.
OK, if you're just gonna
make a big joke about it...
I hit it, didn't l?
Sam, I was terrific!
What happened to me today
put a period at the end of my career.
The last thing I need
is a cheerleader right now.
Well, that's what you need the most!
You know, I was looking at you
at that interview today.
I didn't see
a washed-up ex-former has-been.
No, I saw a guy who has a great deal
to look back on with pride.
And a great deal
to look forward to with hope.
Yeah?
It didn't hurt that you
were standing next to a Cro-Magnon.
Sam, here's the point.
You have to put the past behind you.
You have to turn and face the future.
You have to open your eyes,
see what's in front of you.
You're young, you're alive.
Feel that in your whole body.
Appreciate what you've got.
Live for today. Go for it, Sam!
I tell you, go for it!
Are you OK?
Yeah... I'm fine.
Look. One of my lights is out!
It's a reflex I learned in a class.
Practical Feminism.
What was your final?
Crippling a Buick?
I'm sorry I had to do that,
but I came in with honourable
intentions of helping you out.
No, I'm sorry, you're right.
Thank you.
I really appreciate you coming
in here. High point of my day.
How long have you wanted to do that?
Do what?
Kiss me.
How long have you denied
that burning desire?
It just came to me.
It was an impulse.
Good, cos if you've been thinking
about anything between us,
- it's out of the question.
- No, I haven't.
Good.
Listen, Diane. Thank you.
I will put the past behind me,
and tomorrow I'll feel better.
But tonight I'm gonna feel bad. OK?
Yeah, OK.
Will you do me a favour?
You want me to try
and take your purse, right?
OK, I deserved that.
No, I'm curious.
I want to hear about the Booger.
- The what?
- The guy from Baltimore.
Listen, I may not have had 80 majors,
but I know when I'm being patronised.
Second game, bottom of the ninth,
Boog's up again...
- Again?
- I'm seeing the clown in my dreams.
See, if I serve him a gopher ball,
we're five games out of
first place with eight to play.
There's only one guy on base,
but it's Don Buford.
He's over there dancing around.
I had to go over there 20 times.
To talk to him about dancing?
No. You see,
you gotta throw the ball to first
to keep the runner close to the bag.
If you don't...
Wait. Don't you throw the ball
at the batter?
Look, this story's going nowhere.
Let's just forget it.
- Good. Now my cheerleader story.
- OK, Buford's on first...
- Where?
- Right there.
Put it down. Easy mistake.
I'll give you another shot.
Gentlemen. One more time, please.
Let me give you a chance
to break even. I feel just terrible!