Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Oh, Woody.
Our baby-sitter
just canceled.
Could you sit
with Frederick tonight?
Okay.
Oh, great, Woody.
Thanks.
Yeah, I'm used to it.
I used to baby-sit
a lot back in Hanover...
well, before the incident.
You know...
I think Lilith's mother
owes us a favor.
Thanks anyway, Woody.
Oh, good, Woody,
come here for a minute.
Listen, I'm gonna go out
of town for the weekend
and I want you
to feed my cat.
Now I know it's an imposition,
but, you know.
Okay.
Well, you're really good
with animals, aren't you?
Well, yeah.
I mean, I had lots of pets
back in Hanover...
before the incident.
Yeah, Woody,
on second thought,
I'm gonna ask
my next-door neighbor,
but thanks anyway.
Hey, Woody,
that's a really
clever trick.
You get out of doing
anything with that.
Yeah.
Just wish I'd thought of it
before the incident.
(theme song begins)
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always
glad you came ¶
¶ You wanna be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ¶
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
We realize
it's short notice,
but this dinner tonight
is something
we simply cannot miss.
We're desperate
to get a sitter.
I would really like
to help you guys out,
but children make me nervous.
I'm afraid I'm gonna drop them.
Oh, Rebecca...
holding a baby is
the simplest thing
in the world.
(glass breaks)
I'm sorry. What did you say?
Thanks anyway.
Kelly,
how was class?
(sighs heavily):
I'd rather not talk about it.
I'm sorry, Woody.
I didn't mean to jump down
your throat like that.
Well, uh...
what's wrong?
Well, my final project
for sociology
is an in-depth study
of a past work experience.
And I've never had a job.
I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
Well, let me get
this straight--
you can't do your
little school project
because you're
stinkin' rich
and you never had to work
a day in your life?
Yeah.
And I used to complain
because I had no shoes.
I feel so out of place
in my sociology class.
Do you know what it's like
to sit in school all day
and not contribute anything?
Well, it's been a long time,
but that sounds familiar.
I don't even know
how to get a job.
Kelly,
come over here, here.
Want ads.
Okay?
Plenty of jobs in there.
If you can't find
anything there,
call an employment agency.
Plenty of places
to get a job.
Hey, you know, Norm,
for a guy who's unemployed,
you certainly know a lot
about getting work.
Well, Cliff, I know
a lot about water, too,
but you don't see me
drinking it.
Uh, Ms. Howe,
do you think
Kelly could work
here for a while?
I know she doesn't have
any experience...
I don't think so, Woody.
Oh, well, I just
thought I'd ask.
It's no big deal.
Look, Woody.
It says here I can make
$10,000 a week
being an escort.
Okay, Ms. Howe,
now it's a big deal.
Please, please,
let her work here.
You can always use
an extra hand
and you don't
have to pay her.
Yeah, it's just
for the experience.
All right, Woody,
all right.
As a favor to you.
But this is
a real business.
This is not
a training ground.
We need people to work here who
really know what they're doing.
(glass breaks)
Tell her to wear shoes.
Thanks, Ms. Howe.
Hey, Kelly, guess what?
Ms. Howe said
you can work here.
Really?
Oh, that's great.
Oh, thanks, Ms. Howe.
Oh, welcome aboard, Kelly.
I can't believe
I have a real job.
You know what
to do with this.
Wow, I sure do.
Do you guys have lobster
for lunch every day?
Well, does that mean
you're canceling tonight?
All right, all right.
Well, maybe some other time.
Boy, women'll break a date
with you at the drop of a hat.
Like her grandmother
won't still be dead tomorrow.
Sam, am I to understand that you
suddenly have the night free?
Yeah, you got anything for me?
Perhaps.
Quite cute.
Oh, yeah?
Cute's nice.
And young.
Oh, I like young.
Give me more details.
Well, about 32 inches.
I usually I like them
a little bustier than that.
I'm just trying to find out
if you would like to sit
for Frederick tonight.
Oh, yeah.
I'd love to do that.
Really?
I love that little guy.
Why not?
Done deal.
All right.
Frasier, can I
speak with you?
I don't know how comfortable
I feel with this setup.
He's just a baby.
He needs supervision.
Well, Sam can
take care of it.
I'm talking about Sam.
You know how out of control
he can get at times,
what a mess he can
make of everything.
Well, Sam can clean it up.
Oh, you're talking
about Sam.
I'm talking about Sam.
Darling, it'll just
be for a few hours.
All right.
But if anything goes wrong,
he could be scarred for life.
You mean Sam, right?
Yes, and it is a threat.
Sam, can you be at our place
in about an hour?
You bet.
Where are you guys
going tonight?
Oh, well, I'm proud to tell you
that my lovely wife
is being honored tonight
by the scientific community
for her contributions to the
study of sensory deprivation.
It was serendipitous,
I admit.
I'd returned to the lab
after a two-week holiday
to find that I'd locked
my lab assistant
in the isolation tank.
Suffice it to say, what could
have been an ugly lawsuit
turned into
an award-winning paper.
Say, Carla,
I'm, uh, baby-sitting tonight.
You got any advice for me?
Sure. Here's everything
you need to know about babies.
Remember,
you're the boss.
Yeah.
Don't let him
give you any lip.
And if they start
to act crabby,
stick a bottle
in their mouths.
Great.
Okay, great.
Okay, I'm ready.
Okay.
Here's everything you need
to know about customers.
Remember,
you're the boss.
Don't let 'em
give you any lip.
And if they start
to act crabby,
just stick a bottle
in their mouths.
Hey, Miss.
I ordered a beer.
And he passes to Frederick.
Frederick takes the ball
and goes for a jam.
Yes! Yes!
He's a freshman
out of the learning center.
Yes!
Oh, a rookie.
Wonderful shot.
Here we go.
Take another one.
He goes for the jam.
He goes. He runs.
The Garden is going cra....
Oh. It's...
Great shot.
Okay, Malone, top of the key...
Do you want to watch
a little TV?
(pants slightly):
You know something?
That's a good idea.
Uncle Sam
is a little tired here.
Whoo!
Good idea, good idea.
I don't know how to do this one.
Do you know how to...
I have a different one
at home there.
(TV clicks on)
Oh, far out. Thanks.
That's great.
Oh, great,
this is The Flintstones.
This is the one where Barney
gets stuck in the mailbox.
I actually haven't seen this one
all the way to the end.
Freddie?
Hey, Fred,
whatcha doing in there?
Peek-a-boo!
(doorknob rattles)
Freddie?
Uh-oh.
Uh... oh, boy.
Fred.
Hey, listen to me now.
Listen to Uncle Sammy.
Unlock the door, Freddie.
T... Freddie, turn the knob.
You see the knob?
See that little knob?
Turn the knob, Freddie.
(toilet flushes)
No, wrong knob, Fred.
Shoot.
Um, okay, all right.
I'll get you out of there.
Got to be a key around here.
(giggles)
Oh, I know what
I'm gonna do, Fred.
We'll do the old credit card
jimmying the lock open here.
I don't have a credit card.
I know, here, here,
I'll use a $20.
This is gonna work.
Yeah, here we go, Freddie.
No, Freddie... hey...
give me my $20 back.
(toilet flushes)
Fred, no.
Don't fl... oh... shoot.
You little...
I'm in trouble here.
Okay, don't worry.
Uncle Sammy's gonna get you
out of there, Freddie.
Yeah, I'll just come around
the window here.
Ooh.
We're way high, aren't we?
Okay.
No big deal.
Ooh.
Okay.
Here we go.
Here comes Uncle Sammy.
Oh, yeah.
Burglar-proof.
Right. Yeah.
Your mommy and daddy told me
about that, didn't they?
Okay.
Hey, Freddie.
Whoo!
(groans)
Damn, damn, damn!
You didn't hear that, Freddie.
You didn't hear that.
(groans):
Oh...!
Damn it!
You heard that one, didn't you?
Hey, Freddie...
Uncle Sammy doesn't know
what to do here.
Can you open this window?
Do you know the word "open"?
Yeah, yeah, open.
Open.
Can you open the window?
D-do you know the word "open"?
Good boy.
Bye-bye.
Carla, I just waited
on a man at table 5
and he left too much
money on the table.
Should we go find him?
No, uh, you see, this
is what we call a tip.
It's a little monetary gift
for the head waitress.
Here you go.
Boy, do I feel dumb.
Oh, no, you're just new.
Kelly, can I have
a beer, please?
Okay, let me go get Woody.
Oh, no, you don't need Woody.
Come here. I'm gonna
show you how it's done.
Take a glass,
stick it underneath
this black lever here,
okay?
Voilá, you have a beer.
Now there's a, uh, black book
underneath the cash register.
It says "Norm's tab" on it.
You mean this one here
with all these little marks?
Right.
Now, Kelly, each one of these
little marks
represents a beer that
I've purchased... in advance.
Every time I order one,
you have to take this eraser
and, uh, erase one
of those little marks.
Don't forget to erase now.
I don't want any free beers!
Okay, Mr. Peterson.
Thank you.
Unbelievable!
I'm in the presence
of sheer genius.
Thank you, Cliffy.
Kelly, can I have
another beer
for my dear friend
Clifford Clavin?
And what the heck,
take it off my tab.
Hey, Freddie!
(knocking on window)
Freddie, Uncle Sammy needs
some help here, bud.
Hey, Fred,
do you know about rain?
Because that's what's happening
out here, Freddie.
You know...
¶ Itsy-bitsy spider
went up the waterspout ¶
(thunder rumbling)
Okay, Fred.
Look, back away from the window
there, Fred.
Uncle Sammy's gonna break
the window...
and every little bone
in his hand.
Oh!
Okay, Fred.
Tell you what I'm gonna do here.
I'm gonna jump over to that tree
and climb on down.
I'll be back in just,
before you can... Oh! Oh!
(crashing)
Bye.
Carla, I need to ask you
some questions for my paper,
since you're my co-worker.
How do you feel that
the work experience
has enriched your life?
It's given me varicose veins,
stomach acid, lower back pain
and a complete hatred
for all mankind.
That's great.
And what would you say
are the negative aspects?
Just do the dishes.
Yeah.
I hate that one, too.
We have an Australian couple
that do it at home.
Oh...
By the way, here's another one
of those tip things.
Why, thank you very much, Kelly.
Boy, she is really dumber
than cotton.
Hey, Carla.
Hey, Cotton.
Who's ready, huh?
You thirsty?
Come on.
Norm, come on.
Let us buy a round.
I insist.
Kelly, another round
for my friends here, okay?
Okay, Mr. Peterson,
but my hands are getting sore
from all that erasing.
Now, now, Kelly,
you wanted a real job.
You can't go through life
getting everything handed
to you for free.
Let's get some beer over here.
How about you fellows?
You ready?
Oh, we've really got
to get back to the site, Norm.
Come on. You're only working
on the second floor.
Yeah!
A round for these guys.
Hey-hey-hey,
isn't that that Henri?
Oh, yeah,
it's Pepe LePew himself.
Yeah, he's got
a lot of guts
showing his sleazy Gallic mug
around this place.
Yeah.
If I was, uh, Woody,
I'd have popped that guy
a long time ago, you know?
Hello, fellows!
ALL:
Hey, Henri!
What do you say?
Buy you a beer?
And he's such a phony, you know?
Uh, Woody, loan me
ten dollars until payday.
When's payday?
How do I know?
You're the one who's working.
Kelly!
What are you doing
with those drinks?
Hello, Henri.
I'm working here for a while.
Isn't that exciting?
Yes, you are!
Serve me a drink
so that I may pinch
your bottom as you leave.
Henri, I wish you'd stop
saying things like that.
Well, Woody,
but I am the customer,
and the customer
is always right.
Darn.
Got me on a technicality.
You know, if this Kelly thing
works out,
I might finally be able
to take my vacation.
The last one I had
was three years ago
when I went to Graceland
for a weekend.
But now I got six weeks
saved up.
I'm gonna take me
a real vacation.
Where are you gonna go?
Graceland.
Woody, may I have a soda,
please?
Stealing your girlfriend
is thirsty work.
All right, Henri,
I don't know how things are
in France,
but in America,
guys don't like other guys
saying they're gonna steal
their girlfriend.
It's not polite.
Oh! I'm, I'm so sorry.
I, I see your point.
Uh, as we say in France...
Je vais te piquer ta copine.
What does that mean?
I'm going to steal
your girlfriend.
Wait a minute.
You take that back.
Oh!
I-I...
What are you doing?!
Oh, hey, Freddie!
I'm back.
I must have blacked out
there for a while.
Whoo!
Uncle Sammy sure is lucky
the glass recycling bin
broke his fall.
I'll tell you.
Somebody sure drinks a lot
of wine in this building. Uh!
You look all tuckered out there.
What do you say we watch
a little,
a little television here, huh?
Oh, shoot!
Flintstones are over.
Fred?
Freddie?
Oh, no, man!
Don't lock... shoot!
Come on, Freddie!
It was funny once!
All right.
Okay, Freddie, here I come.
Oh, no, no-no-no.
There we go.
Okay, Freddie, here I come.
Freddie!
Freddie, what are you doing
to Uncle Sammy?
Come on.
Bring the dog back, Freddie.
Woody, can I talk to you
for minute, please?
Sure, Ms. Howe.
Woody, I don't think things
are working out with Kelly.
Oh, well, that's my fault.
I'm afraid of commitment.
Woody, I mean here
at the bar.
I mean, she's a big
distraction to you;
your work is suffering;
and, and this bar fight
is just the last straw.
I'm afraid I'm gonna
have to let her go.
Well, I guess
that was a tough decision
for you to make, Ms. Howe.
Yeah, well, sometimes managers
have to learn how
to give bad news to employees.
So go fire
your girlfriend, Woody.
Hey, I'm getting better at that.
I think I'll go
get a facial.
I earned it.
Wait. Whoa, wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Is it true?
Are you firing Kelly?
Because I want you to know
that she is the best thing
that's ever happened
to this bar!
Since when did you ever care
what happened to Kelly?
Wait. Whoa, wait, whoa!
Something's happening
to Kelly?
She's not leaving,
is she?
Yes, as a matter of fact,
she is.
I guess you're both going to
have to learn to live with it.
She's here one day
and everybody loves her.
I'm here five years
and nobody gives a damn!
By the way, Norm.
why'd you want her to stay?
None of your business.
Why'd you want her to stay?
What did you want
to talk about, Woody?
Well, Kelly, you don't
really like this place
all that much, do you?
Oh, sure I do.
I love this place.
It's keen.
Oh, boy.
Kelly, Cheers is not
such a great place.
Well, what
do you mean, Woody?
Oh, I mean it's nice
on the surface,
but when you get
right down to it,
there's a dark side
to Cheers.
Really?
Aw, Kelly, Kelly, Kelly,
you're so naive.
Nobody respects
anybody here.
Oh, they're nice
to your face,
but as soon
as you turn around,
they're plotting some way
to get rid of you.
And they never do
their own dirty work.
Nope. No, no.
They wouldn't
stoop to that.
They'd rather use some
poor innocent farm boy
to carry out
their sinister deeds
while they go prancing off
to get a facial!
Well, I'm not doing it anymore!
I quit!
Then I quit, too!
Bye, everybody.
Oh, man, I knew that I should
not have had Woody fire her.
When am I
gonna learn?
If you want something
done right,
you've gotta do it yourself.
(glasses break)
Be careful walking back here.
Ms. Howe.
Yes? What do you want?
Well, uh, listen,
I've had a lot of time
to think since I quit,
and, uh, I've done
a little growing up
and, and, and if you haven't
filled my old position yet,
I'd like to...
Woody!
I-I-I know that I'll have
to go back to starting wages
and, and that
I'll lose my seniority.
Woody...
I-I-I know it'll take me
a few weeks to...
Woody, just shut up
and get to work! God!
Boy, they sure aren't very nice
to new employees.
Darling, do my eyes deceive me
or is our little Frederick
actually asleep?
Oh, he is!
Where's Sam?
(banging outside)
Sam!
Over here in the tree.
But I can still see the kid.
Whoo!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4nx5q
Help other users to choose the best subtitles