CARLA: Hey, Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Hi, it's me.
Li-listen, I've, uh...
I've been thinking about you and...
Oh, what the hell.
Will you marry me?
Sam?
SAM: Well,
who else do you think it'd be?
Sam, if this is some kind of a joke...
SAM: No, I'm serious.
Will you marry me?
Oh!
Oh, my God.
I'm... I'm stunned.
I mean, it's-it's not like
I never expected to hear this from you.
It's just that
one is...
...is never quite
prepared for the question.
Oh, Sam, I'm touched. I...
(Diane laughs)
All... All at once, I...
I'm-I'm feeling giddiness,
fear, euphoria, relief.
I-I don't know what to say.
Oh, that's okay.
I'm not listening anymore.
Sam,
I-I-I...
I can't answer you now.
Not like this.
Every woman
wants her proposal to be...
enchanting,
something she can remember
for the rest of her life.
Find something like that.
Keeping in mind I don't
care for sports arenas,
theme parks or miniature golf.
All right, young lady, you just prepare
to be swept off your
feet tomorrow night.
I already have been.
Bon soir, mon coeur.
R-Right, right.
Ugh.
I'll get another one.
(piano plays)
♪ Making your way in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like to get away♪
♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always glad you came ♪
♪ You want to be where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You want to go where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Good afternoon, everybody.
ALL: Norm.
Hey, Mr. Peterson.
What's the story?
Boy meets beer.
Boy drinks beer.
Boy gets another beer.
Uh,
boy, have I got an
evening cooked up for us.
Yeah? thanks for thinking of me, Cliffy,
but, uh, I think I better
get home early today.
What?
Yeah, Vera's getting
home from Springfield,
and I thought a special elegant meal
would be the proper way to
welcome her home, you know.
How thoughtful, Norm.
Say, what's on the menu?
Yeah, whatever she
feels like whipping up
after a five-hour bus trip.
Oh.
SAM: Hey Woody,
didn't you say you'd been to this,
uh, Le Petit Orange Restaurant?
Yeah. CLIFF: Hey, Woody,
you been to that, uh, fancy joint, eh?
Yeah, a couple of times. Yeah?
Yeah, well, how was it?
Did they treat you well?
I didn't eat there.
I just went in to use the men's room.
Well, the-the restaurant
part-- did it look like a...
a nice romantic place to take a lady?
Well, who could tell, Sam?
It's real dark in there,
and they got this guy
running around playing a violin.
SAM: Oh, no.
I bet they got those
pictures of those guys
that are half men,
half horse, too, right?
I'm glad you said that, Sam.
I thought I was seeing things.
I've been racking my brains all day
trying to find a place
that's out of the ordinary
and classy for dinner tonight.
How about a nude barbecue?
No. It's kind of dangerous
with all those sparks.
Oh, right.
Uh, well, what's the
occasion there, Stretch?
Well, let's just...
Let's just say it's a special evening
for a special lady.
Ooh! Get out your scorecards, boys.
Sounds like Sammy's back in action.
Yeah! Yeah!
FRASIER: I, uh, take it this means
you've terminated
your relationship with
Councilor Eldridge.
Ooh, yeah, in-in the dumper.
CLIFF: Well, gentlemen,
in memory of the
Councilor, may I suggest
we lower our cocktail
napkins to half mast, huh?
Yes, let's not forget the
traditional 21-peanut salute.
Oh, no.
Sammy, another round for the back?
Yeah, but I want to know
who's the lucky lady tonight.
CLIFF: Yeah, come on, Sammy.
You'll-You'll find out soon enough.
Just come on, help me
think of a place here.
Well, all right, Sam, I-I got something
that might be just the ticket for you.
How about this?
A sailboat anchored offshore,
you know, chilled champagne,
candlelit dinner
underneath the stars, huh?
Worked great for Sean and Madonna.
Where do you hear all this stupid stuff?
Let's just say
inquiring minds want to know, huh.
A sailboat. That's a good idea.
Maybe I'll call and
see if I can rent one.
Hey, Sam,
I just remembered something
that might help you.
What's that?
Now my Uncle Wade was a master
at putting women in a romantic mood.
Well, what-what'd he do?
Gave 'em money.
Worked like a charm.
Uh, thank you, Woody,
but I'm looking for a place
to take someone, a-a
very special place.
As a matter of fact, come here.
Can you keep a secret?
Can I keep a secret?
You still don't know Carla leaves early
on your night off, do you?
Good, good.
Listen, I'm only telling you this
because I-I like you,
and I... and I trust you.
I'm thinking about proposing.
Oh, well, Sam, I'm flattered, but...
You probably don't mean me, huh?
We'll talk later.
Boy, oh, boy, I wouldn't
mind being a barnacle
on the rudder of Sam's sailboat,
if you know what I mean.
I'm sure you'd be better-looking,
but would you be happier?
Ooh.
NORM: Woody, are you in pain, buddy?
No, I was just thinking.
Yeah, well, the first
time's always the worst.
Who do you think Sam's
gonna propose to tonight?
What're you babbling
about, Billy Bob Joe Jim?
Well, Sam said
he was gonna propose to someone.
FRASIER: That's odd.
He said he broke up
with Councilor Eldridge.
Who could he possibly be
talking about proposing to?
(Frasier and Carla scream)
You've chosen the most beautiful spot
in which to anchor.
Everything's absolutely perfect.
This is the most wonderful
idea any man ever came up with.
(chuckles)
Who came up with it?
Come on, give me some credit.
I have an original thought now and then.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Was it Frasier?
Actually, it was Cliff.
Well, okay then, don't tell me.
(giggles)
Right now I'm having a
rather unoriginal thought.
Are you as happy as I?
Oh, yeah.
I just wish I could get this song
out of my head.
Song?
Yeah. You-You know how
sometimes you connect certain places
and things with certain songs?
Oh, I know exactly what you mean.
Thank you.
This may sound a bit pretentious,
but every time I'm in a taxi,
I can't help but hum "Dove
Sono" from Le Nozze Di Figaro
simply because once a
rather zaftig Parisian cabbie
sang the entire aria on a trip
through Montparnasse to La Coupole.
(laughs)
Anyway, whenever I get
out on the water like this,
I can't help thinking about this tune.
Uh, Cappy Johnny, the old
sailor who taught me how to sail
used to whistle it all the time.
(whistles "Popeye the Sailor Man")
"Popeye the Sailor Man?"
You know it?
Oh, yes.
Well, that one haunts me, too.
May I propose a toast?
Indeed you may.
No, no, a, uh, shrimp toast.
A shrimp toast is even better.
Hmm.
To us.
How eloquent.
(laughs)
Boy, us.
(laughs) Mm.
What a pair, huh?
The important thing is that
this finally seems right.
Yeah.
I'm so happy about us.
I feel so good.
To think I almost let you
get away because of Janet.
Well, you had some crazy
notion you cared about her.
Well, hey, if it weren't for Janet,
I wouldn't be here right now.
Which reminds me, I guess I better...
better get to why I came
here in the first place.
Can you, uh, give me some room here?
Oh, oh, yes, indeed.
Mm. Ha, ha!
(laughs)
You know, for the longest time,
I kept pretending about you.
I guess I was afraid to
really admit my feelings.
But from the very start,
down deep inside,
I have been crazy about you.
Crazier about you
than any other woman I've ever met.
I mean, hell, I was crazy about you
even when I hated you.
(laughing)
What I'm trying to say is...
will you marry me?
No.
No?
Are you serious?
I'm afraid I am.
Well...
seems to me you have two choices.
One, I can throw you in,
or two, you can jump in.
Sam, I warn you...
It's very simple.
One or two. Sam, you haven't...
It's not open for debate, Diane.
Sam, I think after you've
heard my explanation,
you won't...
Sam, throw me a line, please?!
Okay.
What's a nice girl like you
doing in an ocean like this?
Sam!
(dishes banging)
What are you doing?
SAM: The dishes!
(dishes banging)
Sam... calm down.
You're upset.
Only that I fished you out.
I know my answer was unexpected...
Unexpected. No, no.
Don't be silly.
I brought you out here
so I could be dumped
with a nautical theme.
(grunts)
(glass shattering)
(dishes banging)
Sam... if you'll stop
that for a moment...
if you'll stop that for a moment,
I'll try and explain... my answer.
Are you done?
Maybe.
All right, then.
As it happens, I came out
here with every intention
of... accepting your proposal...
but when you spoke of Janet, I...
had this enormous pang of doubt.
"What if wanting to get married
"is a knee-jerk reaction to losing her?
Does he want me or just someone?"
Oh, Sam, I want it so much,
but I have to be free of
doubt before I can say yes.
Sam?
Did you notice that?
Notice what?
Everything just got calm.
I don't notice any difference.
Oh, yes, yes.
There's a difference in everything.
The whole world just changed for me.
Oh!
Look!
The stars are new.
The moon is new.
Sam Malone is new, and I like him.
And I like them, and they like me.
And none of us like you.
Am I going overboard again?
No, no, no, don't be silly.
That would mean I care, and I don't.
Bye-bye, Diane.
Where are you going?
I'm going to swim ashore.
You can't do that.
Very well... I'll take the dinghy.
You... See how quickly
the new Sam adjusts?
You're going to just leave
me out here all alone?
Yes, I am.
Sam. Sam Malone.
If you leave me out here all alone,
you are the most despicable
creature on Earth!
Well, I yam what I yam,
and that's all what I yam.
(whistling "Popeye the Sailor Man")
Hello, Mr. Clavin.
Hey, Woodrow. Uh, suds du jour, please.
Oh, there he is!
Normie, eh!
So, uh, Vera get home from
Springfield last night, huh?
Yep. Yeah, yeah?
So, uh, how'd it go?
Well, I'll tell you, Cliff,
it got pretty hot in
our bedroom last night.
CLIFF: Whoo-hoo!
Yeah, yeah? Air conditioning broke down.
EVERYONE: Hey, hey!
The lucky fella.
Let me get this over with.
Uh, I asked her. She
said no. End of bulletin.
CARLA: Sorry, Sam.
I feel like dirt.
I'm fine, everybody.
I just don't want to
talk about it, that's all.
Can I talk to you just for a minute?
Sure, Sam. What can I do you for?
Well...
I'm kind of worried
that Diane may get hurt.
My God, Sam, that is very noble of you.
No, I-I mean that I...
I had a dream last night
that I killed her...
and-and-and-and it
felt really good.
Does this mean I'm-I'm crazy or...?
No, no, of course not.
It's very normal for most sane people
to entertain insane impulses sometimes,
and it's very natural
to want to hurt someone
that's rejected you.
Well, for example...
Well, there's me.
But I can't tell you
how many times I felt
my own hands around her windpipe...
strangling her...
fingers tightening...
cartilage snapping!
And, uh, I'm a respected psychiatrist.
Look, Sam, you've been through
an emotional meat grinder.
My best advice to you is get away,
relax... reflect on what's happened.
You know, I still have the boat
rented for a couple of days.
I guess I could sail up to Marblehead.
Great. Cool it out there.
Thank you. You know, maybe
I'll work on the old tan.
Terrific. It'll be just
what the doctor ordered, Sam:
sun, salt air, ocean spray in your face.
I know I-I wish I could come with you.
Well, I wish I could ask.
I understand.
Ooh, boy, how 'bout that Diane, huh?
Eh, just like all women.
If they're not turnin' down
your proposal of marriage,
they're... they're accusin'
you of suspicious behavior
in the lingerie changin' room.
Oh, uh, hello, Diane.
Norman.
Excuse me, miss,
aren't you confusing
this bar with the one
where everyone isn't
repulsed by your presence?
Oh, Frasier, please
tell me where Sam is.
I have to talk with him.
Diane... in light of your
disposal of him last night,
I think it's better that
he be left alone right now.
That poor man.
Can you imagine how he must feel?
Gee, I'll try.
Of course. I'm sorry.
It's just that I'm so distraught.
I fear I've made a terrible mistake.
Sam's instincts were superior to my own.
He was right, and I was wrong.
I should've said yes.
You're running back to him?
If he'll have me. I...
Oh... my neck is so stiff
from that water last night.
Would you give me one
of your special massages?
Please? Please, please, please?
Certainly. Thank you.
I was such a fool out
in that boat last night.
(sighs)
When I told him no,
I was listening to my
head and not my heart.
I should've known.
Sam and I are inevitable.
Why fight it?
Frasier...
You don't mind me talking to you
about this, do you?
No, no, no, no.
Uh, I'm happy for you. Feels better.
Thank you. Good, good.
No, I'm-I'm really happy for you.
Uh, Diane, I think it's
wise to go to him now.
Yes. Uh, right-right now.
Yes, yes, right... Where is he?
Oh, uh...
(laughing): He, uh,
he, uh, took the boat
to Marblehead. Oh, thank you, Frasier.
I'll wait till tonight
and motor out to the boat.
Yes. Oh, this is perfect.
Sam will already be asleep,
and I'll slip into bed
beside him and give him
the surprise of his life.
Eh, uh, Diane?
Sam's nose is, uh, pushed
out of joint, and I think
you better let him cool down.
Oh, don't be silly. He proposed.
You can't turn off
emotions like a spigot.
Besides, making up has always been
the cornerstone of our relationship.
You know, that's...
that's what I always loved
about the two of you, Diane.
That's-that's beautiful, really.
You and Sam are magic.
I should've killed her
while I had the chance.
Hey, everybody.
Sam!
Thought you were on the high seas.
Yeah, well, I changed my mind.
I decided the best way
to forget about Diane
was to start dating some babes
long on legs and short on syllables.
Sounds like a good plan, too.
Besides, I ran into
an old friend of mine,
Monsignor Demarest.
He needed to relax a little bit,
so I sent him out to
Marblehead on the boat.
Oh, my God!
What?
Nothing.
Oh.
(engine shuts off)
Thanks for the lift.
(engine starts)
(Diane and man screaming)
Yes!
Yes, what?
Yes, I will marry you.
Oh, oh, I see what's happening here.
You-you're still under the assumption
that that offer is still valid.
No, no, no, no.
The-the statute of limitations
on that proposal ran out
the second your feet hit the water.
In that case, may I
suggest you propose again?
I assure you this time, I
will accept your proposal.
Fine. I propose that you step
in front of a speeding bus.
(all laughing)
You know, and I...
from now on, I'm
dedicating myself to life,
liberty and the pursuit of every woman
in Boston except that one,
so, to celebrate,
drinks are on the house.
Come on, everybody!
(all cheering)
Wh-What do you think you're doing?
I'm going to work.
I'll probably stop working
when we get married,
but I need a little
money for my trousseau.
Who knows when the first
little Malone will come along?
Yeah, how do I say this clearly
enough to register with you?
I'm buying everybody a drink
in this bar to seal the fact
that you and I are through forever.
Oh, come on, Sam, come on.
Nobody believes that.
Well, go ahead. Ask them.
Yeah, all right, I will.
Hey, turn around here
for a minute, guys.
Now, after everything I just said,
do you think that Diane and I
will ever get back together again?
Could I have my drink before I answer?