Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
( Carla humming )
Boy, look at her.
What a glow she has.
You know, strange
as it sounds,
there are
actually times
when I resent
being a man.
Ah, that's all right, Fras.
Sometimes we resent
you being one.
( Sam laughs )
I was referring to
Carla's condition.
You see, she's able
to do something
we men never shall--
experience the miracle
of creating a new life.
SAM:
You know, I'll
have to admit.
I've often wondered
what it would like
to have another human being
moving around inside you.
Must be spooky,
but real neato.
Yeah.
There's probably nothing
so awesome
in the entire universe.
Yes, gentlemen,
I'm afraid
that we've
been relegated
to the position
of observer.
Passive, sitting
on the sidelines.
Doomed by nature
to a life of envy.
God, feels like
there's a dump truck
parked on my bladder.
Well, then again,
nature is wise
in her way.
( piano plays )
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always glad
you came
You want to be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You want to be where everybody
knows your name
You want to go
where people know
People are all the same
You want to go where
everybody knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
What makes me think
this belongs to you?
( gasps )
My jasmine scented
oriental massage oil.
Oh, God.
God, I thought
I'd lost this.
I found it wedged
underneath the couch cushions
in my office.
Ah.
I don't think I want to
know how it got there.
I'm kind
of curious.
Tell you what.
Why don't you, uh, put that back
where you found it,
and that way, we'll know
where it is when we need it.
When hell freezes over.
Well, that's perfect,
'cause this stuff heats up
when you rub it in.
Now, what... what's wrong
with her, you know?
Maybe one of the chains
in her underwear is twisted.
Afternoon, everybody.
ALL:
Norm!
Hey.
What's going on,
Mr. Peterson?
Let's talk about
what's going in  Mr. Peterson.
Beer, Woody.
How's the job-hunting going?
Oh, lots better, Sam.
Today I actually got turned down
for an executive position.
It's a good way
to lose that.
I'm sorry, Mr. Peterson.
You've been cut off.
Oh. Okay, where's the camera?
This is no joke.
According to my books,
you are way over
your credit limit.
SAM:
Well, what's the big deal?
What's he over--
ten, 20 bucks?
837.
But in other words,
under $900, huh?
You can't cut off
one of our regulars.
The poor guy
is unemployed.
FRASIER:
Look, Miss Howe, uh,
Norm here is
in a very delicate spot.
His self-confidence
has been shattered.
Uh, what he needs from us now
is help and support.
Isn't there some other way
to resolve this problem?
Well, you could pay
his bar bill.
Norm, the woman
will not listen to reason.
Maybe he could
work it off, huh?
( laughter )
No, I'm serious. Whoa,
whoa, whoa, hey.
Listen, maybe there's
some accounting he
could do for the bar.
Our corporation's books
are handled
by Franklin, Sussman
and Gurwitz.
Ooh, they're
very good, Sam.
They canned me a
couple years ago.
Please.
( sighs )
Are you good
at anything?
Yeah,
but you cut him off.
SAM:
No, no.
Come on, don't you have
any other skills?
I can barbecue.
Oh, hey, hey.
Yeah.
NORM:
All right,
well, I,
uh... I did a little
house painting in college.
You know, to make ends meet.
( laughs ):
Norm, Norm, Norm.
Norm, I think
they're talking about a job
where you get, uh,
paid with money,
not with little grain pellets
dropped out of a chute.
Cliff, you, uh, you got
something against painters?
( laughs ):
No, no, no. I...
I'm in favor
of hiring the blithering.
( laughs )
Do... do you need
any painting done around here?
I guess you could
repaint the office.
Are you willing?
It's been an awfully long time.
CLIFF:
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's gonna take you
at least, what,
seven or eight seconds
to relearn that skill.
( laughs )
'Cause, you know, Cliff,
I'm beginning
to pick up
a little thread here. Uh...
Ah.
Would you mind explaining
this little obsession
you have about painters?
CLIFF:
Well, all right.
Uh, well,
it's manual labor.
I mean,
it's beneath you, Norm.
Well, if you take a job
like this, we're gonna be
on entirely different
social strata.
We'll have nothing
to talk about, all right?
Semigloss or enamel?
Hey, Woody, would you close up
for me tonight?
I got to get home.
No problem, Carla.
By the way,
I really am envious of you
having a nice big family
to go home to.
Oh, yeah, it's great, all right.
I got 11 people
living under a roof
that was meant for only six.
Gino's dog just had puppies
on my side of the bed.
My daughter-in-law
is driving me nuts, and somehow,
my mother-in-law got a hold
of our address.
Puppies.
You lucky duck.
( humming )
You seem to be
enjoying yourself.
Oh, sorry. Uh...
No, that's all right.
Oh, uh, you got a phone call
here, uh...
Eva Ake?
I could swear
it was a man.
Oh, well,
there's paint here.
Evan Drake. Uh...
That's my boss.
Yeah.
What did he say?
Well, he said, he, uh...
he wants you
to tear up my bar bill.
I... Well...
I didn't think
I'd get away with that.
Uh, but, no, he said
he's on his way over here.
Sometime, like, uh...
around nowish.
Now?!
God.
Shall I, uh, comb my hair, too,
or will I be leaving?
This is just a business meeting.
( phone rings )
Rebecca Howe.
Oh, hello, Mr. Drake.
I thought you were--
Norm.
No, no, no, I know
you're not Norm.
You're Evan.
What I meant
to say was--
Get out of here.
No, no, no, not you.
You stay right
where you are.
No, I swear...
Get out!
Oh. Hello?
Well, that was
fast, Mr. P.
Yeah, she got a phone call
from Mr. Drake.
Hey, Mr. Peterson,
I really feel bad
about you being cut off.
Yeah.
You know, I remember
the good old days
when you used
to come in here and
say something funny.
I'd pour you a beer.
You'd drink it,
I'd pour you another one,
you'd drink that, too.
Yeah.
Yeah, I remember, Woody.
So look at that--
hardly even touched.
Yeah.
I'll tell you, I don't
normally drink beer, but, uh,
I just cleaned the taps,
and I wanted to make sure
that everything was all right,
so I had one.
It was like a mountain stream,
only colder, fresher.
You know, sometimes
there's nothing
like a nice cold beer
to really hit the spot.
Yeah, I think I read
that somewhere, Woody.
You know,
I-I really like this color.
I think it's gonna really
spruce up the office
quite a bit.
( sobbing )
Again, it's just
an opinion. Uh...
( sobbing )
Is there something wrong?
( tearful mumbling )
Right. Well, yes,
I understand, of course.
Here, here, have a seat,
have a seat.
Just relax.
Oh, God.
Here.
Some authority figure.
I'm sorry.
It's probably
just job stress.
Oh, you shouldn't
be having job stress.
You're doing a great job here.
Oh, tell that to Mr. Drake.
He said I should consider
the last fiscal report
a personal embarrassment.
( sobbing )
Norm, I need your help.
Uh, you just started.
You're-you're gonna do fine.
Things are gonna turn around,
I swear.
Uh...
No, you idiot.
My hair's stuck to the wall.
( sniffles )
Oh, great.
No, no, it's
really...
It's not, uh...
not that bad.
I paid big bucks
to have Vera's
hair frosted.
Didn't turn out
half as good.
Well, maybe
I better take off.
When people are upset,
they...
they like to be alone.
Nonsense. I'm fine.
Talking about me.
I'm feeling a little queasy.
Oh, please stay.
I mean,
this office is a real
inconvenience like this.
All right.
( sniffles )
Would you, uh,
would you like to talk
about what just happened?
No.
Phew.
( sighs )
You really do seem to be
enjoying this job.
Yeah. Yeah, I actually do,
you know?
I think painting is just
so vastly different
from accounting.
This is real, you know?
This I have some control over.
I mean, when I look back,
I finish a job,
I can say,
"You know, I did that."
Door must have moved.
You know,
I think that this color
is the exact same color
as Mary Lou Sebold's car coat.
Who?
This girl
I had an insane crush on
in the third grade.
Except she had no idea
that I was alive.
I used to leave
little notes for her.
"I love you."
And one day,
I finally got up the nerve
to sign one, N.P.
The next week,
she was going steady
with my best friend,
Nicky Petropolis.
What'd you do?
The only thing
I could do, really.
I went over to Nicky,
and I calmly explained
the situation.
Then I sat on him.
( laughs )
( continues laughing )
Oh, God.
I think that's the first time
I've really laughed
since I took over here.
Oh, it is, trust me.
Why'd you tell me that story?
Well, I don't know.
It's kind of late.
We're alone.
I'm a man, you're a woman.
Maybe it's the paint talking.
Norm?
Yeah.
Do you find me cold?
You?
Cold? No.
No, I wouldn't say cold.
Coolish.
In the brisk area,
but, uh...
Why? Who, uh...
who says you're cold?
Everyone.
Oh. Well...
I don't think you're cold.
Really?
Yeah. I always meant
to tell you that,
but I didn't feel
as though I could approach you.
Thank you, Norm.
Oh.
Thank you.
Uh, well, I'd better
get out of here.
Um, would you mind
locking up for me?
No, no, I don't mind at all.
Listen, would you
please not, uh,
mention that I like
painting to the guys?
Cliff already thinks
I'm a weenie.
Well, from what I've seen,
he's an authority.
Yeah.
Well...
And, really, thanks
for letting me paint an office
that clearly didn't need it.
No problem.
You're a nice man, Norm.
You're kind of nice yourself.
I guess we like each other.
Guess so.
Great.
This will just be
our little secret.
Oh, yeah.
I am a little worried about
the direction this
bar is taking.
How so?
Well, it just
doesn't seem right
when the stakes
for a game of pool
is a round of
wine spritzers.
Not even the pool room is safe
from the encroaching
hordes of yuppiedom.
How long will it be
until we're all suffocated
beneath an avalanche
of alligator shirts,
German cars, and racquetball
club memberships?
Oh, oh, by the way, Sam,
uh, may I have another
Perrier with lime?
Have a cup of coffee
or something, Sam?
Make it a beer.
On the house.
I say we check the office
for pods from outer space.
I wonder what
that's all about, huh?
Look, did it ever
occur to any of you
that she just might
be a nice woman?
Oh, yeah, right.
And so am I.
( sighs )
So, how come you guys
are so chummy, huh?
Sorry, Sam. Can't talk about it.
Kind of private.
Oh, give me a break.
Guys are supposed
to talk about girls
behind their backs.
( swallows hard )
Didn't I tell you
everything about me and Diane?
Well, now's your chance
to thank me.
I'm not really at liberty
to go into details.
Suffice it to say,
Miss Howe had a little
personal crisis
last night, okay?
Few tears were shed.
Real tears?
You sure she didn't just
pull a hair out of her nose?
No, Carla.
She got a little sad,
and I happened to be there
to comfort her.
I think it really
just takes
a little warmth
and compassion,
and she warms
right up to you.
Compassion, huh?
Mr. Malone.
Mm-hmm.
Do you realize we're
running low on seltzer?
I'm so sorry.
Ho-How can these things happen?
Is there anything I can do?
Yes, let me
know next time.
Well, of course I will.
I just hope that's enough.
Are you feeling
all right?
Yes, thank you very much.
That's very sweet
of you to ask.
Norm, I gave you
my address, didn't I?
Yep. See you tomorrow.
See you.
Whoa, what was that all about?
Just a little bit
of painting at her apartment.
Listen, uh,
you know, I can
really sympathize
with your situation
of painting.
Uh, you know, if the fumes
and everything bothers you,
you can always
spend the night at my place.
I don't think so.
That's it.
I say she's a guy.
Good night, Sammy.
Say, uh... Norm,
wait a second here.
You know... you know,
I like to paint.
Why don't I help
you, man, you know.
( scoffs )
Come on.
No. I know you.
You just want to
log a little sack
time with her.
Come on, no. The
truth is, I just...
I got to find out
if there's a real human
being in there, man.
I-I can't keep working
for a cold fish.
Please, come on.
All right.
But no funny stuff.
No, I swear to God.
I won't touch her.
I make no guarantees
about you.
You've been driving me crazy
in this little white outfit.
Yeah? You should
see me in my caftan.
( doorbell rings )
Oh, hi, Norm.
Come on in.
Thank you.
I was just...
Hi.
Oh, God.
Now it knows where I live.
Sorry, I, uh, needed a helper,
and when I checked around,
most of the fellas
expected to be paid.
And you're doing
this for nothing?
Well, it's an act
of compassion.
I'm doing this
out of the...
goodness of my heart.
Norm.
Yeah.
I'd like all
the wood here
and the moldings
done in high gloss.
Great.
You have any questions,
if you need anything,
I'll be in the back.
NORM:
Okay.
So that's where
the old bedroom is, huh?
Sammy?
What? I'm not
doing anything.
You promised.
No, I'm fine.
All right, I want to start
with, uh, sanding for you.
Here.
All right.
All right, uh,
try this post right here.
Yeah.
I'll do a little taping.
Hey, come on.
Hey, Sam.
What?
Sam, uh...
you have to do it
with the grain, okay?
Oh.
Sand with the grain.
My arm hurts
when I do it like that.
Very sorry, Sam.
That's the way it
has to be done, all right?
I don't think I like sanding.
Just try to tape one pane
at a time, all right?
I don't think I
like taping, either.
Norm.
Hmm?
It's Carla on the phone.
Your wife needs you
at home right away.
Something about two feet
of water in the basement.
( groans )
Oh, boy, that's serious.
That's, like, a foot
more than usual.
I'm sorry.
It's just a little delay.
I'll be right back.
No problem.
Sammy, can I, uh,
trust you here alone?
Yeah. Swear to God
I won't touch her.
Tragic, huh?
Absolutely tragic.
I beg your pardon?
Oh, I just couldn't help
thinking about Norm's basement.
Yes?
Well, it's not just, you know,
the water filling up.
You know,
it's those photo albums,
those old letters.
Cherished mementos, you know,
ru-ruined for...
( weepy ):
Oh, I'm sorry.
Ooh, boy.
Oh, this is embarrassing.
I-I'm sorry.
I just, uh...
( sniffles ):
I can't help feeling this way
ever since my dog, Lucky, died.
Something is going on here.
I'm not exactly
sure what it is.
Could it be that
you're jerking me around?
Okay, uh...
( clears throat )
I'm sorry.
It's just that there's
a rumor going around the bar
that you've got this soft side,
and I just thought
I'd like to see it for myself.
Maybe get to know you better.
I guess I ought to just...
Wait a minute.
I want to get
this straight.
You came over here
on your day off
to paint my living room
in hopes of getting
to know me better?
Pretty silly, huh?
What'd you want to know?
Well?
Um, I'm thinking.
I-I didn't think I was
gonna get this far. Uh...
Well, all right, all right,
Um... where were you born?
San Diego.
California, huh?
No, Kansas.
Come on.
My father's a captain
in the Navy.
My mother's an
interior designer.
My brother's a surgeon.
My other brother's an attorney.
My sister was Miss San Diego.
( mimics gagging )
The only really happy moment
of my life
is when I ran away
to San Francisco
and hung out with Grace Slick.
Do you want to know
the lyrics to "White Rabbit,"
or can I quit now?
Ah. Boy, it sounds like some
of the kids in your family
are pretty successful, huh?
Yeah, well,
if you measure success
in terms of wealth, happiness,
and my father's
undying devotion, maybe.
Yeah. Boy, I know.
I got a brother like that.
International lawyer.
Handsome, smart, funny.
And the guy plays the piano,
and he speaks four languages,
flies his own jet.
( mimics gagging )
Seems like my whole life
I've been trying to get out
from under his shadow.
I know just what you mean.
Does he ever come in the bar?
No, but, uh, I'll call him,
if you'll call Miss San Diego.
Nah. They'd probably
end up leaving together.
( both laugh )
Well, hell, this is kind of
a warm and friendly moment,
isn't it?
I must admit,
it's a... better moment
than I ever thought
I'd have with you.
I'm glad this happened.
Yeah, me, too. Me, too.
Will you excuse
me a moment?
Sure. What are you going
to do?
I think I better change.
Honesty.
Who would have thought?
Say, can I, uh--
great, great--
can I, uh,
put on some music here?
Sure, be my guest.
( jazzy music playing )
( laughs )
( Velcro unfastens )
I'm gonna be at the gym
for a couple of hours.
But you just go right on...
You jerk.
Wha... what?
This whole thing about
coming over here and painting
is just another stupid
attempt to get me into bed.
I-I am shocked and...
and deeply insulted.
God. I told you
all that personal stuff
about my brothers and my sister
and me being the fattest girl
in high school.
Wait a minute.
You didn't tell me that.
Well, I wasn't.
Get out.
Slow down here.
Just li...
I admit it.
I'm a attracted to you.
Now, what's the big deal?
Is that a crime
or something?
You know, are you
always this defensive
about people who
find you sexy?
No, just you.
Is that right?
Well... you know, I'll
tell you something, lady.
There was a time when I was
considering making love to you,
but now it's
out of the question.
As a matter of fact, you know,
I wouldn't make love to you
if you asked me,
if you begged me
to make love to you,
I wouldn't.
Go ahead, just ask me.
Just try it.
See what happens.
Would you make love to me?
Well, okay, but just once.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org