Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
CARLA:
Woody, here's
your dinner.
Oh, thanks, Carla.
Boy, I'm going to be glad
when I drop this double load.
My veins are killing me.
Your veins, huh?
Yeah, varicose veins.
I had them stripped
twice already.
How do they do that?
Surgically.
They cut a hole
in your leg,
and they pull the vein out.
No kidding?
Yeah, it's like pulling
a long, slimy worm
out of you flesh.
Gee, imagine that.
Can you believe maintaining
that postcoital tristesse
is gender oriented.
Do you mind, Dr. Crane?
I'm trying to eat.
( piano plays )
Making your way
in the world today
Takes everything you've got
Taking a break
from all your worries
Sure would help a lot
Wouldn't you like
to get away?
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
knows your name
And they're always glad
you came
You want to be
where you can see
Our troubles
are all the same
You want to be where everybody
knows your name
You want to go
where people know
People are all the same
You want to go where
everybody knows your name.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Woody, does it look
like we're going to get
a good turnout
for our auction?
Oh, yeah.
I'll bet by now
there isn't anyone in Boston
who doesn't know about it.
What auction?
We're having an auction?
It's terrific.
It's a benefit
for Children's Hospital.
All these women
get together
and they bid
for an evening on the town
with eligible bachelors.
Local celebrities,
athletes.
They raise a lot of money,
they do it every year,
and it's a great deal of fun.
Where'd you hear about it?
I must have been to one once.
Anyway,
I told Mr. Drake...
Who'd you bid on?
I told Mr. Drake
I thought
it would be great publicity
for Cheers.
Who'd you bid on?
And since it's for a good cause,
he agreed...
Who'd you bid on?
A hairy linebacker.
Are you satisfied?
Ooh.
Oh!
Were you?
( laughing )
The point is,
Mr. Drake
thinks it's a great idea.
Woody...
So, Sammy, you going to be
taking part in this auction?
Are you kidding me?
I hate that stuff.
It's one thing
for guys
to bid on chicks, but...
that's sick.
You know, as a matter of fact...
Here you go.
Excuse me.
Listen, I'm going to save
you the embarrassment
of asking and then
being turned down.
I'm not going to be
doing your auction.
So just forget
it. No way.
Not me.
Fine.
We need to create
a stage.
I think right there
as you walk in the door...
Hey, what's "fine"
supposed to mean?
Well, it means I hadn't planned
to ask you in the first place.
Oh, well, good, good.
'Cause I really don't
care for that stuff.
All right.
We need a podium.
Because the emcee
is going to be
standing at the podium,
and all the women
will be standing around...
Excuse me, one
more time here.
Why...
why hadn't you planned
on asking me?
Well, I guess
I just don't find you
as irresistible as some do.
You, for instance.
But if you want to participate,
you're perfectly welcome...
No, hey, forget it.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter to me
either way.
I'm only doing this
for charity.
You know, Vera has that
carved on our headboard.
So we're agreed then, right?
Just plain simple
gold wedding bands.
With an exquisite
marquise diamond on mine
so we can
tell them apart.
You give me such glee.
Here we are.
Sit here, my betrothed.
I'll go get us
something to drink,
and, oh, uh, exchange
a few lies with my buds.
I understand.
Your daily dose
of male bonding.
Well, not for
much longer.
You know what's are breaking
up that old gang of mine.
As a guess, I'd say
hypertension and cirrhosis.
You're irrepressible.
Sam, champagne, please.
Ah, guys.
Norm, Cliff.
Won't be long now
before the boys of the bar
are going to have to manage
without me.
Can do.
Yeah, no sweat, Fras.
Champagne, huh?
Well, wild romance
is a fictive term
with no correlation
to any actual
physiological behavior.
We, nevertheless,
like to humor convention
by going through
with these preposterous rituals.
Champagne, huh?
Hey, Frasier,
can I ask you something?
When you and Lilith
wake up in the morning,
which one of you
is the first to scream,
"What have I done?"
Well, my darling,
to us.
Thank you, darling.
It's been a lovely evening.
You've revealed
previously unsuspected depths
of romanticism.
Well, Lilith, we have
a whole lifetime
of romantic evenings
ahead of us,
but for now,
we've got to plan.
We don't have much time.
We've got to get
the wedding license,
have blood tests,
see the lawyer
draw up the
prenuptial agreement,
invite the guests...
Excuse me.
What prenuptial agreement?
Well, wherein we decide what
you are or are not entitled to
in event of a divorce.
It's merely a safeguard.
You're already
planning for the divorce?
Have you selected
my cemetery plot also?
Well, assuming we stay together,
you'll be right between me
and Cousin Lemuel.
I cannot believe my ears.
This is your idea of romance?
Lilith, man does not live
by romance alone.
He also needs hardheaded
practicality.
If your head was any harder,
it would etch glass.
Where are you going?
I have no intention
of spending the rest
of the evening,
let alone
the rest of my life,
with a compulsive,
anal retentive, chowderhead.
Now, Lilith,
let's just both stop right now
before we say something
to spoil the mood.
Why don't you go
make love to your accountant.
You know, if more people
followed that advice,
this world would be
such a happier place.
You know,
I just figured out
what you're doing here.
You're using
reverse psychology.
You really want me to be
in that auction of yours,
so you're pretending
that you don't,
am I right?
I don't care
if you're in the auction.
( laughing )
I don't care
if you're not in the auction.
Yeah, right.
I have never felt
more honestly and passionately
indifferent
about anything in my life.
I really don't care.
All right, okay, you win.
I'm volunteering, all right?
150. Do I hear 200?
200.
I hear 200.
275.
Three.
Okay, I have 300.
Anybody give me 350?
I want 350.
No. Okay,
300 it is.
Going once...
going twice...
Sold for $300!
( cheering )
Okay, okay,
I'm going to let you gals
take a breather
while we get the next big hunk
up here on the block.
( cheering )
Boy, oh boy, you can call
me a traditionalist,
call me out of step
with the times,
but I prefer to get my women
the old-fashioned way.
In a plain brown wrapper?
Ah, women.
They can talk all they like
about romance,
but what it really
comes down to
is just pure animal lust.
Is that supposed
to refer to me?
If the shoe fits.
Things a little strained
between you two?
Oh, why should you ask that,
Sam?
Just because
she's a pigheaded witch?!
So you two kids
set a date yet?
This is great.
We're just $2,000 away
from breaking the record.
How many guys
do we have left?
Just Sammy.
Oh, well.
There's always next year.
$2,000?
Oh, gee, I might actually
have to comb my hair.
Come on, you guys,
there's no way
he can get that by himself.
God, if we just had
one more hunk.
All right, all right,
all right.
Mr. Clavin, that is
a really sweet gesture...
but, um...
isn't there some regulation
against, uh...
government employees in uniform
participating in this kind
of a thing?
Oh, that is
a very salient point,
and one which I came
within a hair of overlooking.
I thank you.
I shudder to think
what might have happened.
We all do.
Woody. Woody, what about you?
You're young,
single, cute.
Come on, Woody,
what do you say?
Oh, gosh,
Miss Howe, I...
WOMAN:
Oh, come on.
( shouting encouragement )
Come on, buddy.
I don't know, I'm going
to have to give this
some very serious thought.
There isn't time.
That's okay. I'm finished.
I'll do it.
Good!
All right, man.
Shucks. I hope I'm
not making a mistake.
Yeah, I know
what you mean.
Being gawked at
and herded around
like a prized pig.
Gee, now that you
put it like that.
Yeah, sounds great.
Now we have a little bonus
for you ladies.
Please welcome
our next eligible bachelor--
Mr. Woody Boyd!
( cheering )
WOODY:
Good evening, ladies.
I happen to be a very good chef,
and your evening with me
will be a wonderful
home-cooked country meal
with all the fixin's
from my native land, Indiana.
And let me
just mention
my special ingredient--
pork.
And please remember,
this is for charity.
Who'll start the bidding
at 100?
$100.
100.
125.
Excuse me. 200.
I have 200.
Do I hear 250?
Uh, you know, I think pork
might actually be out of season.
250!
275.
Three.
( ice rattling )
I have 300.
Do I hear 325?
I'm going to go
out on a limb here, Cliffie,
and say this is not
her first time in a bar.
I have $325.
Do I hear 350?
350.
375.
Four.
I have 400.
Do I hear 450?
450.
You can't do that.
Okay...
400. Going once...
going twice...
Sold to the lady
right over there.
How do you do?
You better be good.
Yes, ma'am.
Uh, will you excuse me
a minute?
I have to do
a couple things before we go.
Cute little gal
there, Woody.
Is it me,
or is she a little scary?
Woody,
the electric chair
is a little scary.
Hey, you know, um,
400's not bad.
Now Sam only has
to reach 1,600
to break the record.
The day any woman
pays 1,600 for Malone,
I'll tattoo his name
on my butt.
Sammy,
quick,
loan me 1,600 bucks.
And now, our grand finale.
Former Red Sox great Sam Malone!
Come on up here,
Sam. Yeah!
The big gun! Whoo!
( whooping and cheering )
Thank you, thank you.
Ladies, let's see.
( clearing throat )
Your enchanted
evening with me
will begin with a
leisurely sunset drive
up to a small,
secluded oceanside inn,
where we will enjoy
a candlelit,
romantic dinner for two.
( oohing and aahing )
SAM:
Yes, yes.
And then this being
the beginning of the weekend,
who knows
where dinner will lead?
( squealing and whooping )
EMCEE:
Well, okay.
Does anyone
want to start the bidding
at, uh, say, $100?
I meant $250.
$250!
I have 250.
300!
I have $300.
Do I have $400?
500!
We're rolling now!
I see you...
575.
Do we hear $600?
600.
Do I hear 650?
You were saying?
Okay, we have $600.
Come on, ladies,
loosen
those purse strings.
They stopped at $600.
Uh, no problem. $650!
Carla, where are you going
to get $650?
Don't need it.
700.
See? All you got to do
is goose the bidding
a little bit
when it starts going down.
$900!
900!
$900.
Now, do we have 950?
Come on, ladies--
hot stuff here!
( laughter,
whooping and cheering )
I have 900.
Do I hear 950?
That's it;
they're not going any higher.
No problem. 950!
Carla.
I hear 950.
$1,000!
I have $1,000!
You can keep 'em
going all night.
$1,100!
1,100!
We are rolling!
1,200!
Do I have 1,250?
1,250, anyone?
Oh, come on,
now, ladies.
( excited conversation )
1,250!
$1,250!
Well, well, well.
$1,300.
Do I hear $1,300?
That sly Rebecca, huh?
Quite a date
you're passing up, here, ladies.
I said 1,250.
Do I hear 1,300?
EMCEE:
Come on, now, ladies.
You heard
the young lady.
Will anyone say 13?
Not me.
I'm out.
She wants him
more than I do.
1,250 going once...
No, please, please...
Going twice...
Please.
1,250,
going for the last time.
I bid $2,000.
Sold!
( cheering )
Yes, we broke the record,
Mr. Drake.
Sam, all by himself,
got $2,000.
Well, thank you very much.
Good-bye...
Mr. Drake.
( sighing )
Okay, well, here you go.
It's called Larry's
Sanitary Tattoo.
Make sure you
ask for Frank.
He likes to do it
the old-fashioned way.
You'll scream a lot.
What do you think
you're doing?
Helping charity.
Don't worry, it's just
some money I had put aside
to buy you a ring.
You are not actually
going to go off with Sam
to some inn on the
Cape for the weekend?
Why not? Did we have
a prenuptial agreement
to the contrary?
No, of course not.
Sam,
I understand
we're going to the Cape.
I'll just bring the car around.
We can stop at my place,
and I'll throw some things
in a bag.
Actually, Lilith,
you know, that
won't be necessary.
Perhaps not,
but I believe in being prepared.
I hope you do, too.
CARLA:
Wha-ho!
Sammy, looks like you're going
to get your lobster boiled.
Ah, no, I'm not.
She's just doing that
to bug Frasier.
Well, you know, you could always
trade with Woody.
I don't think
her intentions are honorable.
Sam, Sam, I...
I-I've got to talk to you.
You can't go through
with this.
Come on, man, she's
just doing it to
make you jealous.
Oh, God, I'm losing her, Sam.
Oh, would you stop that?
You're my friend.
I'm never going to take
a woman away from you.
What about Diane?
And didn't God punish
me with a vengeance?
Well, yes,
but gee whiz, Sam...
Oh, come on.
Listen, wait a minute.
There's got to be...
You know, I'll tell you what.
You know, this ought
to be a chance for me
to bring the two of
you together again.
What do you mean?
Well, all right, l-listen.
I'll pretend to go along
with the date, right?
I'll rent the room,
I'll get some wine,
and then I'll tell
her how great you are,
and then pow, you
burst in on us.
I do?
Yeah. Yeah, why not?
I mean, you
followed us up there.
It'll prove how crazy
you are about her.
She'll be putty
in your hands.
Well, it has a certain panache.
( cash register rings )
Yeah, here you go.
Here's the address.
Now, uh, be up
there by 9:00,
and, uh, just throw
me out of there, man.
Show me no mercy.
By God,
I'll send you packing!
All right.
Ready to go, Sam?
Yes, yes, you bet,
yes, sirree.
Coming.
I'm eager to get somewhere
we can be alone.
SAM:
Oh, not half as
eager as I am.
My God, look at that,
Cliffie, will you?
She's smoked about
eight packs of cigarettes.
Where does
all the smoke go?
I'm waiting to see
where it comes out.
You guys got
any last-minute advice for me?
Yeah, leave a trail
of bread crumbs.
A little more bubbly here?
Whatever you suggest, Sam.
I'm agreeable
to anything you suggest.
Ah, well, good, good, good,
because, um, quite frankly,
I'd like to talk just
a little bit more about Frasier.
You know, uh,
one of the, uh,
qualities that I admire
most about him
is his reliability.
He's always
very punctual,
isn't he?
Frasier, Schmasier.
Let's have some fun.
( uneasy chuckle )
Heck of a guy, Frasier,
I'll tell you.
( changing radio stations )
A lot of, uh,
remarkable qualities...
( smooth, sexy music playing )
( changing radio stations )
Uh... you know,
he's, uh, he's faithful,
he-he's devoted...
( jazz music playing )
And he's, uh, musical, too.
Very musical
guy, you know?
He's always, uh,
whistling something
or singing some tune.
Or making that...
that funny little
chirping noise
he makes with his lips.
What are you doing?
It's too bright.
Talk about bright.
I tell you, uh...
Frasier's just about
the brightest guy I've ever met.
You don't mind if we turn
some of these back on, do you,
in case we want to read later,
or something?
Hey, you know, Frasier
reads a lot, doesn't he?
( music continues playing )
Sam, we've talked
enough about Frasier.
Let's talk about you.
Oh, me,
well, I'm just a...
an ordinary guy
who happens to
respect and admire
the hell out of Frasier,
I'll tell you.
Smell good?
You bet; I sniff him
every time he comes in the bar.
Listen to that music.
Makes me want to do
uninhibited things.
Well, you know, that just about
wraps up our date here.
Uh, I hope you don't feel
ripped off, or anything,
but I think
we ought to be getting back.
What's your
hurry, sailor?
Well, I just thought that, uh...
All right,
good, good, good.
Yeah,
check around the bed
and make sure you haven't left
anything there.
Uh, then,
uh, you know,
to tell you the truth,
it's getting kind of late.
I'd like to, uh,
I'd like to drive back.
What are you, uh...?
( weak chuckle ):
That's very funny.
Lilith, may I,
may I have my keys, please?
Lilith, stop it;
I'm serious.
Lilith, I want my...
Lilith, I-I... don't...
I'm very serious, now.
Listen to the
tone of my voice.
Give me my car keys.
Oh, don't...
Why do you want
to go back?
We have
such a nice room here.
Nice? I wouldn't
let a dog sleep here.
Maybe the curtains
aren't that bad.
Feel that music, Sam.
Lift me down.
Oh, all right. Oh! Oh!
Dance with me.
Uh, I don't think
that's such a good idea.
Well, maybe just
a little bit.
Do you know what I always
have the urge to do
whenever I see you, Sam?
Uh, please don't tell me.
Unbutton your shirt.
( chuckling ):
Oh, oh, well...
Uh, boy, they didn't,
uh, set the clocks back
and forget to tell
me, did they?
Did you read
Lady Chatterley's Lover?
Uh, Lady Chatterley's Lover?
Uh, yes, as a matter
of fact, I did read that.
Or parts of it, at least.
I have the strangest desire
to twine flowers
in your chest hair,
( chuckles )
then deflower you.
Listen, Lilith, uh...
Mmm. Mmm.
Oh, boy. Mmm...
Aha! I found you...
...kissing!
Got her all warmed up
for you, there, Fras.
And yourself in the process,
I see.
Oh, come on.
Well, let's
just step outside,
settle this like gentlemen.
Oh, don't be
ridiculous, man.
At least do me the honor
of pulling up your pants.
All right, I will.
All right.
Now, what is going on here?
I might ask you the same.
Look, I'll ask the questions
around here!
Would you two stop sniping,
for goodness sake?
Do you have any idea
how ridiculous you look?
You two were actually
going to...
Oh, of course not.
That was only
for your sake.
What? You mean
you knew I was coming?
Frasier, darling,
yin to my yang,
I know your mind
as I know my own.
Of course I knew
you'd come.
I knew you could
do no other.
Besides, I could hear
your muffler behind us
all the way up Route 3.
And what a joke on me.
What a cruel,
wonderful joke on me.
Why, Lilith, why?
Because I was angry
about that
prenuptial agreement.
Oh.
And hurt.
Look, I'm-I'm sorry
I ever brought that up
in the first place.
It's just that I've seen
so many failed marriages.
I just wanted some insurance,
I guess.
Of course, I...
I forgot I'm marrying
the perfect woman.
Don't forget
that, Frasier.
And I certainly didn't
mean to hurt you with Sam.
By the way, what took
you so long getting here?
Oh, well,
when I first arrived,
I went to the wrong room.
Uh...
By the way,
we're having breakfast tomorrow
with Jack and Peggy
in number eight.
I'm paying.
Frasier, you dear,
sweet ninny.
I do love you, you know.
And I, you.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org