Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Hey, Sam!
Hey, Woody. Is it all right
if I hang some Christmas
decorations in here?
Sure. Boy, is it that time again?
Wow, Christmas comes earlier
every year, doesn't it?
I think if you check, Sam,
it always comes on the 25th of December.
Of course, of course, of course.
Thank you, Woody, thank you.
Oh, look at that, will ya?
Nice Rudolph.
I made him myself.
No kidding?
You know, uh, Rudolph is my favorite guy
in the Christmas songs.
Yeah.
You know, apparently
then, Woody, you're unaware
that the story of Rudolph
the Red-Nosed Reindeer
is one of the most unrealistic,
and therefore potentially damaging
in all of children's music.
It gives them a horribly
distorted view of reality.
Yeah, but you gotta admit,
it's easy to whistle.
Look, I'm serious.
You know, first the other reindeer tease
and then ostracize him.
And then when his abnormality
proves of service, they use him.
But then do they allow him to play
in their stupid reindeer games?
BOTH: Yes.
Oh, no, no, no,
I know how the song goes.
In fact,
not only do Donner, Blitzen, et al,
not love him and laugh out with glee,
but they doubly despise the
bulbous-nosed little wimp.
Well, I gotta be off.
(cheerful): Happy Holidays!
(piano plays)
♪ Making your way in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like to get away♪
♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always glad you came ♪
♪ You want to be where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You want to go where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Prithee, friends, what thinkst thou?
You look ridiculous.
I beg your pardon.
This is an absolutely authentic example
of feminine colonial headwear.
I'm sorry.
Thou lookest ridiculous.
Hey, Miss Chambers, what's
the pilgrim get-up for?
Oh, I was hoping somebody might ask.
We're gonna have to talk later, Woody.
My graduate American Literature
professor, Doctor Narsutis,
annually recreates the first
Thanksgiving dinner at his home.
He only invites two or
three favored students
to break bread with his
family and other honored guests
such as William Styron.
And guess who's going to be there?
William Styron?
Yes, Woody.
Ah, heck, anybody coulda got it
if they'd really been listening.
What a wonderful
opportunity for you, Diane.
You know, perhaps in the evening
you can establish a
rapport with Mr. Styron
while passing the yams.
Who knows? Come pie time,
he may well have taken
you under his wing
and launched you into
the literary galaxy.
Frasier, you and I are of like mind.
Except one of us is kidding.
Sam, I had thought we would
spend the holidays together,
but when you made no
move in that direction,
I made these alternate plans.
I hope it won't spoil your holiday.
Thank you. No, I, I
have, I have other plans.
Oh, good. I'm glad to hear that.
And in all fairness, I will understand
if you get an escort for the day.
It really wouldn't hurt my
feelings in the slightest.
Good. Good, good,
'cause I already have a date with Wendy.
How could you?
Now you just said that
it was okay, didn't you?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
Besides, I know that
we'll have many holidays together
when you and I are one.
You already are one, Diane.
So, what's everybody else doing?
Oh, the holidays just
kind of snuck up...
NORM: My
mother-in-law...
Yeah, that sounds like fun, too.
Well, I'm on my own this year.
Kids aren't with ya?
Nah. They're in Atlantic City with Nick.
Yeah, this is my first
Thanksgiving away from home.
I mean, unless you count last year.
Wait a second. Listen to you.
Carla, you have a new place.
You could have a little gathering.
Forget it.
Oh, come on.
What could be more enjoyable
than opening your heart
with holiday cheer?
Opening yours with a can opener?
That sounds great!
No, I meant the first
part, Miss Chambers.
Well, why not?
But it's gonna have to be potluck.
Sammy, why don't you bring
your date and join us?
All right.
Tell you what, Carla.
I'm good for dessert.
So I've been told.
You know, I'm glad to see
that you're all fending
off the holiday blues.
This time of year is
filled with arguments,
suicides, murders.
Yeah, I guess it's the seasonal
happiness of others tends
to throw a glaring light on the flaws
in our own interpersonal relationships.
But see, of course,
that's no problem for me.
I'm alone.
Wanna join us for some bird, Frasier?
Could I?
Sure. The more the merrier.
Hey, so, uh, what time do
you want us there, Carla?
What do you mean "us," Clavin?
Well, you know...
This party
is for lonelies, not homelies.
Besides, you'll be with your mother.
No, no, not this year.
Uh, she's goin' down
and ladle out some cream of something
to the folks down at the Rescue Mission.
Yeah. Oh, how sweet.
Why don't you join her?
Are you kiddin'?
I did my part this year.
I was in "Hands Across
America," remember?
Oh. Okay.
All right.
Norm, how about you and Vera?
Yeah?
No, I can't make it this year.
Why not? I mean, we never even met Vera.
CARLA: Yeah.
No, we gotta go to Vera's mother's.
Such a drag.
No beer, no TV, heat turned up to 80.
CLIFF: That's all
right, Normie, you know.
You gotta do what your
little wifey wants you to do.
You either got 'em or you don't.
All right.
You know somethin', Cliff,
you're absolutely right.
Eight years I've been goin'
to that old bat's house.
I think Vera owes me one, all right?
I'm gonna march into that house.
I'm just gonna say,
"Vera, this year we're goin'
to Carla's for Thanksgiving.
That's the last I wanna
hear on the subject."
All right! Good for you, Norm.
Okay, Norm's out.
Just count me in, all right? You'll see.
Well, my house, noonish?
WOODY: Oh, this is gonna
be the greatest, huh?
SAM: All right.
Well, I'm so relieved.
Now I don't have to worry
about my poor little
Thanksgiving orphans
whilst I sup with the literati.
Boy, you know, I don't
know who's luckier.
You, 'cause you get to
go to that great party,
or us 'cause you get to
go to that great party.
Taken down at the 40.
And there's the gun
ending the first half.
Yeah, this is just like bein' back home.
Yeah, hey, uh, Carla, look, I, uh,
I really wanna tell ya
how much I appreciate
you, uh, invitin' me over here.
Don't mention it.
I, uh, really appreciate it.
No, I mean, don't ever mention
to anyone that I let you in this house.
May I change the channel
or are you guys watching
this halftime salute
to our fabulous universe?
No, go ahead.
Oh, the parade.
And who's this flying our way?
None other than a 60-foot Mighty Mouse.
All right, Mighty Mouse!
(doorbell rings)
I'll get it.
Afternoon, everybody.
ALL: Norm!
Where's Vera?
She's, uh, she's gonna put
on a little more makeup.
That, uh, first coat didn't really take.
She is comin', isn't she?
Well, uh, maybe.
Well, what're you sayin' there, Normie?
We had the worst fight of our marriage.
Oh, it's tough.
She knew how much this meant to me
and she still insisted
on goin' to her mother's.
So I told her, "Look,
I'm goin' to Carla's.
"You wanna meet me there, fine.
"If you want to go to your mother's,
you can just stay there."
CLIFF: Brutal.
Well, you know, Norm,
I don't think you should worry about it.
She'll probably come to
her senses and show up.
The important thing is that
you're here with us now.
This is gonna be the
best Thanksgiving ever.
All right, Woody.
You know, I brought
that turkey and, uh...
Mr. P., that turkey
seems kinda big and raw.
You think it's gonna be
ready in time for dinner?
Well, I had planned on just a
bit more cookin' time, Woods,
but, uh, traffic on I-93
was bumper-to-bumper.
I-93? I took the side streets.
I got here in 35 minutes, buddy.
You didn't take Mass Avenue all the way?
I took Commonwealth.
(all talking)
I need the quickest way to
get to the kitchen right now.
Oh, yeah, come on.
I'll show you where everything is.
Oh, hey, no waitin'
around for my contribution.
Here ya go.
Popcorn balls!
Chow down, hear?
Hey, aren't these what you brought
to the Halloween party?
Well, yeah, they're a
perennial favorite, Woodman.
Yeah, but aren't these the ones
you brought to the Halloween party?
(doorbell rings)
Hi.
Oh, hi, Sammy. I thought
maybe you were Vera.
Boy, I can't wait to meet her.
FRASIER: Sammy, yo!
Hey, Sammy! Hey, Sam.
So, uh, where's your date?
Oh. Well, there's a change of plans.
Her sister showed up from out of town
and they didn't like my idea,
so what the hell, you know?
Hey, guys.
Hey, yeah, watch the parade.
You know, the important thing
is that you're here now, huh?
We're all here.
This is gonna be the greatest.
Yeah. Who needs family?
You know, Woody, you're right.
Family is not necessarily
limited to blood relations.
That's right.
Uh, this is much better
than, uh, hangin' around
with a bunch of dingbat
cousins all day long
that you don't get to
see but once a year, huh?
Yeah, or waiting for some
duddy old aunt to show up
(doorbell rings) and spoil all your fun.
Gobble, gobble!
(doorbell rings)
Come on, open the door.
No, no...
It's Thanksgiving, Carla.
Oh! Okay...
maybe she'll choke on a drumstick.
Yeah.
Thank you, Carla.
Hello, everyone.
Hi, Miss Chambers.
Hey, uh, Diane.
Ooh, Carla, I like what
you've done with the place.
What do you want?
Well, I decided that I'd
rather be among friends
than with my stuffy old professor.
Oh, dear, oh, dear.
What happened?
Oh... Come on.
I'm afraid my golden
afternoon turned to dross.
I thought it was clouding up.
The moment I arrived at
the home of my professor,
I was greeted by a man with a
clipboard who handed me a tray
and told me to serve a
daiquiri to Ms. Radziwill.
Oh...
We students were
invited as domestic help.
(Carla giggles)
That might be all right when
you're a wide-eyed 19-year-old,
but it's certainly not all
right when you're... not.
We're all... we're very sorry, Diane.
Thank you, Sam.
Yeah.
Well, at least you told
that pinhead off, didn't ya?
Oh, I dropped the
tray, burst into tears,
took a moment to freshen
up my mascara, and fled.
The important thing is
you're here now, huh?
This is gonna be great.
Would somebody put a gag on Andy Hardy?
You know, Diane, if I were you,
I'd call that guy up
and nail his sheepskin to the wall.
You're absolutely right.
Hey, better yet.
Why don't you go on over
there and tell him in person?
Yeah, good idea. Yeah, that's right.
Hello, Dr. Narsutis?
This is Diane Chambers.
I... yes, the one who fled.
Listen, I... I beg your pardon?
Well, yes, of course
I accept your apology.
He's invited me back.
Go, go. Go.
Dr. Narsutis, I'm sorry, I can't.
I'm here with my friends,
my support system,
and there's really no
place I'd rather be.
I trust this won't affect my grade?
Thank you.
Good day, sir.
Turned him down, huh?
Now that I find myself in
the warmth of your company
how could I possibly go?
Take Mass Ave.
I-93.
You holiday hooligans.
Give me a beer.
So, Sam--
Thanks.
Where's your date?
Oh, change of plans.
Her sister showed up.
Of course she did.
Chortle, chortle.
No, I'm serious.
I had a date and it fell through.
Oh, you don't have to convince me, Sam.
I believe you.
I'm telling you the truth.
And I love you for it.
How's the turkey doing there, Norm?
I'd say pretty good
for about five minutes.
Oh.
Hey, half-time's over.
The game's back on.
Oh, great.
Oh, you're watching sports?
Hey, don't worry about it, Diane.
Game's almost over.
Oh, I hope so.
ANNOUNCER: ...knocked away
and it's incomplete at the 45.
Yeah, I deliver his mail.
Isn't this game over yet?
Not yet.
Well, their uniforms
are different colors than before.
Uh, well, they gotta change them
every time they score
a touchdown, Diane.
Hey, Normie,
where the hell is that bird?
Cliffy, it's a big turkey.
So are you.
ANNOUNCER: ...with a
tremendous body slam!
Now wait a minute!
Diane, Diane, you're absolutely right.
You know, let's turn it
back on the football, guys.
There you go. No, no, no!
Enough is enough!
I don't think watching television
was the pilgrims' original intent
when they created the holiday.
Well, uh...
No, hey, hey, hey... Hey, come on!
All right, all right,
look, look, look, look,
the turkey's probably almost done.
Let's just adjourn to
the dining room, huh?
All right!
I second that emotion.
Okay, we'll be sitting
boy-girl,
boy-girl.
Clavin, you can sit anywhere.
Somebody save me a seat.
I got to see a man about a horse.
He doesn't really have to
see a man about a horse.
All right.
Well, what do you say
we, uh, dig into this, uh,
Jell-O surprise here?
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh...
we're not eating
until the turkey is on the table.
Everybody went to a lot of bother
to make this fine meal.
We're not going to eat it in pieces.
Keep your hands off the food.
Listen, guys, the, uh,
turkey's not exactly brown just yet.
What color is it, then?
Off-white.
(all moan)
But I've reset the timer
and I turned up the gas.
I expect the little pop thing
will be popping out any time now.
Great. Well, I hope it
hurries 'cause I'm starved.
Well, I suggest we take
advantage of the delay
and engage in one of
my family's favorite
little Thanksgiving traditions.
Sam, I know you're
standing in the hallway.
Get in here.
Rats.
In lieu of grace,
we stand up and take turns
toasting that for which we are thankful.
Since you're already standing,
Sam, why don't you begin?
All right, I'm, uh...
I'm thankful that I have a
super car and a cool stereo
and that I'm not dressed
in a pilgrim's outfit.
(chuckling)
I'll drink to that.
You make a mockery of everything.
Oh, well...
Hey, can I go next?
I don't see a line.
(chanting): Woody. Woody. Woody.
(chuckles)
Uh...
I'm thankful that I'm an American.
Hey, all right.
I'm thankful for the upbringing
my parents gave me.
Uh, I'm thankful for all the friends
I've made in Boston.
And, uh...
I'm thankful that I can do this.
Yo!
Put it away.
(chuckling)
Hey, can you guys do this?
Oh!
That makes my thing look kinda stupid.
I can wiggle my ears, watch this.
You guys ever see tongue push-ups?
Look at these ears flapping.
Watch this.
Please, please!
We are not here to be thankful
for strange things we
can do with our bodies.
Norman, you're next.
Well, I'm thankful that
there's a turkey in the kitchen
that needs to be checked.
Yeah. Yeah, get the damn thing out here.
(everyone talking)
All right, I guess I need
to give you an indication
of what I had in mind.
Now I, too, am very
thankful for my health
and for my dear friends.
But on this very special occasion,
my mind goes back over the years
to the people who have influenced me.
And I would like to name
some of them for you.
Teilhard Chardin...
George Sand...
Caravaggio...
Oh, Emily Dickenson...
the Buddha...
Frank Lloyd Wright...
...Jean d'Arc...
Shari Lewis and Lamb Chop.
Uh, guys, uh, listen,
I'm having a slight, uh, problem
with the damn bird, all right?
What color is it now, Norman?
Well, I think we're moving
into the earth tones.
This better be good news, Norm.
Look, uh, I'm sorry, guys.
The little pop thing won't pop out.
There's something wrong with it.
There's something wrong with you.
No, no, it's the little pop thing.
Hey, could somebody please explain to me
where the little pop
thing is on the turkey?
I mean, 'cause maybe it's
different in the city,
but in the country where I come from,
turkeys aren't born
with little pop things.
The little pop thing has a name!
It's called a thermometer!
Now can we all please say "thermometer."
(yells): Thermometer!
Thermometer, yeah!
We can say it till
we're blue in the face.
It's not gonna make
it pop out any faster.
I think something's wrong
with your oven, Carla.
Hey, my oven was just fine
until you stuffed Birdzilla in it.
Come on, you guys, come on.
We don't have to bite each
other's heads off here.
It may be the only thing we
get to eat this day, Sammy.
Hey, you guys, this is Thanksgiving.
And I still say this is
going to be the greatest.
Oh, who the hell do
we think we're kidding?
We're all a bunch of pathetic dropouts.
Scorned by our loved ones,
as if anybody ever loved us at all.
Hey, will you lighten up, man?
The only thing wrong
here is we're hungry.
Now who else wants
to join me in these...
ice-cold potatoes?
Hey, they'll go great here
with the, uh, Jell-O soup.
I'm dying to try some of the hair
growing on the crudités.
Well, pass me my peas.
I made them so I know they're okay.
Was that remark, uh, directed
at me, Carla, by any chance?
No, it was directed
at your stupid turkey
and your stupid stuffing
and your stupid gravy.
What's wrong with my gravy?
Oh, nothing, except you could
walk across the skin on top of it.
Oh, well, I'm sorry, Julia Child.
Here's your perfect peas.
Oh, look, I spilled one. Sorry.
Thank you.
Norm, I'm sorry about what
I said about your gravy.
All right.
It's okay. Fine.
And so are the carrots.
Uh, anybody want some of
these, uh, lovely yams?
Woody, would you care
to test the gravy skin?
People! People! People!
Stop this immediately!
I have never been witness
to such a silly, soph...
Sam Malone...
kiss your butt good-bye!
Food fight!
(yelling)
I knew this was gonna be the greatest.
Huh?
Good bird.
Hey, Diane, may I say
you look saucy in cranberry.
(chuckling)
Laugh while you can, Sam.
Just remember that revenge is a dish
best served cold.
You won't know when and
you won't know where,
but I'm going to get you.
Now that we're done with dinner,
I'd like to make a
toast to our loved ones
who weren't fortunate
enough to be here with us.
Nice thought.
Uh, Mom, Dad...
Uncle Fergie...
My kids.
All right, Vera.
Yeah. Ma.
Coach. ALL: Yeah.
Oh... God bless you all. Very nice.
Well, I think we're
about ready for dessert.
Yeah.
Everybody get enough to eat?
You know, I never had a
chance to try the potatoes.
(doorbell rings) I'll get it.
Oh, well, here, let
me, uh... Oh, thank you.
There you go, man. Sure.
NORM: Vera. You came.
Honey, I'm so happy.
Hey, you guys, uh...
Come on, Vera, come on
in, meet all the guys.
This is great. We
finally get to meet Vera.
Sam...
think fast!
Everybody, this is, uh, Vera...
VERA: Charming friends, Norm.
Get your coat.
NORM: Yes, dear.