(Sam)
cheers  is filmed before
a live studio audience.
Hey, woody.
I'll have a nice,
tall iced tea.
Yeah, in just a second,
dr. Crane.
I gotta take
a couple of aspirin.
I got a splitting
headache.
You know,
there's a school of thought
that suggests
that all physical pain,
headache, earache,
stomachache, what have you...
a headache.
Pay attention.
Thank you.
Anyway, these people say
that those pains are
merely physical manifestations
of some deeper trauma,
either psychological,
emotional, or spiritual.
See, suppose you just relax
and try to remember
the very thing
you were thinking
when the headache
first started.
Then we may be able
to get to the root
of the problem.
All right. Well,
i was, uh,
i was standing here,
and i was thinking about
how when i was a little kid,
i was the only kid
in my town who
didn't have a bicycle.
Ok, go with that.
I mean, all the other kids
had one. Why not me?
Excellent. Continue.
And then i bent down
real fast to pick up
a napkin and--
[thudding]
[sighing]
i hit my head again!
So what do you think
it is, dr. Crane?
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Making your way
in the world today
takes everything
you've got
taking a break
from all your worries
sure would help a lot
wouldn't you like
to get away
sometimes you want to go
where everybody
knows your name
and they're always
glad you came
you wanna be
where you can see
our troubles
are all the same
you wanna be
where everybody
knows your name
you wanna go
where people know
people are all the same
you wanna go
where everybody
knows your name
(carla)
last week on cheers...
now all we
really know is that
robin is using
my--my secret password
to break into my corporation's
confidential files.
And from the date on these,
well, it looks like he's been
doing it since...
well, since the day after
we first slept together.
So all i think we can really
conclude from this is that
i am too stupid to live!
Rebecca. My darling.
What are you doing?
I'm turning you in.
You used me.
And don't try to deny it
because i've got proof.
Robin, i'm a human being
and i deserve to be treated
like one.
Well, it's about time
i stood up
and did what was right.
Goodbye, robin.
Rebecca.
Will you marry me?
Ok.
No, whoa, whoa, wait.
Excuse me, excuse me.
But, it's-- it's not
rebecca's fault.
It's not her.
It--it's robin colcord
who planned this whole
hostile takeover thing.
I mean, she called this
meeting to warn you.
It's not her fault.
Do you have any evidence
to back it up?
Yeah, you bet i do.
You want evidence?
Look at this.
If this doesn't clear
rebecca's good name,
i don't know
what will, huh?
I mean, look at it.
[People chattering]
hey, wood,
you see the paper?
No. I don't read
the paper anymore.
It's too depressing.
Many people feel
that way, woody.
Yeah, i mean, uh, lucy's
always pulling the football
away from charlie brown.
The lockhorns
are always fighting.
Henry still doesn't
have a mouth.
Woody, woody.
Front page.
Look who got indicted
for insider trading.
Wow.
That guy looks exactly
like robin colcord.
Whoa! He even has
the same name.
Hey, let's kid him about it
when he comes in, huh?
Woody, this is obviously
the same robin colcord
that we all know.
Well, then it'll be
even funnier.
Well, it's always good
to see justice done.
But i--i have to tell you,
i hate to think
of the poor man in prison.
Those wretched places
are filled with
the worst degenerates
and most worthless dirty scum
ever on this planet.
Frasier,
why would you say that?
Well, i was
a prison counselor.
You know, very often,
i was their only friend.
So what do you suppose
will happen to mr. Colcord?
Well, i suppose he'll get
the full measure of the law.
You see,
this country is sick and tired
of these corporate raiders
that have plundered
our economy.
The days of junk bonds
and wall street deals
are behind us.
Although i--i do hear
there's some good
penny stocks out there.
Say, you know,
i think i'll give
my broker a call.
Good morning, everyone.
Well, mr. Colcord,
what a surprise.
I hate to bring up
a sensitive subject,
but shouldn't you be
receiving love letters
from a certain
one-eared gentleman
named turk about now?
Excuse me?
Oh, you're referring
to my arrest, uh...
robin is out on bail,
and it looks like
he'll probably get off.
He has a clean record,
and this is his first offense,
and i think the judge
will be very lenient with him.
Oh, i must run.
I've got a meeting
with counsel to discuss
my defense strategy.
Can't let you be
the bride of a convict, hmm?
If he goes to jail,
he'll be the bride
of a convict.
The social life
of those people is shocking.
Bye-bye, sweetie.
Everything is gonna
turn out fine.
That's the way
we'll be kissing
on visiting day
for the next 20 years.
I thought you were so sure
he was gettin' off.
Are you kidding?
He'll fry.
Street lamps will dim.
Rebecca,
they do not fry people
for insider trading.
But what if they do, norm?
What if they do?
I mean, i love that man,
and i'm just about ready
to lose him.
Have you ever thought
what it would be like to be
without vera for 20 years?
Oh, my god.
You see?
You'd miss vera.
Oh, i thought you said beer.
Oh, hey, rebecca.
There you are.
You heard
they got him,
huh, sam?
Yeah.
Yeah, i really feel
terrible about that.
I--i want you to understand--
i don't know
what happened.
I thought that,
and i really feel
ashamed to say this,
but i thought
that you ratted on robin.
But then i realized
you would never do anything
that indecent,
and i know that no matter
how much you hate robin,
you would never jeopardize
my happiness like that.
Oh, boy, uh, you really
know me better
than i know myself.
Well, i'm gonna go
freshen up.
Every time i cry like this
i get all red and swollen
and puffy and raw.
And that's just your ankles.
Goodbye.
Poor kid.
Just when it looks like
things are gonna
work out for her,
like she's gonna finally
achieve her life's dream,
her--her heart gets broken,
and her whole life
is shattered yet again.
Yup. You can just about
set your watch by it.
Mr. Malone, i'm glad
i caught up with you.
The board of directors
is anxious to reward you
for saving our corporation.
(Cliff)
savin' the corporation?
Uh, yeah, uh...
well, thanks.
Why don't you just, uh, send
me a calendar or something?
Oh, no, no, no.
Sam, you're being
much too modest.
We know you've been
trying to buy back this bar
for some time now,
and we've decided
that, as a token
of our gratitude,
the least we can do
is sell it to you
at a reduced price.
You're kidding.
How much?
$1.
Take it
or leave it.
This bar?
I--i give you $1,
and--and this bar is mine?
That's right, mr. Malone.
No catch.
I can't believe this.
This bar is mine, and all
i have to do is give you--
oh, shoot, shoot, shoot!
Hey, give me $1, huh?
I'm tapped out.
Anybody.
W-woody, give me $1, man.
Now, you already
owe me $1, sam.
Come on.
Sam, i got a quarter.
Oh, hey, hey, sammy,
here--here's a dime.
Here, here,
here's 4 bits.
Great.
I, uh, ok, i--i got,
uh, 85 cents here.
Hmm, i'll take it.
All right!
Hey, guys,
i low-balled him.
There's the title deed,
mr. Malone.
[Exclaiming]
sammy, what's going on?
I just bought the bar back.
Sammy's got the bar back!
What?
[All cheering]
(all chanting)
sammy's got the bar back!
Sammy's got the bar back!
Shut up!
Some of us might be depressed.
Hey, sam got
the bar back, miss howe
what?
Goodbye, mr. Malone.
Yeah, thanks very much.
Well, it's the least
we can do for the man
who gave us colcord.
You turned robin in!
You are a dead man, buddy!
You are a dead man!
(All chanting)
sammy is a dead man!
Sammy is a dead man!
My bar.
It's my bar.
My glasses, my tables.
[Gasping]
my, my.
Sammy,
i am so proud of you.
Yeah!
[Laughing]
hey, hey. I know
how we should celebrate.
Yeah?
Why don't you just take me
right on top of the bar
like you did
in the old days.
I never did that.
Then who was that guy?
Oh, that was
the manager of the bar
where i worked before this.
Hey, can anybody give me
a ride to the broken spoke?
Hey, guys, guys, huh?
Remember this, huh?
All right.
(All)
hey.
Yeah, you've been gone
too long, big guy.
[Exclaiming]
well, somehow,
everything feels all right
with this world tonight.
Yup, it's only been
a few hours, cliffie,
but the air smells fresher,
stool's a little
more comfortable,
and the beer tastes better.
Ok, guys.
Closing time. Beat it.
I don't know if i like
the new owner, though.
Come on, norm,
i'll give you a ride.
(Frasier)
well,
warmest congratulations, sam.
You know, it's always
heartening to see a man
realize his dream.
Especially poignant
when he realizes
such a pathetic dream.
Thanks, man.
Oh, i only joke with you,
sam, because i love you.
Well, i didn't know
you were joking.
[Sobbing]
oh, i didn't know
i loved you.
Uh, fellas, fellas,
you want-- you want
to give frasier
a ride home here?
[Sobbing]
i love you all, i...
well, it's all right
for a man to cry, you know.
(Norm)
you're sitting in the back
with the windows open,
frasier.
(Carla)
sammy?
Yeah?
Woody and i are so happy
to be working for you again.
And we're not
the only ones.
[Cackling]
yeah?
Hey-hey, dave!
I missed you, sammy.
Yeah, i missed you, too, dave.
[Laughing]
actually, that was me, sam.
Yeah, i know, woody,
i know.
Sam, uh...
i'd like to, uh, apologize
for my earlier outburst there.
I guess i just got
a little over-emotional.
Dave!
[Sobbing]
is that dave?
Dave is back.
I love you, dave.
Come on.
You're riding on the hood.
Hey, sam,
is it really all right
for a man to cry?
Absolutely not, man.
I didn't think so.
No.
I'm leaving now.
Don't anybody look at me
or talk to me.
Hey, well, no, i can't let you
walk out like this--
hey, wait, listen to me.
I only turned him in
because i thought that
they were gonna go after you.
You're right.
I should listen
to your side of the story.
Yeah, all right, all right.
It's about time.
Would you stop it?
Hey, hey, hey.
Let go of me!
I wanna get out of here!
I just took my stuff
from your office,
and now i'm leaving.
Miss howe,
you're leaving for good?
I mean, i guess i should have
realized that you would,
but now that
you actually are...
[sobbing]
i'm gonna miss you.
Don't those push pins
belong to the bar?
Woody, woody, woody,
it's all right, man. Don't--
yeah, whoa. Now what?
These index cards?
And these staples?
Woody, she's upset.
Well, she's taking
all our stuff, sam.
This is even our box.
Woody,
shut up, will ya?
Oh, this my sweater!
Woody, shut up! Come on!
You just take
your own damn stuff.
I don't wanna be reminded
of this stupid place anyway.
Oh, wait, miss howe,
this isn't my sweater.
But if you don't want it...
come here.
Listen, i can't let you
walk out like this.
Y-you got to
forgive me.
Please.
All right, i forgive you.
I wish you well.
Goodbye.
And i hope you're happy
with your crummy bar
and your stupid friends,
and your trampy waitress.
Goodbye, carla.
It was nice working with you.
You, too.
I'd just like to say,
that men have treated me
like dirt all my life.
So?
I just like to say that.
Keeps me humble.
Thank you, carla.
Where you gonna go, hmm?
Wherever robin is.
I'm starting
a new chapter in my life.
The mrs. Robin colcord years.
Goodbye, sam.
Agent munson, f.B.I.
Do any of you have
any knowledge
of the whereabouts
of a mr. Robin colcord?
Why? What's the matter?
We have reason to believe
he's jumped bail
and left the country.
Well, why would you
think that?
Well, it seems,
he's destroyed
his personal files,
wired all his money
to switzerland,
and flown his private jet
out of american air space.
Ok, rebecca,
now it's your turn.
Repeat after me.
Men have treated me
like dirt all my life.
Oh, honey--
oh, don't "oh, honey" me.
I don't need an "oh, honey."
This doesn't prove anything.
I think robin's
been framed.
Hey, miss howe,
a fax just came in
for you from mr. Colcord.
So, have any of you seen
colcord in the last 24 hours?
Look, i'm not gonna
say a word.
You could tie me
to a hard chair
and work me over
under hot lights all day.
We wouldn't do that.
Well, you could.
Especially him.
Oh, my god.
What's it say?
It says, um...
"dear, rebecca,
goodbye forever. Robin."
What does that mean, sam?
Well,
"dear, rebecca," that's you.
No.
I know what it means,
but, i mean,
what does it mean?
Does it mean that he left me,
and you were right all along,
and he was just using me?
I'm sorry.
I can't believe it.
Anything we can do?
[Sobbing]
no.
You just go ahead and leave,
and--and i'll lock up.
I'm just gonna...
you know, cry it out.
So, how's rebecca
doing this morning?
I don't know.
Let's go ask her.
[Sobbing]
she looks better.
Uh, what the hey, cliffie.
She's a survivor, huh?
Shoot some stick?
Honey, you ok?
Yeah.
[Gasping]
i'm fine.
May i have
another glass of water?
I'm starting
to dehydrate again.
You're gonna have to
snap out of this, sweetheart.
Why? I don't have
anything to live for.
Oh, come on.
You got plenty
to live for.
Hey, what do you think,
you're the only person
who's ever been dumped?
Look at sam.
He was in this
horrible relationship
with this woman for years,
and it ended up
she ditched him
at the altar.
What did he do?
Look, he took
all his money,
he bought a boat,
he sank it,
then he had to
grovel around here
for tips for 3 years.
But look at him now.
He got his bar back.
And all he had to do
was turn in your boyfriend.
[Sobbing]
oh, forget it, man.
There's no cheering her up.
Come on, sweetheart.
You're a beautiful,
bright woman.
You got a great career.
Oh, there's a letter
for you, miss howe.
Why don't you just
go ahead and read it, woody?
It's probably just
another letter from robin
telling me to get lost.
Uh, no.
It's from the corporation.
You're fired.
[Sobbing]
i'm fired!
I'm fired!
Oh, god!
God, they're blaming me
for this whole thing
with robin.
Well, actually it says here
they never much cared
for your work.
Woody, don't.
Come on,
what does this matter?
Listen, this is sammy
talking to you.
As long as i got a bar,
you--you got a place to work.
No, i don't think
i could go back
to managing this bar.
Oh, and i don't--
i wouldn't want you to.
No, i--i was thinking
more of you being a waitress.
A waitress?
Yeah.
Carla could train you.
[Cackling]
[sobbing]
boy, you know,
you're right.
There's no
cheering her up at all.
So he asked me to marry him,
obviously
meant nothing to him.
He hops on his jet
and leaves me here to rot.
Can i have my drink?
You know,
you men are all alike.
Yeah, so where was i?
Uh, you were engaged
to one of the richest men
in the world.
Can i just have my check?
Are you a man?
Sure.
Woody, i'm gonna need
some more drinks.
What kind?
Doesn't make any difference.
Rebecca, can i speak to you
for a minute, please?
What is it, sam?
Is it my break time?
I wanna know
why you're driving
everybody out of here.
Why--why are you
attacking all the men?
Because they are evil slime.
Oh, come on.
Not all men are evil slime.
Oh, yeah, sure.
You would defend them.
Carla, will you please
take over for rebecca?
What's the matter
with that waitress?
She keeps throwing drinks
in people's face.
Well, she's heartbroken.
Her boyfriend
left her, and--
and she's feeling
a little bitter.
Here you go.
Then what's her problem?
She's just mean.
Look, i know
you are going through
a hard time here,
but, you know,
there comes a point
when you have to face reality.
I do not have to
listen to you.
Oh, would you
cut that out?
What? What are you
gonna do, fire me?
No, wait, wait, wait.
I got a better idea.
Tell me you love me,
ask me to marry you,
skip the country,
and then fire me.
Hey, stop it!
I am not robin!
I'm not doing
those things to you.
You know something?
I'm sick of getting kicked
in the teeth
because someone else
dumped you.
Well, i am sick
of getting dumped.
I'm sick of you
getting dumped.
You know somethin'?
You know what i'm
really sick of?
Your own face!
No, i'm sick of you--
i'm sick of you
getting angry at me
when all i'm trying to do
is help you.
Well, you can't help me.
I'm beyond help.
You can't help somebody
who's done everything wrong
since the day she was born.
Oh, stop it, will you?
What have i done right?
Well...
you got excellent taste
in clothes.
What?
This old thing?
Well, yeah.
But everything else.
I've been wrong about men,
i've been wrong
about my career.
You know, if i'd just done
everything the opposite
of the way i did it,
i probably would've had
a very happy life.
Well, what's that
supposed to mean?
[Sighs]
it means that
i really loved robin,
and he ran off.
And the man i've been
pushing away all these years,
is right here
caring for me,
giving me a shoulder
to cry on.
God.
Life is so weird.
[Sniffs]
sam, kiss me.
[Gasping]
listen,
i think
this is wrong, honey.
I said wrong is
what i do best.
I just--
i just don't want us
to do anything here
that you're gonna regret.
That's all.
Fine, fine.
Maybe you're right.
[Panting]
is rebecca in her office?
I thought you ditched her
and skipped the country.
I did, but i've come back.
I finally realized
what rebecca means to me.
What use is my money
or my freedom
if i don't have
the woman i love?
Rebecca!
I'm back!
(Robin)
oh, my god!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org