Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
I don't know, Eddie.
Try-try under the bed.
Well, if they're
not there,
look in the back
of the closet,
or behind the
dresser,
or in the washing
machine.
Yeah, if-if you still
can't find them,
call me back.
I swear to God,
that man would
lose his head
if it weren't
bolted on.
What's, uh...
what's up there, Carla?
Eddie wants to
take the twins
for a walk.
Uh, can't find his shoes, huh?
No, he can't
find the twins.
( piano plays )
¶ Making your way
in the world today ¶
¶ Takes everything you've got
¶ Taking a break
from all your worries ¶
¶ Sure would help a lot
¶ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ¶
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles are
all the same ¶
¶ You want to be where
everybody knows your name ¶
¶ You want to go
where people know ¶
¶ People are all the same
¶ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ¶
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
Oh. Excuse me.
No, no, it was my fault.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm just fine.
But how nice of you to be
so completely concerned.
Well, you know, you can't be
too careful these days.
Yeah.
So, uh,
when's your baby due?
I'm not pregnant.
Oh. Well, then
I really am sorry.
Excuse me.
Well, why don't you just watch
where you're going then
next time, Buster?!
Sam,
does this outfit
make me look
like I've put on
a little weight?
The outfit?
Uh, yeah, no.
That's what
it must be.
Right, yeah.
Turn around.
Let me see.
Yeah, blame it
on the outfit...
You know, you've been wearing
an awful lot
of fat clothes recently,
haven't you?
Oh, just shut
up, butthead.
She called me a butthead.
I think I'm gonna cry.
Oh, don't
worry, Sam.
It only looks that
way from the back.
Want another beer, Mr. P.?
Love to, Woody, but
I got to get back
to painting Frasier
and Lilith's place.
This is the first job
anyone's given me
in, like, four months,
so I'm not going to do anything
to jeopardize it.
I'm really making an effort
this time
to be the kind
of dependable professional
that I'd like
to have working for me.
See you, Mr. Peterson.
What, Wood?
I said, I'll see you.
Well, damn it, Woody.
Now you made me late, man.
All right, as long as I'm late,
I'll just have another beer,
I guess.
Oh, much
better.
Yes, much
better, yes.
You know, I never thought
our wedding portrait
lived there.
Um, where should it go, Ivan?
Here's a spot.
Perfect.
Why clutter a home
with mementos?
Did I tell you last night
I programmed myself
to dream about your space?
You didn't.
We're thrilled.
Hmm.
To begin with,
we lose this wall.
Uh, by lose,
do you mean
we redesign it so that it
practically disappears,
or lose, we knock it down
so that we're left
facing the back of our stove?
Hmm... fret not.
We'll be transforming il cucina
into an atrium.
I love this idea.
I adore it.
But what about eating?
I design, I don't eat.
Now, over here I imagine
removing the ceiling
and extending the wall up
to the second story,
culminating in a skylight
to flood the room
with natural illumination.
But, uh...
that's our...
that's our bedroom up there.
Is that all
you people think about,
eating and sleeping?
Tell me this was a gift.
Doctor, might I have a word
with you?
Certainly, Doctor.
How do you feel
about Ivan?
Feel? Look,
the man is one of the most
famous designers in the city.
He's been written up
in every magazine
from Metropolitan Home to HG.
He's got more awards
on his shelves
than we have shelves.
I'd like to beat the crap
out of him.
Maybe we should
let him go.
If that's your final decision,
my cherub, I concur.
The heave-ho.
Wait.
At the risk of
sounding sexist,
I do believe this
is man's work.
It requires
a firm hand.
Please feel free to leave
the room if you must.
This could get
unpleasant.
Sir.
You're too good for us.
Your masterful design
would make our poor
little lives
just seem drab
by comparison,
and of course,
we'll, uh,
see to your severance
pay, two weeks?
Six months?
IVAN:
Fine.
I can't tell you
what a once-in-a-lifetime thrill
it's been to bask
in your talent.
Uh, bye-bye now.
Watch the steps.
Huh.
I only hope he can recover
from that tongue lashing.
So, dandelion,
now that you've given away
the farm to Ivan,
do you have some
Swiss bank account we can empty
to pay another decorator?
Well, I'll go that one better,
Dove bar.
I submit
that between the two of us,
we have enough taste
and intelligence
to redesign our
own habitat,
sans outside help.
Bite me, I love you.
I take back my bite.
We suck.
Much better.
Much better!
Pardon me?
Yes, by simply
moving that chair,
an intimate conversation area
is created,
at the same time, opening up
a new traffic pattern
that gives the entire room
a whole new dynamic
sense of flow.
Plus, I can spackle behind here.
Of course, if...
if you really want a better shot
at the intimate thing,
I'd, uh, take these, uh--
what do you call it--
these Louis Couture's jobbies,
uh, and move them over like so.
Get the table...
over this way.
Okay.
Now, this table
would have to come
like yea.
Right?
And, uh,
sofa could come around
this way.
Of course.
Okay?
Now, uh,
that desk has got to come out
of there, you put the piano
into the bay,
all right?
That chrome and glass,
you put into the harbor.
Uh...
I tell you what.
I'd-I-d move
into the warm tones, all right?
Reupholster, redrape,
the whole damn thing.
Splash a little bit
of paisley around.
Throw down a nice
Bukhara rug.
Top it off with a fine piece
or two of chinoiserie,
and we're there.
Well, bite us, Norm,
we love you.
So, uh, what
do you got in
there, Woodski?
Oh, boy.
My Aunt Edna's killer
fudge brownies.
Ooh, killers, huh?
Yeah, they're
called that because
the first time
my Uncle Ford ever
smelled them baking,
he came running in
from the field and
got hit by a combine.
He hung on for
a few days.
At the end, he was
just praying to die.
Well, eat up,
everybody.
Hi, everybody.
Oh, hey, Rebecca.
Want a brownie?
Oh, I'm sorry,
I forgot.
Moment on the lips,
a lifetime on the hips.
CLIFF:
You know,
Rebecca,
I don't know why you're so, uh,
concerned about your figure.
You know, back
in the Renaissance
time, uh,
full-figured women
were revered.
Get out.
It's true.
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah.
Artists would only paint big,
voluptuous women.
In fact, that's how they got rid
of a lot of their old paint.
You know,
speaking
of, uh, weight
and stuff,
I got
a riddle.
Which is heavier,
a pound of
Cliff's brain
or a pound of
dead flies?
It's a trick question.
A pound is a pound.
They both weigh the same.
Go ahead, ask me another
of Mr. Clavin's brain questions.
Okay, let's see.
Uh..
( clears throat )
if you dropped
Cliff's brain
and a bowling ball
off the top
of the Empire
State Building...
Yeah? Yeah?
Well...
Norm, we had to rush over
to tell you.
The new window treatment
you designed just went up.
It is spectacular.
Are you speaking
to another Norm,
or do you have a death wish?
Beg your pardon?
Come on, come on.
You think I want these people
to know
I'm an interior decorator?
We're sorry, Norm.
It's just, we simply
cannot moderate
our approbation.
Well, give it a shot,
okay?
But you should
be decorating
professionally.
Oh, no, no, no.
Please.
Doing you folks a favor
was one thing.
Any more
of this interior decorating junk
could really eat
into my reputation
as a lazy, beer-guzzling lump
of mashed potatoes.
But, Norm, you have a gift.
Gift?
Try curse, pal.
I spent my whole damn life
trying to cover up the fact
that I have a great sense
of color,
and I always know
where to stick the ottoman.
Oh, it's a pity.
You see, we've just met
this new couple,
and they-they need a decorator.
Dearest, Norm has made
his feelings clear.
Yes, but they're
very well off.
Frasier, it's not
a matter of money.
They're willing
to pay five figures.
But, Frasier...
Hey, Elvira, back off.
If the left side
of Cliff's brain
leaves New York
on a train traveling
at 65 miles per hour,
and the right side
of Cliff's brain
leaves L.A. on...
Wait, wait, wait.
Let me get a pencil.
Yeah!
Damn, I am good.
Bring these people on.
I'll wipe up the floor
with them.
Who are they, anyhow?
Well, actually, they're friends
of friends.
NORM:
Yeah?
But I have to warn you-- they're
the essence of the Y word.
That's the yuppie word
for yuppie.
NORM:
Oh.
Are you implying
that I'm a yuppie?
Oh, forgive me, I erred.
If I ever do it again,
you may cut out my tongue
and serve it to me in a fajita.
( doorbell rings )
Yup, here we go.
Uh-huh.
I'm going to take one last look
in the kitchen.
Hi, we were just
talking about you!
( chuckles )
Kiss-kiss.
Yes, yes.
Sorry we're late.
We couldn't decide
whether to take
the Range Rover or the BMW.
Oh but don't keep
us in suspense.
The Beamer.
Well, we're all here now--
what fun.
Uh, Kier Royales all around?
Super.
That'd be
great, Fras.
I can't get over
what your decorator
has done with this place.
It's warm, it's solid.
It's real.
It's super.
Oh, hi, what's going on?
Hi...
Kim and Robert Cooperman,
I'd like you to meet
our decorator,
Norman Peterson.
Hi.
KIM:
How do you do, Norman?
Great.
You know,
this is the last cold beer.
We could split it or something?
No, thanks,
we're taken care of.
Okay, well, suit yourself, huh?
Sit down everybody.
It's beautiful and functional.
You know, uh,
Frasier told me
a little bit
about your place,
so I did take the
liberty of, uh,
jotting down
a few ideas.
Uh... excuse me.
Are those cocktail napkins?
Yeah, I'm sorry,
did you need one?
No.
Veggie pâté?
Oh, yes, yes, please.
I'm on empty over here.
Anyway...
I heard your place
is pretty modern, you know?
And most of your stuff
is kind of gray.
So I thought, maybe, you know,
some, you know,
color would be good.
Uh, actually, we hadn't
totally sold ourselves
on the concept of change.
NORM:
Oh.
You could keep, uh,
some of your old stuff,
and, you know,
throw in some new stuff, too.
Um...
Fras, uh, could you, uh,
help me with
this wall treatment?
Sushi?
I rolled it myself.
What's going on?
I'm dying over here.
Well, it's not you, Norm,
it's them.
Yeah?
They're narrow-minded,
trend-sucking dilettantes,
who insist that...
well, their chefs be French,
you know,
that their mechanics be German,
and that their designers be...
...stylish.
Ooh.
You mean, stylish.
Very stylish.
'Nough said, Fras.
I'm sorry, Norm.
This could have been
a real lucrative job for you.
I don't know what to say.
That's okay, I do.
Um...
( sighs )
Listen, uh,
did I tell you that, uh,
last night, I programmed myself
to dream about your... space?
Miss Howe, I don't
mean to insult you,
but you're looking
kind of puny.
Have you lost weight?
Is this a setup?
Did Sam tell you to say that?
No, ma'am, I told
myself to say it.
Yeah, I'm worried
about you, you know?
If you're not careful, you're
going to start wasting away,
and pretty soon your
ribs will start to show,
like this guy back in
Hanover, Kyle Lefferts.
Of course, he'd
been dead awhile
when they found him.
Thank you, Woody.
That's the nicest thing
anyone's said to me all week.
Your hair's been looking
kind of ratty, too.
Unfortunately,
that's the second nicest thing.
What, no kiss?
No, I've got
to weigh myself.
Oh, we got your scale back here.
What's it doing behind the bar?
We needed it
to settle an argument
about how much
Mr. Clavin's brain weighs.
I think I am in for
a pleasant surprise.
SCALE:
Your weight is 162 pounds.
( laughs )
What?!
SCALE:
Have a nice day.
Malone!
Get out here!
I know what you just did!
Congratulations.
Not you, I was
talking to...
Forget it.
Okay, okay, look.
Cliff's brain
is found murdered in a room.
All the doors
and windows are locked.
Good, he's here.
Hello, Norman!
What's going on?
Oh, hi.
No, no, no, let's,
uh, let's sit up here.
Um, well, Dick
and, uh, Tracy.
How did you ever
track me down?
It's the address
on the cocktail napkin
you did your sketches on.
( gasps )
You're good.
You know, Norman,
we've never been
in a gay bar before.
Yeah.
It seems
just like a regular bar.
Oh, honey.
Look at those two.
Anyway, how about some drinks?
All right. Miss?
Oh, uh, no, no,
I'll take care of it.
He's kind of touchy
since the operation.
Yo, Woodo, uh,
my friends and I need a couple
of, uh, white wine spritzers
and a beer... spritzer.
You feeling okay?
Sure, very manly,
never more so.
Spritzers á trois on the way.
Thank you.
You know, Norman, we didn't just
pop in here on a whim.
We love the work you did
on our place so much
that we want you to do our
mountain retreat next.
( sighs )
Gee, uh, I-I don't know.
My schedule's kind of...
We know it's an inconvenience,
all right,
so can we double your rate?
Only because I love you kids
so much.
Listen, if you could
scope it out this weekend,
that would be super.
Super.
Super!
( Kim chuckles )
I'm glad you can make it,
because we have another friend
who we've been dying
for you to meet.
And he's really cute.
( Kim laughs )
Um... he?
Unless somebody's
already snapped you up.
Well, yeah, darn it,
I have been snapped up.
By, um...
that fellow over there.
The one who had
the operation?
Bite your tongue! No!
No, the, uh,
tall hunk
rinsing glasses.
Wa-Wait a minute.
Isn't that Sam Malone,
the pitcher?
Oh, I've heard of him.
Didn't he used to play
for the Sox?
Uh...
Yes, yeah,
but now he plays for me.
KIM:
Oh.
Oh, man, the guys at the gym
are gonna freak!
No, um...
Why don't you
bring him over
and introduce him to us?
Uh, I think he's probably
a little bit too busy right now,
um...
All right, all right,
I'll, I'll get him.
( clears throat )
Sam, can I have a word, please?
Yeah, now, come here.
Sam, uh... I need
a favor, pal.
Okay, I have
these clients,
and they're big
fans of yours.
Oh.
And, uh,
it'd mean a lot
if you could just come
over and say hi to them.
Oh, no problem.
Thanks so much, Sammy.
Thanks, bud.
Oh, and uh,
one more thing, man, okay?
We're lovers.
Kids, this is
Sam Malone.
Sam Malone, this is Kim
and Robert Cooperman.
Pleased to meet you.
You sure do
make a cute couple.
Just accept
the compliment, honey.
Thanks.
I have a confession
to make.
We came in here tonight
to try to fix Norman
up with another man.
Naughty, naughty.
But since the two of you
are together,
how about if the
four of us spend the
weekend at the cabin?
It'll be a hoot!
Is that good for you, Sam?
What do you mean
is it good for me?
It stinks for me, man.
Come on, I can't.
I can't hack this.
Don't do this to me.
Listen,
I like babe...
I love babes,
and babes love me.
Babes.
"Babes" is his pet word
for linebackers.
Norman, I pride myself
on being a very
perceptive person.
Now, is something amiss?
Yeah.
Sam and I have had a tiff.
Look.
Maybe meeting Michael
is just the thing you need.
I mean, he lives
right around the corner.
Kim, go call him.
No. No-no-no-no-no,
folks, please.
I can't go on with
this any longer.
Look, I don't care if
it costs me the job.
I got to tell you
the truth, okay?
I wanted to be
your decorator,
so I pretended to be who I
thought you wanted me to be,
but... it's time that I
came out of the closet.
I'm straight.
Impossible.
( laughs )
No, no, I-I...
Ever since I
was a little boy,
I've known that
I preferred girls.
Actually, I'm a
guy with a wife.
I mean, uh, I
sleep with Vera.
Well, you know,
I sleep next to her.
Actually, it's in the room
next to her,
but, uh,
I do keep the door open.
( sighs )
But the point is, you know,
I think you should judge people
for what they do,
not for...
who they do.
You're absolutely right,
Norman.
I can't believe
we've been the perpetrators
of this kind of
discrimination.
( sighs )
We'll see you, Norman.
No, well, listen...
Hey, folks,
I could still, you know,
decorate your mountain
retreat there.
Kim and I happen to be
people of principle, all right?
And we put our trust in you,
our faith.
We trusted you with our most
prized possession, our home.
And how did you
return that trust?
You lied to us,
you betrayed us.
You made fools of us.
I could do it for half price.
Here's the key.
There's Perrier in the fridge.
If the neighbors ask,
you're a plumber.
Gotcha, can do, can do.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
( sighs )
How 'bout those
Celtics, huh?
What, what,
what, what?
What?
( scoffs )
Norm?
How could you do this to us?
What? Do what?
We're your best friends.
I mean, I can't believe that
you didn't feel close enough
to... share this part
of your life with us.
This part, what?
Guys, I'm straight,
I'm not gay.
No, no.
Who cares about that?
You can get stuff
at wholesale.
I need a sofa.
Yeah?
And I could use a lamp.
And, uh, can you get me a deal
on a good Bacca lounger?
All right, all right.
But I have to tell you folks
that I am not cheap.
Even for your lover?