Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
This is sick.
Just stop harassing me.
You'll get your money
when I'm good and ready.
And if you try
to contact me
at the workplace
one more time,
I'm gonna turn you over
to the authorities!
Jerk.
Which one of your
kids was that?
That was not one of my kids.
I don't talk to my kids
that way.
Bill collector, then, huh?
No,
it was my mother.
Her Social Security check
is late, like it's my fault
she's getting old.
Did you hear the way
she talked to her mother?
I could never talk
to my mother like that.
Hey, Carla,
could you give my mom a call?
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
It's the Crane
Family Circus.
Let the mayhem ensue.
SAM:
All right,
you're here, let's go.
All right, Sam, what
is the big mystery?
Where are you taking us?
Oh, I wanted to have it be
a big surprise,
but I can't keep it
to myself any longer.
Freddie, who would
you like to see
more than anyone else
on your second birthday?
Oh, Sam, you got tickets
to the Nanny G concert--
the 1992
Tickle Tummy Tour.
SAM & LILITH:
# Tickle your tummy #
♪ Life is kind of yummy ♪
♪ When you're feeling crummy ♪
♪ Just look up
and laugh a lot. ♪
Somebody hand me a blunt
instrument, please.
Here you go.
Use it label-side-up
so it doesn't crack.
Thanks, you're a doll.
Look,
you kids, uh,
go to the concert without me.
Frasier, this is
Frederick's first concert.
Yes, and this is my bugging out
of Frederick's first concert.
I intend
to do this
all through his childhood
and teenage years.
Then, finally,
when he's in his mid-20s
and he comes
to me and says,
"Father, let's go hear
Bobby Short at the Carlyle,"
I'll turn and say, "Son,
now you're talking."
Frasier, you're missing the
whole point of this concert.
The show for us
is not on the stage.
It's in the delighted eyes
of your child.
Oh, right, delighted eyes,
shiny face, yada yada yada.
Well, let's go
see Nanny G.
SAM:
Come on.
Nanny G?
I saw her Itsy Bitsy World
concert and fell in love.
Her in a peasant blouse...
boing!
I just don't understand
why people don't
expose their children
to good music anymore.
When I was a lad, my
parents took me to see
Peter and The Wolf,
The Nutcracker Suite,
Swan Lake, not...
♪ Tickle your tummy ♪
♪ Life is kind of yummy. ♪
See, it's catchy, isn't it?
Well, sure, when I do it, but
I can sing the phone book.
Hey, guys, how you doing?
SAM:
Hey, Woodrow.
How's it going?
What are you
doing here, man?
Eh, took a chance,
called a scalper.
Money talks.
That's great.
Where are you sitting?
Oh, I'm up in the second balcony
next to the last row.
At least I'm not
in the last row.
Those poor suckers.
(chuckles)
Oh.
Say, uh, these
are nice seats.
Aren't they, though?
I don't suppose
anybody would want
to trade me.
You know,
someone who wasn't, say,
as devoted a lifelong fan
as I am.
Sam?
You could at least
make eye contact.
Hey, Freddie, I'll
give you ten bucks.
Woody.
Now we can enjoy
the show.
(both chuckle)
ANNOUNCER:
Boys and girls of all ages,
it's showtime.
And who are you here to see?
ALL:
Nanny G!
WOMAN:
I can't hear you.
ALL:
Nanny G!
I still can't hear you.
Come out in the damn audience!
You'll hear 'em just fine!
ALL:
Nanny G!
(lively music plays)
(cheering)
♪ Tickle your tummy,
life is kind of yummy ♪
♪ When you're feeling crummy,
just look up and laugh a lot ♪
♪ Ha-ha-ha-ha... ♪
I know I've seen her before.
Where, where?
I hate it when this happens.
Frasier, please
be quiet.
I'm trying to
hear the lyrics.
♪ ♪
♪ And nothing you can do
will turn that... ♪
Oh, my God, I know who she is.
That's Nanette Guzman.
Who?
My first wife.
Uh, I was just talking to Sam.
And what were you
saying to Sam?
Your first wife?
Wow.
Isn't that a kick?
I thought I was
your first wife.
Daddies, you all stand up
and clap with me.
Okay?
♪ ♪
Frasier, sit down.
I'm a daddy.
What else have you
lied to me about?
Darling, I... I'm sorry
I didn't tell you.
I just couldn't seem
to find the right time.
I guess
I-I just loved you so much
that you made me forget that
there ever was another woman.
Oh, serve
it on toast.
Lilith, Nanette and I were,
we were just kids.
I was first-year
med school.
It only lasted
a few months.
Well, I barely
remember her.
I remember her cat better--
Bobo Black Paws.
He used to love to sleep
on my naked back.
Oh, God, he used to purr like
an airplane when we were...
Shoot,
I can't remember.
It's all gone.
(giggles)
(song ends, cheering)
Thanks so much.
You know what?
My favorite thing
in the whole big, wide world
is making new friends.
(slow intro plays)
Oh, I'll bet.
♪ When you meet someone ♪
♪ Who might become
a friend to you... ♪
So, Frasier, have
you been married
to any other well-
known performers?
If, for instance, we
should take Frederick
to the circus
next month,
should I feel threatened
by Jojo The Dog-Faced Girl?
♪ I... want... to... ♪
♪ Shake your hand... ♪
Lilith, you have got to get
a handle on this thing.
The marriage was
a silly mistake.
We rectified it.
We went on with our lives,
we've never spoken since.
If we ran into each other
on the street,
she wouldn't know me
from Adam.
♪ I want to shake your hand,
shake your hand ♪
♪ You and I... ♪
Oh, my God. (sighs)
(music stops)
Don't you want
to shake my hand?
She shook everyone's hand.
She even kissed some guy
in the fourth row.
They don't shake your hand
in row YY in the second balcony.
Oh... no.
They'll happily charge you
$28.50 a pop,
but that don't buy no handshake
in double Y.
So Frasier was married
to that-- oh,
how would one
describe her?
Bitch.
Never even told me
about her.
Well, if that's what he wants,
he can have it.
♪ I want to shake your hand,
snatch you bald ♪
♪ I want to scratch
your eyes out ♪
♪ I want to drain your blood
and replace it with a... ♪
♪ Mercuric chloride,
formaldehyde ♪
♪ And alcohol solution. ♪
(laughing)
You had to be there.
Boy, never seen this side
of Lilith before.
I like it.
Oh, I know
what Lilith's going through.
When I was in high school,
I used to date this guy--
Corky Pasavak.
He was in drama class, but he,
but he was still real macho.
Anyway, one time he asked me
to go to the movies,
and when we were walking
down the aisle
we ran into his old girlfriend.
I don't even know
why I'm telling
this story;
I mean, I'll just end up...
(quavering):
...getting a lump in my throat,
trailing off...
(sobbing):
...and bursting into tears.
Not this time,
damn you, not this time!
Well, I think that
was a new record.
Where is Lilith?
She's in the ladies' room.
Hey, Fras,
heard you used to be married
to a children's singer.
What's the matter?
Burl Ives
turn you down?
Look, am, am I the only one
who was ever married before?
It's history,
it was a long time ago.
So I didn't tell her.
So what?
Yes, Frasier, but why
didn't you tell her?
Hmm?
Marriage is built on trust,
you know.
You ever told her how
you really feel inside?
Have you ever
shared with her?
Have you ever cried with her?
You're right, Norm.
I should have told her about it.
I, I'll never forgive myself.
That was beautiful,
Normie.
Where'd you get it?
Last week's Matlock.
I don't know what he
got the guy off for,
but that was his summation.
Oh, it's my first husband.
Now, cut that out.
Where's my son?
Where's Frederick?
Did you sell him to the gypsies
so you could spend more time
with Nanny G Spot?
It was perfectly innocent.
Oh, Frasier,
let's just not talk about it.
You say it was
a youthful indiscretion.
I'll take you
at your word.
I can do that because
I'm secure within myself.
I've also had
a wee bit of Dewar's.
So it's...
it's really behind us?
Yes, just don't mention her.
The chapter is closed.
So, in other words,
you don't want her to come
in here and apologize to you.
No.
(door opens)
Hi.
Storm over yet?
Time to make a rainbow?
Lilith, I'm so sorry
if I caused you any pain.
I would have hated it
if anybody had kissed my husband
the way I kissed yours.
I guess
I've just always been a...
a kissy person.
(chuckles)
A huggy,
kissy person.
Give me a big hug.
I'd really prefer not to.
Lilith is not
a huggy person.
I know someone who could
never get enough huggings.
Well...
Well, I feel like
I want to hug you.
You don't have to hug back.
(humming)
And you didn't.
Nanny G, I was wondering
if you could...
Lilith, I'd really like
to make this up to you.
...ignore me like
a cheap piece of trash.
"Oh, you could?
Thank you so very much."
I have a super idea.
Frasier tells me you're
having a birthday party
for your little boy tomorrow.
How about if I
come by and sing
for the kiddletinos?
LILITH:
Oh, well,
actually, it's not really
going to be
much of a party.
It's just a small
family gathering.
NORM:
Oh, hey, if, uh,
Nanny G's going to sing,
you know Vera's
nieces and nephews would
love to come.
It is free, isn't it?
Sure is.
CARLA:
Oh!
My God, wait till
the twins find out.
I'll be their hero.
I couldn't get tickets
to the concert.
Guess I should've tried.
It's free, right?
Actually, as much
as I'd love to invite
all of you and
your little folk,
the party's going
to be in our own home,
and, frankly,
it's much too...
well, I just don't
want you there.
Well, I'll tell you what,
why don't we have it in the bar?
Before we open,
tomorrow morning; it'll be fun.
Well, that's settled, then.
See you all tomorrow.
And don't forget
to have goofy dreams.
You know, most people would make
that sound corny, but...
Yeah, well, I'd better, uh,
make some phone calls.
I've got a whole neighborhood
full of brats.
If I bring 'em, they'll, uh,
probably tell me
where my car is.
Darling, are you going
to be okay with this?
Am I going to be
okay with this?
Let's see.
Earlier today I discovered
that my husband
had an ex-wife
he never told me about.
Then I had the pleasure
of watching him kiss
said ex-wife in front
of a thousand children,
including his own.
Then, to top it all off,
she hugged me.
Can you deduce from my tone
whether or not
I'm going to be
okay with this?
Baby, you're the greatest.
Pretty good eats,
huh, Norm?
Not bad for a two-year-old.
I, myself, have been enjoying
these teeny little
tuna fish sandwiches shaped like
tiny little dinosaurs.
Yeah, quite ironic
actually, uh,
seeing as how tuna, known
in Latin as Pisces middayicus--
roughly translated
as "lunch fish"--
was, uh, was not
a contemporary of the, uh,
prehistoric reptilian
land wanderers.
Hi, pal.
You want some
apple juice?
Okay.
Frasier, where's the Nanster?
Oh, she'll be here.
You can always count on Nanette.
You know, I, I can't
get over
her becoming
such a big star!
Although she always
had a gorgeous voice.
Personality... God,
she'd light up a room
when she entered it.
Really?
I wasn't making a direct
comparison, dear. It's...
You and, you and Nanette
are apples and oranges.
But you are by far
the finer of the two produce.
And which one would that be?
Uh... app-ranges.
Look, allow me to preempt
any further discussion
by simply saying that
you are the love
of my life.
And nobody,
nobody could ever
pry my eyes from
your beautiful face.
She's here!
(applause)
Hi.
♪ Who is turning two today? ♪
♪ Who today is two today? ♪
♪ Freddie's turning two today ♪
♪ Hoo-de-hoo
de-hoodley-hoodley-hoo today. ♪
(applause)
FRASIER:
Isn't she wonderful?
You know, I used
to be married to her.
But now I've got
this honey.
Happy birthday, Freddie!
And...
a big hello
to the birthday mother.
Great, now I'm going
to smell like gingerbread
for the rest of the day.
Cliffie.
Huh?
You smell gingerbread?
Yeah, let's
hunt it down.
My goodness, Frasier.
I can't believe you have
such a big, wonderful boy.
Frasier and I
weren't together
long enough to have
any children.
Although we sure did
try a lot, didn't we?
I, uh, I don't remember.
I do.
Hey, Nanny G.
Hi, I'm Carla.
Hi, hello.
And these are my twins,
Jesse and Elvis.
My, they're glorious.
Thanks, thanks.
They're a little shy,
but they'd both like
an autographed album.
Why, sure.
"Love, Nanny G."
It's for you.
Would you like an autographed
album for your little girl?
Oh, that's so sweet.
Twenty bucks.
They grow up so fast.
Oh, sure, she's got lots of time
to hook the little consumers.
Oh, Woody.
Have a Fruit Loop necklace
and chill out, will you?
Come here.
Say, Nanny G?
Yes?
Somebody here wants
to meet you.
Come on, come on.
Oh, no, Sam,
you don't have to introduce us.
I recognize this fellow.
The next to last row
of the balcony,
section YY.
I couldn't forget your smile.
Although I haven't
seen it since.
There it is!
I, I...
I love you, Nanny G!
You think he bought it?
Yeah, he's an easy sale.
Good.
Hey, no cuts!
You're not
the boss of me.
You like that stool?
Yep.
Drink pretty good there?
Tell you what, kiddo...
Here you go, scoot, go on.
Wish someone
would've done that for me
when I was seven years old.
Mommies, daddies,
boys and girls...
half a bar full of people
I've never seen before...
I'd like you to gather
around here at the steps
for a special sing-along
with Nanny G.
She saw me!
She saw me in the theatre
from a hundred miles away.
She's magic.
Nanny G is magic!
Get a life.
Well, my, my,
my, oh, my.
Well, I was going
to start by singing
"The Doodle Bug Song."
(cheering and applause)
Thank you.
But instead,
I want to begin by singing
a very special song
for a very wonderful boy.
♪ The first time ♪
♪ Ever I saw your face ♪
♪ I thought the sun rose
in your eyes ♪
♪ And the moon... ♪
Why is she looking
directly at you?
She isn't looking at me.
She's looking in the general
direction of our loving family.
I think she's singing
the song to you, Frasier.
Oh, you're being paranoid.
She's singing a lovely song
to a two-year-old child.
♪ The first time ♪
♪ Ever I lay with you... ♪
All right!
That's it!
Stop the music!
Leave my man alone!
I'm sorry,
I can't help it.
Frasier, I've never
stopped loving you.
Well, maybe this'll help!
(groans)
Girl fight!
You know, I'm going to suffer
for this tomorrow,
but today, right now,
this exact moment,
I'm the happiest man on Earth.
Girls!
Well, Lilith, the bleeding's
finally stopped.
(whistles):
Those head wounds.
Serves you right
for trying
to get between us.
Darling, I, I had to stop
the two of you.
Although I must say I was
proud to see you
fight for me.
It made me feel so loved.
Of course, Nanette
was pretty vicious, too.
Oh, but you were
by far the most vicious.
Thank you.
Lilith, I...
I should have told you
about my first
marriage before, but...
I just didn't
think it was
relevant to our
lives today.
Frasier, I know
why you didn't tell me.
You didn't tell me because
you're a craven coward.
You know me so well,
it's frightening.
Can you ever forgive me?
I suppose I'll have to.
You know, if I must say so,
you hug better than she does.
Frasier, you're such a toady.
Yes, but I'm your toady.
Dr. Crane, I didn't
want to interrupt you
while you were bleeding,
but, uh, I found this box
underneath one
of the tables over there
when I was sweeping up
Nanny G's hair.
"To Frederick from Nanny G."
Oh, look!
It's a little
Nanny G doll.
(chuckles)
Oh, it says "push here."
♪ Here's a silly
little song ♪
♪ To help you out
when things go wrong ♪
Isn't that cute?
♪ If you get lost
and can't find home ♪
♪ Just remember the number
of your phone ♪
♪ My number is 555-6792 ♪
♪ 555-6792... 555-6792 ♪
♪ That's 555... ♪
Frasier, this is
her phone number.
She's giving you
No, she's not.
She doesn't want
you to forget it.
She's just using it
as an example.
♪ 555... ♪
Oh, Lilith, no, don't do...
(song stops)
There, gone
and forgotten.
NORM, CLIFF & WOODY:
# 555-6792 #
♪ 555-6... ♪
Whoa!
Whoa! Hey!