Cheers is filmed before
a live studio audience.
What do you want to
do tonight, Cliff?
Eh, I don't know.
What do you want to do?
I don't know.
You guys!
You do this
all day long for hours.
Face it, Rebecca, we're bored.
Nothing ever happens
around here.
(steady beeping, Rebecca gasps)
Oh, my God!
Hey, it's Andy Andy.
What, you know this person?
Yeah. Former major felon.
Once killed a waitress.
(beeping continues)
Where's Diane?
I demand to see Diane!
Well, Miss Chambers
hasn't worked here
in five or six years.
Oh, really?
Well...
okay.
So, what do you want to do?
(theme song begins)
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot ♪
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna be where
everybody knows your name ♪
♪ You wanna go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Well, well, well, so Maggie
O'Keefe is back in town, huh?
Couldn't get enough of
the Old Clavin monster, I guess.
Who's-who's Maggie O'Keefe?
That's Cliff's old girlfriend.
I'm sorry, Cliff's what?
Oh, no, no, no, I've been
thinking about you, too.
What?
Aw, come on, I can't say
that in front of the guys.
All right.
I love you, too.
That was Ma!
Maggie's back in town!
So, how long has it been
since you've seen Maggie?
Oh, about six months.
She, uh, skipped off to Canada
for a while, you know, and...
according to Ma,
she's back in town, wants to see me.
I guess she's just looking for
a booster shot of "vitamin CC."
Yeah, maybe things just
didn't work out in Canada.
Yeah, I'll never forget when
my Uncle Orlo left Hanover to
seek his fortune in the big city.
You know what happened?
Terre Haute just
chewed him up and spit him out.
Yep, he came back
with his head between his legs.
Actually, I think the
expression is "tail between his legs."
Oh, no, there was
a train accident on the way back.
Yep.
It's a real tragedy.
Yeah, a year later,
he drowned in a sitz bath.
Guess what I kept seeing
as I was driving
into work just now.
The middle finger
of every driver in Boston?
No. The new ad campaign
for Gary's Old Towne Tavern.
He's got billboards,
buses, tops of taxis, he's got everything.
I'm telling you that guy's
business is gonna double.
Yeah? Well, what
am I supposed to do?
Well, I think that we
should do some advertising.
Maybe we should do a
commercial on the radio,
you know, a jingle,
something real catchy.
No, I don't want to do
a jingle- that's stupid.
You know, Sammy's
right there, Becs.
What you want is a
word-of-mouth campaign.
I'd be happy to help, you know.
I'll talk it up
down at the old post office.
Before you know it,
this place will be wall-to-wall
with letter carriers.
Now, you think I'm entertaining?
Multiply me by a hundred.
Jingle!
Jingle! Jingle!
♪ ♪
Well, Miss Howe, you
have certainly come
to the right place-
I'm gonna hook you up
with our very best composer.
Send in Jason.
We should probably
talk about budget now.
Yes.
I am prepared to spend
as much as $200.
Keep Jason.
Somebody wake up Sy Flembeck.
Oh, advertising.
You know, I almost
went into advertising.
I bet that I would've
been real good at it,
because I am
really good with, um...
Oh, God, what is that when
you call and people are...
you get two people and
they're talking to each other?
You mean communication?
Yes!
I have a real
knack for that. Oh.
So, it's curtains for me, huh?
The old "Adios, Flembeck."
I knew this day'd come.
I gave this firm
the best years of my life.
It turns around and kicks me right
in the old haemorrhoid hotel.
Pardon my French, babe.
Well, before I go,
let me tell you something,
Mr. Pimply-Faced Teenager
Who's Running the Shop
This Week.
I wrote "Chocolate, chocolate,
who ate my bar?"
when you were still dangling
from your mother's breast,
you cheap S.O.B.!
Sy, we've got a job for you.
You didn't let me finish!
You have to be that way,
'cause you're a leader!
Leadership has its price,
and I respect that,
and I respect you!
Does it show?
The love, I mean?
Well, here you go, Miss Howe.
$200 worth of perfection.
Yeah, well, let's go
to my cubicle, babe.
We'll throw some
ideas at the wall and see if they stick.
(whispers):
This is so exciting!
This...
is Cheers.
Great.
Where's the old 88's?
Oh, right over here.
Listen, do you think you can
write something for this place
that's really gonna capture
the spirit of Cheers?
But you have to do
it right away,
because, you know, there's a
lot of competition out there.
Hey, let me ask you something.
Why don't you put a little
more pressure on me,
'cause I haven't had a stroke
in about two months. Thank you.
Sorry.
I'm sure you'll do a great job.
Of course I will.
Perhaps you heard
my humble efforts
for Fred's Tune-ups.
(plays arpeggio flourish)
(to "Old MacDonald Had a Farm"):
♪ Tune-ups, tune-ups, that's our game ♪
♪ F-R-E-D-S ♪
♪ If you don't come here,
that's a shame ♪
♪ F-R-E-D-S ♪
♪ With an F-F here... ♪
Everybody!
♪ F-F there... ♪
FRASIER: Excuse me!
Isn't that just
"Old MacDonald's Farm"?
When Old MacDonald
pays me 200 bucks,
it'll be "Old MacDonald's Farm."
Look, Cliffie, when is, uh,
when is Maggie actually
gonna show up here?
Yeah, where is this
alleged girlfriend of yours?
Well, uh, Paul,
I'm sure there's
a very good reason
why she isn't here.
Well, thank you, Carla.
Namely that Clavin
dismembered her
and stacked her in his freezer.
Yeah, you know, the police
took that call of yours
very seriously.
(laughing)
Missed a half a
day's work, thank you very much.
Poor Ma didn't know
what to think.
She tossed out
a whole year's worth
of Omaha steaks
trying to protect me.
You must be pretty excited
to see Maggie, huh?
Oh, yeah.
Darned excited, Sammy.
Yeah, boy, when we're together,
we're the hottest
couple imaginable.
Yeah, I got the hormones,
the drive, the needs.
Yes siree, yeah, my body's
like one big erogenous zone.
Five, four, three...
What are you
doing, Carla? Counting down.
I'm about to launch my lunch.
Oh! Oh, look at that!
Here comes Maggie now.
Yeah, well,
I'd just better stand firm.
I mean, nobody ties Cliff Clavin
down, that's for sure.
She can have me back,
but, uh, no commitments.
Mark my words.
Hey there, baby.
Remember me?
I sure do, Cliff.
Or should I say "Daddy"?
How is he?
Oh, I'm sure he's fine.
Hey, how's
he doing there, Fras?
Oh, better, I think.
Carla volunteered to bathe
his face with cold water
and was doing fine until
the seat came down on his head.
I should go to him.
No. Trust me,
I'm a doctor.
I've seen many cases of shock.
What I suggest that you do
is go out for a while,
give Cliff time to
regain his composure,
and then you can come
on back, sit down
and have a nice little chat
with him about, uh...
Well, whatever it is
you wish to discuss with him.
Thank you, Doctor.
Perhaps it was a bit much
to spring on him. Yes.
Tell him I'll be back
in a little while. All right.
Well, from our "things you never
thought you'd hear" category,
that woman is carrying
Cliff's child.
Come on, buddy.
Where is she?
She had to step out
for a little while.
Hey! Ha! I'll be damned!
Let me be the first
to congratulate you, Cliffie!
Uh, thanks, Sam.
You dog, Cliffie!
Yeah.
I got to say, man, I'm shocked.
How come?
Well, you know, I mean,
you always claimed that
you and Margaret were,
you know, doing it,
but, you know, I never really,
you know...
I'm just surprised,
is all, Cliff.
So, she's pregnant
with your child.
You gonna go through
Lamaze, or, uh,
do you figure it'll just
burst out through her chest?
Why'd you do it, Cliff?
I begged you
to get yourself fixed.
I even offered to pay for it.
Hell, I offered
to do it for you!
SAM:
Come on, come on, you guys.
It's celebration time here!
Hey, drinks on the house-
my friend's gonna be a daddy!
OTHERS:
Yeah! Yeah!
You are gonna marry her,
aren't you, Mr. Clavin?
It'd be a shame
to have to stone her.
Well, uh...
I-I guess you do,
uh, things differently
back there in Hanover,
don't you, Wood?
America's Heartland.
Well, I don't know,
I should have expected it.
I mean, the, uh, Clavins
never fire blanks.
We're breeders, spawners.
My loins are brimming
with vitality.
Well, I'll never eat again.
Anybody else?
Let's get your mother
on the phone
and tell her about it, huh?
Get her down here, we'll have
a little celebration.
There you go.
Good idea, Sammy.
But, uh...
What?
Could I, could I see you?
Well, uh, what do
you think Cliffie will have- a boy, a girl?
Is there a third choice?
Sammy, you know,
I-I-I don't, uh,
I don't think that's my baby.
Why not?
Oh, well, let's
just say that, uh, you know,
sometimes studs know.
Remind me again how studs know.
Well, you know,
sometimes studs just choose to...
well, you know, wait it out.
Cliff, you-you never actually
had sex with Maggie, did you?
W-Well, that depends
there, Sam.
Define sex.
Oh...
Now, you know,
we, uh, we meant to,
but we just never really got
around to it, there, Sam.
You, uh, still think
I'm a stud though, don't you?
Oh, yes, of course I do.
More than ever, man,
more than ever.
Yeah. You know,
sometimes it takes, uh,
it takes a bigger stud,
not to have sex.
What the hell does that mean?
I don't know, man.
I'm just trying to help you.
Work with me here, will you?
Aw, Sammy, I'm such a failure.
I feel so ashamed of myself.
No, no, don't do that, Cliff.
You know, uh, lots of people
don't have sex on dates.
Hell, I've dated lots of women,
never had sex with them.
That's kind of hard to believe
there, Sammy.
You're not working
with me here, Cliff.
Let's, uh... Wait a second.
I don't get something here.
Now, if it's not your kid,
how come Maggie's
coming in here and calling you "Daddy"?
Uh, that's easy.
She's setting up a trap for me.
All right, put yourself
in the frame of mind
of the female psyche.
Now, she goes off,
gets herself pregnant,
looking for a husband,
provider, best friend, lover.
Okay? First name
on top of her wish list.
Cliff Clavin?
Bingo.
So, what do you think, Sam?
I mean, I-I don't know
if I'm ready to get married or not.
Well, you don't have to.
It's not your kid.
It's not your responsibility.
Yeah, but, you know,
I was out there
in front of the guys braggin'
about my sexual prowess.
Well, hell,
they don't have to find out about this.
You know it's none
of their business.
Well, yeah,
but what do I tell them?
Tell them, uh, that you weighed
the pros and cons,
and at this point in your life,
you don't feel like marriage
is the right thing for you.
Hey, that's great,
Sammy, great. Thank you.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, stud handshake.
Uh, oh, well.. Oh!
All right.
There you go.
Hey, uh, listen, Sam,
just to, uh, you know,
set the record straight,
just 'cause I didn't have
sex with Margaret,
uh, doesn't mean I haven't
bagged my share of chicks.
No, I know that.
I know you do.
I'm a pretty sexy guy.
You know, women
sort of pick up on that.
Yeah.
Want to know my secret?
Don't wear any underwear.
It's too restraining.
That's, that's super, man.
Thank you.
Thank you for sharing that.
I've got a little
announcement to make.
Margaret and I will
not be getting married.
See, I've weighed
the pros and the cons...
That's not your kid, is it?
Uh, no.
See I've weighed...
You and Maggie didn't
do it, did you?
Well, no.
(laughs)
Look, I didn't tell you guys
'cause I didn't want you to,
you know, think any less of me.
Oh, I don't think that's
actually possible, Cliff.
Thank you, big guy.
Hey, babe!
Your ship just came in!
The muse has visited
Sy Flembeck.
Want to hear what
she had to say?
Oh, boy, do I.
You know, I just love
the whole creative process.
And I can be pretty
creative myself.
Oh, yeah?
Well, then why don't you be Sy Flembeck
and I'll be the
annoying broad? How's that?
Go ahead.
All right.
"The Cheers Theme"
by Sy Flembeck.
(plays flourish)
(to the tune
of "Old MacDonald Had a Farm")
♪ Beer and pretzels,
that's our game ♪
♪ C-H-E-R-S ♪
♪ If you don't come
here, that's a shame ♪
♪ C-H-E-R-S ♪
♪ With a C-C here,
C-C there... ♪
No, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait!
What are you doing?
That's all wrong!
First of all, "Cheers" is
spelled with two E's.
Second, I paid you
a lot of money
to come up with
an original tune.
You don't need
an original tune!
You want something
that'll bore a hole
through the public's
little pea brains.
But you are all hype
and no substance!
I was mesmerized
by your show business savvy.
You couldn't write a jingle
to save your life.
Uh, hey, babe!
Come on!
Wait a minute!
What is it, huh?!
What? What?
The "Old MacDonald" melody?
Hey, I could change that.
Yeah, Sy Flembeck is nothing
if he's not versatile.
All right, just a minute.
Okay, okay, okay, I got it.
(to the tune of
"Mary Had a Little Lamb")
♪ Beer and pretzels, that's
our game, that's our game ♪
♪ That's our game ♪
♪ Beer and pretzels,
That's our game ♪
♪ C-H-E-R-S. ♪
E! E! E-E!
Out.
What's the matter, babe?
You can't work with a man
you're attracted to?
Oh, God! Out!
I'll be home all night.
The pay phone's just down
the hall from my room.
God. Oh, what a hack.
You know, I, I
should have known it
the first time I heard that
stupid Fred's Tune up song.
Thanks a lot, lady,
now I'm gonna have
that stupid jingle
in my head all night.
What stupid jingle?
You know the one.
♪ Tune-ups, tune-ups,
that's our game ♪
♪ F-R-E-D-S. ♪
You know, I could
use a tune-up.
Are they any good?
You heard the song.
Tune-ups are their game.
Well, where are they located?
♪ 1413 Burlingame ♪
♪ F-R-E-D-S ♪
Sy!
Sy, wait a minute!!
Oh, Cliff, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine, Maggie.
Thanks.
I'm sorry I was gone
for so long.
I went out and had some pizza
and ribs
and ice cream
and pickles and chocolate.
Maybe it's Norm's kid.
Maggie, uh, I'd like to
talk to you in private
for a few minutes.
Do you mind, uh, stepping,
uh, this way, here?
Uh, Sammy, okay if we, uh,
use your office there, buddy?
Promise me you won't go
through my drawers?
Yeah, okay, I won't.
That's what you said last time.
How many times
can I say "I'm sorry"?
Here, have a seat
there, Maggie.
Maggie,
Maggie, Maggie, Maggie Maggie
there's, uh, so much
I want to say to you and...
so much you want to say
to me, and...
so...
Holy cow!
For a guy who's always
crying poverty,
Sam Malone's doing pretty well
for himself.
Cliff?
Oh, yeah.
You know, Maggie,
I've been thinking.
And you and I both know that
that baby
couldn't possibly be mine.
(sobbing)
Aw, Maggie.
Cliff, I am so ashamed.
You're right.
The baby isn't yours.
I just didn't know
where else to turn.
Well, what happened, Maggie?
Well, um, up in Canada,
I met a man and fell in love.
And everything was perfect,
and we were gonna get married.
And then he got scared
and called everything off.
And I didn't have anyone
to turn to,
so of course,
I thought of the most decent,
honourable man I know.
I'm sorry, Cliff.
You know, you...
you just run out on me,
and you meet this guy,
get pregnant, and he dumps you,
and you come back
so old Cliff Clavin can
take care of you, huh?
That's right, Cliff.
Can do.
What?!
I will marry you, Margaret!
Oh, thank you, Cliff!
(both chuckle)
Hey, here's a
little-known fact:
I'm gonna be your daddy!
You know, this isn't
exactly the way I, you know, dreamed about
starting a family there,
Maggie, but, uh...
you know, I've always
thought the world of you.
And I know that you'd
do the same for me
if the situations
were reversed.
But, Cliff, how could the...
Never mind.
All right.
So, hey, look, here's what we do.
We, uh, skedaddle down
to the City Hall,
make this thing legal,
and we go over to my place,
sedate Ma and give
her the good news.
Huh? Huh?!
Okay!
Oh, let me just call Jerry
and tell him he's off the hook
so he won't worry about me
anymore.
Uh, is it okay to use
this phone to call long distance?
Oh, yeah, sure.
I do it all the time.
Well, Sammy,
champagne all around.
ALL:
Hey!
Yeah, I decided
to marry Margaret, you know,
make an honest woman of her
and, uh, raise her child
as my own.
SAM:
Oh, that's great.
Congratulations, Cliff.
I know you'll enjoy reaping
the rewards of fatherhood.
Yeah, it's not like
I'm not prepared.
I mean, I do own a copy
of The Little Mermaid.
Well, let me be the first
to propose a toast.
CLIFF:
All right.
To the new father,
Cliff Clavin.
ALL:
To the new father!
Thank you, gentlemen.
Cliff.
Ha! Excuse me.
(quietly):
The old ball and chain.
Cliff, I just talked to Jerry.
I hope you told him
that a real man
is going to, uh,
take care of you and the baby?
He wants me back.
Beg your pardon?
He said he loves me.
He can't stand the thought of
another man raising his child.
So, you're off the hook.
Aren't you happy?
Well, if you're happy.
I'm happy.
Well, then I'm happy.
Yeah...
Uh, ladies and gentlemen.
Please, don't just sit there.
Raise your glasses
in a toast to, uh,
Mother Margaret here and,
uh, the new father, Jerry.
Jerry?
ALL (lacklustre):
To Jerry.
Thanks, everyone.
Oh, uh-uh, Cliff,
would you mind
giving me a ride
to the bus station?
If I leave now, I can
be there in 72 hours.
Yeah, sure.
I'm a little confused, Sam.
Well, Maggie's going back
to Canada
to marry the,
the father of her baby.
And Cliff was going
to marry her,
but now he doesn't have to.
No, I mean about it taking
72 hours to get to Canada.
I thought it was much
further than that.
You know, Cliff, in a way,
I'm a little disappointed
that we're not getting married.
We'll never make love again.
Again?
Maggie, I think your
memory is as, uh, faulty
as your birth control, uh...
We, we never actually
did make love.
Sure we did.
The night before I left.
Remember?
You had those two wine coolers?
No kiddin'?
I-I thought I
fell asleep.
You, you mean, you
and I actually, uh...?
I don't remember.
Boy, that's something.
So, uh, how was I?
The truth, Cliff?
Naw.
You were great.
Yeah!
(laughing)
Both times.
Both times! Wow!
Wow! Whoo-hoo!