(Sam)
cheers  is filmed before
a live studio audience.
What are you doing
here so late, dr. Crane?
Oh, i had to
make a midnight run.
Lilith's having another one
of her pregnancy cravings.
Oh, no, not again.
W-what was it
this time, huh?
Oh, just butter and flour.
What, she wants
to bake something?
No. That's what she was
eating when i left.
Bowls of butter
and fistfuls of flour.
And i had to get out of there.
Boy, oh, gee. Pregnancy
really makes women screwy,
doesn't it?
Yeah, well, it's amazing
how they let hormones
take over their entire body
for that period of time.
Tell me about it.
You know,
the other morning at 4:00,
i had to run clear
across town to this
particular pizzeria
to get lilith
a deep-dish pizza,
4 cheeses,
with sun-dried tomatoes,
prosciutto, and anchovies.
Oh, my god.
How far did you have to go?
Oh, out by the airport.
That's what? An hour's drive
just for a craving?
It's insane, isn't it?
Well, you were lucky
they were open.
Oh, they're open all night.
All night?
Ooh, i could use
an anchovy pizza.
It's a hell of a pie.
Sometimes you want to go
where everybody
knows your name
and they're always
glad you came
you wanna be
where you can see
our troubles
are all the same
you wanna go
where everybody
knows your name
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
my life is fabulous!
Keep it to yourself.
Oh, did i say something?
I must've been
thinking out loud.
Thinking out loud
about my fabulous life.
Does anybody know what
time it is?
Why ever do you ask?
Well, just because
my rich new sweetheart,
robin colcord,
sent me this beautiful,
very expensive gold watch
from zurich,
and i can't tell
what time it is.
Can you read this?
Yeah, it says,
"this could feed my family
for a year."
Carla, don't be childish.
If anybody needs me,
i'll be skipping
around in my office.
Say, uh,
when's your rich boyfriend
coming back?
In about a week.
Oh, good, good.
That'll give you time
to make up excuses
not to go to bed with him.
[Scoffs]
i wanna go to bed with him.
I'm just waiting
for the right time.
Well, maybe that's why
he gave you the watch.
Don't worry, rebecca.
There's nothing wrong
with making a guy wait.
It piques their interest.
I once made a guy wait
until we were
both undressed.
And how do you know
that i haven't been
to bed with robin?
Did sam tell you that?
No. I'm a woman.
A woman knows.
You know, i must say,
i'm with carla
on this one.
I mean, there's nothing wrong
with 2 people
getting to know each other
before they have
a physical relationship.
And how did you know?
Well, i'm a psychiatrist.
A psychiatrist knows.
What are you
waiting for, becky?
Yeah, hit the sheets
already, kid.
Sam.
Pool players know.
I cannot believe
you told everyone.
Not having sex
is a very private thing
between a man and a woman.
You don't see me
going around saying that
norm and vera
didn't have sex last night.
Hey, hey.
Ok, bad example.
The point is,
i don't want you
talking about me.
There's to be no more gossip
about my private life.
Sorry i'm late
from lunch.
I made the mistake
of mentioning
to my waitress that
my boss was
dating robin colcord.
She wanted to know
if it was true
they haven't
slept together.
You know,
it is amazing what happens
when you mention
that guy's name.
Oh, yeah?
I mean, i had all these people
swarming around my table,
asking me all kinds
of questions:
do i know him very well?
Do i see him often?
Do i want soup or salad?
Yeah, it's tough
being a celebrity.
You know, i used to
get that all the time when
i was playing for the sox.
It's a real pain.
Yeah, you're lucky, sam.
Everyone forgot about you
a long time ago.
Last time
i saw your name in print
was 2 years ago
in a crossword puzzle.
"Name a former
red sox player in 15 letters."
And even then i had
a lot of spaces left over.
Yeah, well,
i still wouldn't trade places
with poor old robin.
"Poor old robin"
happens to be
one of the richest,
most powerful men
in the world.
Not to mention,
being generally gorgeous.
Yeah, but he hasn't gotten
anywhere with rebecca,
has he?
You didn't get anywhere
with that babe, either.
I'm not one of the richest
most powerful men
in the world.
I'm just
a lowly bartender.
What's his excuse?
Good point, sammy.
I--i know why she's not
going to bed with that guy.
'Cause there's this little
voice in the back of her head
that keeps saying:
"wouldn't you really
rather drive a sammy?"
[All laughing]
that poor chump
doesn't stand a chance.
Yeah, but still, sam,
it would be nice to have
colcord's money, wouldn't it?
Ah, so he's got bucks. I mean,
what's he do with it?
All he does is hustle.
Me? I enjoy my life.
I live it my way
on my own terms.
[All agreeing]
and well you should be, sam,
you know.
You may not be
wealthy and powerful,
but those who
really know you respect you.
(Man)
that's true, sam.
Ah, yeah,
thank you very much.
How could we not? You know,
you've-- you've been
through adversities
that would've crushed
other, lesser men.
Well, i don't know.
Oh, no, really.
When i think of
the sorry state
your life's in now...
w-what do you, uh...
all right, yeah. Maybe i'm not
as young as i used to be,
and maybe i did blow
my life savings,
and maybe this job
doesn't pay that much,
and maybe i don't have
a family
or any future
to look forward to,
but at least...
what, sam?
At least i'm happy.
(All)
that's true.
[All agreeing]
and that's why
we admire you.
You know,
i think i speak for everyone
in the bar here when i say,
that if it had been any of us,
we would've blown
our brains out years ago.
Ah, that's very sweet
of you guys.
You know, i think the--
i think the secret's
not to sweat the small stuff.
There you go.
It'd take a hell of a lot
more than that
to get under my skin.
Sam, remember to
fill up all the pretzel bowls.
Oh, that does it!
I hate this life!
I don't mind
that other stuff,
but i can't stand
the damn pretzels.
Well, things are going to
change around here,
you know.
I'm gonna change.
I'm gonna be somebody.
Who can i be?
Sam, if you feel a need
for a new direction in life,
uh, perhaps a career change
would be in order.
Well, for example, uh,
getting one.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's not bad.
Except all i've ever
enjoyed doing
is playing baseball
and running this bar.
I'm too old
to play baseball,
and i don't own
this bar anymore.
So that's that.
Why don't you
start another bar?
Ah, yeah, where am i
gonna get the money?
Well, i have some money
i'd like to invest.
I can't take
your money, frase.
Thank goodness.
I suddenly had an image
of lilith coming after me
with a cleaver.
Sammy, why don't you
just get a loan, huh?
Oh, i could do that.
But, you know,
another bar's
not going to be
the same as cheers.
Cheers wasn't cheers
before you bought it, sammy.
It was just another
boring run of the mill
beer hall.
How do you know?
I was here every night.
You made cheers
what it is, pal.
[Men agreeing]
(man)
it's true, sammy.
I did, didn't i?
You're damn right.
Yeah, and i'm still sammy.
I could do that again.
Yeah.
I agree.
All right, maybe this is what
i've been needing.
You know, a whole new chance
to start over again.
This kind of feels good.
It's amazing how
when you get a focus
on your life,
everything just
falls into place.
Kind of feel like i'm
a guy with a dream.
And nothing can stop
Sam, be sure and
put out plenty of pork rinds.
So how much longer
are you gonna be
in switzerland, anyway?
Well, couldn't you just
jet in for the weekend?
I know, i know.
World peace.
Ok. Bye-bye.
Oh, i miss him so much.
Carla, eddie's
gone all the time.
How do you
handle it?
Well, when my eddie's away
with the ice show,
i just picture him
having a great time.
Yeah?
You bet. Carousing,
drinking with the boys,
carrying on
with some floozy.
And i call him up
in the middle of the night
and i curse at him
until he begs me
to forgive him.
Even though he probably
didn't do anything wrong
to begin with.
And that helps?
I didn't say it helped.
It's just what i do.
Boys, boys.
Since it's
closing time anyway,
what do you say we, uh,
go do a little after-hours
at the future site
of sam's place?
[Exclaims]
you really found a place?
Was there ever
any doubt?
Of course, i did.
It needs a little work,
but you know,
a little elbow grease,
i think it'll be
as great as cheers.
Wanna go?
I'm kinda bushed, sammy.
It's either that
or go home, you know.
All right, i'll drive.
No, no, no, we agreed
i'd be designated driver.
No, no, no. I said you'd be
designated driveler.
Where's everybody going?
Oh, boy oh boy,
this is a moment
i've been dreading here.
Now, i just gonna come out
and say this.
Rebecca,
i'm giving 2 weeks notice.
I'm leaving cheers
to open up my own place.
Please don't say anything.
Just
read that note.
"Dear, rebecca,
it's so hard to say goodbye.
"We've been through
a lot of ups and downs,
"but i've always considered
you more than a boss.
"You're really
a special friend.
"Love, sam.
"P.S. Be at my apartment
in 2 hours
naked and ready."
[Door opening]
(sam)
come on, everybody.
Come on in here.
Watch your step.
Here we go.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let there be light.
Let there be dark.
Come on,
what do you think?
Don't you think
this place could
be as fun as cheers?
Sam, i don't think
this place could be as
fun as world war ii.
All right, i--i-- listen,
i know i can't afford
to just, uh, buy a place
you can move right into,
but, uh, look at
the potential here.
Come on, use your imagination.
I'm using mine, sam.
Atta boy, woody.
I'm imagining
what's making that
little scuttling sound,
and it's scaring me.
Come on. W-wait, guys.
Sammy's right.
I mean, no place could look
good boarded up like this.
But what if we were to, uh,
say pull off some of these--
[screams]
(cliff)
what--what is it now?
Oh, nothing, i just wanna
wash my hand
for about 20 minutes.
Big deal!
What has everybody
got against maggots?
Sam, i've got the slogan
for your bar.
"Sam's place.
It's alive with larvae."
I don't suppose
you bothered to check
what was behind the larvae?
Go ahead.
Oh, wow.
It's a leaded
glass window.
Yeah.
Big old nice one, too.
Yeah, they don't
make 'em like that anymore.
And if look under this ratty
old linoleum
you'll find the, uh,
the original oak floor.
Come over here, you guys,
look at this.
Huh?
Wow, marble.
That's a beauty, sam.
Yeah, you bet.
All the original
brass fixtures
are around the back, there.
I tell you, as soon as this
loan comes through,
i'm going to own
one classy bar.
[Laughs]
all right, and i get
first pick of the barstools.
This one right here.
That's the one you want?
You bet.
Yeah, i'll take, uh,
i'll take this one.
Yeah.
Don't you, uh, want
to sit next to me?
You could move down.
But then i won't
get my first pick.
I won't tell anyone.
You're a real pal, normie.
(Sam)
ah, look at you guys.
You're getting
the hang of this thing.
Can't you just imagine
me and woody
behind the bar,
carla waiting tables,
you two sitting at
your places?
All right.
It's gonna be
just as good as cheers.
Eh, huh?
It's gonna be
better than cheers.
(Cliff)
yeah?
You're gonna drive up
to the front door,
and someone's gonna
take your car.
No, no, no, we can't
afford valet.
I know,
but there's a couple of
neighborhood kids out there
doing it for free.
My car.
My car!
My car! My car!
Wait! Wait a minute!
Wait!
Everybody,
sit up straight.
Robin's back from europe.
Come on.
Up, up, up.
All right, he just called
from his car phone
to ask if he could
pop by for a minute.
"Pop."
Isn't robin adorable?
Well, he does have
haunting eyes.
Well, he does,
doesn't he?
I think the important thing
is that
mr. Colcord is gonna find
an entirely new woman
from the one
he saw 2 weeks ago.
A hungry woman.
A confident woman.
A woman who's willing
to give to her man
with total abandon.
I think i see him coming.
I'm not ready yet.
Jeez. Women.
You can't live with them,
pass the beer nuts.
Is miss howe in?
Oh, yeah,
she's in her office.
Ah, mr. Colcord? Excuse me.
Um, you just got back
from switzerland,
right?
Yes.
Now, uh, do you--
do you go over there
and talk with those
swiss people very often?
Every few months.
Um, listen, you think
if i gave you some money,
you could maybe
pick up one of those
army knives for me?
There may be, um,
customs restrictions.
Oh, then forget it.
I'll just go
to the drugstore.
Yeah.
Boy, uh, you got to go figure,
a rich guy like that.
Why is he putting up
with rebecca
if she's not, you know,
putting out for him?
Maybe all
of the equipment's
not in working order.
There you go.
Oh.
Or maybe he's got
so many other babes
on the side
he just doesn't
have time for her, huh?
Yeah.
Now, that's good.
Or maybe he's a gentleman.
Woody, who the hell
brought you up?
Hey, boys.
You're looking
at a scale model
of sam's place.
You're still
going through
with that thing, sam?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
The loan came through today.
This thing's happening.
What, even after mr. Clavin's
car got stolen, stripped,
and left across town?
[Muttering]
that was just, you know,
one little incident.
A friend of mine
down at city hall says
it serves me right
for parking my car
in the worst crime
sector in boston.
I don't believe it.
You were there.
You saw it.
No. That you
have a friend.
Come on, guys. Well, hey,
doesn't this look great?
Lovely.
Oh, that may be, sam,
but, you know,
there's an old real estate
maxim that says
the 3 most
important things
in looking
for a property are:
location,
location, location.
That's just one thing.
That's the point,
woody.
What, that real estate
people are stupid?
No, that location is
the one most important thing
in real estate.
Then why do they say
it's 3 things?
Because real estate
people are stupid.
Ah-ha.
Why am i talking
to you guys?
You don't know
anything about bars.
I'm telling you,
this is going to be
the best damn bar in boston.
Ah, what's that?
Oh, mr. Colcord.
N-nothing.
I was just, uh,
just talking, that's all.
No, you seemed, uh, pretty
excited about something
just now.
[Rebecca scoffs]
sam wants to reopen
some stupid, disgusting,
run-down place
on the waterfront.
Small world.
I own some
property down there.
Perhaps we'll
be neighbors.
Really?
You think that
this would be a good place
to open a business?
Well, i'd like to hear
your plans.
Well, great. Yeah, great.
Why don't we, uh, just...
can we use the office?
No.
It'll only be
for a moment.
What, did i say "no"?
I meant to say "yes."
I mean,
i very rarely ever say "no."
Like tonight,
i'll be saying "yes."
Yes, yes, yes!
I think this gives you
a pretty good idea
of what the place
will look like.
Except, you know, bigger.
So, what you're
finally saying is,
you're gonna reopen
the same business
in the same location
where it went
belly-up just last year.
No, no, no.
See, this is new. This is
completely different.
Now it's sam's place.
What was it before?
Tim's place.
Sam, do you want
my, um, honest opinion?
Oh, yeah, you bet.
This could work.
Yes!
By work i mean, if you pour
every dime you've got
into the place,
struggle, scrimp, and save,
and somehow hang on
through the lean years
you might begin
to show a tiny profit.
After that,
living month by month,
year after year,
praying there's no recession,
you might actually
scrape a living,
a dismal, altruist
living out of it.
Ok. Ok.
So, um,
what's the downside?
Sam, don't
shortchange yourself.
Do you want just any bar
or do you want the best bar?
Look here.
I've always found that
the secret of success is
having a dream and then
having the courage
to run after it.
Reach for
the stars, sam.
Astonish me.
Astonish yourself.
Yeah. All right.
Now, i get this. I get--
all right.
Y-you're saying
that i, uh--
i shouldn't settle
for this crummy little place.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Yeah, i should, uh, buy
the whole block.
Keep talking.
Right, and i could, uh,
i could tear it all down and--
and--and build a high rise
with a great river view.
That's wonderful.
And apartments and condos,
and 24-hour donut shops.
And--and--and a real big tall
building with sam's place
on the top.
And it'll be the best damn bar
on the east coast.
Beautiful, sam.
Can you do it?
Yes, i can.
No, you can't.
No, i can't.
Come down to earth,
for god's sake.
Sam, w-w-what you gotta
ask yourself is:
"what do i really want?"
Well, i don't
know what i, uh...
what i really...
well,
i ougtta tell you
what i want.
I want my--my beat-up
old desk back.
I want my sports stuff
back on the walls.
I want to get rid of those
creepy plants out there
and that stupid world map
of wherever the hell it is.
I want cheers.
Then do it.
Oh, god.
I mean, i--i'd love to get
cheers back.
But i--i don't even think
i can get out of this--this
crummy little deal here.
See, i'd be happy to make
some phone calls for you.
I know quite a few people
around town.
That's my, uh, private number.
[Exclaims]
well, god, this is great.
Thank you.
Uh, i don't know
if i can ever repay you here.
Let's just say,
you owe me a favor.
All right. Yeah.
All right, one favor. Anytime.
Yeah. Thanks very much.
Hey, guys!
Hey, listen to this!
I'm not going to buy
that stupid crummy bar.
[All cheering half-heartedly]
i'm gonna buy
this stupid crummy bar.
[All cheering wildly]
hey, rebecca,
can i work the next shift?
I need the overtime.
Sam, look, i know what
you're trying to do here.
But forget it.
It's gonna take you
the rest of your life
to save enough money
to buy cheers.
Hey, if sam says
he can do it, he can do it.
We have faith in you, sam.
Cheers is gonna be yours.
I just hope
i'm still alive to see it.
Is rebecca in?
Yeah. She's, uh, she's
in her office.
Oh. I'll have a brandy.
Say, uh, mr. Colcord,
i just want to thank you
for, uh, getting me out of
that other deal so fast.
Well, uh, let's say
you owe me one, eh?
Yeah, right, right.
Actually, i had a thought
about that other idea we had.
And i decided
that might be fun, too.
What idea was that?
Well, you remember,
the high rise
with the river view.
It turns out
it's adjacent to the property
that i'm developing,
so i decided to buy
the whole block
and give it a go.
But you--you said
that was impossible.
No, i said it was
impossible for you.
For me
it was 2 phone calls
and a handshake.
[Chuckles]
but that was--
that was my idea.
Was it?
So hard to recall.
The ideas were flying
so fast and furious
in there, weren't they?
Wait--wait a minute.
Now, if i'd bought
that--that property,
couldn't i have
sold it to you for a profit?
But you wouldn't take
advantage of a friend,
would you?
You--you talked me
out of that place just so
you could get it yourself.
No, i--i didn't talk you
out of anything.
I talked you into
following your heart.
You're a man
with a dream, sam.
I envy you.
But if it makes you
feel any better,
i'm willing to
come to an arrangement.
Oh, yeah?
Yes, uh, let's see.
Yes. You no longer
owe me a favor.
Oh, uh, robin.
I'm all set.
Let me just get my purse.
Darling, you look lovely.
I'll get miles to
bring the car around.
And, um, oh,
that's for the drink.
So, rebecca,
tonight's the big night, huh?
[Giggles]
it's not
gonna happen.
I can feel it.
It's not
gonna happen.
I know that i'm gonna
chicken out again.
Oh, robin's gonna be
so disappointed.
No. No, he won't.
He's already
done it to me today.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org