Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
( chuckling )
Well, that cute little dimple?
Well, I think
I still got it.
It's kind of hard for
me to see back there.
( laughing )
Um, Renee, I'm going to have
to get back to you.
Yeah, bye-bye.
Uh, Linda, sweetheart,
uh, can we continue
this over lunch?
Well, um, your place.
Don't cook.
( laughing )
Let me guess-- personal call?
Very.
Malone, I find winking
really smarmy.
Yeah, but beneath this smarm
is a lot of charm,
and I think you know that.
I know this...
I want you out
of my office now.
All right, all right.
I'm sorry.
I know I'm not supposed
to get personal calls here,
but what the hey, you know;
super-strength Sammy
has been off the shelves now
for over a year--
there's a lot of pent-up demand
out there.
What can I say?
Say, "I'd better
get back to work.
I don't want to get fired."
You're cute
when you're humorless.
Did you know that?
( telephone rings )
Cheers.
No, Simone, I'm sorry.
Sam's working.
( whispering ):
Simone? Wait, wait, wait.
Try him later at home.
Well, then, perhaps
on your next visit
to the States.
Simone?
Man, you just cost me
a roll in the hay.
I owe you one.
You're on.
I didn't mean that.
Wait a minute. I think
we need to get something...
( piano plays )
♪ Making your way
in the world today ♪
♪ Takes everything
you've got ♪
♪ Taking a break
from all your worries ♪
♪ Sure would help a lot
♪ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ♪
♪ Sometimes you want to go
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always glad
you came ♪
♪ You want to be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ You want to go
where people know ♪
♪ People are all the same
♪ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Geez... listen to this.
"Scientists discover
wild parrot
who claims to be Elvis."
So?
"So?"
I mean, this one
wins the "Too stupid
for even you,
Cliff" award.
Now, really,
must you two wallow
in this sensationalistic tripe?
It pains me no end
to see America's wits dulled
and their morals abrogated
by this opiate of the asses.
( Norm scoffs )
Well, let's check this out,
Cliffie.
"I was Sigmund Freud's
love child."
No!
I've heard rumors
that he betrayed Martha
with his sister-in-law,
but I never dreamed
there were progeny.
You rapscallions.
( Woody whistling )
What are you
whistling about, huh?
You haven't got a
dime to your name.
You're working for a woman
who's a meat grinder,
and you look like a
baboon in that uniform.
Boy, life really stinks.
( whistling happy tune )
SAM:
You okay?
I feel like puke.
Well, you're wearing
the right uniform.
Want to talk about it?
No, what's there to say
about a no-good, ice-eating
little geek like Eddie LeBec.
He's known since a week ago
that I got
his bun in my oven,
and what the hell
has he done about it?
Jack Diddley.
Don't look now,
but your ice-eating geek
just walked in.
Don't you just love him?
Hi, Carla.
Hi, Eddie.
You, uh, busy?
CARLA:
Just a minute.
Uh, look,
would you just write down
what you want,
and hand it to Howdy Doody
over there?
I'm all yours.
Okay.
So, what's new?
Well, I, uh, I've had
a lot on my mind lately.
Yeah?
You know, training camp's
really been rough
and a lot of
competition at goalie,
and really having to work
my tail off to keep up, eh?
Sounds rough.
Yeah.
Say, you know, uh,
since I'm already here,
there's something
I've been wanting to ask you.
Yeah?
It's a question.
I like questions.
Okay, but,
see, this is
the kind of question
a guy really
doesn't want to ask
if he thinks he might
get "no" for answer.
Well, it's kind of hard for
a girl to give an answer
until she knows
what the question is.
Okay, but, you see,
it would be
a lot easier for a guy
if he had
some sort of sign...
Ask me, you little frog!
Okay.
Carla, would you...?
Yes! Yes!
Oh, oh, oh.
Eddie, yes.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Carla, do you mind if we,
you know,
we keep this quiet?
You know me, I don't
like a lot of hoopla.
Oh, yeah, sorry.
Would it be okay
if I just told Sam?
I guess.
Hey, Sammy!
Me and Eddie
are getting married!
( applause )
Oh, my God.
Hey, hey, hey.
( bell ringing,
people cheering )
Get over here, Eddie!
( whistles )
What's going on?
Oh, great news,
Miss Howe.
Carla's marrying
Eddie LeBec.
Oh, that cute little guy
with the dents in his nose.
Hey, listen up, everybody.
Wait, wait, wait,
here we go.
Here we go, here we go.
I want
to be making a toast
to my beautiful
bride-to-be.
Listen, you know,
I don't make my living
using words, so this
is gonna be kind of hard
for me, okay,
but here it goes.
Uh, Carla...
Well, you know.
ALL:
Yeah.
I love you, sweetie.
Hey, congratulations, man.
This is terrific.
Thanks.
Are you gonna take her
on a honeymoon?
Hey, got any suggestions?
Yeah.
New Orleans.
I found a great
little honeymoon spot
just kind of tucked away
off Bourbon Street.
Great food, very romantic,
steamy atmosphere, you know.
Yeah, I had the
time of my life,
and then Vera tracked me down.
Well, if I get any time off
from training camp,
I thought maybe Carla
might like to see Waikiki.
Waikiki...
Honolulu, Hawaii?
Sure, we'll hit them all.
Yeah, right!
I only hope
I can get some time off
from the Howitzer.
Sorry. Miss Howitzer.
Time off?
Well, you'll be having
all the time in the world.
You think I'd be
having a wife of mine
work in a crummy
bar like this?
No offense, Miss Howitzer.
It's Miss Howe.
Oh, take it easy.
They're just complimenting
your big guns.
Wait a minute.
Y-You're telling me
that I don't have
to work anymore?
You mean, I can just
sit around the house all day,
eating peanut butter
out of a jar,
and watching
my toenails grow?
She's, uh, quite a catch, Ed.
Boy, you know,
I'm gonna miss you around here.
Oh, Sammy, I'll drop by
once in a while
to watch all you 9-to-5'ers
spill drinks
on your butler suits.
So, when's
the big day, Carla?
Well, I'd like to do it
as soon as possible
before my little hunk
of back bacon here
changes his mind.
Ah, no way, I'm not
one of those flakes
you used to go out with.
Oh, but listen, we
have to get married
on a day with
a two in it
'cause two's
my lucky number.
Rats. Mine's three.
Oh, no sweat.
Lucky two, lucky three...
We can get married on
the 23rd or the 32nd.
That's right, honey.
Oh, right, right.
No, um...
As long as it's not
on a Wednesday.
Ooh, yeah, bad juju.
Yeah.
This is going to be
an interesting wedding--
the two most superstitious
people in the world.
Hey, hey, don't say that,
it's bad luck.
Listen, whatever you do,
don't make any plans afterwards
'cause we're going to throw you
the biggest wedding reception
in history right here...
Oh, great!
( applause )
( clears throat )
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Force of habit.
Not my place to do that.
I'm sorry.
Ms. Howe's going to throw you
the biggest wedding reception...
( cheering )
I need to talk to you
right now.
Uh, wait...
before you say anything,
let me just, uh...
I had an idea.
Why don't you
invite your boss,
what's-his-name,
Evan Drake.
You know,
he's a sports fan, so I hear.
Maybe he'd enjoy
meeting Eddie LeBec there.
You know, you could
throw him a big bash,
impress the pants off him.
What were you
going to say?
I was going to tell
you to smile more.
Mm-hmm.
I didn't say smugly.
Excuse me,
I have a phone call to make.
Hey there, Eduardo,
looks like you and Carla aren't
the only lovebirds in town.
Check out DeeDee
and David there.
Who?
DeeDee and David Lefsowski,
the Weekly Gabbers'
odd couple of the month.
See, she weighs in there
at 480 pounds,
and he tips the scales
at a mere, uh, 92.
But I mean, just look
at the love in his eyes.
I think that's fear, Cliff.
Cute baby he's holding.
That's her arm, Woody.
Cute arm he's holding.
Hey. Picked a date yet?
Yep.
Eddie wants to do it
a week from Saturday,
anytime before 4:00 p.m.
which is okay
with my psychic,
as long as our auras remain
in the blue spectrum,
and there's no
solar eclipse.
It's really tough
planning a wedding, isn't it?
Ooh, tell me about it.
You know, I'm just
a little nervous
about waiting eight days.
Gives Eddie an
awful long time
to come to his senses.
Look at him.
He's absorbed in
thought over there.
Well, maybe not.
There.
The table looks nice.
Woody, don't you think
the table looks nice?
I think it looks nice.
Looks nice.
You think so?
Oh, damn,
I bet chucklebrain
forgot to pick up
the napkins.
Oh, no, Sam didn't forget.
Eddie brought these special
wedding ones they had made up.
"We don't want
to get married.
We have to. Ha, ha."
Cute.
You see the
little hillbilly
with the shotgun?
Yes, he's nice, isn't he?
But I think these are
just a little too funny
for the reception.
Burn them.
Did you remember to get
the cinnamon almond decaf?
Yeah, I did.
Who likes that?
Evan does.
Everyone does.
Excuse me, Miss Howe,
I know it's none
of my beeswax, but...
it seems to me like
you're awfully nervous
about Mr. Drake
coming by today.
Do you like him
or something?
In a business sense, yes.
I admire his skills
and accomplishments.
You like him.
Boys...
we're all set up
with my buddy Bruce.
He can get us the same
silverware Carla picked out
from the Filene's catalog
for over two-thirds off.
Oh, yeah.
So what's the bite-ski?
20 bucks apiece.
I'll catch you guys later.
Say, Norm, there
isn't any chance
that this stuff
is stolen merchandise, is there?
No, of course not.
Listen, if anyone asks,
we never heard of Bruce,
we can't find the receipt,
and if you run into me
up on the street,
call me Larry.
My mind's at ease.
So, Sam, what are you
concocting there?
You know how superstitious
Carla and Eddie are.
I thought I'd mix them
up a batch
of my good-luck
wedding punch.
It never fails.
Isn't that the same
stuff you made
when you were
getting married
to Miss Chambers?
Woody, you want to flush this
down the toilet.
Hi, guys.
Hey.
Carla, what are you doing
here on your wedding day?
Oh, oh, actually I came by
to get my last paycheck.
See, the bridal shop
has this policy
about their wedding gowns--
"Fork over the jack,
or it stays on the rack."
So where is it?
Oh, I'm so sorry
that I don't have it ready
for you right this very second.
I guess
I've just been busy
putting up
every single decoration
and ordering
all the hors d'oeuvres
and getting a band together
at the very last minute
so that your reception
could be just perfect for you.
Could you step on it?
I'm in a hurry.
Soda, bartender.
Coming right up.
So how's the bride
on her big day?
Couldn't be better, Sammy.
All celestial omens
are favorable.
Seems that Eddie and I picked
the one day this century
when all the planets
and constellations
are in perfect alignment.
So either we get married
by 4:00 today,
or we wait
until the year 2042.
I don't know, call
me old-fashioned,
but I still think you
ought to get married
before your baby does.
( chuckles )
How'd you manage to
swing a church wedding?
You know, being
divorced and all.
Don't you remember?
I had my marriage to Nick
annulled years ago.
Oh, right, right,
right, right. Took forever.
Mm-hmm.
But things got
speeded up
when Nick tried to sell
the Bishop his watch.
Oh, hey,
isn't that Eddie LeBec
sashaying down those
stairs, there, Doc?
Sure looks like it.
But Carla's here.
Isn't there
some superstition
about the groom seeing the bride
before the wedding?
( screams )
Nobody believes
in that anymore.
You saw me.
I saw you.
I saw you see me.
I saw you see me see you.
Oh...
Shut up.
You're making it worse.
Oh, my God.
We were so careful
about every single thing,
and then we blew
the single most important
superstition of all--
seeing the bride on
the day of the wedding.
What are you
doing here?
I was meeting my mother.
What are you doing here?
I came by to get my check!
That's it.
We've blown it.
We can't get
married now.
Call me in 2042.
Yeah, okay. I'll see ya.
You guys are kidding.
Come on. Eddie.
Wait a minute.
What am I doing?
Carla...
Look, I don't want
to give up the best thing
that ever happened to me.
Oh, come off it, Eddie.
You're just as
superstitious as I am.
Well, not anymore.
And I'm going
to prove to you
there's nothing
to all that mumbo jumbo.
Woody, hand me a mirror.
Huh?
You know, the one Sam's
always looking at himself in.
What are you
going to do?
I'm going to break it.
The bad luck is
starting already.
He's lost his mind.
( gasps )
Hey, that's my mirror.
You see? Nothing.
The ground didn't open up
and swallow me.
That's because they want
you out in the open
where lightning
can get you.
Don't do that!
Oh!
Which shoulder do you throw
salt over to avoid bad luck?
The left, the left.
No! No, no!
Forgive him,
demons of Hell.
He's a hockey player.
( phone ringing )
Don't, don't answer it.
Don't, don't...
Cheers.
Thanks, Woody.
Carla, it's for you.
Go on. Go on, answer it.
Would you take it.
Come on.
Hello.
Oh, hi, Dr. Nadelson.
How did my tests come out?
You've got to be kidding.
What? What is it?
Twins.
He spills the salt,
he breaks the mirror,
and I'm the one
having twins.
I told you something
horrible was going to happen.
What is so bad?
Twins means
we're twice blessed.
Yeah, I had twins once.
It was the happiest
day of my life.
Lighten up.
Carla... Carla,
this is great.
Eddie...
You're really happy
about this?
I'm the happiest
man on Earth.
Listen, Carla,
you and me, we can...
we can overcome
any obstacles
that are in our way.
You're a great guy, Eddie.
Dumb as a skate blade,
but a great guy.
Ma!
Oh, my baby's home!
You see? I knew
things would look up.
What's wrong?
Ma, nothing.
Everything's aces.
It's just that, hey,
when you called
about getting remarried,
I realized
how much I love you.
I just wanted to be
with you on this day.
And?
Uh, and Dad's TV shop--
it went under.
We got evicted,
and I can't get unemployment
'cause Daddy didn't declare me
an employee.
Well, I'm just glad
my little boy's
here for my wedding.
What about his lovely wife?
I'm just glad my little
boy's here for my wedding.
Actually,
Mother Tortelli,
we didn't want
to return to Vegas.
We don't think
it's any place
for children
to grow up.
You're having a kid?
I'm talking about us.
So, if we could find
someone here in Boston
with an nice house
and lots of extra room...
Do you know anyone
like that, Mother Tortelli?
No, no, no.
You don't want to come live
in my little, tiny,
overcrowded house.
Ma, it's just temporary.
Just till I get
back on my feet.
Hey, if it's a problem,
we'll find someplace
else to stay.
Yeah. I think I saw
a nice cardboard box
in the alley.
See, see?
What did I tell ya?
This is the bad luck
I've been warning you about.
Carla, don't
worry about it.
I mean, the more
the merrier.
Look, I'm going to get
a major salary bump
this season,
and then I'll buy us all
the biggest house in Boston.
Wow. A new house?
You bet.
Now do you
finally believe
that nothing bad
is going to happen?
No. I'll just have
more closet space
when it does.
Anthony, I'm Eddie LeBec.
I guess I'm your
new stepfather.
I'm hoping one day
you'll call me "Dad."
Hey, Nick Tortelli
is my dad.
You are not my father,
and you never will be!
Anthony!
You only knocked up my ma
so she'd have to marry you.
Ma, I'm sorry.
The guy was asking for it.
Come on, Annie,
let's go.
Forgive him.
He has the hot passion
of his race,
and I have the envy
of every woman I know.
Well, this is it.
This is the bad luck.
I mean, what
could be worse
than my kid hating
my husband?
Look, it's okay.
He's just a kid.
Oh, you don't
get it, Eddie.
He's the nicest
one I got.
Look, Carla, he's just
being protective of his mother.
God knows
that I think my maman's
the greatest woman
on Earth.
And I can only hope
that our kids feel the same way.
Are you from this planet?
Carla, here's your
final paycheck.
Thank...
I might say that you have
been a unique employee,
and it's going to
be very difficult
to fill your uniform.
Thanks.
You don't happen to know
any other short, pregnant
cocktail waitresses, do you?
Yeah, can I help you?
Eddie LeBec.
Maman?!
Tu es merveilleuse!
Je ne peux plus attendre
pour que tu rencontre Carla.
Là voil, au bar.
Carla...
Carla. Carla.
Non, Maman...
Maman...
Eddie, c'est qu'elle est belle.
Non, non, Maman.
C'est Carla.
( chuckling )
Carla!
Non, non, Maman.
No, no, no, no.
Me Rebecca.
Her Carla.
Enjoy.
Carla.
I'm so happy
to meet you.
Non. Non.
Je ne permettrai
jamais mon fils
à marier ce petit souris
avec le grand ventre.
Maman... Maman...
Je ne permettrai ce mariage...
noon, avec le...
Maman.
O, mon Dieu!
She says she has to catch a bus.
Maman!
I get the feeling
she wasn't nuts about me.
What'd she say?
What makes you
think I'd know?
'Cause all you pompous
windbags speak French.
She said she'll never
allow this marriage.
Especially to a
pregnant hussy
who's only trying
to trap her son.
Then she said she'd rather
be dragged around town
by her tongue...
or else she called you
a small grapefruit.
Eddie, Eddie, Eddie, Eddie,
wait a minute.
Before you say anything,
I know what your
mother said.
And it doesn't
matter to me.
You finally convinced me
that our love can conquer
any bad luck that
comes our way.
I mean it.
Anthony and Annie
moving in,
your ma hating me,
Anthony hating
you, twins...
Every time one of these
little piddling
things came up,
I kept thinking
you were going to say
the wedding's off.
The wedding's off.
Yeah, that's what I kept
expecting you to say.
The wedding's off.
Yeah, yeah,
we're all clear
on what I thought
you'd say.
The wedding's off.
But you never said it.