REBOUND (PART 1 )
Hey, everybody.
l'm back from my Florida vacation.
Good to be home,
back with the old gang.
Hey, how you been, pal?
Glad to, buddy.
Look at that. Here's the old bar.
lt hasn't changed a bit.
Hey, you're back! Good to see you.
- lt's good to be back.
- Oh, it's you.
From behind
you looked like a friend of mine.
Hey, you kidder. l'll get you for that.
- So, hi, Coach.
- Hi, Cliffie.
Boy, did l have a spectacular time
basking up the old Florida sunshine.
l'll tell you. l really got my head
screwed on straight, too.
That experience changed me.
l'm now at one with the cosmos.
No more getting caught up...
At one with the cosmos, Coach.
No more getting caught up
in the irritations of day-to-day life...
l'm just the kinda guy...
Yeah, l stood on many a wind-swept
beach and felt a oneness...
felt...a...
Anybody want a Mai Tai?
Mai Tai, Cliff! Look! You get it?
Mai Tai, Cliffie!
- Good afternoon, everybody.
- Norm!
Beer, Normie?
You know how to make it
sound tempting, you fast talker!
- Guess who, buddy.
- Hey, Cliffie.
Missed you the last couple of days.
- l've been gone two weeks.
- l know.
Oh, God, l missed this guy!
Norm, how's Vera? Any luck
getting her in the family way yet?
- Still working on it.
- Hey, Norm, you want a kid?
Not really. l'm just kinda going along
with it to shut Vera up.
She wants to start a family
to have something to do.
Poor Norm's been shooting blanks
for the last couple of months.
Little louder. We'll dance to it.
Don't worry, Normie. You'll be planting
your seed before you know it.
l hope so. The doc says
if something doesn't happen soon,
we may have to take a drastic step.
- You mean...
- Sleep together.
- Our prayers are with you.
- Thank you.
Coach, how's Sammy been
since l've been away?
Just about the same, Cliffie. Terrible.
You should've seen him the other night.
He walks in with this lady librarian.
She's off-duty, right?
They both have a snootful.
- The lady librarian's got...
- Hey, gang!
Never mind. My story's obsolete.
- Coach?
- Yeah.
- This is my bar, isn't it?
- Yeah, it sure is, Sam.
l told you l owned a bar.
l like it, Sam.
lt's not much. But then again, l am.
Hey, Sammy? l think you got one
over the legal limit there.
Hey, Cliffie's back!
How was your vacation?
My vacation. You remembered?
- Atlantic City, right?
- Yeah, it was terrific. Thanks a lot.
What branch of the service
are these young ladies in?
l stole them off the front of a parade
last night, Coach.
At this very moment there are 26
tuba players marching right into the river.
Show them your stuff, girls.
God, l love it!
Excuse me, Sam.
While you're waiting
for runway clearance...
do you mind taking a look at this?
This is a piece of paper, isn't it?
And those are words.
- This is a letter or something.
- lt is Joanne's resignation.
Hey, girls, take a break
and give your dimples a rest.
- What?
- We lost another waitress.
She found out
she wasn't the only girl in your life.
Nonsense, Carla.
She's been listening to vicious rumours.
Sammy, this means
that l have to work alone again.
We can't keep a waitress
because you keep breaking their hearts.
Well, obviously l need a good talking to.
Sammy, this is serious!
We've had eight waitresses
in six months.
Bet l can remember all their names.
Dee Dee, Carlene, Angela, Sneezy,
Dopey, Donner and Blitzen.
OK, girls, yo!
Step right this way, ladies.
lt's time for the half-time show at the
Sammy-dome. Here you go, step lively!
Poor Sam.
Yeah, my heart bleeds for him.
Sure, Cliffie,
he looks like he's having fun,
but this is just the first stage.
He's going to end up
drinking himself senseless.
He's turning into a real jerk.
Spends his time boozing
and loving and leaving waitresses.
l wonder what set him off.
Suppose it might have been Dia...
Diabetes!
You were going to say that name?
- l wasn't.
- You know my rule.
- But l didn't say it.
- l don't even want you to think it.
Use that name
and l will give you a sunroof.
What difference does it make
how it started?
The important thing is
can we do anything to stop him?
lf we can't, can we join him?
lf we can't join him,
do you think he'd let me watch?
Cheers. Yeah, he's here.
l'll give him the message.
Normie, it's Vera.
She says to hurry home.
Her cycle is at its peak.
Again?
Her cycle has more peaks
than the Adirondacks.
All systems are go there, big fella.
Even Secretariat got to wait
till he was in the mood once in a while.
Poor Coach!
After all you went through with Sam,
seeing him right back where he was.
Really, Carla, it's eating me up.
l'm so desperate l feel like
l'm going to do something crazy.
l am going to do something crazy!
- Wait. What are you going to do?
- l know exactly what Sam needs.
- Coach, your apron!
- He's got an apron!
- Just put them down there.
- Thank you, Miss.
Now l know why l became a chauffeur
instead of a longshoreman.
l would have been 72
on my next birthday.
l appreciate your bringing me home,
Boggs.
Your mother and l felt strongly
that the first face one should encounter
on leaving a place like that
should be a friendly one.
Why didn't she ever visit me there?
She wanted to visit you,
Miss Diane,
but you know how uncomfortable she is
around psychiatrists.
She could have written me a letter.
And let them see her handwriting?
Boggs, that's insane.
As your mother would say,
''Let's see them prove it in court.''
Which reminds me,
l should be getting back.
- Thanks again for driving me home.
- lt's my pleasure.
lt's so nice to see you happy again.
Boggs, l think l'm as happy
as l've ever been. l have a new life.
All these wonderful things
have happened to me. l'm better now.
Miss?
l'm fine, Boggs.
l was just a little startled.
- lt's a perfectly normal reaction.
- Perfectly.
- Who is it?
- lt's Ernie Pantusso.
Coach? What do you want?
l have to talk to you. lt's important.
Coach, you're a dear man and l love you
and l've missed you,
but you're part of a period of my life
that l want to see fade into memory.
Do you understand, Coach?
Western Union.
This is a man l could never resist.
- How have you been?
- Fine. And you?
- l'm OK, thank you.
- Sorry l had to fool you that way.
Perhaps l should be taking
this opportunity to be going along.
Say hello to Mummy.
Why don't you have her call me?
You know how she feels
about telephones.
Well, tell her to write. Or, l'll write.
Or maybe we'll just run into
each other sometime.
Nothing would please her more.
Goodbye.
How many pairs of socks
has a guy like that got?
l have no idea.
Can l get you something?
l don't know what l've got. l've been
away several months at a sana...
...vacation.
You didn't run into Cliffie, did you?
No. Did he have
a nervous...vacation, too?
Oh, he's a wreck.
Listen, Diane,
have you thought about stopping by
and saying hello to everybody?
Coach, that wouldn't be a good idea.
Why?
Does anyone there ask about me?
No, that Carla won't let them.
Diane, l want you to come back
to Cheers and have a talk with Sam.
Talk with S...
Yes, it's very important.
Maybe S...
Maybe the bartender there didn't tell you
about our last conversation,
but it ended in wrath and acrimony.
l vowed never to return to Cheers.
Let's be clear,
nothing in heaven or hell
will ever get me back there.
Diane, you might be my last chance.
Sam's boozing again.
Oh, dear.
Poor S...
Poor, dear S...
Am!
Well, l'm back.
- What'll it be, Normie?
- A transfusion with a head on it.
Norm, are you sure
you want to have a kid?
Once the monster comes along,
your whole life will be different.
You've had kids.
Does a baby change you?
Are you kidding, Normie?
lt can't even change itself.
Well, l'll have to remember that.
- What day is it?
- Friday.
That's it.
Good night, everybody.
- Sam, please! You can't leave.
- Why not?
A friend of yours is dropping by,
and l promised you'd be here.
Great! One of my old buds?
- l smell high times coming.
- Actually it's an old girlfriend.
Better still. Hope it's one of the wild
ones. But then, weren't they all?
- No, they weren't all wild.
- Hold it right there, Coach!
lf you are talking...
...about the stick, l'll pull your lower lip
over your head like a cabbage leaf.
Cut it out, Carla.
Diane's not coming back here.
- She said she's not coming back.
- Well, she might.
- What makes you say that?
- l asked her.
- What the hell did you do that for?
- Please listen to her.
- Promise me.
- l know what this is all about.
lt's this drinking crap, isn't it?
l'm drinking because l like it,
because it tastes good,
and because l want to.
l don't want to see Diane Chambers.
You're going to have to see her
because she'll be here any second now!
God! We are all sitting around here
like we're at the Queen's Tea
and that thing is on its way.
ln fact, it's very close. l can sense it.
lt's here! And it's going to walk in
and say something.
Stay out of this, Carla.
Hello...Sam.
Hi there. Did you forget something?
l dropped in to see how you're doing.
l just got back from Florida, Diane.
Everybody's fine. You're looking good.
- Thank you. How are you doing?
- l've never been better.
For God's sakes, will you stop it, Sam?
You've been boozing with two hands
ever since Diane walked out on you.
- Sam, l'm so sorry.
- You're both crazier than hell!
l threw her out of here and my drinking
has got nothing to do
with Diane Chambers. You hear that?
- Nothing!
- No, you're all wrong.
Sorry!
l did start drinking when she left.
l was celebrating.
Celebrating the day l got rid of you.
You hear?
Celebrating!
l'll tell you something.
l have two birthdays now.
One for when my mother bore me,
and one to commemorate
my glorious rebirth when l left here.
Just once more. You did not walk out,
l kicked you out.
l'd do it again, except no man
deserves that much pleasure in one life.
Your brain could find shelter
in the shade of a snow pea.
Don't, Sam! Please.
l didn't come here
to fight with you.
l came here to help.
Well, l've never been happier
in my entire life.
You're going to help me out
of all my happiness?
- You're the one person who could do it.
- No.
l want you to see a friend of mine.
He's a man l met recently at a sana...
vacation.
She's been locked up in a mental home
for three months.
l was not locked up. l could come
and go at will. Besides, it's not true.
- And how did you know about it?
- l got a cousin who's a private dick.
l wanted to find out if you were really
gone. And you were really gone!
l entered Golden Brook of my own
volition for a little rest, relaxation...
What are you laughing at?
Well, l've had women get depressed
when they left me,
but l've never had one that went...
Charm like yours is a hard thing
to live without all right.
lt had nothing to do with you, Sam.
After l left here,
l decided l needed to regroup.
l needed to take a good look at myself.
Shock treatment.
Carla, let's help Sam first.
And when the psychiatric profession
has gained confidence from that triumph,
we'll put them all on your case.
- Will you please meet this man?
- Come on, Diane.
Look... Yeah, l'm drinking again,
but it's not the same thing.
This time
it's good-time controlled drinking.
Before it was negative. Now it's fun.
- lt won't kill you to talk to the guy.
- Coach, it's a waste of time.
Am l right, Carla?
- See what her friend has to say.
- Oh, come on...
- You listening to this, guys?
- Sammy, you're my friend, right?
Don't get defensive,
but maybe you are drinking too much.
- Well, so are you.
- l already have a mother, lush face.
Sorry, l just think maybe
you ought to hear the guy out.
Sammy, the way l see it
is it can't do any harm
and psychiatry has come a long way
since ''The Snake Pit'' age.
Sam, they're all trying to tell you
you need help.
l know what they're saying and why.
Coach here's gotten them all
to gang up on me.
When you try to be a fun-loving drunk,
you find out who your friends are.
OK, fine, forget it. Drink all you want.
l know the reason why you're doing it.
What are you talking about?
You're afraid that l'm right
about you and the doctor.
You can't stand admitting
l'm right about anything.
Wrong again!
You're scared, Sam.
lf l see this guy and he tells me that
l'm happy and well-adjusted,
which he will, if the quack has a brain,
would you all please leave me alone?
- Of course. Won't we?
- Yeah, sure.
OK, fine. Tell him to drop by.
l'll try to fit him in between dames.
Why don't you say hello
to him now?
l'm Dr Frasier Crane.
Sorry l startled you.
This is weird.
Diane said you're open-minded
and would be responsive,
so l dropped by a little early.
- She said that?
- She says lots of nice things about you.
Really?
So what say we go somewhere
and have a cup of coffee
and...get to know each other?
OK. Fine.
A few cups of lrish coffee and a chat
it is. Mind if l freshen up a bit?
- Fine.
- Thank you, Sam.
Boy, you sure are back in here
for somebody who said
they were never coming back in here.
Human beings change, Sam.
l've changed. So can you.
Rest assured, l'm only visiting.
Correct me if l'm wrong,
but you just called me human
for the first time.
l guess l just needed a little time
to think about it.
- l knew it.
- What?
Are you kidding?
Don't you see she's nuts about me?
Her young Doctor Killjoy there
is just her way of saving face
to get back in the bar.
- l don't know, Sam.
- l know the look.
She's in love.
- l have to run.
- Diane, you're remarkable,
to help a man
who's caused you so much grief.
l'm free of it now, Frasier.
l'm free of so many things now
that l've fallen in love with you.
l am the luckiest person on earth.
The second luckiest.
Not here, Diane.
Of course. l get carried away.
- l understand.
- That's why l love you.
English ( en)