Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
All right,
here you go, Cliffie.
How about
getting your mom
a pair of these soothing,
gel-filled insoles,
and odor eliminators.
It's only her birthday,
it's not Christmas.
How about one of these
Lucite snack trays
that plays the theme
from Cats?
Yeah, Valentine's Day, 1963.
Back then
it played "Exodus."
Hummingbird feeder?
Come on, you guys
are just being silly
now, right?
Well, then, Cliff,
I'm afraid
you're going to spend
a little more than $1.99
for your mom's gift.
Yeah, you're right, Normie.
You only turn 70 once.
Speaking as a mom,
you know, when
my kids give me gifts,
the ones that always
mean the most
to me are the ones
they make themselves.
For instance, look
at this little
key chain here.
Anthony made this for me the
first year he went away to camp.
I carried it with me
ever since.
I think it might be
the most precious
thing I own.
Well, I'll give you
three bucks for it.
Done.
( piano plays )
¶ Making your way
in the world today ¶
¶ Takes everything you've got
¶ Taking a break
from all your worries ¶
¶ Sure would help a lot
¶ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ¶
¶ Sometimes you want to go
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You want to be where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ You want to go
where people know ¶
¶ People are all the same
¶ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ¶
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Sam, you're working a big party
the 26th at Mr. Gaines'.
Another big party...
How come you always
get roped into running
these things?
I'm not running this.
I'm just delivering
the message.
Yes, I will be attending
the party,
but as an honored guest.
An honored guest who happens to
show up a couple of hours early
and leave a couple hours late.
And I will do as
any other good guest will:
help clean up,
and maybe park a few cars.
So what's the shindig
for this time?
Oh, it's one of those
welcome-back-from-your-fabulous
all-expense-paid-trip-
to-Europe,
you-sniveling-snot-brat
of-a-vice-president's-
daughter's tennis brunch.
Gee, I've never
been to one of those.
Good.
You're tending bar.
There's the address.
I'll see you at 10:00,
Sunday morning.
She played right into my hands.
REBECCA:
If I do say so myself,
I do throw
a lovely party.
Oh, Mr. Gaines,
I don't believe
I've been introduced
to the guest of honor,
your lovely daughter.
Oh, Kelly would love
to meet you.
Oh, she's busy.
Jack Daniels, neat.
SAM:
Coming right up, sir.
Say, aren't you Sam Malone?
Didn't you used
to be a pitcher?
Yep, that's me.
Now you're doing this?
Well,
nothing wrong with tending bar.
It's good, honest work.
Uh, here's a little
something for you.
Those rich snobs, man.
They think they can look
down their noses at you,
and then make everything better
by slipping you a measly...
50 bucks?
Two white wines,
please.
Yes, sir.
Coming right up here.
You know, Woody, I tell ya,
it's a long way
from pitching
in the major leagues
to slinging drinks.
What am I gonna do,
you know?
I mean, life's dealt me
this lousy hand.
I guess I'm just
gonna have
to play it out, huh?
I'm sorry, sir.
Uh, there
are your drinks.
Thank you.
Oh, bless you.
I'm definitely
on to something here.
Excuse me,
bartender.
A little more champagne.
Sure.
Maybe I'll get
a tip, too, Sam.
Listen, this whining for
dollars routine is mine.
Anyway, I'll be summering
in D.C., God help me.
Dad's favoring me
with the option of going up
on the Hill to page
or being a clerk.
So what do you think?
Oh, uh, excuse me
for interrupting,
but I'd go
with the clerk job.
I had a blast the summer I
clerked at the Piggly Wiggly.
Uh...
I'm sure you did,
but I was talking about
being a legal clerk.
Oh, this was all
in the up and up.
Are you always this obtuse?
The cummerbund
makes my waist
look thick.
Yeah...
yeah, thick.
That's the word
I was searching for.
Write it on your hand.
You'll never forget it.
He's very funny.
Well, here's to you,
Malone.
And, uh, I wish you
lots of luck
on that triple bypass.
Thank you.
Bless your heart.
You having a
heart problem, Sam?
Yeah, it feels like there's
something pressing on it.
Maybe like...
all this cash.
( speaking quietly )
Excuse me, uh, bartender.
Can I give you
a little tip?
Looking good, Sam.
Sure.
For the rest of the afternoon,
just keep your mouth shut.
Excuse me?
You're here to work,
not to chitchat with the guests.
You think just
because you're rich
you can boss people
around?
We've got guys like you
back in Hanover.
You know what
we call them?
What?
"Sir."
But after we say it,
we roll our eyes.
You know, kid, you're really
starting to annoy me.
I think I'm going
to teach you some manners.
Step outside.
Uh, uh, I'm sorry, all right?
I was out of line.
I don't want to fight.
Oh, you're not as
stupid as you look.
Now I want to fight.
Whoa, whoa, what's going
on here, man?
This guy just said
I wasn't as stupid
as I look, Sam.
Whoa, whoa, come here.
Listen, whoa, whoa, stop.
I mean it. Really, listen,
before you go out there,
let me just say
a couple of things here.
Now I've been a bartender
for quite a few years
and I've broken up a lot
of fights in my day.
And I'll tell you
no matter who's involved,
whether they're rich guys
or poor guys,
tall guys or short guys,
fat guys, skinny guys,
guys with speech impediments...
What's your point?
Well, the point is, that usually
by this point in the story,
the guys would forget
what they're angry about
and they'd kind of wander away.
Yeah, well, I, I, uh...
I guess this isn't
the right time or place.
Yeah, you're right.
All right, there you go.
Very good, very good.
Now why don't you just go
back to the bar here, Woody.
Will you tell me
the rest of the
story later, Sam?
Well, maybe we'll, uh...
we'll meet again,
when your daddy isn't around.
I don't need him
to protect me.
I'll meet you
anywhere, anytime.
You can find me
at Cheers.
I'll see you there tomorrow.
I'll be there with bells on.
That's just an expression.
Excuse me, please.
Excuse me.
Yeah?
Sam, I heard
what you've been doing.
Going around
giving everyone
a hard luck story,
so they give you
big tips.
I find that completely
unprofessional,
and I will not
condone it.
I'm going to dock you
a day's pay.
Did you hear that?
Woody,
cognac
for all my friends.
We're celebrating
this year's recipient
of the Fisk Foundation grant.
NORM:
All right.
I knew you could do it, buddy.
What the hell is it?
It's a very prestigious
and lucrative fellowship
that will enable me, finally,
after all these years,
to complete my treatise.
"Man's need to work,
the never-ending drive.
To build, create
and achieve."
Yeah, must feel
pretty good.
Oh, you bet.
If I can cop one more fat grant,
it's loaf city.
Ah.
The only thing missing now
is a fine cigar.
Well, allow me.
Carla, three of your
finest Tampas, please.
You got it, gentlemen.
Look at these beauties.
That'll be 45 cents.
Carla, we asked for a cigar,
not this flammable bratwurst.
Come on, Fras, these
are pretty tasty.
Yeah, and they
outlast the others
by what, a good,
eight or nine hours.
Cliffie, make a smoke
ring go around my head
the way you do.
Uh-huh.
Okay, Boyd, I'm here.
Yeah, so am I.
Course, I'm always here,
so it's no big deal.
You know, I wouldn't feel right
beating you senseless,
unless I warn you in advance,
I was on the boxing team
at Princeton.
Yeah? Well, while you're
beating me senseless,
keep this in mind:
I was first alternate
on the Hanover High
Boxing Squad.
What is that supposed
to mean?
It means if anybody
got sick or hurt,
I'd be the one...
No!
I mean, is that supposed
to make you a tough guy?
Tough enough.
Yeah, well, proof
is in the pudding.
All right, that does it.
Nobody says that to me.
Who wants to see a rich boy
get his butt whupped?
( crowd clamoring )
CROWD ( chanting ):
Woody! Woody! Woody!
Wait a minute, wait a minute!
I can't leave here.
Look, if you're gonna fight,
go fight in the back.
But remember, you gotta
bus your own blood.
Let's go.
( chanting ):
Woody, Woody, Woody,
Woody, Woody, Woody, Woody...
( blow lands, body thuds )
Rich guy! Rich guy!
Ugh, did I get struck
by lightning?
No, Woody.
Oh, right, I guess that only
happens once in your life.
He's okay.
Gee, I hate for you guys
to see me like this,
all dopey and muddle-headed.
Yeah, we barely recognize you.
We Boyds don't appreciate having
our faces caved in.
SAM:
Yeah?
I'm gonna get that guy.
Calm down, Woody.
Isn't it enough that you left
little bits of face
in his pinkie ring?
( Cliff laughing )
And your nose really messed up
his shoeshine when you fell.
I'm gonna get that guy.
I'm gonna get him good.
Oh, come on, Woody.
What do you...
how can you get him, man?
He's rich, he's smart,
he's in good shape, he's tough;
hangs out with a better class
of people...
Hey!
You know what
I'm talking about, guys.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Hey!
How can I get that guy?
He must have some weak spot.
Oh, hi.
I hope I'm not too late.
I heard my boyfriend
was coming here
to fight
that nice bartender.
Fight?!
I've had sneezes
that lasted longer.
Oh, I am so sorry
Nash did this.
He has such
a ridiculous temper.
If there's anything I can do,
please, don't hesitate to ask.
Are your hands just
naturally this soft,
or you use
a special lotion?
Lotion, but you can't
buy it in the States.
Smells good, too.
No, it's fragrance free.
You smell my hair.
I rinse it in an essence
of Belgian wild flowers.
They make a boy's version?
I'll have my personal shopper
check and send you a case.
I feel just terrible
about what Nash did.
It'd be a shame if you got
a scar on that cute face.
I'll be okay.
Okay. Bye.
Bye.
Now, how could I get
that Nash guy?
Woody?
Woody, I think it's
kind of obvious,
if you know what I mean.
Beat up his girlfriend?
I don't think you could.
Whoa.
Come on.
Now think with
me here. Think.
Now, have you met
anybody recently,
kind of cute, you know?
Somebody who smells good
and has hair down to here?
I'm interested in what
you're saying, Sam,
but I just had a thought.
If I went out with that girl,
I could make Nash real jealous.
( all chanting ):
Woody! Woody! Woody...
I'm back!
This has been a fabulous day.
As I walked through the halls
of headquarters,
I received nothing but kudos
for my fantastic party
yesterday.
Mr. Gaines said
I displayed leadership,
imagination and class.
I am it.
That's great, Miss Howe.
Listen, do you think it'd be
okay if I took an hour off?
Of course, Woody,
take two.
You deserve it.
Oh, great.
I'm going to go ask your boss
for permission
to date his daughter, okay?
Okay.
No!
And so, Mr. Gaines,
please allow me to stress again,
in the strongest way possible,
that my being here
in no way reflects
upon Miss Rebecca Howe
or her chance for advancement
in your corporation.
I'll take that under advisement.
Now, if you'll please get on
with your business?
Yes, sir.
My business is
that I'd like permission
to date your daughter Kelly.
I think you'll find
that I'm generous, hardworking,
friendly, cheerful, and honest.
Oh, yeah, and I'm funny, too.
Well presented, young man.
And a charming, old-fashioned
gesture, besides.
Ready to hit
the links, Walter?
In a minute, Nash.
Anyway, as you can see,
your visit has been
in vain, Mr. Boyd.
My daughter Kelly has been
dating young Nash here
for some years now.
Well, Boyd,
how's that chin healing?
Never mind my chin,
how's your ring?
Nash, it seems Mr. Boyd here
has his eye on Kelly.
Oh, what a coincidence.
Only yesterday,
he had his eye on my Topsiders.
Come on, son.
We're on the tee
in ten minutes.
That sounds good,
but I have to warn you,
I've never played before.
He's talking to me, Gomer.
You'll show yourself out?
Well, you better
get going, Boyd.
You're going to be late
for that bus.
A lot you know.
It doesn't come around for
another 15 minutes.
MR. GAINES:
Nash?
Let's do it!
I'll see you
later, Kelly.
Got to go let your dad
beat me at golf again.
Well, I better be going, too.
Wait a minute.
I heard your dad's answer
and I heard Nash's answer,
but I still haven't heard
your answer yet.
Oh, gosh, Woody, I couldn't.
I understand.
Wait a minute.
Why not?
I'm not Nash's property,
and I just hate it when he
always assumes that I am.
Well, beans, this'll show him!
Aw, that's great.
That is terrific.
All right.
I'll pick you up tomorrow
at 8:00, okay?
Now, I promise you you're going
to have the best time possible.
You may think from looking
at me,
that I'm an unsophisticated guy
who doesn't know his way around,
but you're going
to find out I do, okay?
I'll see ya.
Woody?
Yes?
Do you know you're in a closet?
Yeah, but I thought it might be
more sophisticated
just to lay low
and then sneak out
after everyone went to bed.
Good night.
Sam, has Woody come back
from his date yet?
Uh-uh.
I changed his schedule around so
he can all of his evenings off
so he can continue to date
that lovely young woman.
Wait a minute, now you
want him to date?
I mean, what happened
to the Attack
of the Screaming Boss Lady
from Hell?
Now I will admit
that I didn't want him
to ask her out originally,
but let's face it--
he's on a date with her.
And the more they date,
the more of a chance
he has to become
the boss's son-in-law.
And boss's sons-in-law become
VP's
and in the corporate world,
it always helps
to have a VP
in your corner.
That's disgusting.
Sam, I don't make up the rules.
I just follow them.
Thanks again for a wonderful
evening, Woody.
You introduced me
to a whole new world.
Yeah, it's hard to
believe a girl like you
has never been to
a monster truck and
tractor pull before.
Oh, Woody!
On the first date!
How you going
to top that, buddy?
Well, there's no need
to top it.
It's a one-shot deal.
Wh-What do you mean?
What...?
I mean, the only reason
she went out with me
was to make a point
with her boyfriend.
Wait, wait, wait,
how do you know that?
'Cause she told me.
I mean, it only seems fair.
The only reason
I went out with her
was to get revenge
at her boyfriend.
At least that's what I told her.
NORM:
Woody,
that is beautiful.
That's the kind of honesty
that's going to keep you out
of marriage.
Kelly.
Your dad said
I might find you here.
Nash, I know what
you're going to say,
and I don't want
to hear it.
I'm tired of being
treated like chattel.
Excuse me, I think that's
pronounced cattle.
You know, when I heard
what you were up to,
I got really mad.
Then I, well, I realized,
you couldn't possibly
be doing this
for your own enjoyment,
so you must be doing it
to prove a point to me.
And I have to say,
point well taken.
This has been a humbling
experience for me.
Nothing personal.
That's okay, I didn't
understand it.
Anyway, from now on,
new Nash.
Just hope you'll give me
another chance.
Well, okay.
Great.
Hey, let's go.
Maybe we can catch
a late supper at Guiseppi's.
I don't know.
Are we finished with our date,
Woody?
Yeah, okay, I guess it's
over... if you want.
Well, thanks again
for a fun evening.
Kelly?
What?
Nothing.
Do you have something you want
to say to me, Woody?
No.
I had a great time.
It was nice meeting you.
I was really happy
to get to know you.
I guess I did have
something to say to you.
So, I... guess
we should be leaving.
Yeah, I guess I should be
getting back to work.
Well, have fun working.
Yeah, have fun leaving.
Woody, come on, man.
Go get her.
I can't, Sam.
What could I possibly
say to her?
Just say, "I like you.
Will you go out
with me again?"
Oh, right, just like that.
And she's going to dump
her rich boyfriend
who she's been seeing
for all these years,
for poor, old, nobody Woody.
I'm afraid the real world
doesn't work
like that, Sam; trust me.
No, Woody, come on.
Hey, listen, just do me
a favor: Go get her.
Now, if it doesn't work out,
I'll buy you dinner.
If it does, you owe me.
Just go out there.
Say, "I like you, will you
go out with me again?"
Come on, before it's
too late, go get her.
I'll give it a try, Sam.
Excuse me.
Kelly, uh...
I like you.
Will you go out with me again?
Sure.
Oh, great,
great.
Well, we can't do it tonight.
I've got to take Sam out.
Oh, no, no.
It's okay, we can
go out now.
Uh, yeah, I have
a standing reservation
at Pizza by the Yard.
Oh, wait a minute.
What about Nash?
Well, I was getting in the car
with him
when I realized...
Woody, I have
a lot more fun with you.
Ah, yeah,
I know what you mean.
I didn't have much fun
with Nash, either.
Hey, Miss Howe?
Can I leave now?
Take Kelly out?
I promise I'll work
a double next week.
Oh, don't worry about it.
Go, go ahead.
Have a good time.
And if you want to stay out
real late and get married,
then come in anytime tomorrow.
You're the greatest, Miss Howe.
WOODY:
Okay, let's hurry.
If we get there by 6:00,
we can sit
at the Pac-Man table.
What's a Pac-Man?
Oh, Kelly, I have
so much to teach you.
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/492u
Help other users to choose the best subtitles